<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344057065290-1</Id><Title>==== HUGE ==== Jenna Jameson supports Mitt Romney</Title><Msg>Retired adult film actress Jenna Jameson voiced support for presumptive Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney at a strip club Thursday, CBS San Francisco reports: "I'm very looking forward to a Republican being back in office," Jameson said while sipping champagne in a VIP room at Gold Club in the city's South of Market neighborhood. "When you're rich, you want a Republican in office."</Msg><Username>unclenam</Username><Timestamp>1344057065290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 01:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344057531951-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ralph Nader: "The people want to be paid!" Mr. Obama: "Let them buy stock."</Title><Username>longon2007</Username><Timestamp>1344047538755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:32:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve Jobs: "Let them share."</Msg><Username>difftone</Username><Timestamp>1344057531951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 01:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344068624088-3</Id><Topic><Title>Trader X is a little disgruntled these days</Title><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1344038302868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet that is true about him losing a boatload of money. He once let slip in a rant responding to one of my posts that he lost a lot of money listening to the longs. So now it appears he is getting some satisfaction by continually bashing the longs. My guess is he lost the money being long BAC and now he somehow sickly wishes for the company to go under as if that would be some kind of revenge. Or he wants longs to suffer like he suffered, which is another sick reaction to his bad luck or bad investing. Whatever the explanation is, that guy is one sick obsessed puppy.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344068624088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 04:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344069235831-4</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344048829801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just as the white house bon.g head aka the talking m.o__nkey</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1344069235831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 04:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344069786984-5</Id><Topic><Title>163,000 JOBS CAN ANYONE SAY THAT'S GOOD WITH A STRAIGHT FACE!!!??</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344020257522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:57:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you finally figured out the cap lock. Try practicing that before you move on to posting, ok?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1344069786984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 04:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344078559951-6</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will get a bump during the convention. Then when it is explained what his platform is, bye bye.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344078559951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344078840128-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because the wealthy are not circulating the money. To have recovery improve we have to get the idle money form the idle rich in circulation. GOP tax policy of the last 30 years has destroyed the middle class and prosperity. Those tax policies have to change and raising the rate in the top brackets is the first step.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344078840128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344078982565-8</Id><Title>New Campaign for Us</Title><Msg>"Make her day, take a carpet muncher to Chick-fil-A"</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344078982565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344079315321-9</Id><Topic><Title>New Campaign for Us</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344078982565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Make his day, take the knobgobbler, Fish2kil to Chick-fil-A"</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344079315321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344080479833-10</Id><Title>Not all of Hollywood is Democratically soiled</Title><Msg>Clint Eastwood just made Mitt Romney's day. Appearing at a fundraiser at the Sun Valley Resort in Idaho, the Hollywood legend and Oscar winning actor and director endorsed the presumptive GOP nominee. When asked by reporters outside the event why he's supporting the former Massachusetts Governor, Eastwood said, "Because I think the country needs a boost somewhere." Introducing Romney during the fundraiser, Eastwood said he first saw Romney when shooting Mystic River in Boston and Romney was running for governor. He joked that he kept thinking "he's too handsome to be governor, but he does look like he could be president." The staunch Republican created a bit of confusion after Chrysler's "Halftime in America" ad that aired during the Superbowl. Many saw it an endorsement of President Obama, forcing Eastwood to state on Fox News that he was "certainly not affiliated with Mr. Obama."</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1344080479833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344081657630-11</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know any economic theory that claims increasing taxes in a very weak economy would lead to economic growth? Tired old philosophy from liberal democrats just doesn't work. Whether taxation is done at the end of gun barrel ie the Soviet Union or through laws it produces the same result. Either people flee or they figure ways around it ie corruption or hiding their money in tax shelters. Talk about idle money. Putting money in the mattress is not going to promote economic growth!!! Modern economic theory realizes the best effect is achieved when participation is "voluntary." For example I would love to invest a lot of money into natural gas to liquid fuels for motor vehicles in this country but there is a huge risk in that if Obama gets a second term his radical epa would outlaw fracking and then I would be out of my money. We are experiencing regulatory overload causing extreme burdens, indecision and stagnation. Some part of the economy have literally tens of thousands of pages of regs to comply with and the regulators have no clue which ones to enforce. Heck it would take decades to even learn all the regs in the proper sequence in some cases. Getting back on topic tax increases do not help the economy and how is government going to expand the middle class anyways? 70-90 billion more at best may go into the treasury if Obama's tax increases go into effect. How will that stimulate growth exactly? It will do nothing to a 1.5 Trillion yearly deficit. If that would solve all our problems the 200 Billion Bush stimulus and the 880 Billion Obama stimulus would have made the economy soar by now.</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344081657630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344082067313-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because the stupid politicians - cannot stop their stupid spending habits - an the wasteful spending - an keep wanting more an more taxes - to cover their stupidity .!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344082067313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344082253786-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>liberty - you are dead worng - stop the stupid spending an wasteful habits - then if needed raise anyones taxes .!!!!!!!!! its like little childern - make them grow up - an get their house in order .!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344082253786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344083304799-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'as a first step' to what, fundamentally changing the US to a socialist country where the elite have it all and the rest have no chance to aspire to 'more'? If everyone who was yammering to 'tax the rich more' while ferreting out ways not to pay their own 'fair share' there'd be a whole passele of silence going on.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1344083304799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344083708050-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because it's the drumbeat of divisiveness that makes the masses feel better about being non or lesser achievers and gives them hope of cashing in for free on the 'haves'.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1344083708050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344084057443-16</Id><Title>The Brits have it correct</Title><Msg>Mitt is a twit and will not be elected even though unemployment is now 8.3%. Am I an Obama fan, not at all but I truly believe the Republicans will lose the upcoming election solely because of the candidate that was selected by their party.</Msg><Username>bcboxboy</Username><Timestamp>1344084057443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:40:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344084629897-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read a report awhile back where many who work in the Obama administration have not paid their taxes. Some for as many as 10yrs owing back taxes. Perhaps Obama should check his own house before demanding folks pay their fair share</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344084629897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344084908667-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe the answer I've read to that is in any large group of people (over a dozen, two, perhaps) you have a few 'problems' and they consider that reasonable. Like we have many scofflaws in congress, drunks, druggies, and people who just plain got where they are being crooks.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1344084908667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344085096447-19</Id><Title>Perhaps Obama should "fix" the IRS before he demands tax increases???</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — The Internal Revenue Service may have delivered more than $5 billion in refund checks to identity thieves who filed fraudulent tax returns for 2011, Treasury Department investigators said Thursday. They estimate another $21 billion could make its way to ID thieves' pockets over the next five years. The IRS is detecting far fewer fraudulent tax refund claims than actually occur, according to a government audit that warned the widespread problem could undermine public trust in the U.S. tax system. Although the IRS detected about 940,000 fraudulent returns for last year claiming $6.5 billion in refunds, there were potentially another 1.5 million undetected cases of thieves seeking refunds after assuming the identity of a dead person, child or someone else who normally wouldn't file a tax return. In one example, investigators found a single address in Lansing, Mich., that was used to file 2,137 separate tax returns. The IRS issued more than $3.3 million in refunds to that address. Three addresses in Florida, the epicenter of the identity theft crisis, filed more than 500 returns totaling more than $1 million in refunds for each address. In another troubling scenario, hundreds of refunds were deposited into the same bank account — a red flag for investigators searching for ID thieves who may be filing for refunds for multiple people. In one instance, the IRS deposited 590 refunds totaling more than $900,000 into one account.</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344085096447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344085587095-20</Id><Topic><Title>Perhaps Obama should "fix" the IRS before he demands tax increases???</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344085096447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The IRS should be tasked with collecting what's already owed them before anyone's taxes are raised to cover government profligacy. Oops. they already are. they just don't do it.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1344085587095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344085701530-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not little children and the arguments on spending are only about what it should be spent on. That isn't going to change. Right now you hear the GOP saying we can't cut defense lets cut social security and medicare. . Taxes are the lowest they ave been in half a century. Balancing the budget is not a one way street like the tea party would like for you to believe.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344085701530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344086201870-22</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are confusing taking existing wealth away with the concept of increasing taxes. No one is proposing taking existing wealth away, just raising the tax on what that wealth produces for them during the year. No one is going to run away. After WWII the top rate was 90% it was more than 50% when Reagan took office and was 39% during Clintons term. Now argue we have been more prosperous with lower rates on the top earners. The wealthy have increase their portion of the pie over the last 30 years at the expense of the middle class and at the expense of national prosperity. Few will argue that the period after WWII was the most prosperous time for the USA. Look at the tax rates. Supply side was a failed experiment for all but the rich. It is time to give up the idea that you can get something for nothing by lowering rates.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344086201870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344086306331-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,what are you HIDING with your TAXES??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344037902151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reid's new VA Hospital is set to open in Las Vegas Aug.14 ... the total cost $1B when you include 4 new outpatient centers open and rarely used. It will serve only 60,000 of the 400,000 veterans that live in Las Vegas...but are those numbers true? The Director of the hospital hinted that they will be busier "in the future" as more people "move back" to Las Vegas...just how many people moved out of Nevada?</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344086306331</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344086524138-24</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a first step to the conditions that made the county prosperous. Tax fairness where tax is distributed by the economic benefits you receive from operating under our system with OUR workers, the most productive in the world, and with OUR infastructure, stability and protection. Which is the point Obama makes when he says you didn't build this by yourself.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344086524138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344087017206-25</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Reagan lower the top rate from 70 to 50%? Wouldnt it make sense that the real economic impact is from lowering or raising and not some magical rate that your analysis implies? from wiki: Prior to the Reagan administration, the United States economy experienced a decade of rising unemployment and inflation, (known as stagflation). Political pressure favored stimulus resulting in an expansion of the money supply. President Richard Nixon's wage and price controls were phased out.[3] The federal oil reserves were created to ease any future short term shocks. President Jimmy Carter had begun phasing out price controls on petroleum, while he created the Department of Energy. Much of the credit for the resolution of the stagflation is given to two causes: a three year contraction of the money supply by the Federal Reserve Board under Paul Volcker, initiated in the last year of Carter's presidency.[3] In his stated intention to increase defense spending while lowering taxes, Reagan's approach was a departure from his immediate predecessors. Reagan enacted lower marginal tax rates in conjunction with simplified income tax codes and continued deregulation. During Reagan's presidency the annual deficits averaged 4.2% of GDP[4] after inheriting an annual deficit of 2.7% of GDP in 1980 under president Carter.[4] The rate of growth in federal spending fell from 4% under Jimmy Carter to 2.5% under Ronald Reagan. GDP per working-age adult, which had increased at only a 0.8% annual rate during the Carter administration, increased at a 1.8% rate during the Reagan administration. The increase in productivity growth was even higher: output per hour in the business sector, which had been roughly constant in the Carter years, increased at a 1.4% rate in the Reagan years.[2] Before Reagan's election, supply side policy was considered unconventional by the moderate wing of the Republican Party. While running against Reagan for the Presidential nomination in 1980, George H. W. Bush had derided Reaganomics as "voodoo economics".[5] Similarly, in 1976, Gerald Ford had severely criticized Reagan's proposal to turn back a large part of the Federal budget to the states. Reagan's policies have since become widely accepted by many Republicans.</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344087017206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344087190801-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Reagan lifted remaining domestic petroleum price and allocation controls on January 28, 1981,[6] and lowered the oil windfall profits tax in August 1981, helping to end the 1979 energy crisis. He ended the oil windfall profits tax. Reagan followed his 1981 tax cuts with the Tax Reform Act of 1986 which sought to eliminat deductions, lower marinal rates, and broaden the tax base.[7] In 1982 Reagan agreed to a rollback of corporate tax cuts and a smaller rollback of individual income tax cuts. The 1982 tax increase undid a third of the initial tax cut. In 1983 Reagan instituted a payroll tax on Social Security and Medicare hospital insurance.[8] With the Tax Reform Act of 1986, Reagan and Congress sought to broaden the tax base, eliminate many deductions, and reduce rates. In 1983, Democrats Bill Bradley and Dick Gephardt had offered a proposal to clean up/broaden the tax base; in 1984 Reagan had the Treasury Department produce its own plan. The eventual bipartisan 1986 act aimed to be revenue-neutral: while it reduced the top marginal rate, it also partially "cleaned up" the tax base by curbing tax loopholes, preferences, and exceptions, thus raising the effective tax on activities previously specially favored by the code. Ultimately, the combination of base broadening and rate reduction raised revenue equal to about 4% of existing tax revenue.[9] President Ronald Reagan signs the Economic Recovery Tax Act of 1981 at his California ranch. The primary effect of the tax changes over the course of Reagan's term in office was a change in the composition of tax revenue, towards payroll and new investment, and away from higher earners and capital gains on existing investments. Federal revenue share of GDP fell from 19.6% in fiscal 1981 to 17.3% in 1984, before rising back to 18.4% by fiscal year 1989. Personal income tax revenues fell during this period relative to GDP, while payroll tax revenues rose relative to GDP.[4] President Ronald Reagan's 1981 cut in the top regular tax rate on unearned income reduced the maximum capital gains rate to only 20%--its lowest level since the Hoover administration.[10] This tax benefits the wealthy, however, in 1986 President Reagan set tax rates on capital gains at the same level as the rates on ordinary income like salaries and wages, with both topping out at 28 percent.[11]</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344087190801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344087810842-27</Id><Topic><Title>Perhaps Obama should "fix" the IRS before he demands tax increases???</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344085096447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find in life that those who advocate penalizing another person or group are often the "most guilty" of all. If you are a criminal what better place to be than in government? You have the power to operate freely with the least amount of checks and balances while attacking your enemies or competition. How long will it be before some massive corruption scheme is uncovered between the banks and government where vast sums of moneys are missing or not reported? Perhaps one of these developed socialist nations will be caught in such a scheme and what might that do to the markets when that is uncovered? I think the collusion between the government ie fannie and freddie and certain financial institutions was a forerunner of things to come. We have lost our moral compass and anarchy in culture always results when that happens. Essentially dying from within</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344087810842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344088269268-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More taxes. Read this and weep! Did you know that if you sell your house after 2012 you will pay a 3.8% sales tax on it? That's $3,800 on a $100,000 home, etc. When did this happen? It's in the health care bill, -- and it goes into effect in 2013. Why 2013? Could it be so that it doesn't come to light until after the 2012 elections? So, this is ‘change you can believe in’? Under the new health care bill all real estate transactions will be subject to a 3.8% sales tax.</Msg><Username>zenstar666</Username><Timestamp>1344088269268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344088876810-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,what are you HIDING with your TAXES??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344037902151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you complaining about the government improving care for vets or the housing market in Las Vegas? Now explain why this is Harry Reid's hospital. I doubt he could even be treated there. If Reid is responsible for increasing the care of disabled Vets then more power to him.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344088876810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344089072568-30</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The top income tax rate in Spain is 52% why are they not prospering?</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344089072568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344089842337-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You read too many wingnut e mails. Go search the truth of that. It just isn't so. You are being lied to again and believing it.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344089842337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344090597797-32</Id><Title>SERENA WILLIAMS THE BENEFICIARY OF GOOD WHITE PLANTATION BREEDING</Title><Msg>Thank the Masters baby!!!</Msg><Username>gargantousdick</Username><Timestamp>1344090597797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344090686801-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most economist today will agree that when taxes are excessively high it reduces growth. However they will also accept that there is a point of diminishing returns on lower taxes and that we are well below that threshold. You failed to point out that while Reagan lowered taxes he increased the debt with overseas borrowing at record levels which made us the debtor nation we are today and saddled future generations with high debt interest payments. The infusion of borrowed money coupled with less money being take out of the private sector was a great 5 trillion stimulus. We don't have the luxury to do that kind of borrowing again. Government grew in leaps and bounds while feeding the military industrial complex and bringing unemployment down to 6% in 6 years.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344090686801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344090828534-34</Id><Topic><Title>SERENA WILLIAMS THE BENEFICIARY OF GOOD WHITE PLANTATION BREEDING</Title><Username>gargantousdick</Username><Timestamp>1344090597797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You notice they never say, thank you!</Msg><Username>asprin_headache</Username><Timestamp>1344090828534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344091007185-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google this on You tube for the answer: "Excellent Video on the Tax-the-Rich Mentality"</Msg><Username>asprin_headache</Username><Timestamp>1344091007185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344091292067-36</Id><Title>Taxes and more taxes under Reagan</Title><Msg>Sheldon Richman 1988 "Reagan came into office proposing to cut personal income and business taxes. The Economic Recovery Act was supposed to reduce revenues by $749 billion over five years. But this was quickly reversed with the Tax Equity and Fiscal Responsibility Act of 1982. TEFRA—the largest tax increase in American history—was designed to raise $214.1 billion over five years, and took back many of the business tax savings enacted the year before. It also imposed withholding on interest and dividends, a provision later repealed over the president's objection. But this was just the beginning. In 1982 Reagan supported a five-cent-per-gallon gasoline tax and higher taxes on the trucking industry. Total increase: $5.5 billion a year. In 1983, on the recommendation of his Spcial Security Commission— chaired by the man he later made Fed chairman, Alan Green-span—Reagan called for, and received, Social Security tax increases of $165 billion over seven years. A year later came Reagan's Deficit Reduction Act to raise $50 billion. Even the heralded Tax Reform Act of 1986 is more deception than substance. It shifted $120 billion over five years from visible personal income taxes to hidden business taxes. It lowered the rates, but it also repealed or reduced many deductions. According to the Treasury Department, the 1981 tax cut will have reduced revenues by $1.48 trillion by the end of fiscal 1989. But tax increases since 1982 will equal $1.5 trillion by 1989. The increases include not only the formal legislation mentioned above but also bracket creep (which ended in 1985 when tax indexing took effect—a provision of the 1981 act despite Reagan's objection), $30 billion in various tax changes, and other increases. Taxes by the end of the Reagan era will be as large a chunk of GNP as when he took office, if not larger: 19.4%, by ultra-conservative estimate of the Reagan Office of Management and Budget. The so-called historic average is 18.3%."</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091292067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344091736506-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you will find that those who were found in arrears were quickly brought in to compliance, Gietner for example. Still there are many workers in government service that are not up to date on their tax payments but not necessarily part of the Obama administration or hired by him. Yes, they should be Garnisheed until fully paid up.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091736506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344091869718-38</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have proof? Can you tell us what he paid in 2007,08,09. We can find Buffets information.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091869718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344092136451-39</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes and more taxes under Reagan</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091292067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reaganomics Vs. Obamanomics: Facts And Figures + Comment now President Ronald Reagan - Image via Wikipedia In February 2009 I wrote an article for The Wall Street Journal entitled “Reaganomics v Obamanomics,” which argued that the emerging outlines of President Obama’s economic policies were following in close detail exactly the opposite of President Reagan’s economic policies. As a result, I predicted that Obamanomics would have the opposite results of Reaganomics. That prediction seems to be on track. When President Reagan entered office in 1981, he faced actually much worse economic problems than President Obama faced in 2009. Three worsening recessions starting in 1969 were about to culminate in the worst of all in 1981-1982, with unemployment soaring into double digits at a peak of 10.8%. At the same time America suffered roaring double-digit inflation, with the CPI registering at 11.3% in 1979 and 13.5% in 1980 (25% in two years). The Washington establishment at the time argued that this inflation was now endemic to the American economy, and could not be stopped, at least not without a calamitous economic collapse. All of the above was accompanied by double -igit interest rates, with the prime rate peaking at 21.5% in 1980. The poverty rate started increasing in 1978, eventually climbing by an astounding 33%, from 11.4% to 15.2%. A fall in real median family income that began in 1978 snowballed to a decline of almost 10% by 1982. In addition, from 1968 to 1982, the Dow Jones industrial average lost 70% of its real value, reflecting an overall collapse of stocks. President Reagan campaigned on an explicitly articulated, four-point economic program to reverse this slow motion collapse of the American economy: 1. Cut tax rates to restore incentives for economic growth, which was implemented first with a reduction in the top income tax rate of 70% down to 50%, and then a 25% across-the-board reduction in income tax rates for everyone. The 1986 tax reform then reduced tax rates further, leaving just two rates, 28% and 15%. 2. Spending reductions, including a $31 billion cut in spending in 1981, close to 5% of the federal budget then, or the equivalent of about $175 billion in spending cuts for the year today. In constant dollars, nondefense discretionary spending declined by 14.4% from 1981 to 1982, and by 16.8% from 1981 to 1983. Moreover, in constant dollars, this nondefense discretionary spending never returned to its 1981 level for the rest of Reagan’s two terms! Even with the Reagan defense buildup, which won the Cold War without firing a shot, total federal spending declined from a high of 23.5% of GDP in 1983 to 21.3% in 1988 and 21.2% in 1989. That’s a real reduction in the size of government relative to the economy of 10%. 3. Anti-inflation monetary policy restraining money supply growth compared to demand, to maintain a stronger, more stable dollar value. 4. Deregulation, which saved consumers an estimated $100 billion per year in lower prices. Reagan’s first executive order, in fact, eliminated price controls on oil and natural gas. Production soared, and aided by a strong dollar the price of oil declined by more than 50%. These economic policies amounted to the most successful economic experiment in world history. The Reagan recovery started in official records in November 1982, and lasted 92 months without a recession until July 1990, when the tax increases of the 1990 budget deal killed it. This set a new record for the longest peacetime expansion ever, the previous high in peacetime being 58 months. During this seven-year recovery, the economy grew by almost one-third, the equivalent of adding the entire economy of West Germany, the third-largest in the world at the time, to the U.S. economy. In 1984 alone real economic growth boomed by 6.8%, the highest in 50 years. Nearly 20 million new jobs were created during the recovery, increasing U.S. civilian employment by almost 20%. Unemployment fell to 5.3% by 1989.</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344092136451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344092274498-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buffett's adjusted gross income last year was $62,855,038 Buffett's taxable income last year was $39,814,784 Buffett paid $15,300 in payroll taxes last year Buffett's federal tax bill came to $6,923,494, or 17.4% of his taxable income last year Romney paid 3 million on 21 million income for a 13% effective rate.. Now explain your reasoning.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344092274498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:57:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344092574017-41</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes and more taxes under Reagan</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091292067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And it only cost 5 trillion in borrowed money. An amount equal to all of the already accumulated debt of the nation. He, whoever wrote that piece, also Ignores what Volcker did that was the real cause for the economic reversal.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344092574017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344092771372-42</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes and more taxes under Reagan</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091292067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It won't let me post page 2. Well if borrowed money was what you claim to have stimulated the economy under Reagan than why are we not booming under Obama's 6 Trillion debt accumulated in just 4yrs???</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344092771372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344092798749-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want to compare Obama to Romney on tax fairness? Obama and First Lady Obama filed their income tax returns jointly and reported adjusted gross income of $789,674. They paid $162,074 in taxes, at an effective rate of 20.5 percent. The first family also reported paying $31,941 in state income tax to Illinois. I wouldn't think so.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344092798749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344093181209-44</Id><Topic><Title>Taxes and more taxes under Reagan</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344091292067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple question and Obama's 6 Trillion borrowed?</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344093181209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344093247914-45</Id><Title>Average tax rate 2011</Title><Msg>The average effective tax rate for all taxpayers was 18.8 percent in 2011, . where were you? Above or below? Obama paid over 20% Romney paid under 14%</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344093247914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344093642220-46</Id><Title>Obama could only dream of Reagan's economic numbers</Title><Msg>Not even the most die-hard, partisan Democrats would dare argue that the Obama recovery has been especially vigorous. Instead, they argue that the new president was dealt an impossible hand. But was he? Nearly three years after the Great Recession officially ended, the jobless rate is still above 8 percent — the longest stretch of such high unemployment since the Great Depression. Add back in all the discouraged job seekers and the part-timers who wished they had full-time gigs, and the unemployment rate is just shy of 15 percent. While the economy is growing, it’s not growing rapidly. At this point in the typical post-World War II recovery, the economy was growing at an average pace of nearly 5 percent. The Obama recovery has managed just over 2 percent average annual GDP growth. UPI Barack Obama Indeed, take-home pay for US workers, adjusted for rising prices, has actually fallen over the last year. Then there’s the moribund housing market. This week’s data show home prices still falling; nationwide, they’re off a third from their 2006 peak — all the way back to levels last seen in 2003. Economic consulting firm IHS Global Insight concludes that “signs of a turnaround are nowhere in sight.” All in all, Obama’s economic rebound kind of feels more like a bust than a boom. His defenders insist that’s not his fault — that the Great Recession was not only nastier than any other economic downturn since the 1930s but also different; it wasn’t caused by an oil shock or a sharp spike in interest rates. Economic downturns caused by a financial collapse, they argue, are typically followed by lackluster recoveries. So cut Obama a break, America. Judge Obamanomics on a sliding scale, because the president was dealt such an awful hand coming into office. Give him another four years to show what miracles the wonder-working power of more government spending, regulation and taxes can conjure. But this excuse doesn’t quite make it off the runway. A Federal Reserve study from late last year looked at the behavior of recoveries from recessions across 59 advanced and emerging market economies during the last 40 years. The Fed found, to no great surprise, that recoveries “tend to be faster” after severe recessions, such as the one we just had. It’s the “rubber-band effect”: The deeper the downturn, the more robust the rebound — unless government messes things up. For example, during the 1981-82 recession, output fell by 2.7 percent and then rose by 15.9 percent over the next 10 quarters (at an average pace of 6.0 percent). During the Great Recession, output fell even more, by 5.1 percent. But during the 10 quarters since, total economic output is up only a paltry 6.2 percent. Score one for Reaganomics. But what about the depressing effect of Wall Street’s near-death experience back in 2008 and 2009? Well, that same Fed study found that bank or other financial crises “do not affect the strength” of subsequent recoveries. Yes, the collapsed housing market is another fly in the ointment. But a recent analysis from JP Morgan suggests that housing might explain half of the Obama recovery’s underperformance versus the Reagan recovery. The other half? Maybe we can attribute that to policy differences. While one president cut long-term marginal tax rates, the other tried a massive burst of federal spending. One empowered private enterprise; the other empowered government. Of course, economies will eventually recover on their own, as this one seems finally to be doing. But Obamanomics shouldn’t get much credit for it. Nearly three years after the Great Recession officially ended, the jobless rate is still above 8 percent — the longest stretch of such high unemployment since the Great Depression. Add back in all the discouraged job seekers and the part-timers who wished they had full-time gigs, and the unemployment rate is just shy of 15 percent. While the economy is growing, it’s not growing rapidly. At this point in the typical post-World War II recovery, the economy was growing at an average pace of nearly 5 percent. The Obama recovery has managed just over 2 percent average annual GDP growth. UPI Barack Obama Indeed, take-home pay for US workers, adjusted for rising prices, has actually fallen over the last year. Then there’s the moribund housing market. This week’s data show home prices still falling; nationwide, they’re off a third from their 2006 peak — all the way back to levels last seen in 2003. Economic consulting firm IHS Global Insight concludes that “signs of a turnaround are nowhere in sight.” All in all, Obama’s economic rebound kind of feels more like a bust than a boom. His defenders insist that’s not his fault — that the Great Recession was not only nastier than any other economic downturn since the 1930s but also different; it wasn’t caused by an oil shock or a sharp spike in interest rates. Economic downturns caused by a financial collapse, they argue, are typically followed by lackluster recoveries. So cut Obama a break, America. Judge Obamanomics on a sliding scale, because the president was dealt such an awful hand coming into office. Give him another four years to show what miracles the wonder-working power of more government spending, regulation and taxes can conjure. But this excuse doesn’t quite make it off the runway. A Federal Reserve study from late last year looked at the behavior of recoveries from recessions across 59 advanced and emerging market economies during the last 40 years. The Fed found, to no great surprise, that recoveries “tend to be faster” after severe recessions, such as the one we just had. It’s the “rubber-band effect”: The deeper the downturn, the more robust the rebound — unless government messes things up. For example, during the 1981-82 recession, output fell by 2.7 percent and then rose by 15.9 percent over the next 10 quarters (at an average pace of 6.0 percent). During the Great Recession, output fell even more, by 5.1 percent. But during the 10 quarters since, total economic output is up only a paltry 6.2 percent. Score one for Reaganomics. But what about the depressing effect of Wall Street’s near-death experience back in 2008 and 2009? Well, that same Fed study found that bank or other financial crises “do not affect the strength” of subsequent recoveries. Yes, the collapsed housing market is another fly in the ointment. But a recent analysis from JP Morgan suggests that housing might explain half of the Obama recovery’s underperformance versus the Reagan recovery. The other half? Maybe we can attribute that to policy differences. While one president cut long-term marginal tax rates, the other tried a massive burst of federal spending. One empowered private enterprise; the other empowered government. Of course, economies will eventually recover on their own, as this one seems finally to be doing. But Obamanomics shouldn’t get much credit for it.</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344093642220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344093839536-47</Id><Title>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Title><Msg>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344093839536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344094201004-48</Id><Topic><Title>SERENA WILLIAMS THE BENEFICIARY OF GOOD WHITE PLANTATION BREEDING</Title><Username>gargantousdick</Username><Timestamp>1344090597797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So are you feeling deprived that you got really poor genes? If your ancestors had been a bit more selective maybe you would have had something to work with. Then again, maybe there is a good argument for abortion.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344094201004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344094380625-49</Id><Title>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Title><Msg>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel Based on Sanford C. Bernstein estimates of the marginal cost of oil production, the geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now. Reminding the market that a strategic cushion exists—without necessarily deploying it—provides a check on that premium rising even further. Sweet Crude Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel. That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline. Sanford Bernstein geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline.</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344094380625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344094449225-50</Id><Title>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market</Title><Msg>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market. 28-July-12 07:23 am Many analysts say oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market. “The economic price for (West Texas Intermediate) oil is in the $50-$60 range,” said Mickey Cargile, managing partner at Cargile Investments, basing his estimate on where he sees supplies locally and in Cushing, Okla., the delivery hub for Nymex oil. “Our range valuation suggests a 20%-30% risk premium priced for potential supply disruption from Iran,” he said. This equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.50 per gallon</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344094449225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344094555499-51</Id><Topic><Title>The Brits have it correct</Title><Username>bcboxboy</Username><Timestamp>1344084057443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 08:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That, a poor platform and four years of stalling the economy trying to make it as bad as possible so they could blame it on the White House. Republicans can have the White House if they would throw the twits out of Congress.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344094555499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344094742940-52</Id><Title>When will Obama fix the economy as promised? Reagan had his economy booming</Title><Msg>by this point and that is why Reagan won in a landslide in 1984. Jobs were being created at a pace of 250 to 600k per month. Obama is actually not even keeping up with population growth that is why the labor participation rate keeps falling each month, its now the lowest in 30yrs</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344094742940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:39:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344094788624-53</Id><Topic><Title>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market</Title><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344094449225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to remain confused thinking the oil market is a free capitalist market. It's not. Your logic will never work as long as you start with the wrong premiss.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344094788624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344095442515-54</Id><Title>I am so glad Obama's Big Government solutions are working so well i was losing faith in liberalism</Title><Msg>Thank goodness. They are working great right?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344095442515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344096495704-55</Id><Topic><Title>SERENA WILLIAMS THE BENEFICIARY OF GOOD WHITE PLANTATION BREEDING</Title><Username>gargantousdick</Username><Timestamp>1344090597797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another racist liberal.</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344096495704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344097344016-56</Id><Topic><Title>Average tax rate 2011</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344093247914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a small businessowner and was not allowed to deduct mortgage interest or college loan interest in 2011 due to some new threshhold IRS set, and our effective tax rate was 38.33% !!! We have to pay even more $$$ to IRS and State of NC because of it. Thomas Jefferson said we need a revolution to occur and now is the time.</Msg><Username>investrman</Username><Timestamp>1344097344016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344097947972-57</Id><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Msg>"The Reagan recovery had one of the fastest rates of growth we ever saw," said Barry Bosworth, an economist at the Brookings Institution. "If anything it was too strong. It was spectacular." Just take a look at the numbers: The economy grew at 4.5% in 1983, with a few quarters of growth north of 8%. In 2011, meanwhile, the economy grew just 1.7%. In just one month -- September 1983 -- the economy added more than a million jobs. For the full year, the economy added almost 3.5 million jobs, a trend that continued into 1984, an election year in which Reagan captured 49 states in a landslide victory. Obama can claim job growth of 1.8 million in 2011. A welcome comeback, but still tepid by comparison. Looking ahead to 2012, Obama could replicate the 243,000 jobs created in January over each of the next 11 months and still not approach Reagan's total for 1984 of 3.9 million.</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344098077093-58</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that article was cnn money from feb 2012 and since then the monthly job numbers have gotten worse! The Obama recovery already the weakest since WW2 is dangerously close to tipping into recession</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344098077093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344098562580-59</Id><Topic><Title>Average tax rate 2011</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344093247914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but Obama wants you to pay your "fair share" Are you paying your fair share??? Half the people in this country don't pay any effective federal tax. Is that fair or not? Should more and more people be living off the government and rich people like you pay higher and higher taxes to support them?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344098562580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344099506613-60</Id><Topic><Title>Average tax rate 2011</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344093247914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats 14% of what he didn't hide !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344099506613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344099818059-61</Id><Topic><Title>Average tax rate 2011</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344093247914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember the fist time I saw a thousand bucks come out of pay check under Bush SR and I was killing myself, now I live off investments and rentals and sit on my a and never pay over 15 %</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344099818059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344099938637-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan tripled the national debt and doubled the debt ratio, which had reached a post WW II minimum under Jimmy Carter of 0.4 in 1979. Reagan got it up to 0.8. And then we have the s&amp;L disaster..Charles keating, the Bernie of his day. This was reckless spending and a taste of what Bush I would give us. Bush II ruined the US economy. He truly made Govt insolvent (which was Reagan's plan..starve the beast) but made all Americans insolvent as well. This econ is worse than anything the US has ever seen. There is no inflation, which is sign that the patient is dead. Just deflation as our system implodes. Reagan inherited an inflating economy and the repubs then got interest rates up to 23%. The real austerity hero, if Repubs could look at themselves in the mirror and for once, just once, face facts and be honest, was Jimmy Carter who came closer to eliminating our debt than any post-WW II pres. Regan was a disaster and he defined the modern Republican approach...be cynical about Gov't and kill it. Just wait another 20 years and watch the Chinese Panzers come rolling into a city near you.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1344099938637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344100003128-63</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan eonomy was on credit, Obama started with a broke country plus Reagan added hundred of thousands of goverment workers Obama has lost hundred of thousands of government workers.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344100003128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344100058778-64</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not Obama recovery...Bush II Armageddon. You don't recover from armageddon. Bush II killed the USA, following the footsteps of Altzheimer Ronnie.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1344100058778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344100406933-65</Id><Topic><Title>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market</Title><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344094449225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why are oil prices and gasoline prices going up. I live in the Chicago area and gasoline prices have gone from $3.50/gallon two weeks ago to over $4.00 as of 8/4. Tell me what's going on !!??</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344100406933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344101286825-66</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so both of you seem to argue both ways. Which is it debt creates growth like you say happened under Reagan or debt kills growth? If debt is the answer we have added more debt in 4yrs with Obama than any other 4yr period. So Reagan's outstanding job growth numbers were due to only government workers? Please you need to tell me what you are smoking?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344101286825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344101620882-67</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so the government is the source of all wealth creation? You sound like Obama. Each week there are reports of memo's circulating to government employees to stop looking at porn on their computers. I guess it depends on what you mean by growth? Lmao</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344101620882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102090343-68</Id><Topic><Title>Senator McCain stated last Tuesday that his VP list included Romney, but he picked Palin because, "She was the best candidate for the job. Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!!</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344047002067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republican heavyweights aren't mute about showing no love for Wayward Willard. Meanwhile, rectal drip dumpobamie continues to "make a splash."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344102090343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344102096247-69</Id><Title>Obama I knew Reagan and Clinton and you are no Clinton or Reagan</Title><Msg>you are weak more like an emu. Your economy is the weakest post WWII economy on record and you offer no new ideas only blame and class warfare. You should stick to the gay agenda and let adults work with the complicated things you don't understand</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102096247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102186535-70</Id><Topic><Title>Obama I knew Reagan and Clinton and you are no Clinton or Reagan</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102096247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>green_now16. just another boring SW rectal drip.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344102186535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102366578-71</Id><Topic><Title>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market</Title><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1344094449225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oil, electric, water , cable all fixed here, free market ? You want see a free market go for a job !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344102366578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102405562-72</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney can't dodge the draft dodge issue, and his fellow republicans are now piling on and not letting him dodge the tax dodging / offshore accounts issures. Romney is DOA before he can pick a VP.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344102405562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102452549-73</Id><Topic><Title>Obama I knew Reagan and Clinton and you are no Clinton or Reagan</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102096247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am straight I would never be in SW's poop chute, you on the other hand have a serious fascination with that issue</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102452549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:47:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102686754-74</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many years of tax returns will the VP pick be willing to disclose?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344102686754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102705757-75</Id><Topic><Title>Libertylies is this the summer of recovery, ver 3?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1344034939476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:02:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the great summer of recovery? What does one mean by recovery is that like it depends on the definition of the word is is?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102705757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344102963190-76</Id><Topic><Title>When will Obama fix the economy as promised? Reagan had his economy booming</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344094742940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:39:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately Obama is rigidly aligned with European Socialism and well that's not working too well</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344102963190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344103082625-77</Id><Topic><Title>Why aren't Obama's policies creating jobs like Reagan's Lets look at some statistics</Title><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344097947972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:32:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't feel bad Obama wants to increase student loans that will never be paid back much like he argued for more poor people to be given mortgage loans. I am sure it will turn out so much better this time though you think?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344103082625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344103107497-78</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many more republicans need to pile on before Willard gives it up? Not that it matters, Willard is doomed.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344103107497</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344103250402-79</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is willard? Is that like Barry Soetoro?</Msg><Username>green_now16</Username><Timestamp>1344103250402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344103606414-80</Id><Title>Obama Inspired Gay Activists Storm and Vandalize Chick-Fil-A</Title><Msg>Adam Smith, then the CFO of a medical supply firm, created a wave of interest on the Web when he posted a video of himself berating a Chick-fil-A worker at a drive-through window in Tucson, Ariz. Smith, who said he "just couldn't stand all the hate," wasn't exactly showing his sweet side. Smith tells the employee, who offers him free water and wishes him a nice day, "I don't know how you live with yourself and work here. I don't understand it. This is a horrible corporation with horrible values. You deserve better." Smith's employer, Vante, was not impressed, stating in a press release that Smith no longer works for the company. Overnight, a Chick-fil-A in Torrance, Calif., was vandalized with the spray-painted message "Tastes like hate" in advance of today's "National Same-Sex Kiss Day." Some gay activists have encouraged same-sex couples to document themselves smooching at the restaurant chain's locations. This comes after Wednesday's Chick-fil-A Appreciation Day, organized by former Arkansas Gov. Mike Huckabee, which brought out tens of thousands to wait in long lines and, Chick-fil-A confirmed, resulted in a "record-setting day" for the business. Mayors in Chicago, Boston, and San Francisco have rolled up the welcome mat to the chain, and in Los Angeles, Mayor Antonio Villaraigosa praised his city for its "vibrant" LGBT community. New York City's Michael Bloomberg, on the other hand, a supporter of gay marriage, said on his radio show Friday that it is not appropriate for government "to look at somebody's political views and decide whether or not they can live in the city, or operate a business in the city, or work for somebody in the city."</Msg><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1344103606414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344104128608-81</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayward Willard: it's time to PUT UP!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344104128608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344106415902-82</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I lived in las vagas for years and harry ried is a stupid piece of s%%that the mob has had in there pocket for years..i even knew harry when he was a fighter..we called him the drive man harry..ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344106415902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344106854031-83</Id><Title>Obama Gay supporters chant "up my butt for 4 more years!!"</Title><Msg>You can't make this stuff up lol</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1344106854031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 15:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344107333682-84</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is all lies....i'm a ex las vagas odds maker and the true is that romney is leading obama by 4% across the board..and gaining ground daily..ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344107333682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 15:08:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344110571687-85</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Rep. Walter Jones (R-N.C.) said Thursday that Mitt Romney's refusal to release more than two years of tax returns will hurt him in the presidential election.</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344030470133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TIME TO "PUT UP", WILLARD!!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344110571687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344110694183-86</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TIME TO "PUT UP," WILLARD!!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344110694183</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344111617895-87</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"plugs" Biden is in Vegas today taking credit for blowing $1b and 6 years to build the new VA this same building would cost Mayo Clinic $100m to build....this VA is built so far out of town it might as well be in area 51...this is a research facility that will be run by the military...the veterans will still have to go to the run down clinic on West Owens in the ghetto for care...the Affordable Care Act will destroy the VA's....the new clinics are all empty...just like the ones recently built in California...empty</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344111617895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:20:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344112667286-88</Id><Title>Obama's hope and change turned into Romney's tax returns?</Title><Msg>We should aspire to such great heights in this nation. I for one wouldn't vote for someone like Obama he needs to be held accountable based on his results and tell the American people why we need to vote for him again. Frankly I don't know why anyone would want these last 4yrs repeated?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344112667286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344113027215-89</Id><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Msg>Read a thesis on Obama win by a comfortable margin and slight chance of Democrats controlling both Senate and House. Do Google search for "Moondra Post" for the article (YHOO Finance wouldn't let me post the link)</Msg><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344113492220-90</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why anyone would vote for massive debts and record high unemployment is beyond me. I guess America is so far down the tubes performance in your job means nothing anymore</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344113492220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344113906558-91</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is not the problem - gridlock in Congress is the problem. Romney is not a viable candidate. Most of debt was piled up by Bush ($1 tr on wars, $1 tr tax cuts, $1 tr bailouts). Strong middle class is the key (they account for 70% of consumer spending) - giving more tax cuts to rich is the dumbest idea. Romney's tax plan is a losing proposition.</Msg><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113906558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344114302947-92</Id><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Msg>We don't have that now!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344116297081-93</Id><Topic><Title>Since Obama's "Budgets" haven't received ONE SINGLE VOTE of support in the House or Senate ....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344115121914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:18:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(at least under that particular alias), his message history shows nothing but a spew of these one-note, one-sentence harangues on a single topic. Congratulations, Dumpster - you've now repeated yourself over 400 times! Polly wanna cracker? It's not just the breadth of his thinking that impresses.... ROTFLMAO picturing Romney strolling through the oceans of dumpobamie's soul without getting his flip-flops wet.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344116297081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344117108741-94</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Inspired Gay Activists Storm and Vandalize Chick-Fil-A</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1344103606414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does anyone know how the popularity feature works on this ne format? Thanks</Msg><Username>fbsbgillie</Username><Timestamp>1344117108741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344117733469-95</Id><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY IS A CROOK AND A TAX CHEATER</Title><Msg>Freaking #$%$ release your tax return. Tell us why you put your money in the Cayman Island and Swiss Bank. WHAT IS WRONG WITH AMERICAN BANK ROMMY ?. I Freaking lying pile crap, if you can't answer these question, you will lose big time.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344117733469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344118113239-96</Id><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Msg>for all the candidates they could have selected. they picked WILLARD. This lying and tax cheating crook.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344118894189-97</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will there be a revolt at the convention to dump Willard? Replacing Willard is the repugs' only hope.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1344118894189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344119360496-98</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boy just wait til your mommy catches you on the computer - she will strap your little legs .!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344119360496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344119517911-99</Id><Title>Happy Birthday President Obama !!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Hee hee LOL sorry I couldn't make it there to see you goofing around. POS President, worse than Jimmie Carter ! Worse than Herbert Hoover !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344119517911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344119851740-100</Id><Title>This board must be an NSA experiment</Title><Msg>to determine if sheep can be taught to eat one another. ROTFLMAO at minders and no-minders everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344119851740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344120230310-101</Id><Title>We learned that Nixon was a crook after the election</Title><Msg>We know that Romney is a crook before the election</Msg><Username>golden_ghandi</Username><Timestamp>1344120230310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344120377116-102</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY IS A CROOK AND A TAX CHEATER</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344117733469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey numbnuts, do you think the IRS had their eyes closed when they reviewed his tax returns? Anyone making that kind of money is an automatic audit. So much for your lies, cheating, sladerous posts about Romney being a tax cheat. You know nothing!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344120377116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344120537591-103</Id><Topic><Title>We learned that Nixon was a crook after the election</Title><Username>golden_ghandi</Username><Timestamp>1344120230310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Washout Willard needs to step down at the convention, and let a repug with some integrity take his place. Oooooops! My bad..., no such animal exists!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1344120537591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344120682377-104</Id><Title>Will Washout Willard step down at the GOP convention to let a repug with integrity take his place?</Title><Msg>Oooooooooops! My bad . . . , no such animal exists!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1344120682377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344121989784-105</Id><Topic><Title>We learned that Nixon was a crook after the election</Title><Username>golden_ghandi</Username><Timestamp>1344120230310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>didn't Obama get an illegal loan from felon Rezko? What about Corzine?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344121989784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344122076913-106</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Birthday President Obama !!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344119517911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:31:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey now not on his birthday. He deserves to golf and plan his next inspiring scheme to discredit Romney</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344122076913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344122144573-107</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Inspired Gay Activists Storm and Vandalize Chick-Fil-A</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1344103606414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah just do like Obama promise everyone free handouts you will get quite popular</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344122144573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344123226068-108</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly too many Americans just want a president that gives them handouts and to Hell with the country!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344123226068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344124489481-109</Id><Title>Who Will Washout Wobbly Wayward Wuss Willard's VP be?</Title><Msg>After all the VP hopefuls with any sense all say no, Palin may be the only one left. She may become the only vice-presidential candidate to ever lose twice.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344124489481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344124968339-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Inspired Gay Activists Storm and Vandalize Chick-Fil-A</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1344103606414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's they way THEY do it! The first word in your diatribe headline is Obama, but in the body of your screed he is conspicuous by his absence. You even magically attribute the protestors' motivations to him, but nowhere in the text do you mention a source for your statement. Did you get get it off Obama's teleprompter? LMAO! No matter; off to an ominous narrative about a tempest in a Tuscan teacup concerning (and you SOUND concerned, I must say) a screw-loose restaurant chain that has pulled off a world-class, P.T. Barnum publicity stunt. I look forward to your continuing coverage of this riveting story, and a treatise upon its relevance to world peace and the election of our next President. When do we get to hear about the motivations of the supporters of Chick-fil-A? Do I need to issue a spoiler alert, or can I go ahead and guess that this latest faith-based initiative was a product of God, Romney and the GOP? ROTFLMAO at purple pansy prose everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344124968339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344125915248-111</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Inspired Gay Activists Storm and Vandalize Chick-Fil-A</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1344103606414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 14:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently pushing buttons is the only play in your playbook. Where's that Olympic spirit? The keyboard is covered with buttons too, mouse-men. Try pushing yourself to use some of them. ROTFLMAO whenever Baltic Smugglers psyche each other up enough to gather under a cloak of darkness, even though they're terrified of the bogey-man.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344125915248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344126216599-112</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Obama is crazy to pursue this hate agenda. I hope the voters punish him for lack of performance this November</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344126216599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344126503984-113</Id><Topic><Title>Who Will Washout Wobbly Wayward Wuss Willard's VP be?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344124489481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:54:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe you should be concerned about a double dip cause if that happens Romney could pick a retard like you and still win rofl</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344126503984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344127475013-114</Id><Topic><Title>Will Obama keep Bumbles Biden for his VP?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344127414109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure Biden is legally coherent? Is he allowed to get a driver's license?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344127475013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344128217819-115</Id><Topic><Title>Congress shall pass no law, that they themselces are exempt from</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1344125718921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little Z they are not exempt from Obamacare. They have the same options as everyone else. Again too many Right wing emails cluttering your mind and you are so gullible you believe them.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344128217819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344128494268-116</Id><Topic><Title>Why haven't Gates, Buffet, Obama, Pelosi and Kerry paid their FAIR share of income taxes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344114338829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So tell us. What did they pay? Obama was a bit over 20%. National average was 18%. Romney paid 13% in the one year we know he paid.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344128494268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344128778865-117</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obama wins the moderate mainstream republicans will have to separate from the wing nuts. Without the moderates trying to cater to the extremist things will improve quickly.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344128778865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344130986479-118</Id><Topic><Title>Who Will Washout Wobbly Wayward Wuss Willard's VP be?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344124489481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 19:54:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I was a retard, I'd be backing Romney, like you are, retard.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344130986479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344131149485-119</Id><Topic><Title>Will Washout Willard step down at the GOP convention to let a repug with integrity take his place?</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1344120682377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:51:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a thought. They all know they can't win with Willard. Pick another slimy fool who at least isn't a draft dodger, and at least knows how to hide not paying taxes without the whole world finding out about hidden accounts.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344131149485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344131579926-120</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be too hurt if Sarah Palin says, "been there, done that."</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344131579926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344132170281-121</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will follow him to the grave. He'll always be remembered as the candidate who had so much to hide, he didn't know where all of it was hidden.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344132170281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344132677869-122</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes common thieves wanting something for nothing</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344132677869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:11:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344133154435-123</Id><Title>john 3:16</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>cboeman</Username><Timestamp>1344133154435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344134737905-124</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You 100% Riight!!! 90% of the voters doesn't even know who George Soros is??</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344134737905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344135051989-125</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY IS A CROOK AND A TAX CHEATER</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344117733469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey fartie I heard you died of the AIDS?? you still preaching what a wonderful SOB Obama is?? Obama is a @#$%^* SOB and anyone that has anything good to say about Odumba is a @#$%^&amp; SOB..ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344135051989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344135218869-126</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY IS A CROOK AND A TAX CHEATER</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344117733469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>excute Old Fartie....he went @#$%*^ crazy over Odumba...All Gays love him..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344135218869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344135396620-127</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repubs are indeed a sad bunch.... sad because Obama is still on office. They will be silly happy when Romney replaces him though! Sing with me..... Happy days will be here again, happy days are near again, oh happy days!!!!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344135396620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135496639-128</Id><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY DID NOT PAY TAXES FOR 10YRS</Title><Msg>this REPUCAN crook should be in jail</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135496639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135527578-129</Id><Title>MY, My, A few Republican cry babies!</Title><Msg>Quit blaming the current President for all our problems. He has never received much help from most of the Republicans! Spiro</Msg><Username>maryc8888</Username><Timestamp>1344135527578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344135591086-130</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fartie your a gay joke...go @#$%$@ someone else...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344135591086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135597063-131</Id><Title>MITTEN LIKE TO SING "AMERICA THE BEAUTIFUL"</Title><Msg>it's like scratching on a chalk board. what a fraud</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135597063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135756078-132</Id><Title>PREDICTION, HOW MANY REPUCANS WILL JUMP OFF A WINDOW</Title><Msg>after MITTEN get his #$%$ handed to him in November ?. Plus the may even lose the house and happy days will be here again.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135756078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135824919-133</Id><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Msg>Or is he a loser wasting bandwidth?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135844566-134</Id><Title>REPUCANS ARE BORN TO HATE</Title><Msg>they feel inadequate, so the end of projecting their miserable lives on other people. what a sad bunch</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135844566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344135896856-135</Id><Title>REPUCANS ARE BORN THIEVES AND LIARS</Title><Msg>they have no shame and their hearts are filled with hate.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135896856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344135945506-136</Id><Topic><Title>PREDICTION, HOW MANY REPUCANS WILL JUMP OFF A WINDOW</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135756078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:02:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you jump off a window? Are you drunk again?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135945506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>