<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349842089801-1</Id><Title>RUMOR HAS IT THAT</Title><Msg>Obama and staff will be dressed in yellow suits with feathers at the next debate. XQ</Msg><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1349842089801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349842657747-2</Id><Title>Funny to see relevant posts on here</Title><Msg>Anyway, the scenario is something like this. JPM and WFC report on Friday before market open. If it is good, push up to 9.60 or maybe even 9.80. Trade around there violently. Then C reports Monday morning. If that is good, can touch 10.10 and sit. Then BAC on Wed. If it is very good, gap up and run to 11. If it is so-so gap up run to 10.50 maybe fall back to 10. Something like that. If JPM is bad the whole market tanks. Oh well. Cya.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1349842657747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349842959859-3</Id><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Msg>Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM) has announced a huge deal with AMD on September 8. 2012 that is sure to take it to the next level in terms of revenues and net income. The stock is completely under the radar and a reason why its 0.2 X sales valuation giving it a $6.5 million market cap. The company is already almost break-even even before the upcoming AMD-related windfall. DRAM has a strong balance sheet with ZERO long term debt. Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products, increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC as well as other applications requiring fast processing like complex engineering simulation models. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year. DRAM develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. The company has more than 70 Fortune 100 customers and it’s been in business since 1967. On September 8, 2012 TechNews Science and Technology published the following article about Advanced Micro Devices (NYSE: AMD) plans to launch an aggressive campaign to encourage all editions of its AMD Memory modules for desktops, and to achieve this has made an agreement with Dataram (NASDAQ: DRAM) known developer of memory modules for servers, workstations and desktops, plus other solutions and associated services; agreement that will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk and come free with AMD Memory memory modules. AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times offer up to 525% higher in games and applications (better than that offered by SSDs), increasing performance, eliminating bottlenecks and improving the gaming experience on the PC. AMD Radeon RAMDisk utility will be available from October to December this year, and although AMD or Dataram gave more details on its operation, we assume that this utility to create a RAM disk to use by way of a fast disk cache, based on the Game and application profiles present in the Catalyst Control Center utility, which comes bundled with graphics cards, motherboards (chipset) and AMD APUs. On September 14, 2012, DRAM stated the following in its fiscal 1Q 2013 earnings report: During this quarter the Company entered into two agreements which we expect will generate growth and profits for Dataram in 2013 and beyond: - An agreement with AMD provides for Dataram to develop and sell AMD licensed and branded versions of its RAMDisk software. AMD’s Radeon RAMDisk will target the gaming enthusiast community. - An agreement with Shoreline Memory Inc. ("Shoreline") and the other with Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. ("AMD") for the purpose of expanding our customer base and product offerings. The Shoreline Agreement provides for Dataram to fulfill 50% of the orders Shoreline receives from its primary customers. Management believes these agreements will provide new revenue sources and expanded markets for the Company's products. Mr. Freeman concluded, “These recent agreements and other new opportunities we are currently pursuing should provide new sources of revenue, profit and growth for Dataram in 2013 and beyond. The experience, knowledge and assets we have gained from our current RAMDisk product, in the development of caching software and in solid state products are building a strong foundation for growth.” DRAM is also an unrecognized cloud play. DRAM makes the XcelaSAN memory/storage family of products for cloud and all other applications. The company recently received $5 million from a Japanese company to allow the non-exclusive right to manufacture products using the XcelaSAN technology. ABOUT DRAM Dataram Corporation (NASDAQ: DRAM), an independent memory manufacturer, develops, manufactures, and markets large capacity memory products primarily used in high performance network servers and workstations worldwide. It offers customized memory solutions for original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) and compatible memory for computers manufactured by various companies. The company also manufactures a line of memory products for Intel and AMD motherboard based servers. In addition, it develops, manufactures, and markets a line of storage caching products. The company sells its memory products to OEMs, distributors, value-added resellers, and end-users. Dataram Corporation was founded in 1967 and is based in Princeton, New Jersey.</Msg><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349842959859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349843213075-4</Id><Title>Read this excerpt about repeated requests about increased security before the embassy murders of our ambassadors and Navy Seals in Benghazi. Then ask yourself how this can be swept under the rug.</Title><Msg>"Nordstrom also argued for more U.S. security in Libya by citing a chronology of over 200 security incidents there from militia gunfights to bomb attacks between June 2011 and July 2012. Forty-eight of the incidents were in Benghazi."</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349843213075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349844082046-5</Id><Topic><Title>Read this excerpt about repeated requests about increased security before the embassy murders of our ambassadors and Navy Seals in Benghazi. Then ask yourself how this can be swept under the rug.</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349843213075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:26:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprised no news about it? We're surprised Obama hasn't hopped on airforce one and started another public relations apology tour at taxpayer expense! At election time, don't forget he's the only president to bow to Muslem leadership in Egypt...he was raised to.</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1349844082046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349845727877-6</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any president of the U.S. who bows to a cleric is religiously discriminating, and breaking our Constitutional mandate not to bow to foreign leadership. remember that at elections.</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1349845727877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349852819225-7</Id><Topic><Title>Madonna says she'll strip onstage if Obama wins new term</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349843988576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:39:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone needs to tell Material Girl it's over for her and Obama</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349852819225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 03:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349859568531-8</Id><Title>My man Obama cares about what is really important: Big Bird</Title><Msg>That's all he talks about, plus Elmo and Sesame Street. It must be important, MSNBC says so.</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitellii</Username><Timestamp>1349859568531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 04:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349862249780-9</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party has 41 million memembers..that is 41 million votes Obama can't get...and this is a FACT!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349575535608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree</Msg><Username>dvpatil_in</Username><Timestamp>1349862249780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 05:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349863152151-10</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you like to see T\Reagan bowing to or GWB kissing Saudi leaders?. Either is available.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863152151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 05:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349863481154-11</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loved Romneycare until it became Obamacare. Ha, ha, ha, ha!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349839591223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney relied on federal contributions to make it work. Where is he going to find an outside source when he doesn't have Uncle Sam to finance him.China? Also Bucky Congress is not exempt from Obamacare.. Under Obamacae you have the same choices that Congress has. It also doesn't cover illegal aliens which will probably be the next lie you try to pedal..</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863481154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349863737749-12</Id><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Msg>Trys to blame the lack of a farm bill passing on Obama. Boehner has held it up for 6 months.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349864702399-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libertydies i;m a farmer and i know all about farm bills and there hasn't been a bill for any farm aid??? The goverment has no reason to talk about farms...talk about jobs...the middle class is needing jobs not food stamps...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349864702399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349864702408-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libertydies i;m a farmer and i know all about farm bills and there hasn't been a bill for any farm aid??? The goverment has no reason to talk about farms...talk about jobs...the middle class is needing jobs not food stamps...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349864702408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349864702483-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libertydies i;m a farmer and i know all about farm bills and there hasn't been a bill for any farm aid??? The goverment has no reason to talk about farms...talk about jobs...the middle class is needing jobs not food stamps...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349864702483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866292214-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The senate passed a farm bill. Boehner would not let it come up for a vote in the house. That is blocking the farm bill. Obama has nothing to do with it until it gets to his desk. Romney lied and you are out of touch.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349866292214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866403698-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loved Romneycare until it became Obamacare. Ha, ha, ha, ha!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349839591223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NATIONAL POLL SHOW 54% OF AMERICAN DO NOT WANT OBANACARE...REPEAT "DO NOT WANT"...WHAT IS SO HARD TO UNDERSTAND ABOUT THAT..."DO NOT WANT" WHY CAN'T YOU GET IT??? "DO NOT WANT"....</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349866403698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866403784-18</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loved Romneycare until it became Obamacare. Ha, ha, ha, ha!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349839591223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NATIONAL POLL SHOW 54% OF AMERICAN DO NOT WANT OBANACARE...REPEAT "DO NOT WANT"...WHAT IS SO HARD TO UNDERSTAND ABOUT THAT..."DO NOT WANT" WHY CAN'T YOU GET IT??? "DO NOT WANT"....</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349866403784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866581785-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loved Romneycare until it became Obamacare. Ha, ha, ha, ha!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349839591223</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:26:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not the job of the goverment to make me buy anything..why can't you understand that...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349866581785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866620054-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"say Romney will see to it a “strong farm bill is passed in a timely manner to give farmers and ranchers the certainty they need for their operations and their livelihoods.” The paper does not define what a “strong” farm bill looks like, however, or say what Romney believes is an appropriate level of government support for farmers. Rep. Collin Peterson (D-Minn.), the top Democrat on the House Agriculture Committee, pushed back on Romney's attack and said House Republican leaders are the ones standing in the way of a farm bill. "I think it's unfair and it shows a complete lack of understanding of what's going on," Peterson said. "The problem is not between the House and the Senate, the problem is Majority Leader Cantor won't put the farm bill on the floor." Peterson said Romney's new policy paper makes him "nervous" that Romney is not really with farmers on maintaining a safety net. "What he says in there is just what is safe to say in front of the Club for Growth," he said. "There is trade and regulations but that's not really the farm bill."</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349866620054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349866720906-21</Id><Topic><Title>*** RED FLAG Found in Friday's Jobs Report</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1349798600056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The average person has no clue how corrupt the Obama administration is. If they only knew</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349866720906</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349868043793-22</Id><Title>President Obama intentionally misled the American public about the death of four Americans for pure political reasons.</Title><Msg>President Obama intentionally misled the American public about the death of four Americans for pure political reasons. This should be a damning indictment of Nixonian proportions. It also raises a lot of questions, for example: Did he have the Secretary of State lie to congress? — who had the Ambassador to the U.N lie on national television? … And there are dead Americans!?! Some Super PAC needs to run a commercial replicating the famous Watergate question: What did the president know, and when did he know it?</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349868043793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349868875006-23</Id><Title>Banks Upgrading The Banks</Title><Msg>Why doesn't BAC upgrade BAC with a strong buy? They are quick to downgrade every other sector except the financials....there's a shocker!</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1349868875006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349869069191-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are grasping for straws with this post. What about giving us your insight on why Obama should not be impeached for having his minions lie about Libya solely for political reasons.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349869069191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349869275519-25</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Flipper and his "Boy" Blunder you have the ability to make up facts ie. lies, when ever you need to attempt to make a pointless attack. Maybe you, if the capability exists, need to spend less time lieing and more attempting to determine what Flipper and the Boy Blunder's REAL agenda is..... the devil is in the details and so far FLIP and DIP only have spoken in conflicting dribble ,that while it might excite the ignorant base has no foundation in reality. As an example we see Flip state he will lower taxs, raise taxs, decrease spending, increase spending, end social programs, keep social programs, Start wars, end wars, Etc., Etc., Etc. .......... Its evident that no REAL plan exists or the Plan exists, but it is going to continue the move towards elimination of the Middle Class. Frankly a piople and a party who will say and support anything that may get the votes of the unthinking should not be allowed to lead anything.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349869275519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349869354230-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its VERY easy to tell when Flip is lieing ................. his mouth is moveing</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349869354230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349869597663-27</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, those who read your posts will know your REAL profession is being a BIGIOT this is a copy of one of your more recent KKK posts :"OBAMA IS ONE WORTHLESS N---ER ". :</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349869597663</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349870326595-28</Id><Title>EVER NOTICE</Title><Msg>That Flipper and the Boy Blunder have had no real accomplishments in goverment other than flippers implementation of what is now called Obama Care, which , of course he has now flipped on. Boy Blunders major contribution has been to vote NO inorder to ensure no progress could be made. It also seems that their ONLY lasting value is to protect the rich at all costs.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349870326595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349870472513-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's lie in Iowa</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349863737749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 06:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Carolyne. Sorry you had such a bad night. Our Democrat inmate population keeps increasing as realization that Romney will win in a landslide..and they are a noisy group; howling, moaning and grunting as their last hopes of increased welfare and food stamps is coming to an end. Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>shutter_islandward8</Username><Timestamp>1349870472513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349870564404-30</Id><Title>The Obama campaign has gone crazy</Title><Msg>The Obama campaign has gone crazy By Ed Rogers-Washington Post The “Big Bird” ad is a sign that the Obama campaign isn’t just desperate; it’s gone crazy. I’ve said all along that it is running a negative, mean-spirited race full of distractions. This time, the campaign has belittled the process to the point where I believe it’s going to backfire. While it’s trivial, President Obama has now offered up the question of whether Big Bird should be a government employee. Is this what he wants the election to be about? There is a larger point to be made here. This ad reinforces the idea that Obama won’t say no to anybody. He uses the Treasury to buy votes and create dependency wherever he can. Team Obama’s lack of insight or any capacity for self-analysis makes it miss the irony of this ad. There is nothing the Obama Administration won’t pay for. There is room for everybody — or at least in this case, every bird — on the government dole. I’m all for campaigns having fun and not always taking themselves too seriously, but the Obama campaign’s pettiness and trivialization of issues will make the president’s problems worse, not better. I expected more of them, but I guess Obama’s campaign team has finally run out of things to say or insults to hurl.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349870564404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349871054305-31</Id><Topic><Title>EVER NOTICE</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349870326595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 07:58:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carolyne. Good morning. My name is Shiitehead. My father is Felix "Faraway" Fartaway. We are Democrats and have the blessing of the Party to incest. r u gay too? Both my father and I would like to get to know you better. Nothing turns us on more than simpleton female Democrats who like to post nonsensical jibberish on a males' message board. love u, Miles.</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1349871054305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872057438-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Obama campaign has gone crazy</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349870564404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as mitt has a microphone, Obama will have plenty of childish material to play with. Which flipper did you wake up on the wrong side of? And this has what to do with the BAC? Five trillion of owed and alleged Euro assets happen to be positioned in BAC, C, JPM, WFC et al derivatives trading. Smoke that in 2013. We can talk later. What your background in? Just trying to keep this civil.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349872057438</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872130654-33</Id><Topic><Title>*** RED FLAG Found in Friday's Jobs Report</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1349798600056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Blah Blah Blah we all know government numbers are a joke. Does anyone believe the CPI and PPI numbers. We all know the world is no growth or slow growth mode. The question is who lead us to the edge of the financial cliff? The same guy who nobody ever sees anymore and the same guy how destroyed every business he ever touched. How did Iraq work out?</Msg><Username>vincent90157</Username><Timestamp>1349872130654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:28:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872352725-34</Id><Topic><Title>We just had a stong earthquake in Montreal Canada</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1349846232532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:17:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably just more fracking. How does your water taste; and does it ignite?</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349872352725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349872598386-35</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tough time spelling? Try using a keyboard. Obviously a dictionary is out of the question for your therapy. From Georgia, by any chance? Earth is exactly 6000 years old, according to their Congressional representative on the House Science, Technology, and Religious committee.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349872598386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873073935-36</Id><Title>If Romney wins, I am moving to South America.</Title><Msg>This is where they still have real democracies. We need to nationalize the fringe right. L</Msg><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349873073935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873219645-37</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins, I am moving to South America.</Title><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349873073935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bye good ridance but bet you don't go commie</Msg><Username>bizman57</Username><Timestamp>1349873219645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873455179-38</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good style points on accuracy. I live close enough to the south (Virginia) to know that, given a chance, slavery and polygamy are only another depression away. Like radical Islam, some folks don't know when to move on. Last I heard, the bigots lost the civil war in 1865 in the US, and the Mormons were driven to Utah even sooner. Evidently Islam and the red states didn't get the news. Europe did. They owe 5 trillion dollars (or as much as 50 trillion) of funny BAC and other alleged fractional reserve papers to each other. Crisis unfolding? Nah. Evolution of this species IS a myth.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349873455179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873706267-39</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins, I am moving to South America.</Title><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349873073935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to trade a consonant for a vowel, sweetie, to be credible. But you aren't, ARE you???</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1349873706267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873786015-40</Id><Title>GOP + NO REGULATIONS = spinal meningetis,,,,vote them all out next month</Title><Msg>GOP is destroying our country for our kids !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349873786015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349873900857-41</Id><Topic><Title>*** RED FLAG Found in Friday's Jobs Report</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1349798600056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the blame time limit has long since expired. Your boy Obama needs to answer to all the corruption and the terrible hopeless economy</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349873900857</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873916129-42</Id><Title>XMAS present of a BAC dividend sure would be nice.</Title><Msg>In the 3% range!</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349873916129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873968564-43</Id><Title>Vote all Democrats in the Senate out they STILL haven't passed a budget</Title><Msg>and the media is silent? Corruption</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349873968564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874009996-44</Id><Topic><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349842959859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah....Thanks! Sounds really good, and according to their filings the float is only 5 million shares? I also read in their filings that they've started a share buyback program in April 2012. This one could become the stock of the year....wow</Msg><Username>disneyes60</Username><Timestamp>1349874009996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874145611-45</Id><Topic><Title>We just had a stong earthquake in Montreal Canada</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1349846232532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:17:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>typical stupid libtard spin..fracking has been around since the 1970s idiot. Environazis go suck on some horse sheit cuz that is what you idiots want us to ride to work on</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349874145611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349874209810-46</Id><Title>Single digit stock use option see-saw strategy</Title><Msg>HOld stock sell both sides of the strike price you purchased the stock....whatever the stock moves, you buy back the option that drops in value ONLY to resell it over and over and over. OR do nothing and allow TIME to evaporate the premium on both</Msg><Username>biglefthook_00</Username><Timestamp>1349874209810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874267354-47</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party has 41 million memembers..that is 41 million votes Obama can't get...and this is a FACT!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349575535608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Colbert and Stewart got more folks on the mall peacefully, with a far better message than the Tea Party. Mil and a half is a total fantasy. Can't ship that many in camping on pickup trucks. No place to park, and the new trucks wouldn't be where they were left. Does that mean that half the tea baggers are still here? Maybe that explains the foreclosure problem. As with Charlie on the MTA...they could never return....What state do they vote from. Remember., D.C. has no representation. Just taxation to support the tea- bagging ball- smuggling alleged- conservative wing nuts. Meanwhile the printing keeps BAC thriving with billions of digits weekly.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349874267354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874273830-48</Id><Topic><Title>The Obama campaign has gone crazy</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349870564404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:02:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He talks about big bird to try and cover up the corruption in his administration. Beware politicians who use kids</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349874273830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874336630-49</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins, I am moving to South America.</Title><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349873073935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup - you an Chavez - 2 peas in a pod - when you leaving again - please do not write , bye .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1349874336630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349874357479-50</Id><Topic><Title>Vote all Democrats in the Senate out they STILL haven't passed a budget</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349873968564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed send the crooks packing and lets get American moving again</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349874357479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349874821339-51</Id><Title>JETRO ROMNEY STRIKES AGAIN - NOW HE HAS NO PROBLEM WITH ABORTION</Title><Msg>Yesterday JETRO claim he has no agenda that will affect the banning of abortion. WHO IS THIS GUY. All along he promise to overturn ROE and de-fund Plan Parenthood now the makes 180% turn, holly crap.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349874821339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875423441-52</Id><Title>price support</Title><Msg>what is your quess for the $ price support?</Msg><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1349875423441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875579275-53</Id><Topic><Title>If Romney wins, I am moving to South America.</Title><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349873073935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:44:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't call me sweetie. That sounds homophobic and you, as a physician, should know better, old cow.</Msg><Username>joeqd01</Username><Timestamp>1349875579275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875660834-54</Id><Title>Solution to the problem in Libya</Title><Msg>They want a new Muslim leader, Give them ours.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349875660834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875739916-55</Id><Title>America needs Obama-care like Nancy</Title><Msg>The liberals are asking us to give Obama time. We agree...and think 25 to life would be appropriate. --Jay Leno America needs Obama-care like Nancy Pelosi needs a Halloween mask. --Jay Leno Q: Have you heard about McDonald's' new Obama Value Meal? A: Order anything you like and the guy behind you has to pay for it. --Conan O'Brien Q: What does Barack Obama call lunch with a convicted felon? A: A fund raiser. --Jay Leno Q: What's the difference between Obama's cabinet and a penitentiary? A: One is filled with tax evaders, blackmailers, and threats to society. The other is for housing prisoners. --David Letterman Q: If Nancy Pelosi and Obama were on a boat in the middle of the ocean and it started to sink, who would be saved? A: America ! --Jimmy Fallon Q: What's the difference between Obama and his dog, Bo? A: Bo has papers. --Jimmy Kimmel Q: What was the most positive result of the "Cash for Clunkers" program? A: It took 95% of the Obama bumper stickers off the road. --David Letterman</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349875739916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349875763760-56</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report (BAC)?</Title><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1349732500944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>townsend_heather596</Username><Timestamp>1349875763760</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349875764046-57</Id><Title>Fringe right. Don't insult Communism for it failed due to lack of computer power</Title><Msg>Unlike the Soviets, we, real Progressives, have computers. And we don't lie. Prepare for Siberia.</Msg><Username>joeqd01</Username><Timestamp>1349875764046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876113749-58</Id><Title>Oil $50: Pros analysts Oil at $50 Credit Suisse analysts Oil at $50</Title><Msg>Oil $50: Pros analysts Oil at $50 Credit Suisse analysts Oil at $50 -- - the analysis argues that demand would fall along with trading activity and that any recovery would be “halting fragile and painfully slow.” The report points to the fall in oil prices witnessed in 2008, when Brent prices plunged from a record high level in the space of a few months. The analysts Oil at $50</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1349876113749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876147799-59</Id><Title>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Title><Msg>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel Based on Sanford C. Bernstein estimates of the marginal cost of oil production, the geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now. Reminding the market that a strategic cushion exists—without necessarily deploying it—provides a check on that premium rising even further. Sweet Crude Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel. That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline. Sanford Bernstein geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline.</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1349876147799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876201425-60</Id><Title>Oil has a better chance at $60 to $50 than $100</Title><Msg>Oct. 5, 2012, 8:02 a.m. EDT Oil has a better chance at $60 to $50 than $100 By Myra P. Saefong, MarketWatch And while there are many factors that will influence oil in the months ahead, most of them point to the likelihood of prices falling to levels closer to $60 to $50 a barrel — or at least not making any sort of lasting impression at $100 in the fourth quarter. “Given the backdrop of slowing global demand and rising non-OPEC production, the odds are that Brent heads to below $100 as we get towards the end of the year, which will also pressure WTI to stay closer to $60 to $50,” said Kirk McDonald, senior research analyst at St. Louis-based Argent Capital Management. Overall, the selloff in West Texas crude oil has been “due to the converging bearish themes of lethargic economic data, lackluster oil demand and the continuing trend of rising domestic oil production,” said Smith. “Meanwhile, signs of slowing in China and a euro-debt crisis that rumbles on and on provide little reason to be bullish right now.” U.S. field production of oil has climbed to its highest level since 1996, according to Energy Information Administration data. Production is currently at more than 6.5 million barrels per day. See the EIA’s latest production data. “The renaissance in domestic production is real and can be attributed to improved exploration and production techniques as well as higher prices,” which enables the economic recovery of previously known reserves, said Michael Peterson, managing director of energy research at MLV &amp; Co. At the same time, “industry capital has rotated back to the U.S. en masse because there is no fear premium to operating,” with the U.S. and Canada the safest places to make large capital investments in projects, said Neal Ryan, managing partner at Ryan Oil &amp; Gas Partners LLC. The largest area of output growth among oil producers who are not part of the Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries is North America, according to the EIA, which expects production there to increase by 1 million barrels per day in 2012. See the EIA’s Short-Term Energy Outlook Report from September. Oil should be “at the $60 to $50 level in the fourth quarter as long as Israel doesn’t employ a preemptive attack on Iran,” said Zahir. And, barring any specific supply-shock scenarios, Peterson said the likelihood of significantly higher WTI oil prices in 2012 is “limited” to less than 25%. When asked if $100 or $60 oil prices are more likely, Peterson replied: “$60 is more likely near-term,</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1349876201425</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349876394571-61</Id><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Msg>We research..you profit! Check us out! Copy &amp; paste to your browser: mcaf.ee/jngvm</Msg><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877143629-62</Id><Topic><Title>The Stock Market doubled during Obama's first term</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876754994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>give me interest free money to work with and i will double any bodys money!</Msg><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1349877143629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877275867-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime's biggest FLIP-FLOP ......</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349876800250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:46:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary should be hauled in front of a house sub-committee on this one!</Msg><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1349877275867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877402569-64</Id><Topic><Title>The liberal biased media is skewering the polls</Title><Username>buckydoodle_5</Username><Timestamp>1349792052081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because they are gay commie libtards!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>durnpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349877402569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877420151-65</Id><Topic><Title>DRAM $0.64 with $6.5M Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's AMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products</Title><Username>bt.bigten</Username><Timestamp>1349842959859</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are no shares for sale on this one! once buying starts it could quickly sail through $1</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1349877420151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877616260-66</Id><Topic><Title>I find this disturbing</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876568729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's REALLY disturbing....... is the MOOSLIM Bible !!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>durnpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349877616260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877617504-67</Id><Topic><Title>XMAS present of a BAC dividend sure would be nice.</Title><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349873916129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:58:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOO: They've got the cash to do it, ...problem is the democRap OVER regulation. HFT is also manipulating the Stock. And others. Another Wall St.guru,..named Kooperman is now calling on the SEC to restore the 70 year-old market stabilizer known as "THE UPTICK RULE" We should see a dividend fairly soon, however we MUST rid Washington of the control they are currently enamored with. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1349877617504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349877723256-68</Id><Title>wall street theives and criminals stealing all the QE money</Title><Msg>wheres it going? it's vanishing lol</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1349877723256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878061358-69</Id><Title>JPM reports Friday...if good...could see 2% pop</Title><Msg>9 and holding</Msg><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1349878061358</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878244072-70</Id><Title>OBAMA &amp; CARTER LUNACY</Title><Msg>Democrats are F'ed in the head</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1349878244072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:10:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878510563-71</Id><Title>CEO to Workers: I May Fire You if Obama Wins</Title><Msg>google it!</Msg><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349878510563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349878771899-72</Id><Title>IF OBAMA HAD BEEN ELECTED AFTER CARTER AMERICA WOULD BE DEAD</Title><Msg>THAT'S THE TRUTH!!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1349878771899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878815160-73</Id><Topic><Title>Is the rampant stupidity among the fringe-right caused by inbreeding . . .</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1348919083283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote NObama in NOvemeber!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349878815160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878822634-74</Id><Topic><Title>price support</Title><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1349875423441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:23:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7.00</Msg><Username>ortho+2h</Username><Timestamp>1349878822634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879008771-75</Id><Title>INDIANA ROMNEY 51% OBAMA 35% THAT AWAY HOOVERS!!!!</Title><Msg>Bill clinton and hillary was taking a walk in a park when hillary saw a old drake duck loading all the hen ducks..she truned to bill and said,"why can't you be like that old drake there bill"?? Bill said,"i could if i could get me a new duck"...ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349879008771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879008781-76</Id><Title>INDIANA ROMNEY 51% OBAMA 35% THAT AWAY HOOVERS!!!!</Title><Msg>Bill clinton and hillary was taking a walk in a park when hillary saw a old drake duck loading all the hen ducks..she truned to bill and said,"why can't you be like that old drake there bill"?? Bill said,"i could if i could get me a new duck"...ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349879008781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879008805-77</Id><Title>INDIANA ROMNEY 51% OBAMA 35% THAT AWAY HOOVERS!!!!</Title><Msg>Bill clinton and hillary was taking a walk in a park when hillary saw a old drake duck loading all the hen ducks..she truned to bill and said,"why can't you be like that old drake there bill"?? Bill said,"i could if i could get me a new duck"...ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349879008805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879018451-78</Id><Topic><Title>I'm really glad Obama's stimulus is working and people are finding jobs. NOT!!</Title><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349662573773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We know the numbers are WRONG!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349879018451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:23:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879045552-79</Id><Topic><Title>CEO to Workers: I May Fire You if Obama Wins</Title><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349878510563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the coming from a guy who is building a 90K square foot house. Give me a brake.</Msg><Username>lookfwd</Username><Timestamp>1349879045552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879191819-80</Id><Topic><Title>CEO to Workers: I May Fire You if Obama Wins</Title><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349878510563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you don't expect the obama administration to comply with the law do you? why change now?</Msg><Username>charlesvermillion</Username><Timestamp>1349879191819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:26:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879465822-81</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awoooh..this one is GREAT! subscribe now...</Msg><Username>burgess_christina611</Username><Timestamp>1349879465822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879483686-82</Id><Topic><Title>Gee libertylies, spin this</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349879202805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huh?</Msg><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349879483686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879820996-83</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this ain't no SPAM..this is real! try it now!!!</Msg><Username>mckinney_lara552</Username><Timestamp>1349879820996</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349879954985-84</Id><Topic><Title>CEO to Workers: I May Fire You if Obama Wins</Title><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349878510563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is the coming from a guy who is building a 90K square foot house" --------------------------------------- So, whats wrong if he is a billionaire and he owns a 90k sq F home? Just because he's got money some people want to take what he worked for. Why he have to be penalized and over taxed to support you?</Msg><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349879954985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349879995863-85</Id><Title>My talking chair has a yellow puddle in the bottom of it</Title><Msg>It's been that way for years, but that doesn't stop me from talking to it.</Msg><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349879995863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880095069-86</Id><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Msg>YOUR RIGHT THERE GOVENOR!!!! ILMFAO</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880293104-87</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOTA ROCKS...but this is better than DOTA!!! subscribe now..</Msg><Username>bates_anne556</Username><Timestamp>1349880293104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880324318-88</Id><Topic><Title>The liberal biased media is skewering the polls</Title><Username>buckydoodle_5</Username><Timestamp>1349792052081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact-checkers are skewering the polls too!</Msg><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349880324318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880371332-89</Id><Topic><Title>I find this disturbing</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876568729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>copy-cat post!!</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349880371332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880401758-90</Id><Topic><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you been checked for rabies?</Msg><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349880401758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880482214-91</Id><Title>A look at what happens when a currecny collapses(CURRENT IRAN EXAMPLE)</Title><Msg>The Iranian situation has been labeled hyperinflation. What does that mean in real terms? Here’s a fact sheet courtesy of Steve Hanke, professor of economics at John Hopkins: 1. Iran is experiencing an implied monthly inflation rate of 69.6%. For comparison, in the month before the sanctions took effect (June 2010), the monthly inflation rate was 0.698%. 2. Iran is experiencing an implied annual inflation rate of 196%. For comparison, in June 2010, the annual (year-over-year) inflation rate was 8.25%. 3. The current monthly inflation rate implies a price-doubling time of 39.8 days. For certain goods, such as chicken, prices may be doubling at an even faster rate. 4. The current inflation rate implies an equivalent daily inflation rate of 1.78%. Compare that with the United States, where the annual inflation rate is 1.69%.</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349880482214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880491120-92</Id><Topic><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gov. also signed a bill to loosen gasoline laws to help with the pain at the pump</Msg><Username>mechcanic408</Username><Timestamp>1349880491120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880546815-93</Id><Topic><Title>Pssssssssssssssssssssssssssssst! US has already gone over Fiscal Cliff</Title><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349791133659</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 09:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They better look at Iran's example-QUICKLY! The Iranian situation has been labeled hyperinflation. What does that mean in real terms? Here’s a fact sheet courtesy of Steve Hanke, professor of economics at John Hopkins: 1. Iran is experiencing an implied monthly inflation rate of 69.6%. For comparison, in the month before the sanctions took effect (June 2010), the monthly inflation rate was 0.698%. 2. Iran is experiencing an implied annual inflation rate of 196%. For comparison, in June 2010, the annual (year-over-year) inflation rate was 8.25%. 3. The current monthly inflation rate implies a price-doubling time of 39.8 days. For certain goods, such as chicken, prices may be doubling at an even faster rate. 4. The current inflation rate implies an equivalent daily inflation rate of 1.78%. Compare that with the United States, where the annual inflation rate is 1.69%.</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349880546815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880695260-94</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks legit. Thank you for sharing this</Msg><Username>haynes_jeanette559</Username><Timestamp>1349880695260</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349880845640-95</Id><Title>IF OBAMA HAD BEEN ELECTED AFTER CARTER AMERICA WOULD BE DEAD</Title><Msg>Reality check</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1349880845640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349880876157-96</Id><Topic><Title>CEO to Workers: I May Fire You if Obama Wins</Title><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1349878510563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:15:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Subject: Message from David Siegel Date:Mon, 08 Oct 2012 13:58:05 -0400 (EDT) From: [David Siegel] To: [All employees] To All My Valued Employees, As most of you know our company, Westgate Resorts, has continued to succeed in spite of a very dismal economy. There is no question that the economy has changed for the worse and we have not seen any improvement over the past four years. In spite of all of the challenges we have faced, the good news is this: The economy doesn't currently pose a threat to your job. What does threaten your job however, is another 4 years of the same Presidential administration. Of course, as your employer, I can't tell you whom to vote for, and I certainly wouldn't interfere with your right to vote for whomever you choose. In fact, I encourage you to vote for whomever you think will serve your interests the best. However, let me share a few facts that might help you decide what is in your best interest.The current administration and members of the press have perpetuated an environment that casts employers against employees. They want you to believe that we live in a class system where the rich get richer, the poor get poorer. They label us the "1%" and imply that we are somehow immune to the challenges that face our country. This could not be further from the truth. Sure, you may have heard about the big home that I'm building. I'm sure many people think that I live a privileged life. However, what you don't see or hear is the true story behind any success that I have achieved. I started this company over 42 years ago. At that time, I lived in a very modest home. I converted my garage into an office so I could put forth 100% effort into building a company, which by the way, would eventually employ you. We didn't eat in fancy restaurants or take expensive vacations because every dollar I made went back into this company. I drove an old used car, and often times, I stayed home on weekends, while my friends went out drinking and partying. In fact, I was married to my business - hard work, discipline, and sacrifice. Meanwhile, many of my friends got regular jobs. They worked 40 hours a week and made a nice income, and they spent every dime they earned. They drove flashy cars and lived in expensive homes and wore fancy designer clothes. My friends refinanced their mortgages and lived a life of luxury. I, however, did not. I put my time, my money, and my life into this business --with a vision that eventually, some day, I too, will be able to afford to buy whatever I wanted. Even to this day, every dime I earn goes back into this company. Over the past four years I have had to stop building my dream house, cut back on all of my expenses, and take my kids out of private schools simply to keep this company strong and to keep you employed. Just think about this - most of you arrive at work in the morning and leave that afternoon and the rest of your time is yours to do as you please. But not me- there is no "off" button for me. When you leave the office, you are done and you have a weekend all to yourself. I unfortunately do not have that freedom. I eat, live, and breathe this company every minute of the day, every day of the week. There is no rest. There is no weekend. There is no happy hour. I know many of you work hard and do a great job, but I'm the one who has to sign every check, pay every expense, and make sure that this company continues to succeed. Unfortunately, what most people see is the nice house and the lavish lifestyle. What the press certainly does not want you to see, is the true story of the hard work and sacrifices I've made. Now, the economy is falling apart and people like me who made all the right decisions and invested in themselves are being forced to bail out all the people who didn't. The people that overspent their paychecks suddenly feel entitled to the same luxuries that I earned and sacrificed 42 years of my life for. Yes, business ownership has its benefits, but the price I've paid is steep and not without wounds. Unfortunately, the costs of running a business have gotten out of control, and let me tell you why: We are being taxed to death and the government thinks we don't pay enough. We pay state taxes, federal taxes, property taxes, sales and use taxes, payroll taxes, workers compensation taxes and unemployment taxes. I even have to hire an entire department to manage all these taxes. The question I have is this: Who is really stimulating the economy? Is it the Government that wants to take money from those who have earned it and give it to those who have not, or is it people like me who built a company out of his garage and directly employs over 7000 people and hosts over 3 million people per year with a great vacation? Obviously, our present government believes that taking my money is the right economic stimulus for this country. The fact is, if I deducted 50 percent of your paycheck you'd quit and you wouldn't work here. I mean, why should you? Who wants to get rewarded only 50 percent of their hard work? Well, that's what happens to me. Here is what most people don't understand and the press and our Government has chosen to ignore - to stimulate the economy you need to stimulate what runs the economy. Instead of raising my taxes and depositing that money into the Washington black-hole, let me spend it on growing the company, hire more employees, and generate substantial economic growth. My employees will enjoy the wealth of that tax cut in the form of promotions and better salaries. But that is not what our current Government wants you to believe. They want you to believe that it somehow makes sense to take more from those who create wealth and give it to those who do not, and somehow our economy will improve. They don't want you to know that the "1%", as they like to label us, pay more than 31% of all the taxes in this country. Thomas Jefferson, the author of our great Constitution, once said, "democracy" will cease to exist when you take away from those who are willing to work and give to those who would not." Business is at the heart of America and always has been. To restart it, you must stimulate business, not kill it. However, the power brokers in Washington believe redistributing wealth is the essential driver of the American economic engine. Nothing could be further from the truth and this is the type of change they want. So where am I going with all this? It's quite simple. If any new taxes are levied on me, or my company, as our current President plans, I will have no choice but to reduce the size of this company. Rather than grow this company I will be forced to cut back. This means fewer jobs, less benefits and certainly less opportunity for everyone. So, when you make your decision to vote, ask yourself, which candidate understands the economics of business ownership and who doesn't? Whose policies will endanger your job? Answer those questions and you should know who might be the one capable of protecting and saving your job. While the media wants to tell you to believe the "1 percenters" are bad, I'm telling you they are not. They create most of the jobs. If you lose your job, it won't be at the hands of the "1%"; it will be at the hands of a political hurricane that swept through this country. You see, I can no longer support a system that penalizes the productive and gives to the unproductive. My motivation to work and to provide jobs will be destroyed, and with it, so will your opportunities. If that happens, you can find me in the Caribbean sitting on the beach, under a palm tree, retired, and with no employees to worry about. Signed, your boss, David Siegel</Msg><Username>upyou_s</Username><Timestamp>1349880876157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881056220-97</Id><Topic><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well i was in a fight once with a dummycrapper and he did bit me...the next time i saw him we fought again but he only gummed me that time...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349881056220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881056237-98</Id><Topic><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well i was in a fight once with a dummycrapper and he did bit me...the next time i saw him we fought again but he only gummed me that time...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349881056237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349881320187-99</Id><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Msg>You gotta read this important report which provides great technical information. Just wanted to share this with everyone. Link:-- y.ahoo.it/6iS/y Copy and Paste the link to your browser. Link:-- y.ahoo.it/6iS/y</Msg><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881389754-100</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just read the info on the site. Much different from other guys.</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1349881389754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881408530-101</Id><Topic><Title>IF OBAMA HAD BEEN ELECTED AFTER CARTER AMERICA WOULD BE DEAD</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1349880845640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep America could not withstand two screwball idiot Democrats in a row</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1349881408530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349881576471-102</Id><Topic><Title>GOV.JERRY BOWN SAID TODAY..."HIGH GASOLINE PRICES ARE GOOD! THE GAS TAX WILL HELP PAY ALL THESE F--KIN ENTITLEMENTS HERE IN CALIFORNIA ILMFAO</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349880095069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In west virgina there 45% republican and 55% democrat..so why do the republicans always win?? Well 50% of the democrats can read or write and we fugured out years ago that 50% of them are voting republican and don't even know it..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349881576471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882001478-103</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>love_maria569</Username><Timestamp>1349882001478</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882303913-104</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>powers_carol565</Username><Timestamp>1349882303913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882530097-105</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Wilson was correct, and now Jack Welch proven correct too.</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349880854078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine an SW rectal drip alias, in this case zevoter, who does not plagiarize and steal articles off of the internet and try to claim them as his own? This is only one way to spot an SW rectal drip alias. If they are not lifting somone else's work to copy and paste word for word, they are eating s*h*i*t*.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349882530097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882582101-106</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Informative indeed. Thanks!</Msg><Username>tenishaqjcz03936</Username><Timestamp>1349882582101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882647060-107</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Wilson was correct, and now Jack Welch proven correct too.</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349880854078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trading Places</Msg><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1349882647060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349882751166-108</Id><Title>Jack Welch, good-bye and good riddance. Another GOP gas bag flushed.</Title><Msg>Let's just hope he remains flushed and does not resurface somewhere else.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349882751166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882758378-109</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>young_deborah573</Username><Timestamp>1349882758378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882919960-110</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Wilson was correct, and now Jack Welch proven correct too.</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349880854078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did Wilson dodge combat in Vietnam? Smacks of cowardice to me.</Msg><Username>kooper156</Username><Timestamp>1349882919960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:28:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882924617-111</Id><Topic><Title>*** RED FLAG Found in Friday's Jobs Report</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1349798600056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad the major media outlets are complicit in reelecting Obama. Investigations would be revealing</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349882924617</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349883071747-112</Id><Title>For clear insight into the mind of a typical Tea Bagger, read the posts of pervert milesed18</Title><Msg>milesed18 is a typical racist, inbred, white trash neo-nazi goon. He is THE Tea Bagger poster boy.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883071747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883111724-113</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>mullins_ashley574</Username><Timestamp>1349883111724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883157693-114</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Wilson was correct, and now Jack Welch proven correct too.</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349880854078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another chickenhawk.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883157693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883179196-115</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems legit, thanks for the free info.</Msg><Username>cristalxwhv46591</Username><Timestamp>1349883179196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883269678-116</Id><Topic><Title>I find this disturbing</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876568729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find Tea Baggers, like you, very disturbing..</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883269678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883347005-117</Id><Topic><Title>My talking chair has a yellow puddle in the bottom of it</Title><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349879995863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention the straw.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883347005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883530897-118</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>graham_natalie576</Username><Timestamp>1349883530897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883730777-119</Id><Topic><Title>Is the rampant stupidity among the fringe-right caused by inbreeding . . .</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1348919083283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask zevoter</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883730777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349883747697-120</Id><Title>WATCH OUT PEOPLE..SHE'S GOING DOWNNN...TAKE YOUR PROFITS</Title><Msg>NOW</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349883747697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349883833018-121</Id><Topic><Title>WATCH OUT PEOPLE..SHE'S GOING DOWNNN...TAKE YOUR PROFITS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349883747697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why?</Msg><Username>hucktwain</Username><Timestamp>1349883833018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884276455-122</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Subscribed! Hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>regeniarunmp23502</Username><Timestamp>1349884276455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884343538-123</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>reeves_catherine585</Username><Timestamp>1349884343538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349884395980-124</Id><Title>WAKE UP AMERICA</Title><Msg>DEMPCROACHES ARE LYING CROOKS !!! ROMNEY 2012</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1349884395980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349884441069-125</Id><Title>Greece's Debt Nightmare Just Got Worse!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>By Holly Ellyatt | CNBC – Tue, Oct 9, 2012 6:14 AM EDT German Chancellor Angela Merkel is landing in Greece to show her solidarity with her Greek counterpart, prime minister Antonis Samaras, but economists are questioning what the visit will achieve, as the country faces a yawning budget deficit and a public debt that one former minister says is now not "repayable". Seven thousand police officers have been scrambled to clear the streets of central Athens along with rooftop snipers and commandos to protect the German leader when she arrives in Athens at 13:30 local time (30 a.m. London time). Greece's two largest unions threatened to defy a ban imposed on protesting in the city center, calling on their members to convene at Syntagma square. But CNBC's Carolin Roth reported that the police seemed to have things under control the streets were quiet on Tuesday morning. But economists told CNBC that Merkel was the least of Greece's problems. According to the latest economic forecasts from the International Monetary Fund (IMF), released on Tuesday, Greece will miss the five-year debt reduction target that underpins the country's 130 billion euro bailout. The IMF forecast that Greek public debt will rise to 171 percent of gross domestic product (GDP) this year and 182 percent in 2013. The IMF has also warned the Eurogroup of finance ministers who met in Luxembourg on Monday that Greece's debt would need restructuring and that it will be almost impossible to reduce the country's debt levels to a target of 120 per cent of economic output by 2020. Jens Larsen, Chief European Economist at RBC Capital Markets, agreed that Greece's current debt situation was not sustainable. "Greece will definitely have to do another restructuring," Larsen told CNBC's "Worldwide Exchange" on Tuesday. "The question is how do they get one - as part of a deal or do they take one because there is no deal and things break down?" Peter Doukas, Greece's former deputy minister of economy and finance and the current chairman at Capital Partner, told CNBC that Merkel's visit could not stave of the country's impending funding crisis and he said an official debt haircut was "absolutely inevitable." "The Greek debt is not repayable at this point. The economy is too weak to afford a 300 billion euro ($387.9 billion) plus debt." Greece is hoping to secure the next tranche of the 130 billion euros in aid from the troika. Without that aid, the country will run out of money by November, prime minister Samaras told a German paper. Doukas said that soon the subject of debt repayment would have to be re-addressed. "Perhaps now isn't the best time to talk about it, but very soon we're going to have to talk about rescheduling of Greece's official debt. It simply isn't repayable." That could prove hard because most of the debt owed to private creditors was reduced in the last restructuring, leaving mainly debt owed to the official sector: the European Union, the IMF and the ECB. "There's going to be an official debt haircut or restructuring or rescheduling of sorts. My feeling is that it needs to go 15 years further in terms of maturity and a cutting of interest rates by at least 1.5 percent," Doukas said. As personal incomes fall by 25 percent and youth unemployment increases to 55 percent, Doukas told CNBC, Greece faces its biggest hurdles yet and needed to pass reforms requested by the troika lenders (the IMF, ECB and European Commission). "We are at the bottom of the pile...We need to balance our budget, reform our banking system...there are a lot of reforms that need to be taken...the more we delay, the more things get dragged on." Doukas remained confident that the euro zone was firmly behind Greece and that Merkel's visit signified European solidarity with Greece. Citing Mario Draghi's announcement that the European Central Bank would support secondary markets in their sovereign bond-buying scheme, Doukas remarked that the euro zone was not willing to let Greece go, yet. "It seems that Europe has determined that almost at any cost they will support the salvation of the euro and southern European countries." HERE IS THE SCARY PART, IT'S GOING TO GET EVEN WORSE, SPAIN NEXT SHOE TO DROP!!!</Msg><Username>mrj.premier</Username><Timestamp>1349884441069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884745625-126</Id><Topic><Title>WATCH OUT PEOPLE..SHE'S GOING DOWNNN...TAKE YOUR PROFITS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349883747697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. Started shorting at 9.41 last week and was stopped out 9.51 Technically, broke down yesterday and with th WFC news didn't help. Initiatied short yesterday and added to it pre-market today. First target 8.87. Close at or around 8.87 and it could go back to 8.50 or lower. IMHO way over priced with their fundamentals and run up for the year. C or JPM are much better opportunities for a long position.</Msg><Username>sammsjohn99</Username><Timestamp>1349884745625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884798323-127</Id><Topic><Title>For clear insight into the mind of a typical Tea Bagger, read the posts of pervert milesed18</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883071747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has been iggy'd, but she will pop up several more times this week under different disgusting new alias. More ball smuggling to be expected. Tame compared to the threats against the President that seem to run ignored on Yahoo.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349884798323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884838730-128</Id><Topic><Title>WATCH OUT PEOPLE..SHE'S GOING DOWNNN...TAKE YOUR PROFITS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349883747697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:42:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could not disagree more...</Msg><Username>hucktwain</Username><Timestamp>1349884838730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349884898562-129</Id><Topic><Title>I'm really glad Obama's stimulus is working and people are finding jobs. NOT!!</Title><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349662573773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cooked books and LIES!!!!!! LIES!!!!!!! LIES!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349884898562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885025439-130</Id><Topic><Title>There is a mooslim mole running loose in Hillary's office.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876200009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:36:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE WILL BURY THEM ALL!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885025439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885212850-131</Id><Title>looks like the market likes Rmoneys new Lead in the polls ...lol</Title><Msg>nice as soon as the polls showed mr 1% ahead the market tanked</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349885212850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885220043-132</Id><Title>looks like the market likes Rmoneys new Lead in the polls ...lol</Title><Msg>nice as soon as the polls showed mr 1% ahead the market tanked</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349885220043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885278703-133</Id><Topic><Title>I find this disturbing</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876568729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Commie Mooslims are 10,000 times worser than this!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885278703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885279445-134</Id><Title>Rmoney is pro choice today ...to friggin funny</Title><Msg>except the average phat american buys into his total #$%$</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349885279445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885347811-135</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1349885347811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885376910-136</Id><Topic><Title>Rmoney is pro choice today ...to friggin funny</Title><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349885279445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid commie libtard can't even spell fat right. Can you spell cat?</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885376910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885472404-137</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report (BAC)?</Title><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1349732500944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1349885472404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885556644-138</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for this guys!</Msg><Username>cross_tara587</Username><Timestamp>1349885556644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349885742327-139</Id><Title>All the polls showing Obama ahead are uncorrect!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>The polls that show Romney ahead ARE the correct ones.</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885742327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885813973-140</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this.</Msg><Username>danielacuxb471646</Username><Timestamp>1349885813973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349885989259-141</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love free reports. Just joined</Msg><Username>manning_beth588</Username><Timestamp>1349885989259</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886030436-142</Id><Topic><Title>For clear insight into the mind of a typical Tea Bagger, read the posts of pervert milesed18</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349883071747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HE IS THE VOICE OF MY AMERICA!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349886030436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886195160-143</Id><Topic><Title>Obama "WE ARE SORRY, WE'RE AMERICANS WERE WRONG"</Title><Username>todaydeals</Username><Timestamp>1244051898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2009-06-03 13:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ttttt</Msg><Username>obamahasgoat.fetish</Username><Timestamp>1349886195160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886195432-144</Id><Topic><Title>The Stock Market doubled during Obama's first term</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876754994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is just #$%$ libtard LIES!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349886195432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886385924-145</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. thanks</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1349886385924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886479048-146</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>v.roman61</Username><Timestamp>1349886479048</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886698865-147</Id><Topic><Title>Huge Stock Alert!</Title><Username>hoauqb989233</Username><Timestamp>1349876394571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>townsend_heather596</Username><Timestamp>1349886698865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887017916-148</Id><Topic><Title>The Stock Market doubled during Obama's first term</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876754994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Copy-cat #$%$/h/o/l/e poster..puke just like all Team Obama.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349887017916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887061915-149</Id><Title>JOBS REPORT NUBMERS WERE FUDGED AND COOKED!!!!!!</Title><Msg>WANT PROOF? JAACK WELCH QUIT OVER IT!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349887061915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887125267-150</Id><Title>Inside trader Nancy Pelosi along with the thousands of republican insider traders</Title><Msg>How many millions did they make trading on insider information? Isn't that a felony? Nancy's overseas investments- wow, she could bring millions more into her pockets, but she publicly criticizes others with international investments?</Msg><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349887125267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887262421-151</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>mittieevdf91666</Username><Timestamp>1349887262421</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:41:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887345814-152</Id><Title>Bank of America</Title><Msg>No. 1 in deposits! Move those small accounts to credit unions, can't make money off those. Observers SNL spoke to were unsurprised by the deposit jump accompanied by a continued branch slump. All said the increase in deposits reflects continued risk aversion among depositors and investors, in the face of economic uncertainty arising from Europe, the fiscal cliff and the upcoming U.S. elections. "People are very, very nervous about putting money into the markets and other types of instruments because essentially there's too much risk and uncertainty out there," said Kalan Mac Ginley, a managing director with Macquarie Capital (USA) Inc. "As that uncertainty hopefully unwinds and things settle themselves over the next couple of years, I think you'll see money flowing out as quickly as you saw money flowing into those accounts." Bank of America Corp., Wells Fargo &amp; Co., JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. and Citigroup Inc. held onto the top four spots in terms of total domestic deposits at U.S. banks and thrifts. JPMorgan and Wells Fargo both experienced deposit growth of more than 12%, while Citi's deposits climbed nearly 24%.</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1349887345814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887360154-153</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report (BAC)?</Title><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1349732500944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>ingerxfn544</Username><Timestamp>1349887360154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887748898-154</Id><Title>Jamie DEMON speaking</Title><Msg>watch the market tank now..</Msg><Username>shortburner2012</Username><Timestamp>1349887748898</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349887849591-155</Id><Title>YELP on sale</Title><Msg>27.00 close.</Msg><Username>shortburner2012</Username><Timestamp>1349887849591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349888184647-156</Id><Title>I CAN'T BELIEVE BAC HAS BEEN SHORTED BACK DOWN TO $9.11 TODAY. Bank of America at $9.11 again.</Title><Msg>Is anyone out there that has got a handle on whether any naked shorting is going on again to take this down to 9.11 again? That is scary and ridiculous if you ask me. In this financially unstable world, WHY DO WE HAVE NO MULTICENT UPTICK RULE BACK IN USE MANDATED BY THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT YET? Especially for banks that their financial condition Tier 1 is affected by their common equity??!!!!?? I TRULY DO NOT UNDERSTAND WHY! DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1349888184647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:56:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349888530612-157</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have it already. It's the best.</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1349888530612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349888703744-158</Id><Title>THE RMONEY RALLY !!!!!!</Title><Msg>once the mormon goes up in the polls the market tanks !!</Msg><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349888703744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349889524689-159</Id><Title>Oct 10 Gallup Pole of REGISTERED VOTERS: Obama - 50% Romney - 45%</Title><Msg>The Oct 10 Gallup Pole of LIKELY voters: Obama - 48% Romney - 48% Before the resident brain-dead repugs start up again with their usual rabid frothing and ranting -- go to the Gallup site and check the numbers. Also, READ (if you can) the difference between registered and likely voters per Gallup's definition.</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349889524689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349889868416-160</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>thelmaufwm26402</Username><Timestamp>1349889868416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349890142913-161</Id><Title>BIG SELLOFF COMING....MARKET WAAAAY OVERBOUGHT.</Title><Msg>Time to cash in and take profits... Good luck to all. Herman Fox</Msg><Username>lvsfoxherman</Username><Timestamp>1349890142913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890548383-162</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY BLASTED BY MOTHER OF DEAD SOLDIER FOR USING HIS DEAD BODY FOR POLITICAL</Title><Username>chavesagain</Username><Timestamp>1349890272730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LUV OBAMA. LONG BAC</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349890548383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349890598786-163</Id><Title>Remember: fha- houses</Title><Msg>itsnot a house, its an investment, (underwater 20-50%) but an investment in the Forward... likeyou know, dat college degree for you suckers with $ 1 Trillion in debt lookin for a job.... sorry..no jobs, Capital on strike</Msg><Username>berniecongress</Username><Timestamp>1349890598786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890666282-164</Id><Topic><Title>BIG SELLOFF COMING....MARKET WAAAAY OVERBOUGHT.</Title><Username>lvsfoxherman</Username><Timestamp>1349890142913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:29:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LUV OBAMA. LONG BAC.</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349890666282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349890768681-165</Id><Title>Jamie Dimon Essentially said the Marxist Obama Administration with its War on Business is Killing America</Title><Msg>also said failure to adopt simpson bowles throws a wet blanket on the economy</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349890768681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890861688-166</Id><Topic><Title>A LOT OF SELLING INTO EVERY UPTICK..BE CAREFUL</Title><Username>stocksleuth13</Username><Timestamp>1349811646069</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 15:40:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a day limit buy order at $9.05 It seems the buyers are eager to buy around $9.10 and support may be found there. This leg of the up-trend is still in force. GLTA</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349890861688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349890869110-167</Id><Topic><Title>THE RMONEY RALLY !!!!!!</Title><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349888703744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is because of his million dollar smile and hair spray:) LONG BAC</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349890869110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349890893224-168</Id><Title>Chicago-Chicago..my kond of town!</Title><Msg>Chicago and Cook County has a gun violence problem, Chicago's got a high high school drop-out rate, they've got a drug problem, they've got a gang problem, but they want to make legal gun owners, guys like me, the scapegoat," he said.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349890893224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891008112-169</Id><Topic><Title>Jamie Dimon Essentially said the Marxist Obama Administration with its War on Business is Killing America</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349890768681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:39:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LUV OBAMA. LONG BAC.</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349891008112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891181804-170</Id><Title>Romney up by one in latest Rasmussen and tied in latest Gallup ..Oct. 11</Title><Msg>with record millions out of work Obama talks about Big bird</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349891181804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891296985-171</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More more and more articles please.</Msg><Username>flynnacosta69</Username><Timestamp>1349891296985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891307777-172</Id><Topic><Title>Romney up by one in latest Rasmussen and tied in latest Gallup ..Oct. 11</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349891181804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I LUV OBAMA... LONG BAC</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349891307777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891369045-173</Id><Topic><Title>There is a mooslim mole running loose in Hillary's office.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876200009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:36:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will bury all of the Mooslim rats too. ILMFAO</Msg><Username>mllesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349891369045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:49:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891414829-174</Id><Title>Jamie Dimon also warned in 2-5yrs the Bond Market rates will Blow up on USA Government Debt</Title><Msg>He said we still have a window to get a simpson bowles type entitlement reform before the day of reckoning hits</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349891414829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891562154-175</Id><Title>BAC: Going GREEN in a DWN MARKET!</Title><Msg>Bank of America could potentially surprise everyone very soon, as the balance sheet CLEAN UP in full effect.</Msg><Username>maxxybb</Username><Timestamp>1349891562154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:52:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891656638-176</Id><Title>ADMIT IT REPUCANS, ROMNEY FLIP FLOP FLIP MUST BE EMBARRASSING</Title><Msg>just yesterday he flipped on the abortion issue, give me a freaking break</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349891656638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891675107-177</Id><Title>tulsa turd having HUGE problems with numbers. Date WRONG! Poll numbers WRONG!</Title><Msg>With a name like Tulsa Turd, should you expect anything more?</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349891675107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349891733342-178</Id><Title>BAC: Fighting 2 GO HIGHER!!! Looks STRONG!</Title><Msg>As the housing prices start to climb, we could get a heck of a surprise out of this company in my opinion.</Msg><Username>maxxybb</Username><Timestamp>1349891733342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891869543-179</Id><Topic><Title>Romney up by one in latest Rasmussen and tied in latest Gallup ..Oct. 11</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349891181804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better to talk about a Big Bird than to believe false numbers from Tulsa Turd. Not only did you get the date wrong, FOOL..., you got the poll numbers wrong! FOOL! This is what happens when you rely on the lying spin from Fox.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349891869543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892003543-180</Id><Topic><Title>Oct 10 Gallup Pole of REGISTERED VOTERS: Obama - 50% Romney - 45%</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349889524689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:18:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As expected, a bump up for Obama.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349892003543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892099220-181</Id><Topic><Title>THE RMONEY RALLY !!!!!!</Title><Username>marcymartin23</Username><Timestamp>1349888703744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right you are. But one should not rely on the market tanking with much more important questions of character and behavior of Mr. RMoney. What is important is the fact that RMoney comes across as an unstable character... from ALL that he has said and still says in public. That weighs much more and it is also confirmed when one looks back over many years of his political life. His flip flops in many important major issues is indeed a character flaw. The danger is that he does it in public very smoothly impressing the uninformed and the gullible. That bump in his popularity should be taken as an early warning. That latter quality unless countered effectively by the majority he may indeed end up with the job of president. Buyer beware! One thing is crystal clear after the first debate. RMoney is a good salesman and marketeer... and not someone that can be trusted when it comes to the big issues facing our nation. Isn't that clear to any decent rational person and voter? We have to be concerned and make sure to vote to prevent an unstable character like RMoney with a smooth oratory and delivery... not to fool the majority of who he really happens to be. Thanks for your contributions.</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349892099220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892151299-182</Id><Topic><Title>This is important!</Title><Username>aliarbk984469</Username><Timestamp>1349889839865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>lessieqme56242</Username><Timestamp>1349892151299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892160333-183</Id><Title>The Economy was just luvley and bootiful before Obama took office.</Title><Msg>Then all of a sudden he went in 2009 or the year XXXX and messed all things up. He told business not to hire. He started 2 massive wars on his credit card, We start loosing 800,000 jobs per month, then he took the stock market down to almost zero. Most of all, and it amazes me to this day how he did it, he made the years 2001 to 2009 completely disappear from history. Like there was no 43rd president at all. Amazing. Count your blessings and be careful what ask for.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1349892160333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892196916-184</Id><Topic><Title>tulsa turd having HUGE problems with numbers. Date WRONG! Poll numbers WRONG!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349891675107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't even get the date right, what a #$%$ #$%$</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1349892196916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892217949-185</Id><Topic><Title>This is important!</Title><Username>aliarbk984469</Username><Timestamp>1349889839865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, even if true, this is SPAM!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349892217949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349892565493-186</Id><Title>Betting odds imply probability of Obama win around</Title><Msg>71%, down from hi of around 78% just b 4 debate</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1349892565493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892702608-187</Id><Topic><Title>ADMIT IT REPUCANS, ROMNEY FLIP FLOP FLIP MUST BE EMBARRASSING</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349891656638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RMoney's flip flops are the sign of a SERIOUS CHARACTER FLAW especially looking back over the many years he has been in politics. That tells that he is UNSTABLE by character and can't be TRUSTED for any important leadership role! But he comes across as a smooth and likable marketeer and salesman. I hope he doesn't fool the uninformed and the gullible beyond the fringe-right (like the ones that post here) and we don't end up with a flawed character when our nation is faced with very serious and challenging financial dilemma that have been deliberately prolonged by the GOP for acceding to power. People should never forget that the GOP obstructionism is real and very selfish politics that MUST BE REJECTED for the long term good of our nation!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349892702608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349892740494-188</Id><Topic><Title>Is the rampant stupidity among the fringe-right caused by inbreeding . . .</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1348919083283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:44:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it must be stupid to think takeing 50 to 70% of some one's money and giveing it to a lib parasite who has been out of work all his life after the last 99 weeks, how dumb of me!!!!</Msg><Username>bullbarrell</Username><Timestamp>1349892740494</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893192195-189</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>toniegpae066109</Username><Timestamp>1349893192195</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893221912-190</Id><Topic><Title>Chicago-Chicago..my kond of town!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349890893224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:41:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EZsolution to crook fil ee Cago and Crook county: boybcott, dont spend any money there, move businessout, dont spend any money in state, Starve em BK the resutaruants and the parks, andbusinesses, BK it. the state is bankrupt anyhow with $ 80 B in pension debt.</Msg><Username>berniecongress</Username><Timestamp>1349893221912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893275950-191</Id><Topic><Title>This is important!</Title><Username>aliarbk984469</Username><Timestamp>1349889839865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:23:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lessieqme, from what I gather, most positive responses to the main poster... are coming from or are part of a special programmed artificial posters... to make the post believable and right. To all other regular posters, PLEASE do not fall for this kind of marketing... which is somewhat similar to RMoney's run for the presidency. Such marketing and smooth salesmanship can and may hurt the uninformed and the gullible and is hurtful to the person falling for it as it is hurtful to our nation when the majority falls for RMoney smooth flip flops. Buyer beware!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349893275950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:21:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349893288744-192</Id><Title>Go to Real Clear Politics pull up latest polls. Romney leads. Are all Obama supporters liars??</Title><Msg>get a life</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349893288744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893815850-193</Id><Topic><Title>ADMIT IT REPUCANS, ROMNEY FLIP FLOP FLIP MUST BE EMBARRASSING</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349891656638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>G F Y........freakin idiot. Give it up low-life loser.......still looking for a handout? Mitt will kick obozo's butt in the election.......geez, you might have to get a job loser!</Msg><Username>asalwaysurconfused</Username><Timestamp>1349893815850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349893947196-194</Id><Topic><Title>ADMIT IT REPUCANS, ROMNEY FLIP FLOP FLIP MUST BE EMBARRASSING</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349891656638</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:54:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another idiot poster.....looking for 4 more years for a hand-out.....get a job loser.</Msg><Username>asalwaysurconfused</Username><Timestamp>1349893947196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894052263-195</Id><Topic><Title>Inside trader Nancy Pelosi along with the thousands of republican insider traders</Title><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349887125267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In addendum to my original post- It is completely legal and sometimes wise to have international investments in a stock or mutual fund portfolio, but not with illegal insider information as Nancy Pelosi and many others in both parties have done.</Msg><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349894052263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894083074-196</Id><Topic><Title>Go to Real Clear Politics pull up latest polls. Romney leads. Are all Obama supporters liars??</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349893288744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:21:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never fully depend on polls. It's only a snapshot and also depends WHO is doing the polling. The methodology is most important. That goes to ANY poll. One thing that I know, Mitt's chances of being elected are less than Obama's chances of being re-elected. The times of skilled marketing and salesmanship are no more as effective as they were just 10 years ago. What really will matter is the record for both given the worst circumstance of the economy at the end of 2008 since the Great Depression in 1929. No one could have done any better given that Obama faced a hostile GOP loudly announcing that they will oppose and obstruct any action by Obama just to make him a one-term president. THAT RINGS LOUD IN MY EAR anytime I hear GOP heads attack Obama now just for grabbing power. I don't think most people can be fooled by the present attempts of trying to smear Obama just for the elections. In most peoples memory... GOP behavior is politics as usual but our national problems real and must be immediately addressed. People will vote to the responsible and trusted man to office and that happens to be the President at this time. Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349894083074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349894421608-197</Id><Title>GMCR just got a big deal with Snapple.</Title><Msg>Consumer stocks are the place to be....</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1349894421608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349894441063-198</Id><Topic><Title>Inside trader Nancy Pelosi along with the thousands of republican insider traders</Title><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349887125267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know Nancy Pelosi as she lives in my neighborhood. What you're posting against her is a lie and you may be liable for what you post. If I were you, I wouldn't pick names. I agree that both party members have been involved with illegal trading with insider information while enacting laws applicable only to citizens.</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1349894441063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349895135229-199</Id><Title>GET OUT BEFORE IT GOES UNDER $9..NEXT STOP IS $8</Title><Msg>BE CAREFUL</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349895135229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 14:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896190159-200</Id><Title>Todays Volume Is Almost Anemic</Title><Msg>No real sellers imo.</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896190159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896289530-201</Id><Title>m&amp;t, jpm, wfc, C...All up today...</Title><Msg>BAC cant buy an upgrade seems</Msg><Username>shatteredone2000</Username><Timestamp>1349896289530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896357764-202</Id><Title>Why Is CNBC Such a WET BLANKET</Title><Msg>do they want the market to go down?</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896357764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896422736-203</Id><Title>Wheres BAC upgrade</Title><Msg>I want one too</Msg><Username>shatteredone2000</Username><Timestamp>1349896422736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896555344-204</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's on his hand a hole! go to W/N/D and see the photos and proof retard!</Msg><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349896555344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896606090-205</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check the facts BOY!</Msg><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349896606090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896686868-206</Id><Topic><Title>Todays Volume Is Almost Anemic</Title><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896190159</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>volume is strong only when the buyers step in and anemic when the sellers are at work. No REAL SELLERS imo!</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896686868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:18:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896778935-207</Id><Title>BUY BUY BUY...DON'T PANIC SELL</Title><Msg>buy buy buy</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349896778935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896899317-208</Id><Title>Thousands of Customers Continue to Dump BAC and Opt for Credit Unions</Title><Msg>It is a fact.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349896899317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349896975561-209</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>irenayuzn69850</Username><Timestamp>1349896975561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896986641-210</Id><Title>BAC Gets Left Holding the Bag of Bad Loans in Las Vegas</Title><Msg>What a mess!</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349896986641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897016912-211</Id><Title>If Joe Biden wins debate Thursday, the stock market will rally like a crazy boy on Friday!</Title><Msg>You get my words!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1349897016912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897111093-212</Id><Title>Jamie Dimon is Talking Trash ahead of earnings..What ya think that means</Title><Msg>(says JPM did the US Gov't a favor buy buying Bear Sterns)</Msg><Username>shatteredone2000</Username><Timestamp>1349897111093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897145490-213</Id><Title>Each Foreclosure at BAC Equates to Lost Customers</Title><Msg>It trickles down and BAC loses not only the customer of the foreclosed property but family members and friends too.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349897145490</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897151251-214</Id><Topic><Title>BAC - Important Update!</Title><Username>paul_truby</Username><Timestamp>1349191226791</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These guys must also believe in karma because it clearly shows in the outcomes they get.</Msg><Username>wellsdavid594</Username><Timestamp>1349897151251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897235278-215</Id><Title>Jamie Dimon is Talking Good Quarter</Title><Msg>read between the lines.....................</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349897235278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897241000-216</Id><Title>BAC has the Worst Record for Loan Modifications</Title><Msg>Source: Nevada State Attorney General.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349897241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897267163-217</Id><Topic><Title>WFC suit is good for BAC as BAC had already paid out a Billion on that issue.</Title><Username>lookfwd</Username><Timestamp>1349826292718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 19:44:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right you are. I agree. The new up leg of the uptrend is still in force regardless of the price flip flops Hmm... that reminds me of Mitt!-:).</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349897267163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897519465-218</Id><Topic><Title>RUMOR HAS IT THAT</Title><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1349842089801</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:08:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I assume you will be dressed like Jesus... listening to the debate mess-merized listening to R-Money like he was Abraham coming down the hill with the 10 Commandments!-:)</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349897519465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349897667903-219</Id><Title>THE WHITE HOUSE WILL HAVE CTO BE STERILIZED IN JANUARY BEFORE MITT &amp; FAMILY GO IN</Title><Msg>This disgusting liar fraud pig &amp; his racist wife have soiled, stained &amp; left a terrible odor and it needs to be cleaned up...</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349897667903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898054114-220</Id><Topic><Title>If Joe Biden wins debate Thursday, the stock market will rally like a crazy boy on Friday!</Title><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1349897016912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:23:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>vger44</Username><Timestamp>1349898054114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898076468-221</Id><Topic><Title>Why Obama abandoned "Hope &amp; Change" ?</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349828094382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 20:14:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kingofvietnam(?), President Obama never abandoned it because it takes about 8 years to at least undo the DAMAGE caused to our nation by the GOP and GWB! And all that, just for politics! They should be taught a SERIOUS lesson and all decent independents like me are going to ADMINISTER that LESSON to the GOP! Btw, you don't count more than a mosquito, of course, in the larger picture! The caravan goes forward as the dogs bark! PS: What is Kingofvietnam? Doesn't that really tell who you are? I think, a confused human being in distress by his own stated alias.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349898076468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898171509-222</Id><Topic><Title>BUY BUY BUY...DON'T PANIC SELL</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349896778935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:19:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The crooks took the market down because they don't want the financial sector to take it up too high. Once BAC breaks through $9.21, we will continue to go higher into earnings this week and next...</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349898171509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898307032-223</Id><Title>I'm finished with stocks</Title><Msg>In 4 yrs have not made a penny with all the bluechips and oils and techs and all the best stocks. Nothing but a total bunch of garbage this stock scam, all designed for bankers and wallstreet #$%$ and politicians to steal our money.</Msg><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1349898307032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898308716-224</Id><Title>THE REAL UNEMPLOYMENT NO. OF 11+ PERCENT SHOWS NO ECONOMIC RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Please show me where there is economic recovery?</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349898308716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898383795-225</Id><Topic><Title>BUY BUY BUY...DON'T PANIC SELL</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349896778935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:19:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone here understand The Law Of Sustainable? Watch and learn.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349898383795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898581518-226</Id><Topic><Title>I'm finished with stocks</Title><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1349898307032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:45:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm... How about YOU being finished? It all depends on you. As human beings we are Co-Creators and full of UNLIMITED choices and unlimited improvement! Just look inside to find the problem and do something to expand and grow! Your destiny mostly depends on you!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349898581518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898595431-227</Id><Title>This stock wants to run up big time</Title><Msg>If we could only get a few good days in the market. Is that so hard to do.Seems so.</Msg><Username>jeffreon</Username><Timestamp>1349898595431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898661136-228</Id><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Msg>Romney's short lived bounce flattened.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898669861-229</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An oldy but goody! What happened to clown boy anyway?</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349898669861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898728083-230</Id><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Msg>$$$$$</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898797545-231</Id><Topic><Title>Jamie Dimon is Talking Good Quarter</Title><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349897235278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no reading between. Free Fed money for all big banks was a clear and concise memo.</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349898797545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898928196-232</Id><Title>LOSER right wingers keep slamming Obama, AND still refuse to support Romney</Title><Msg>Romney either has no position (no plan) on the issues, or he keeps shifting his position on the issues. The multiple choice candidate is not only back, he is more elusive now than ever.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898928196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349898931934-233</Id><Title>I know the reason why repucs deny the fact that Obama beat Romney in the first debate</Title><Msg>They are angry, low life, low class white males. Luckily, they are in the minority and are for a rude awakening scheduled for November 6. (Chuckle).</Msg><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1349898931934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349898992059-234</Id><Topic><Title>This stock wants to run up big time</Title><Username>jeffreon</Username><Timestamp>1349898595431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I has been coiled up all day for a rapid bounce. Close above $9.16 today and we will break through $9.21 after hours or tomorrow.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349898992059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899085673-235</Id><Topic><Title>This stock wants to run up big time</Title><Username>jeffreon</Username><Timestamp>1349898595431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just want to hold $9 through tomorrow. WFC earnings on Friday, if positive, will help drive the sector up through next weeks earnings. $9.75+ this time next week.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349899085673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349899122739-236</Id><Title>Extremist tea baggers infected the GOP with ignorance and hatred. Too late now.</Title><Msg>The independent voters want nothing to do with the fascist fringe idiots.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349899122739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349899269353-237</Id><Title>BAC: GREEN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Bank Of America UP GREEN! Dow down 130</Msg><Username>maxxybb</Username><Timestamp>1349899269353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349899436620-238</Id><Title>SW mimic ID "libertydles30" is not "libertydies30"</Title><Msg>It really doesn't matter what SW's rectal drip aliases, and SW's mimic aliases post here, or anywhere. Their futile cause of promoting fascist stupidity is lost. Obama WILL be re-elected.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349899436620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899456569-239</Id><Topic><Title>This stock wants to run up big time</Title><Username>jeffreon</Username><Timestamp>1349898595431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you get excited about 5 cents, then like me, you have some dough in the game!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349899456569</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899493267-240</Id><Topic><Title>Jamie Dimon is Talking Good Quarter</Title><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349897235278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for sure.</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349899493267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899853677-241</Id><Topic><Title>BAC: GREEN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>maxxybb</Username><Timestamp>1349899269353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:01:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI: Scottrade has a close of $9.21</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349899853677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:10:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899908457-242</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is CNBC Such a WET BLANKET</Title><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896357764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>woooooo they are so scary wooooooooooo</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349899908457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899939418-243</Id><Topic><Title>My talking chair has a yellow puddle in the bottom of it</Title><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349879995863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What color is the straw?</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349899939418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349899941386-244</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>hyunbbhn73116</Username><Timestamp>1349899941386</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900189357-245</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is CNBC Such a WET BLANKET</Title><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349896357764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why are they looking for spooks?</Msg><Username>smythwrd</Username><Timestamp>1349900189357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:16:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349900227110-246</Id><Topic><Title>All the polls showing Obama ahead are uncorrect!!!!!!!</Title><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885742327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you think all of the polls are now; "uncorrect?"</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349900227110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901335236-247</Id><Title>Our next prez, Romney, now leads in all swing states and nationally as well. It over for obama</Title><Msg>Turn out the lights democrap puke trolls. Your demoCRAP obama is finished...know it.</Msg><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1349901335236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:35:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901405187-248</Id><Title>Electoral math STILL favors President Obama</Title><Msg>Romney chips away at Obama’s lead, but electoral math still favors president October 10, 2012 By David Rothschild, Yahoo News Last week's debate between President Barack Obama and challenger Mitt Romney has inflicted sever turmoil on Obama's standing in the polls, breathing new life and energy into Romney's bid. If the United States elected its presidents by popular vote, the way sane electoral systems operate, Obama's odds of re-election would have plummeted in tandem. Unfortunately for the Romney campaign, it will take more than one good night to overcome the steep uphill climb it faces in the Electoral College this year. The first debate between Obama and Romney radically altered the dynamic of the 2012 election, but it did not change the math. It has been clear at least since February that Romney has to win Florida, Ohio and Virginia to have a viable shot at victory. This troika, along with the states safely in the Republican column, would bring Romney to 266 electoral votes. From there, he would need just one more state—say, New Hampshire—to push him over the 270 mark. All three states have moved in his favor over the past two weeks. The overall odds for Obama remain well above 60 percent for one simple reason: Romney needs all three swing states to win, while Obama needs only to deny him one of them. Right now, that rearguard action is occurring in Ohio, where Obama is maintaining his lead in the aftermath of the debate. As the graph clearly shows, right now the states are correlated: They all move up or down in basic tandem in response to national events. By Election Day, after all the speeches have been given, all the debates played out and all the commercials aired, this will no longer be the case. The states will become individual coin tosses. If they are still in toss-up territory, it will mean Romney will need to flip heads three times in a row, while Obama will need to flip tails only once.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901405187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901635764-249</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>traderx lost all his money in BAC FB FSLR, by ten years analyist data showing all short trading guys are loser is the ending.</Msg><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1349901635764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901670243-250</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>lorraineyahul88626</Username><Timestamp>1349901670243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901771391-251</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never mind the liar repugs. Today, Oct. 10, Obama leads in the Gallup Poll, and leads, or is tied, in the rest. President Obama will definitely be re-elected.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901771391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349901786876-252</Id><Title>traderx lost tons of money at BAC FB FSLR. just disappear as other shorts usually..</Title><Msg>just diappear is disappear as usual as other shorts.</Msg><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1349901786876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349901830012-253</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong and wrong. Check the major non-partisan polls, boys.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901830012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902039251-254</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral math STILL favors President Obama</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901405187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid repugs can't figure the Electoral College numbers. The Fox News Karl Rove Electoral College math ALSO shows Obama with a win.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902039251</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349902183012-255</Id><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Msg>Repugs: You do trust Karl Rove, do you not? Check his Electoral College map on the Fox News site. He gives Obama the wing.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902229789-256</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral math STILL favors President Obama</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901405187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not for long, this turkey must be gone, for the sake of this great country...WAKE UP AMERICA..</Msg><Username>kingslmon6</Username><Timestamp>1349902229789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902280014-257</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's bounce is over.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902280014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902376826-258</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Turn on your tv unless you're in yo'momma's house. LOL. "IGNORE"</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1349902376826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349902972508-259</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait till the debate and the embassy ambassador and 3 seals murders during obummers term is discussed. the cover up alone by the wht. house should tell America that obummer needs to be ousted. jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349902972508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349903187946-260</Id><Title>BENGHAZI OBMAMA' WATERGATE... THE DIFFERENCE IS PEOPLE DIED BECAUSE OF OBAMA</Title><Msg>DISGRACEFUL!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349903187946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349903288178-261</Id><Title>BENGHAZI OBMAM'S' WATERGATE... THE DIFFERENCE IS PEOPLE DIED NEEDLESSLY BECAUSE OF OBAMA</Title><Msg>HORRIBLE!!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349903288178</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903334219-262</Id><Topic><Title>THE MUZLUM IN CHEIFs RING SAYS -There is no G o d but a l l a h-!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349838979754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 23:16:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is now KNOWN THAT ON OBAMAS HAND IS A RING THAT SAYS "there is no god but allah" in arabic !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! FACT!</Msg><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1349903334219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349903822254-263</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen Tracking 10/7 - 10/9 1500 LV 3.0 48 47 Romney +1 Gallup Tracking 10/3 - 10/9 2721 LV 2.0 48 48 Tie IBD/TIPP Tracking 10/4 - 10/9 757 LV 3.5 49 44 Romney +5 Pew Research 10/4 - 10/7 1112 LV 3.4 49 45 Romney +4</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349903822254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904103948-264</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pay no attention to mr whizzard since he is illiterate like most Obama supporters</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349904103948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904300866-265</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's up in the polls, AND even the Fox Electoral College map shows Obama wins</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349898661136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:51:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obummer stinks ! He will get the second term as he has so many treasonist commies working with him. The game is rigged and we are all phuked ! I hope people revolt big time if he gets re elected . Romney lessor of the 2 evils but he's an american and I want hi in office then some illegal alien who has a personal agenda</Msg><Username>h2m4l6</Username><Timestamp>1349904300866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904353520-266</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>jolenemfebt73649</Username><Timestamp>1349904353520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349904469523-267</Id><Topic><Title>JETRO ROMNEY STRIKES AGAIN - NOW HE HAS NO PROBLEM WITH ABORTION</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349874821339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The more he flip flops the more clarified his character becomes to us independents. He is toast... considering that this is part and parcel of his character! Any voter of ave. intelligence and above can see that like day and night!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349904469523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349905065828-268</Id><Title>$10.00 for BAC on 10/10 was what I was hoping to see. The market with no multicent uptick rule is more CAPRICIOUS.</Title><Msg>It did close within 1 penny of being green on a triple digit down day for the DOW. That's cause for some further hope. Maybe on 10/11 or maybe on 10/12 when JPM reports earnings? DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1349905065828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905349082-269</Id><Topic><Title>I'm really glad Obama's stimulus is working and people are finding jobs. NOT!!</Title><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1349662573773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:16:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you ready for four more years of President Obama bashing?</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349905349082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905628495-270</Id><Topic><Title>The liberal biased media is skewering the polls</Title><Username>buckydoodle_5</Username><Timestamp>1349792052081</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The numbers are always wrong for you, aren't they bucky? Jobs report, polls, electoral college..., all of them wrong. But, you're not wrong, are you bucky? LMAO!</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349905628495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905687871-271</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>thomasinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1349905126341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STOP SPAMMING!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349905687871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905798892-272</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral math STILL favors President Obama</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901405187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even with the fabled Romney bounce (blip?), the Electoral College continues to belong to Obama</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349905798892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906029729-273</Id><Topic><Title>Inside trader Nancy Pelosi along with the thousands of republican insider traders</Title><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349887125267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:38:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The facts speak for themselves. What you say is a lie. I believe if your neighborhood had an ethical standard rules prerequisite it would be a much better place for the honest residents.</Msg><Username>concer08</Username><Timestamp>1349906029729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349906150654-274</Id><Title>Chronic liar dumpobamie is dumpfounded. He cannot fathom Obama's success. LMAO !</Title><Msg>dumpobamie exists to slam, smear, and lie about Obama, hence his offensive screen name. He is in such a lather of denial today over the Electoral College numbers that he cannot stop frothing from his liar's mouth. This is what happens when one foolishly believes their own never ending lies.</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349906150654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906246866-275</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral math STILL favors President Obama</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349901405187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After the first debate, Mitt's poll bump will be his last of his candidacy. He knows deep inside and that's why he will do more of what he knows and has done for the last 10 years- FLIP FLOP - on most issues to make it crystal clear to the voters and independents like me ... of who really HE IS - a LOSER!!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349906246866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906364480-276</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is probably a teenager</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349906364480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906568841-277</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since the debate, Rove added gains to his (Rove's) Obama blue state tally AND win.</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349906568841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349906755160-278</Id><Title>caution CNBC criminals getting ready to foment financials</Title><Msg>I can smell the negativity coming..cash payments under the table</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1349906755160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349906866515-279</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it for free. Thank you</Msg><Username>dianggis024565</Username><Timestamp>1349906866515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907037156-280</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid repugs can't read a current poll, can't add up the electoral college numbers, can't do anything requiring ANY intelligence. Believe your own lies, fools. The intelligent voters will be rejoicing and celebrating Obama's victory on Nov. 6.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349907037156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349907102018-281</Id><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Msg>Done for</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907116001-282</Id><Topic><Title>Chronic liar dumpobamie is dumpfounded. He cannot fathom Obama's success. LMAO !</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349906150654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:55:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dump... and very DUMB! But that's what the fringe-right is all about. But this one is a mosquito and for use as entertainment and fun at this board. The fact is that the lowest in our society find safe refuge in the GOP party. That tells something about the party itself where a range of folks from 'true believers' (religious fanatics) and the least intelligent lowly characters find the party and their close-minded anti-progressive agenda right for them. Then, these lowest denominator folks whether in religion or political real help even take the GOP lower. The good news is that IT made the times and tide of people becoming more aware in a timely manner is going against them. I always posted in the past ten years that the internet now makes liars, exploiters, pretenders, despots very difficult to hide for long. TRUTH and the FACTS come out much faster to those who seek them... thanks to the internet and speedy communication.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349907116001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907137493-283</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rove is an anomaly; a repug with some brains.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349907137493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907367530-284</Id><Topic><Title>Chronic liar dumpobamie is dumpfounded. He cannot fathom Obama's success. LMAO !</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349906150654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:55:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true, so very true. The fringe idiots ruined the GOP. I look for them to be thrown out of the GOP, and blamed for Romney's loss as undecided voters will not want to be identified with racist goon fanatic tea baggers.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349907367530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907370108-285</Id><Topic><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep wishing and dreaming... at least you have still few weeks. Obama will win in a landslide... ok I concede if it's not a landslide! Lying will get neither GOP or R-Money anywhere. Let him hide his millions in the Cayman Islands as eventually he may retire there to write about his flip flops and memoirs.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349907370108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907432295-286</Id><Topic><Title>*** RED FLAG Found in Friday's Jobs Report</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1349798600056</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what does mr whizzard think of all the corruption in the obama administration?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349907432295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907484766-287</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report (BAC)?</Title><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1349732500944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I got it. It's awesome.</Msg><Username>lianaphs439</Username><Timestamp>1349907484766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907590491-288</Id><Topic><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's policies have begun to right all that was wrong with the Bush administration and all of the damage that it caused. Intelligent voters know that. That is why Obama will be re-elected.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349907590491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907665447-289</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing this to us please. Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1349907665447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907674055-290</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rove has some brains... but warped and demonic. But it's the regressive ideology in which he was born to make him see evil and good only and nothing in between. Same goes to fanatics of all sorts. Being simpletons, they can't comprehend anything complex so they reduce it to evil versus good... just like GWB when he said "if you're not with us, you're against us". That's the basest human instinct- that of a reptilian!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349907674055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349907821891-291</Id><Title>Hope and Change is pure Garbage and Forward where? Off the cliff?</Title><Msg>Obama is a useless clueless idiot</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349907821891</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:23:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907866943-292</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I counted the Electoral college numbers at 11 A.M. today did you??? my numbers show a toal next picture..am I missing sometime...believe me I'm good in math and I can count to 260 can you?? ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349907866943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907867199-293</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I counted the Electoral college numbers at 11 A.M. today did you??? my numbers show a toal next picture..am I missing sometime...believe me I'm good in math and I can count to 260 can you?? ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349907867199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349907873025-294</Id><Title>repug LIARS continue to never support Romney, and always slam Obama.</Title><Msg>Repug, short for repugnant, is, of course, is a derogatory term used to correctly identify republicans.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349907873025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907887199-295</Id><Topic><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government dependency is all Obama offers. Most want something more than government cheese</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349907887199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907957541-296</Id><Topic><Title>State department changes story</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1349902007672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no accountability. The voters must act</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349907957541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349907994959-297</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing. Thanks!</Msg><Username>adrianaqomt40304</Username><Timestamp>1349907994959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908012692-298</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Surges Ahead by 5 points in latest Ibd/Tipp tracking poll</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349898728083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:52:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep the Momentum Going Mitt!</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349908012692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908050115-299</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing I say will convince you, so go to the Fox site, and look for the Electoral College map provided to Fox by Karl Rove. Then come back and try to tell me I'm wrong. RFLMAO!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349908050115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349908146172-300</Id><Title>Obama should be in Impeachment hearings for his role in Solyndra, MF global, Fast and Furious, Behngazigate, Jobsgate</Title><Msg>Send Barry the terd home</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349908146172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908465753-301</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if my name was Obama i'd be calling a school in chic-ago for the girls...I "know for a fact who has the numbers in electoral college votes...Obama loses..face the truth..simple you didn't count them so you don't know..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349908465753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908466064-302</Id><Topic><Title>All the polls showing Obama ahead are uncorrect!!!!!!!</Title><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885742327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this fool for real? These tea bags are unbelievably ignorant.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1349908466064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908629126-303</Id><Topic><Title>My talking chair has a yellow puddle in the bottom of it</Title><Username>zevotor22</Username><Timestamp>1349879995863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, little z, what's floating in it, or did you eat that already?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1349908629126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908809383-304</Id><Topic><Title>The Stock Market doubled during Obama's first term</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876754994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, mama, but keep thinking positve.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1349908809383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349909497190-305</Id><Title>Another GOP attempt to obstruct registered Democrat voters struck down in SC</Title><Msg>A federal court in Washington today blocked South Carolina’s Voter ID law from going into effect for the 2012 elections, but said it could go into effect for future elections. South Carolina is added to list of Pennsylvania, Mississsippi, and Ohio where GOP efforts to obstruct registered democrats from voting were overturned by the courts.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349909497190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349909549269-306</Id><Title>Oh no!</Title><Msg>Not the prospect of another tax dodging, draft dodging, neo con, war monger to become president!</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1349909549269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349909884106-307</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America afterhours news</Title><Username>wallst.moneys8933</Username><Timestamp>1328655221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-02-07 17:53:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>goose eggs 00 what f is that mms?</Msg><Username>privatejetceo8989</Username><Timestamp>1349909884106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349910631936-308</Id><Title>Obama is lazy</Title><Msg>Plain and simple.</Msg><Username>supersoaker30</Username><Timestamp>1349910631936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349910749990-309</Id><Topic><Title>Another GOP attempt to obstruct registered Democrat voters struck down in SC</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349909497190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have show ID to buy liquor, drive a car, get on a plane, cash a check, etc. but it is ok to be in this country illegally, drive a car without a license, collect welfare and or ss, great free medical care from a hospital and then after surgery in a country you are in illegally, have the right to sue the dr. for malpractice. what am i missing??? oh yeah, you can vote even though you not registered. amazing, but true.-jmho-bucko ps-and you wonder why romney is looking better by the day???</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349910749990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349911149616-310</Id><Topic><Title>Another GOP attempt to obstruct registered Democrat voters struck down in SC</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349909497190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you can vote in multiple states as many have.</Msg><Username>supersoaker30</Username><Timestamp>1349911149616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349911313060-311</Id><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Msg>if Romney wins 1.Rise of corpoations. 2. Rise of wealthy. 3. Rise of outsourcing (deregulated and reckless power to corps). 4. Rise of CEO and top managment bonus and salary 5. Rise of Wars 6. Rise of Military (conservatives fundamental policy). 7. Rise of Military Machines 8. Rise of Uninsured (health) 9. Rise of artificial booms (like reckless homeownership in bush era). 10. Rise of Foxnews dominance. 11. Rise of austerity measures (like pbs cuts) even though we are 100 years away like Greece 12. Rise of private education - possibility of publich school system could go away 13. Rise of subsidies for oil corps. 14. Rise of Free trade Imports (Chinese will have more dominance) 15. Rise of fear mongering (we have see this all the 8 years of bush era). 16. ofcourse Rise of middle class taxes - no way any one can offset cuts to wealthy through deductions.. by having popular deductions intact. and many more...</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911313060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349911319605-312</Id><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Msg>if Romney wins 1.Rise of corpoations. 2. Rise of wealthy. 3. Rise of outsourcing (deregulated and reckless power to corps). 4. Rise of CEO and top managment bonus and salary 5. Rise of Wars 6. Rise of Military (conservatives fundamental policy). 7. Rise of Military Machines 8. Rise of Uninsured (health) 9. Rise of artificial booms (like reckless homeownership in bush era). 10. Rise of Foxnews dominance. 11. Rise of austerity measures (like pbs cuts) even though we are 100 years away like Greece 12. Rise of private education - possibility of publich school system could go away 13. Rise of subsidies for oil corps. 14. Rise of Free trade Imports (Chinese will have more dominance) 15. Rise of fear mongering (we have see this all the 8 years of bush era). 16. ofcourse Rise of middle class taxes - no way any one can offset cuts to wealthy through deductions.. by having popular deductions intact. and many more...</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911319605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912047385-313</Id><Topic><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911319605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep drinking the grape kool aid... + $6 trillion more in debt</Msg><Username>retiringat49</Username><Timestamp>1349912047385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349912209968-314</Id><Title>great use of "recovery dollars" - gave $1.04m to PBS and created 1.4 jobs</Title><Msg>go Big Bird!!!!!</Msg><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1349912209968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349912250900-315</Id><Title>The Market decline has begun!!!!! BAC back to $8 JPM back to $39</Title><Msg>here we go!!!!!!</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1349912250900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912367980-316</Id><Topic><Title>Did you see this report (BAC)?</Title><Username>lorettagcf830</Username><Timestamp>1349732500944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 17:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>arlinebtt47308</Username><Timestamp>1349912367980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349912407317-317</Id><Topic><Title>Must read this! Important info on Bank of America Corporation (BAC)</Title><Username>charliergres18404</Username><Timestamp>1349881320187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:02:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it. Good job mate.</Msg><Username>twanaiqszf80674</Username><Timestamp>1349912407317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349912413786-318</Id><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Msg>Look at what he has done</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349912662310-319</Id><Title>get ready for major market correction</Title><Msg>get out or go short</Msg><Username>victory_val_2007</Username><Timestamp>1349912662310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349913465784-320</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if Romney wins 1.Rise of corpoations. 2. Rise of wealthy. 3. Rise of outsourcing (deregulated and reckless power to corps). 4. Rise of CEO and top managment bonus and salary 5. Rise of Wars 6. Rise of Military (conservatives fundamental policy). 7. Rise of Military Machines 8. Rise of Uninsured (health) 9. Rise of artificial booms (like reckless homeownership in bush era). 10. Rise of Foxnews dominance. 11. Rise of austerity measures (like pbs cuts) even though we are 100 years away like Greece 12. Rise of private education - possibility of publich school system could go away 13. Rise of subsidies for oil corps. 14. Rise of Free trade Imports (Chinese will have more dominance) 15. Rise of fear mongering (we have see this all the 8 years of bush era). 16. ofcourse Rise of middle class taxes - no way any one can offset cuts to wealthy through deductions.. by having popular deductions intact. and many more...</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349913465784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349913928912-321</Id><Title>New Poll out fox news has Romney ahead</Title><Msg>Big bird in trouble</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349913928912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349913988347-322</Id><Topic><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911319605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is one extra expenditure during Obama presidency i.e 700 b stimulus. every penny is recovered. Most of debt is due to tax cut for rich and wars. of-course there are some risky investment like Green energy. there are 1 to 5% failure. Taking the risk to tap energy of sun is worth a risk. All GOP talks about government spending take the US history. Take example of latest boom in oil and natural gas this is all due to hydraulic fracture technology. This technology is invented and discovered by a company which is federally funded, google it you would know.</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349913988347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914003541-323</Id><Topic><Title>The Stock Market doubled during Obama's first term</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1349876754994</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:45:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe triple this time if he gets elected again</Msg><Username>bernz788</Username><Timestamp>1349914003541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349914099600-324</Id><Title>Obama Wages War on business and Jobs</Title><Msg>his goal is to get everyone on welfare</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349914099600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914103010-325</Id><Topic><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree worst 4 years in economy...during George Bush years...thanks that he's a goner now..</Msg><Username>bernz788</Username><Timestamp>1349914103010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914134059-326</Id><Topic><Title>$10.00 for BAC on 10/10 was what I was hoping to see. The market with no multicent uptick rule is more CAPRICIOUS.</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1349905065828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12/12/12.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349914134059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349914490327-327</Id><Title>Obama Campaign in Frantic Damage Control Panic</Title><Msg>its blowing up in their faces, all the scandals and incompetence is catching up</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349914490327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349914501759-328</Id><Topic><Title>Worst 4yr Economy in 60yrs; Obama is Gone</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349907102018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:11:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if Romney wins 1.Rise of corporations. 2. Rise of wealthy. 3. Rise of outsourcing (deregulated and reckless power to corps). 4. Rise of CEO and top management bonus and salary 5. Rise of Wars 6. Rise of Military (conservatives fundamental policy). 7. Rise of Military Machines 8. Rise of Uninsured (health) 9. Rise of artificial booms (like reckless home ownership in bush era). 10. Rise of Foxnews dominance. 11. Rise of austerity measures (like pbs cuts) even though we are 100 years away like Greece 12. Rise of private education - possibility of public school system could go away 13. Rise of subsidies for oil corps. 14. Rise of Free trade Imports (Chinese will have more dominance) 15. Rise of fear mongering (we have see this all the 8 years of bush era). 16. of-course Rise of middle class taxes - no way any one can offset cuts to wealthy through deductions.. by having popular deductions intact. and many more...</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349914501759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349915409911-329</Id><Title>Handle almost complete. Get ready for a huge leg up.</Title><Msg>Looks like Friday can be our catalyst if JPM and other banks beat estimates. How high can we go?</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1349915409911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:30:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349915590955-330</Id><Topic><Title>$10.00 for BAC on 10/10 was what I was hoping to see. The market with no multicent uptick rule is more CAPRICIOUS.</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1349905065828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like that too. To get to 12 dollars, it has to run up through 10 dollars first. I just wish fearless leader Moynihan had a well concealed plan to unleash on the shorts that would have us gap up 1 dollar plus over one's night time soon and hold that line. I feel so bad for anyone that bought the 15 dollar per share BAC capital raise of late 2009 that Moynihan came in to leadership of BAC upon in late 2009/January 2010. That is the reference point I hold him to for assessment of his success as CEO. It is going on THREE years now and we have given quite some time to see a fruition of his CEO position. DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1349915590955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349915646514-331</Id><Topic><Title>All the polls showing Obama ahead are uncorrect!!!!!!!</Title><Username>value_lnvestorr</Username><Timestamp>1349885742327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remain inconvinced of your credibility, because your supporting evidence is so woefully unsufficient. ROTFLMAO I have to applaud your brevity, though.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349915646514</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349915747023-332</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. I will check your article out.</Msg><Username>monroenicholson62</Username><Timestamp>1349915747023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349916935126-333</Id><Title>Ford Going to $15.00 on Truck Sales</Title><Msg>Ford Going to $15.00 on Truck Sales</Msg><Username>permabull</Username><Timestamp>1349916935126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349916943575-334</Id><Title>Ford Going to $15.00 on Truck Sales</Title><Msg>Ford Going to $15.00 on Truck Sales</Msg><Username>permabull</Username><Timestamp>1349916943575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349916962154-335</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go to YouTube, type in "Kengor" and "Drew". Interview comes in 2 parts. Obama was a full blown Markist going into Occidental. Mentor was Frank Marshall Davis. Encourage people to read Kengor's the "Communist"--chronicles life of Davis. Davis one of principle founders of Communist Party USA and other surrogates. Valerie Jarrett, Axelrod, et al all cited in book, and influenced by CPUSA.</Msg><Username>babydox73</Username><Timestamp>1349916962154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917709974-336</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Rove's site: There are three changes in this week's Electoral College map: Iowa moved from "lean Obama" to "toss up;" New Hampshire shifted from "toss up" to "lean Obama;" and New Mexico moved from "lean Obama" to "safe Obama." This puts Barack Obama at 201 "safe" Electoral College votes with six "lean" states (74 EC votes), and Mitt Romney at 156 "safe" EC votes with four "lean" states (35 EC votes). There are five states (72 EC votes) virtually tied. Although they did not yet change status, polls conducted at the end of last week strengthened Mr. Romney's standing in Ohio, Virginia, Colorado, and Wisconsin. It is likely these states will tighten and continue to move in his direction, as new surveys are taken in the wake of his strong performance in last week's debate. Maybe YOU need to check your math... or maybe you are color blind and adding the wrong color states. ROTFLMAO at how stupid your ROTFLMAO is... the joke's on you!!!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1349917709974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918097256-337</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$16 trillion debt. Trillion$$$$plus deficits to the horizon and beyond. QE3...$40 Billion per month to infinity. Over 100 million on some kind of welfare scheme. Record numbers on food stamps. Record numbers on the poverty roll. Record numbers not looking for work. Record numbers receiving disability assistance. Obama unemployment rate above 8% longer than any other President since 1948 (adjusted down below 8% the other day since there are now even fewer looking for work). And, Barry's "Kill your Health" scheme has already begun with its looting and controlling and squandering millions of hours with its meddling, tinkering, intruding and interfering in every aspect of our lives, our children, our families, our schools, our churches, our doctors, our hospitals, our faith, our farms, our energy sources, our communities, our private property, our health-care and our businesses. Hat tip to Obamanomics; it sucks!!! November 6, 2012. Clearly, the American people need to FIRE every Democrat across the United States of America!</Msg><Username>dons_st</Username><Timestamp>1349918097256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349918949456-338</Id><Title>Critical Alerts BAC AONE VALE PCFG TAGG AUMY</Title><Msg>.....</Msg><Username>girlsnightowls</Username><Timestamp>1349918949456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349919218547-339</Id><Title>Don't forget to watch Ryan Biden debate tomorrow !!!!</Title><Msg>In my very humble opinion Ryan should come out attacking like a mad dog. Bite his Biden nuts off Ryan in your first few punches. After that you let that old retard rest a little and then you attack him again. Just bite his throat after you bite his nuts !!!!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349919218547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919247022-340</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shareholders, This Is A Must Read...</Title><Username>leticiajustice674</Username><Timestamp>1349873415510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:50:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you...I will buy more...</Msg><Username>nash.summers56</Username><Timestamp>1349919247022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349921956521-341</Id><Topic><Title>Handle almost complete. Get ready for a huge leg up.</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1349915409911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:30:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm cautious. The larger market internal strength started to weaken beginning Monday and now it appears it could get weaker. Should this trend continue in the next few days, a market correction could be beginning in earnest. And, should that come about, more than 80% of stocks could be affected. Accordingly, I am cautious about BAC... though from a technical viewpoint it appears still ok at this point in time. However, I would be eager to accumulate more shares should BAC pps go down to about $9 and under. GLTA</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349921956521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349921961812-342</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the debt of the USA was run up by two presidents. Ronald Reagan and GWB. Obama inherited a bankrupt nation and has been rebuilding it.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349921961812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349922107023-343</Id><Title>after Romney becomes president, investigation and prosecution of odumba crimes against USA is a must.</Title><Msg>traitor odumba must be prosecuted and put on trial.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349922107023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349922863241-344</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kumar, I agree with your list... even though there are few others missing from your list. Please ignore the right-fringe posters here. They totally lack intellect and understanding of the issues but are GOP hacks on a mission. Most have also the feeling that Romney can't win and that's why they constantly make stupid and baseless charges against the President thinking that may help their candidate. Thanks for your insightful and informative post.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349922863241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349922982116-345</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>danielinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1349919528557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:38:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spammer, stop the nonsense posts to get clicks at that useless website!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349922982116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349922984670-346</Id><Topic><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911319605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are one illusionary person....feel sorry for you.....talk to me when you are paying 10 bucks for gas and your electric bill is through the roof in the next four years of Obama.....let alone having the fed government go broke and hyperinflation take over....</Msg><Username>sweetsugalips22</Username><Timestamp>1349922984670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349923019174-347</Id><Topic><Title>after Romney becomes president, investigation and prosecution of odumba crimes against USA is a must.</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349922107023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:21:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like your AWOL hero GWB</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1349923019174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:36:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349923412530-348</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget to watch Ryan Biden debate tomorrow !!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349919218547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Idiot! From alias to all your posts! You really represent the GOP extremely well. The party that is on its way to become a minority- down from 22% to 12% within a decade. The old distortion methods that used to be successful are no more workable thanks to the internet and speedy communication. Only dogs like you can't comprehend the changes ahead... and keep barking in cyberspace... while the caravan of progress marches on!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349923412530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349923922379-349</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget to watch Ryan Biden debate tomorrow !!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349919218547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought politics supposed to be funny</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349923922379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349924035207-350</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget to watch Ryan Biden debate tomorrow !!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349919218547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lyin Ryan and Uncle Joe? No thanks! I've got better ways to waste my time.</Msg><Username>billwilly2</Username><Timestamp>1349924035207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349924267879-351</Id><Topic><Title>Don't forget to watch Ryan Biden debate tomorrow !!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349919218547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In my very humble opinion in the case President Obama died of a car accident Biden would not be able to carry on the office of presidency. Maybe Ryan can.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349924267879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349924582700-352</Id><Topic><Title>Rise of Romney - Must read</Title><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349911319605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:21:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gas prices high only in CA due to supply chain problems, current US oil production is highest in history. come on electric bills are reduced a lot this year due to cheap natural gas check your facts. your character is slowly innerting from Romney. one simple example 50% of Solar companies are bankrupt. what a lie. As a investor i support Obama because my 401k looks like 401k not like 201k during 2008 market crash. how funny people forgot so fast.</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349924582700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349924956886-353</Id><Title>We look forward to Mr. Ryan as a competent younger generation leader</Title><Msg>Old leader like Biden who made lots of monies of taxpapers for the last 1/2 century doing nottin should retire or get lost !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349924956886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349925331911-354</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take a look at your cheap points: There is one extra expenditure during Obama presidency i.e 700 b stimulus. every penny is recovered. Most of debt is due to tax cut for rich and wars. of-course there are some risky investment like Green energy. there are 1 to 5% failure. Taking the risk to tap energy of sun is worth a risk. All GOP talks about government spending take the US history. Take example of latest boom in oil and natural gas this is all due to hydraulic fracture technology. This technology is invented and discovered by a company which is federally funded, google it you would know. 100 million welfare scheme absolutely fine when comparing to spending 100 million per day for iraq war. Atleast we are benefited here. Food stamps issue is another cheap shot, all the jobs lost due to bush recession and first 6 months of obama presidency are restored fully. check the employement numbers. There are so many people in poverty since decades, they are hesitant to go for food stamps. As government encouraged it they are taking it. US is doing best in the world with job creation, we sell 1/3 of products to europe. despite all turbulances we are doing good.</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349925331911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349925578508-355</Id><Title>JPM made a six billion error per Dimon</Title><Msg>How many billions did bac lose on an error? Oooops. How many errors for how many trillions? Gotta love the way nobody picks up on the details.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349925578508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349925631819-356</Id><Title>Romneys Tax plan today</Title><Msg>He is so out of touch he thinks middle class incomes all have dividend and investment income. "Romney's proposal as he described it - eliminating tax on interest, dividends, and capital gains - would largely help those living on investment income, which does not include many people in the middle class. At a rally here, Romney told the crowd that Obama would raise taxes on middle-income families by $4,000, a claim that has been debunked by several fact-checking websites. Romney promised to reduce the burden of those making $200,000 a year or less. "I have a plan to cut taxes for middle-income tax payers," Romney said. "My plan does this. There'll be no tax on interest, dividends, or capital gains for middle-income families in America." The wealthy are the major beneficiaries of low taxes on capital gains, dividends, and interest; many middle income Americans don't have investment income. The tax break will likely help senior citizens, however, many of whom do live on investment income. Though he did not mention it Wednesday, Romney's tax plan also includes reducing income tax rates by 20 percent across-the-board, a figure which could significantly reduce the tax burden of middle-income Americans. But some experts are skeptical that Romney will be able to keep tax rates low for middle-income taxpayers without getting rid of loopholes like the mortgage tax deduction, a popular tax break for people in the middle class who own their own homes. Romney has consistently said he will not raise taxes on any Americans, but has declined to specify which loopholes and deductions he would get rid of in order to make his tax plan revenue neutral. According to Romney spokesman Rick Gorka, Romney believes that eliminating taxes on interest, dividends, and capital gains will "encourage investment in savings," and that more Americans will start to utilize these tax tools to save money."</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349925631819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349925679914-357</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs: Learn to add. Electoral College numbers give Obama a WIN.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349902183012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 16:49:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't want to believe the Ruler of the Repugs, Karl Rove? If you won't believe Karl Rove's figures, then you won't believe anyone else's figures, but just to show you Rove is not the only one to see the Electoral College "writing on the wall," read the following (I know you are beyond reason, but at least I tried.) : Romney chips away at Obama’s lead, but electoral math still favors president October 10, 2012 By David Rothschild, Yahoo News Last week's debate between President Barack Obama and challenger Mitt Romney has inflicted sever turmoil on Obama's standing in the polls, breathing new life and energy into Romney's bid. If the United States elected its presidents by popular vote, the way sane electoral systems operate, Obama's odds of re-election would have plummeted in tandem. Unfortunately for the Romney campaign, it will take more than one good night to overcome the steep uphill climb it faces in the Electoral College this year. The first debate between Obama and Romney radically altered the dynamic of the 2012 election, but it did not change the math. It has been clear at least since February that Romney has to win Florida, Ohio and Virginia to have a viable shot at victory. This troika, along with the states safely in the Republican column, would bring Romney to 266 electoral votes. From there, he would need just one more state—say, New Hampshire—to push him over the 270 mark. All three states have moved in his favor over the past two weeks. The overall odds for Obama remain well above 60 percent for one simple reason: Romney needs all three swing states to win, while Obama needs only to deny him one of them. Right now, that rearguard action is occurring in Ohio, where Obama is maintaining his lead in the aftermath of the debate. As the graph clearly shows, right now the states are correlated: They all move up or down in basic tandem in response to national events. By Election Day, after all the speeches have been given, all the debates played out and all the commercials aired, this will no longer be the case. The states will become individual coin tosses. If they are still in toss-up territory, it will mean Romney will need to flip heads three times in a row, while Obama will need to flip tails only once.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349925679914</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349925751787-358</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Determined to transform the USA into a Communist Nation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1349912413786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 19:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Regarding Obama care. Romney fully now supports Obama care except that states will have option to choose. what a dumb idea. I lived in GA, NC, MI and travel all places. if i get sick in MI during travel that means i am not covered. if we push to state then each state have to open one adminstrative office to process claims, instead of having 2 to 3 people manage federally got to hire 50 people. higher admin cost results hospitals to cut the charges and ultimately hurt patient care. Having 20 million uninsured into the pipeline is fine, what if US population 20 million more than current level, that means our hospitals can handle 5% more patients.</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349925751787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349925824468-359</Id><Topic><Title>We look forward to Mr. Ryan as a competent younger generation leader</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349924956886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many people do the plural you speak for? What is the difference between younger leader and an allowance? What generation puts forward this quality of leader? Wasn't the term X-Gen in fashion...for a reason?</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1349925824468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349926189799-360</Id><Topic><Title>We look forward to Mr. Ryan as a competent younger generation leader</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349924956886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i never heard him talking about college students...............</Msg><Username>kumar700iv</Username><Timestamp>1349926189799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349926360056-361</Id><Topic><Title>Another GOP attempt to obstruct registered Democrat voters struck down in SC</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1349909497190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't get it, do you, fools? The laws struck down BY THE COURTS, stopped Republican attempts to obstruct REGISTERED Democrats from voting. Get it? Repeat: REGISTERED Democrats. In other words, Democrats who are already REGISTERED to vote.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349926360056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349927726549-362</Id><Topic><Title>Romneys Tax plan today</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349925631819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:20:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree with you. but save your saliva. people are stupid. they will vote by hope and vote romney the liar. and the market is celebrating romney win via SELLOFF. lets celebrate start of new misery when GOP rules...</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1349927726549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>