<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344151598854-1</Id><Title>Dick Cheney said Obama is worse than Jimmie Carter</Title><Msg>Dick was wrong ! Obama is worse than Herbert Hoover !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344151598854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 03:26:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344157679315-2</Id><Title>Will Reach 9 + by year end</Title><Msg>Mortgage Settlement with FANNI Housing Improvement Election Momentum</Msg><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1344157679315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 05:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344162474104-3</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Cheney said Obama is worse than Jimmie Carter</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344151598854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 03:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Going to be a great day in american history when cheney dies,lets hope he suffers greatly first.Also lets end all military pensions</Msg><Username>cranberry184</Username><Timestamp>1344162474104</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344162622192-4</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE BORN THIEVES AND LIARS</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135896856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree..sad but true</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1344162622192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344164304292-5</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Cheney said Obama is worse than Jimmie Carter</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344151598854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 03:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he's right!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>perry_879</Username><Timestamp>1344164304292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344164441291-6</Id><Topic><Title>We learned that Nixon was a crook after the election</Title><Username>golden_ghandi</Username><Timestamp>1344120230310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:43:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trying to think of one before you revealed his identity. All I could come up with was dumpobamie, but when I finished reading your post, I realized I was the victim of a false alarm. ROTFLMAO at smoke and mirrors everywhere, but nary a spark to be seen.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344164441291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344164981039-7</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO you pull an ID that makes you sound like a Street playuh, and you're only now beginning to notice a disconnect between job performance and pay? Do you think the compensation plans of Moynihan and the Boyz are commensurate with their hard work? ROTFLMAO at people who need three "Captain Oblivious" T-shirts, just so they'll never be caught out of uniform.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344164981039</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344167484188-8</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Cheney said Obama is worse than Jimmie Carter</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344151598854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 03:26:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dick Cheney should have said "Obama is an idiot"</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344167484188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344167850779-9</Id><Topic><Title>Predictions: Obama win big, slight chance of Democrat control of House</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1344113027215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:43:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen pal Obama has been president for 4yrs an his first 2yrs saw the largest majority of his own party any president has enjoyed since Carter so yes the runaway debt and massive unemployment is HIS problem. Got it you partisan dope?</Msg><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344167850779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344168214160-10</Id><Topic><Title>Will Reach 9 + by year end</Title><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1344157679315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 05:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it gets to 9 (I agree with you), it will test 10. GLTY!</Msg><Username>portguyofva</Username><Timestamp>1344168214160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344169672263-11</Id><Title>What do Obama, Democrats and Serena have in common?</Title><Msg>All are totally classless and an embarassment to normal people: Serena flubs crowning moment by doing the "Crip Walk" at medal ceremony, afterwards pleading ignorance. She knew that even associating the word “Crip” with a gold-medal performance could be toxic to her image, even if the dance itself is now distanced from those gang roots. A reporter asked what the dance was called. “The Serena?” the reporter suggested. “The Wimbledon?” Serena just stared at the ground, embarrassed. “Actually, there is a name. But I don’t know if I — it’s inappropriate,” she dodged. “It’s just a dance we do in California.”</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1344169672263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344173359583-12</Id><Title>Traders cry out for QE3, and you tell me the market is not a ponzi scheme!</Title><Msg>Growth is leveraged to whether the FED injectis money in the economy? What this tells me is the Bush tax cuts really have not created any jobs or sitmulated growth! So as the worker bee class gets pressed with more taxes, the elite continue to game the system..Sweet Jesus when are the 1% going to do something with their hordes of cash other than #$%$ about tax cuts.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344173359583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344174718489-13</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They'll need to do better than select as their best candidate a leading Cult member who believes in magic underwear, multiple wives and baptizing the dead. I tend to keep my kids away from people such as that, know what I mean?</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1344174718489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344175906693-14</Id><Topic><Title>4 brand new Bait cars on tonight</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1344174172615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the reminder, they waaaaay nicer than that Kardashian trash; the brats on 'toddlers and tiaras' and their crazy moms are pretty funny, too.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1344175906693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344176326096-15</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got that right!!!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344176326096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344177118245-16</Id><Topic><Title>LOOKS LIKE OBAMA WILL INHERIT HIS OWN RECESSION IF REELECTED</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344022939481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he will because nothing is going to get better as long as obama is president</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344177118245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344178510308-17</Id><Topic><Title>Traders cry out for QE3, and you tell me the market is not a ponzi scheme!</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344173359583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the stock market is simply being held up by FED funding, then why keep sitimulating? If the markets are truly not just a casino play ground for the wealthy then let it seek it's own level without FED stimulus and let moral hazard really be a factor in determining who gets wealthy! I believe that if you have a great idea, money is available. I know of a start-up that has identified the receptors in the stomach and a compond to block these receptors leading to a cure or at a minimum an oral medication that will control both type 1 and type 2 diabetes. The startup has not had any problems obtaining funding.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344178510308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 10:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344178857289-18</Id><Title>When will BAC raise dividend?</Title><Msg>It seems likely they will soon lift the divy.</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1344178857289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344179955231-19</Id><Title>Liberal Economic Theory Proven Wrong Again (Obama Recovery Worst since Depression)</Title><Msg>From Forbes Jan.2012: Supposedly a forward looking progressive, Obama proved to be America’s first backward looking regressive. His first act was to increase federal borrowing, the national debt and the deficit by nearly a trillion dollars to finance a supposed “stimulus” package, based on the discredited Keynesian theory left for dead 30 years ago holding that increased government spending, deficits and debt are what promote economic growth and recovery. That theory arose in the 1930s as the answer to the Great Depression, which, of course, never worked. That was the beginning of President Obama’s Rip Van Winkle act, pretending not to know anything that happened over the previous 30 years proving the dramatic, historic success of the new, more modern, supply side economics, which holds that incentives for increased production are what promote economic growth and recovery. Indeed, that Rip Van Winklism pretended not to remember the 1970s either, when double digit inflation and double digit unemployment proved Keynesian economics grievously wrong. As should have been long expected, Obama’s trillion dollar Keynesian stimulus did nothing to promote recovery and growth, and almost surely delayed it. That is because borrowing a trillion dollars out of the economy to spend a trillion back into it does nothing to promote the economy on net. Indeed, it is probably a net drag on the economy, because the private sector spends the money more productively and efficiently than the public sector. The National Bureau of Economic Research scored the recession as ending in June, 2009. Yet, today, in the 49th month since the recession started, there has still been no real recovery, like recoveries from previous recessions in America. Unemployment actually rose after June, 2009, and did not fall back down below that level until 18 months later in December, 2010. Instead of a recovery, America has suffered the longest period of unemployment near 9% or above since the Great Depression, under President Obama’s public policy malpractice. Even today, 49 months after the recession started, the U6 unemployment rate counting the unemployed, underemployed and discouraged workers is still 15.2%. And that doesn’t include all the workers who have fled the workforce under Obama’s economic oppression. The unemployment rate with the full measure of discouraged workers is reported at shadowstats as about 23%, which is depression level unemployment. Today, over 4 years since the recession started, there are still almost 25 million Americans unemployed or underemployed. That includes 5.6 million who are long-term unemployed for 27 weeks, or more than 6 months. Under President Obama, America has suffered the longest period with so many in such long-term unemployment since the Great Depression. Notably, blacks have been suffering another depression under Obama, with unemployment today, 49 months after the recession started, still at 15.8%. Black unemployment has been over 15% for 2 ½ years under Obama. Black teenage unemployment today is over 40%, where it has persisted for over 2 years as well. Hispanics have also been suffering a depression under Obama, with unemployment today still in double digits at 11%. Hispanic unemployment has been in double digits for three years under President Obama. Over one fourth of Hispanic youths remain unemployed today, which also has persisted for years. The Census Bureau reported in September that more Americans are in poverty today than at any time in the entire history of Census tracking poverty. Americans dependent on food stamps are at an all time high as well. Real wages and incomes have been falling so steadily under Obama and his confused, throwback, Keynesian/neo-Marxist Obamanomics, that the Census Bureau also reported that real median family income in America has fallen all the way back to 1996 levels. Obama apologists cannot argue that this is because the recession was so bad, because the historical record in America is the worse the recession the stronger the recovery. Based on historical precedent, we should at worst be finishing the second year of a booming recovery by now. Compare Obama’s lack of a recovery 2 ½ years after the recession ended with the first 2 ½ years of the Reagan recovery. In those years under Reagan, the American economy created 8 million new jobs, the unemployment rate fell by 3.6 percentage points, real wages and incomes were jumping, and poverty had reversed an upsurge started under Carter, beginning a long term decline. While Obama crows about 200,000 jobs created last month, the most for a month during his entire Administration, in September, 1983 the Reagan recovery less than a year after it began created 1.1 million jobs in that one month alone. Under Obama, we are still almost 6 million jobs below the peak before the recession started over 4 years ago! In the second year of the Reagan recovery, real economic growth boomed by 6.8%, the highest in 50 years.</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344179955231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344180571397-20</Id><Title>looks like RUBIO to be the man</Title><Msg>Well well well Very likeable person by women voters</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1344180571397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344180621246-21</Id><Title>Country/Merrill Libor Windfall</Title><Msg>Country Wide and Merrill will sue the Banking System for 40 Billion due to the Libor losses. BA, the Bank, will pay a fine of 10 Billion for their Libor involvement..... netting BAC, the conglomerate, a gain of 30 Billion. BAC, the conglomerate, will offer to buy back 3 Billion shares at $10 with the proceeds.... What a deal....</Msg><Username>sinfuel</Username><Timestamp>1344180621246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344182300910-22</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ultimate wall streeter running for the party owned by wall st, seems like a natural fit .</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344182300910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344182723826-23</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Economic Theory Proven Wrong Again (Obama Recovery Worst since Depression)</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344179955231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone can put together a laundry list of gripes. Tell us what you propose for cures, and don't say "Romney" without explaining in specific terms what he will do differently, and why it mightl work. I notice that his name was conspicuously absent from your post. I won't wait up for your reply, but I'll check now and then to see what you and Mr. Magic Panties have to offer in the way of improvements. ROTFLMAO thinking about an old cartoon, Gahan Wilson I believe, or maybe Gary Larson. In the first panel, a guy is lying unconscious in the street with tire tracks across his back. In the second panel, a concerned onlooker points at his prostrate body and shouts "Oh no! Call the Uh-Oh Squad!" In the last panel, a dozen people have encircled the accident victim; all are pointing at him and repeating over and over, "Uh-Oh! Uh-Oh!". ROTFLMAO at concerned spectators with nothing to offer everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344182723826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344183177874-24</Id><Topic><Title>That pesky thing called democracy, will see to the removal of commie obama</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1344174039048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 09:40:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is going to have an Electoral College margin of around 360 to 208. Even the bought-and-paid-for Supreme Court is gonna have a hard time flipping that outcome. Of course, you strike me as a real forward-thinking guy with a lot of analytical skills - go ahead and walk us through the Electoral College map and show us who's gonna fire Obama and where they live. ROTFLMAO at a dearth of map skills everywhere, or is math illiteracy the root cause of the problem?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344183177874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344183910193-25</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why'd your party nominate Romney? He certainly isn't up to the job. The United States is not a corporation, although I have to admit it's moving in that direction. We just got a good look at Romney's foreign policy and diplomatic skills, and he managed to make Palin look like she had her geography and that talking stuff down pat. ROTFLMAO at people trying to beat a donkey with a feather duster everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344183910193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184136302-26</Id><Topic><Title>looks like RUBIO to be the man</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1344180571397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:29:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, that's about as good as it's gonna get for Mitt, and the good news is that Rubio may still have a chance of continuing in politics after the rump-thumping that pair is going to collect. ROTFLMAO at a nice second banana who will assuredly finish second too.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344184136302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184288551-27</Id><Topic><Title>What do Obama, Democrats and Serena have in common?</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1344169672263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 08:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot the most important thing they have in common. In 2012, they're winners. ROTFLMAO at people who aren't looking at the scoreboard everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344184288551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184835210-28</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY DID NOT PAY TAXES FOR 10YRS</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135496639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this shows how stupid you are - ' do you not think that the IRS - would have nailed him to the wall - for not having paid TAXES - by now 2nd have you ever heard of Real Estate Taxes 3rd as Governor of Mass - if he had not paid taxes for 4 years - they would have had him in jail by now .!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344184835210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184854836-29</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think picking a fight over which side is wasting the most bandwidth is likely to further your lost cause, and may even raise awareness that Romney's communication problem is not a lack of bandwidth, but a lack of amplitude. With his abysmal signal-to-noise ratio, no wonder the neo-con SuperPacs are spending so much on airtime. They'd better be upgrading those old transmitters, too. ROTFLMAO at people with only the loosest of grasps on technology. Have you gotten over the shock of your recent discovery that there just might be a disconnect between performance and pay?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344184854836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184910912-30</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd much rather see the country run like a corporation, than like a 60's commune the way obama is running it. You might notice that well run corporations, I'm not talking about Solyndra, last many decades, make money and employ people.America is heading over the fiscal cliff under Bhagwan Shree Rajneesh Obama. Who BTW had ZERO foreign policy experience coming into office..</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344184910912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:41:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184958994-31</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think picking a fight over which side is wasting the most bandwidth is likely to further your lost cause, and may even raise awareness that Romney's communication problem is not a lack of bandwidth, but a lack of amplitude. With his abysmal signal-to-noise ratio, no wonder the GOP SuperPacs are spending so much on airtime. They'd better be upgrading those old transmitters, too. ROTFLMAO at people with only the loosest of grasps on technology. Have you gotten over the shock of your recent discovery that there just might be a disconnect between performance and pay?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344184958994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185076258-32</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>boy you have allot of 2 dollar words an say nothing " making yourself look important " ha still like my trailer - even has pool on top - " ha ha</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344185076258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:44:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344185105564-33</Id><Title>Obama Spending Millions to Demonize Romney</Title><Msg>Calling Romney essentially a felon. Never before have we seen a sitting president stoop to such classless tasteless vitriol.</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344185105564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185404572-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Spending Millions to Demonize Romney</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344185105564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:45:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what is funny - they have stated what they did - wihout thinking IF Romney would have not paid his taxes - the IRS - would have nailed him to the wall before now an I will bet - that his taxes have been audited - several times - by the IRS this just goes to show that Liberals never think .!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344185404572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344185444770-35</Id><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Msg>I just want the numbers and a certification that they are accurate with criminal liability if he plays with the numbers. I don't need to see the tax records but I need to know how much he has paid each of the last 10 years. I can show you mine Mitt. If not, then the rules are really different for the rich! Sweet Jesus, getting to the truth is so simple if all people are forced to one ethical standard. I am sure the Republicans know everything about the Presidents income and taxes and since they can't find anything in those records, the fringe keeps going after the birth certificate #$%$.. just very funny!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185473348-36</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But for a crew that specializes in utterly empty rhetoric, I suppose it looks like my verbal expenditures are out of control. ROTFLMAO at the easily dazzled. In the land of half-wits, anything more is pure elitism.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344185473348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185633678-37</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to try to find something wrong with successful Romney because you can't talk about the success of obama.</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344185633678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185642827-38</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Move to Brazil. ROTFLMAO at people who don't understand what they're asking for everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344185642827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344185794220-39</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well stupid - don't your think that if his TAXES were not accurate that the IRS would have had a field day -by now .!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344185794220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344186217939-40</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD ROMNEY DID NOT PAY TAXES FOR 10YRS</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344135496639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your head is definitely not. If you're serious about helping Obama, pour yourself a tall glass of #$%$ and let me handle this. ROTFLMAO at people trying to fight fire with gasoline everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344186217939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344186229296-41</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice deflection, fair is fair...how do I know he is successful when I can't see how much he makes, how much he pays in income tax. Sorry but us out here on the fruited plain are tired of the media both right and left telling us who is a good and a bad citizen. I have worked hard since I was 17 years old, received an education with the help of good parents and have a social security form that shows how much I have earned every working year. If I ran for President, I would release that statement so everyone of the folks in this country understands that I am a good citizen and not a crook.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344186229296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344186518057-42</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Although to half-wits, it may look like my vocabulary expenditures are out of control, I've hardly dipped into my pocket change. ROTFLMAO at verbally-challenged critics everywhere. Gore Vidal had the same problem.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344186518057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344186774089-43</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction does the Romney Hater have a real job?</Title><Username>stock_runner24</Username><Timestamp>1344135824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you let the free market of ideas operate without intervention, as in, butt out and let stock_runner24 defend himself? Are you two an item? ROTFLMAO at less-that-helpful friends everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344186774089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344186777748-44</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what you are stating - if your neighbor comes over - an as a good citizen - would show your taxes to him - right - how much you made - just to be good citizen from the fruited plain - as I stated - you can bet that Romney's taxes have been Audited - almost every year - since he has been in the public eye 1st Governor - an 2nd since his runs for president - he has been in the public eye -</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344186777748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187037922-45</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do like McCain did, and pick a Tea Bag Rag to ensure losing.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1344187037922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344187108141-46</Id><Title>Obama Job Approval Rating Slips to 44 Percent: Poll</Title><Msg>No president has ever won reelection under 47%</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344187108141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187441659-47</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Spending Millions to Demonize Romney</Title><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344185105564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:45:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This strategy won't win them reelection.</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344187441659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187543804-48</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Economic Theory Proven Wrong Again (Obama Recovery Worst since Depression)</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344179955231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is no Reagan, in fact he isn't even worthy of being in the same paragraph with him</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344187543804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344187674193-49</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My challenge stands on it's own merit. Less personal information like a social security number, I will publish my financial statements in any news paper in the world....will the gentleman that wants to run the country..do the same? This is from someone who actually hates to pay his taxes and believes that he pays to much as a percentage of income!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344187674193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188063197-50</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCANS ARE A SAD BUNCH</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344118113239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:08:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to talk about somthing sad, lets talk about BAC. A miserable bank priced to high now.</Msg><Username>rif521raf5264</Username><Timestamp>1344188063197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188290760-51</Id><Topic><Title>Will Reach 9 + by year end</Title><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1344157679315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 05:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>much sooner than you expected!</Msg><Username>shihv</Username><Timestamp>1344188290760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188540127-52</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" why " would you publish your financial statements - its no bodies business but yours as along as all laws are not broken - all taxes are paid - its not none of my business .! so he made allot of money - why is that a crime just the same as you did - . but if you wish to publish your business - be my guest .!!!!!!!!! Again as I stated - if the IRS is happy with his statements - an all tax laws are correct so be it .! 'Good luck with your Ideals .!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344188540127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188643852-53</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the repugs think Willard's tax dodging and draft dodging are issues concerning his lack of integrity? Says a lot about the repugs.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1344188643852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344189156035-54</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Economic Theory Proven Wrong Again (Obama Recovery Worst since Depression)</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344179955231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>laundry list of gripes the government spends too much money - an wastes it has stupid ideas to make themselves look important collects too large a paychecks for sitting on ther butts - works from 10am to 3pm - an get 250,000 dollars a year for doing it believes on high dollar trips $$$$$$$$$$$$$ to do nothing .! how am I doing ??</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344189156035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344190367795-55</Id><Title>Romney must be a liberal !!</Title><Msg>He sure is f ing over the republican party, showing or not showing his taxes its over.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344190367795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191111485-56</Id><Title>When George Romney, Mitt's father, ran for president, he set a standard by releasing 12 years of his tax returns.</Title><Msg>George Romney said, "presidential candidates need to be even more transparent in their financial dealings. One or two years of returns could be misleading to the public."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191111485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191337588-57</Id><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Msg>Bark bark!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191424257-58</Id><Title>If the Presidency were nothing but Golf Obama would have a stellar performance</Title><Msg>Congrats to you</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344191424257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344191450389-59</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deflection my #$%$ Why do you think YOU have a right to see his private info? How about you send me a copy of your returs just because I want to see them? You are the one doing the deflection. So it makes no sense that there are hidden facts about him breaking the law on his returns, because the IRS has audited them, so when that stupid argument of yours is shown for what it is, YOU DEFLECT by changing the reason you want to see his returns, as well then let's see his returns to prove that he is as successful as she says he is. What stupid argument are you going to DELFECT to next???? We know how successful he has been financially by the investments he holds, the properties he owns, etc., etc.... WHICH IS ALREADY DISCLOSED IN THE TAX RETURNS HE ALREADY FILED!!!!! That is complete proof of what you now say you want proof of.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344191450389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191913298-60</Id><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Msg>What did McCain see in those returns to pick unqualified mental midget Palin over GOP party heavy Willard?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344191976542-61</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It does gives me a pretty good idea of what YOUR diet is, though. ROTFLMAO at conservatives running out of palatable ideas everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344191976542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:39:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191988190-62</Id><Title>Mitt... to the great unwashed “Let them eat cake”</Title><Msg>Could this be Mitt’s Marie Antoinette moment? Some of us hoi polloi have gotten off our knees and want to know what percentage of his total income over the last 10 years was paid out in taxes. A simple request which deserves a simple straight forward answer! Yes Harry, I need to see your percentages as well! Matter of fact, I need to see all Senators and Congessmen and womens percentages because I am tired of pulling the wagon by myself! What they going to do, cut my head off for asking?</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344191988190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192031225-63</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your "challenge" has no merit. It has nothing to stand on. And who do you think you are that your "challenge" would mean anything to anybody? You are just another faceless jerk posting dribble on the internet like oh say a billion other people. Get a life, you are just wasting your time.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344192031225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192221421-64</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Economic Theory Proven Wrong Again (Obama Recovery Worst since Depression)</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344179955231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:19:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no mention of Mr. Magic Panties or which of his crackpot ideas is supposed to turn things around? By the way, how does your belief that people doing nothing shouldn't be drawing fancy paychecks jibe with Romney's 3 years of collecting fancy paychecks for not running Bain Capital? ROTFLMAO at the consistency of your inconsistency.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344192221421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192308234-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See there, my speculation is just as good, and so far just as baseless, as yours. People! We can go back and forth on stupid crap like this all day. Yes, there are questions on both issues, but no there are no answers or proof at this time. You do not contribute a thing by extrapolating baseless conjecture to the point of guilty until proven innocent. It's a huge waste of time and rather stupid.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344192308234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192479598-66</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will any of the VP candidates have enough character to tell Willard, "I'll run for VP only if you disclose your tax returns."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344192479598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344192942052-67</Id><Title>Yahoo minders and no-minders aiding and abetting the distribution</Title><Msg>of right wing venom, while preventing calm and rational counterpoints from appearing on this board. Let's all maintain the illusion that no one objects to their #$%$ ROTFLMAO at ostriches who think they're John Rambo everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344192942052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344193100711-68</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Mitt's father, George Romney, ran for president in the 1960's, he released 12 years of tax returns. He said, "presidential candidates need to be even more transparent in their financial dealings. One or two years of returns could be misleading to the public."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344193100711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:58:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344193647004-69</Id><Topic><Title>Romney must be a liberal !!</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344190367795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow how simple does it have to be for right wingers to understand !!</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344193647004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344193935618-70</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think it was McCain that told Harry Reid?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344193935618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344194549466-71</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have seen his birth certificate. We have proof of his education and his degrees. I don't care what his grade was in freshman English or what his dissertation was about 25 years ago, how many times he was absent or who his teachers were.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344194549466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:22:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344194629611-72</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP!</Msg><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344194629611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344196006213-73</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you shouldnt talk about manchelle that way</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344196006213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344197197149-74</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mrstan4089, I am not running for the Presidency but if I was, I would never have a problem disclosing how much I paid in taxes based upon earned income or investment income. Why is this such a problem and why so much hostility? We need to understand all politicians income. I for one would like to see how much investment incomes climbed for the very few who were in the closed door meetings with Hank Paulson in September of 2008 when it was clear that FED intervention was the only chance for saving the world financial systems! Again, just a simple answer, what percentage did Mr. Romney pay in taxes on his total income in the last 10 years?</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344197197149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344197241107-75</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Obama, I ate dog balls before in Viet Nam too. Very tastety.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344197241107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344197356854-76</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all i want to know is what went on in secret with the new healthcare laws that will affect all our lives and after we were promised transparency? Mitt's taxes are the least of my concern and don't affect me one bit</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344197356854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344198490603-77</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope you don't still believe voting works. We all realize that if a president can have a 20-something% approval rating and still be in office, along with an aspiring candidate whose approval rating is even less, there is *no* democracy, right? I'll give you people time to calculate that.</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1344198490603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344199036269-78</Id><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Governer Romney got the support of all frustrated Americans. OBAMA MUST GO PERIOD.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344199199600-79</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo minders and no-minders aiding and abetting the distribution</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344192942052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A year of sober living "he went to Jared's" decides to admit guilt...Joker won't be crazy either. Speaking of distribution centers...did you read Viewer is in the U.S. Distribution capital for Heroin? No wonder BAC hasn't closed branches in Las Vegas...who is going to launder the money...Skagg Albertson's?</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344199199600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344200139615-80</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes, let's go back to Republican style healthcare where pre-existing conditions disqualify you from buying insurance and they kick you off the insurance plans the minute you get ill. Let's go back to Republican enabled Wall street values of no regulation to see if they can drive the bus completely off the cliff this time! Sorry, you folks had your chance and we are ever so slowly working the country out from the mountain of debt brought on by your Wall street cronies, the unfunded Bush, Cheney wars and tax cuts. Besides, this election is going to be won or lost by the votes of the youth who have a dimmer future because of Republican leadership.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344200139615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344200683465-81</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's 2010 and 2011 tax returns are a matter of public record. His AGI was around $21 million and he paid around $3.2 million in taxes each year.That's about 15%. Most all his income was in the form of capital gais and divdend income since he was a venture capitalist/private equity investor. Morever, throughout most the decade he has filed his financial condition with the Federal Disclosure commission and The MA St. Disclosure commission. Since tax rates on capital have been 15% since the early 2000s no doubt 8 more years of returns would produce the similar numbers. If you don't like his tax rates then change the law. Are you curious where Obama got funds to go to college and law school and py for his around the world junket between stints at Occidental college and Columbia?</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1344200683465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344200733521-82</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obummer adds 5 trillion to the debt and is still in his 1st term and your worried about mitt romney? this country needs a businessman to turn things around. no more play now pay later.-jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1344200733521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344201008556-83</Id><Title>Hate Mongers on this board</Title><Msg>Looks like all the hate mongers are here, as always. That's the problem with the US....too much hatred. And religion has become nothing more than a springboard for that hatred.</Msg><Username>limp.louie</Username><Timestamp>1344201008556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344201181978-84</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IF you give both Romney &amp; Obama $20 each I can guarantee you Romney will turn that $20 into 2 million of dollars while Obama will borrow from his uncle Omar $20 to pay back the creditor. Obama is an idiot PERIOD.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344201181978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344201982447-85</Id><Title>Financial Times - must read. Buy downside protection</Title><Msg>Headlines are getting downright scary and this market is up? Nuts. From COMPANIES 9:32pm Wall St eyes protection against euro exit Banks tell counterparties to restructure contracts US banks haunted by spectre of eurozone</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1344201982447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344202216540-86</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Mongers on this board</Title><Username>limp.louie</Username><Timestamp>1344201008556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the gay religion?</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1344202216540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344202457658-87</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perhaps you'd be interested in making a wager with someone who thinks Mitt's gonna wind up about 62 electoral votes short of the mark. I can't offer you one of those Romney "Gentlemen's $10K Bets", but I'll cover as much even-money action as you want up to a grand. Something tells me, though, that I can close the betting window now. None of the other chest-thumping Baltic smugglers here have been tripping over each other to get a piece of it either. ROTFLMAO at how well cacography and cacophony play together on the conservative side of the street. Oh dear, da23566; I just dropped $4 bucks of vocabulary in one sentence! It's a mere pittance, though, when you compare it to what the GOP's SuperPacs have already spent trying to peddle spoiled meat.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344202457658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344202641940-88</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still too embarrassed by the GOP's candidate to mention his name? ROTFLMAO at people who ran out of ammunition and clues a month ago, but still believe they're gonna win the war in November. Let's hear it for faith-based initiatives everywhere!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344202641940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344202925393-89</Id><Title>Shorts. Futures are up 220 points. You and Mitt and dead meat. Chuckle.</Title><Msg>The way it should be. The way I like it.</Msg><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1344202925393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344203074344-90</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Mongers on this board</Title><Username>limp.louie</Username><Timestamp>1344201008556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are who I think you are, then you are real deal. All the rest are rectal drip SW. That's firm.</Msg><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1344203074344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344203258845-91</Id><Title>Good Republicans (contradiction in terms) must demand that Mitt disclose at least 100 years of his tax records</Title><Msg>That should be a condition for the convention. If he fails, we need someone else. I propose Dan Quale. Chuckle.</Msg><Username>libertydles30</Username><Timestamp>1344203258845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344203420553-92</Id><Topic><Title>Hate Mongers on this board</Title><Username>limp.louie</Username><Timestamp>1344201008556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:10:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The definition alone justifies the application of 'monger' to these lulus: "a dealer or trader; usually in compounds (e.g. fishmonger); sometimes used figuratively and derogatorily. Mittmonger has a nice ring to it, too. Now let me show off the 3 years of Latin I took 40 years ago: the word is derived from the Latin 'mango'; a dealer in tricked-out wares! It's also the root of another appropriate word to apply to these Baltic Smugglers: 'mangle', which is what they do to history, facts and reason every time they open their yaps and start braying again. ROTFLMAO at defenders of the rich everywhere, as long as we're talking money rather than education or vocabulary.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344203420553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344203477739-93</Id><Title>I don't hate Republicans. I just think they should be wiped off this Earth or sent to Siberia</Title><Msg>This is not hatred. This is a necessity. They must be obliterated if the Earth is to continue Progress. MK</Msg><Username>joeqd01</Username><Timestamp>1344203477739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344203695756-94</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans enjoyed privatizing the profits during the go, go years on Wall street leading up to the crash of September 2008. Then the country had no choice but to socialized the debt they left behind or meltdown the economy. A total failure of the theory of efficient markets. I submit the crash of 2008 and the reckless unfunded Bush, Cheney wars are the reason we are in this sad state of fiscal affairs. My fear is Mr. Romney will not learn from the history of Iraq and Afghanistan. The current administration and military leadership understands how to fight the terrorists with limited special forces on the ground, airpower and UAV's. We will get out of Afghanistan under the current President but I am not sure of this if a Republican President is elected.Terrorists hate these tactics, they call them unfair...ha. Watch remotely and strike them when they show their faces and for heaven sake, keep our brave kids out of these poop holes and stop providing the terrorists with targets. The andym_30054 doctrine is simply.... terrorists, don't cause trouble in the civilized world and we will leave you to you alone. Cause trouble and we will rain so much "HE" double toothpicks on your heads that you won't live to take another breath! Hear endeth the lesson!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344203695756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344203767669-95</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo minders and no-minders aiding and abetting the distribution</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344192942052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Yes, waiter, just bring me whatever SHE'S having." Elmo loves ya, viewer....but so do I. ROTFLMAO at smart shoppers everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344203767669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344204109370-96</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo minders and no-minders aiding and abetting the distribution</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344192942052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:55:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've got a small but fine collection of Victorian-era Mt. Washington and Depression-era Fenton satin art glass, and it has consistently out-performed the market and the banks. The last thing I need is Fenton-reducing solvents. ROTFLMAO at obscure and unexpected threats everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344204109370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344205161555-97</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just want to get some of yours..... ROTFLMAO and PMP now. Why don't you see if Mitt will front you $20 to put down on a sure thing? Did you use to work on a cattle ranch in Vietnam? I know the "all hat, no cattle' syndrome when I see it. Same goes for hoof 'n mouth disease.....ROTFLMAO at people soliciting donations for unworthy causes everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344205161555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344205389678-98</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like the cut of your jib, f.buckskin. ROTFLMAO at signs of encroaching senility in my immediate neighborhood.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344205389678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344205533327-99</Id><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Msg>We had a meeting last nite and we ALL agreed that we did make a mistake voting for Hope &amp; Change the last time. OBAMA IS A LIAR !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206019498-100</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly too many Americans just want a president that gives them handouts and to Hell with the country! And Obama wants to make more people like this to support his reelection</Msg><Username>asprin_headache</Username><Timestamp>1344206019498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206173054-101</Id><Topic><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>according to latest rasmussen poll. romey leads obama 47% to 45% . obama still leads in electorial votes in 12 key states but polling these states says that the race is very close.. bucko ps-just wait till rubio or christie is picked as vp.</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1344206173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206690046-102</Id><Topic><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney - Portman would be a very good ticket. OBAMA MUST GO !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344206690046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344207742888-103</Id><Topic><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you tell them you've got a sucker on the line who's willing to double how ever much of their money they want to bet on Romney? Maybe between you, the family can come up with that $20 that Mitt couldn't front you. Still waiting for a response as to how much even-money action I should sign you up for. ROTFLMAO just imaging your family meeting....</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344207742888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344208085569-104</Id><Topic><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, go with Sara. It will leave the ticket top-heavy with women, but as John McCain so emphatically declared, she's the best of the bunch. ROTFLMAO at rotten second bananas everywhere. Your top banana looks like he's ready for the banana bread, too.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344208085569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:08:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344208379044-105</Id><Topic><Title>My entire family will vote Mitt Romney !!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344205533327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just tell us where to find an Electoral College map that supports your assertions. By the way, in those 12 key swing states, show us the source for your claim that it's very close. ROTFLMAO at armchair quarterbacks lobbing Hail Mary passes everywhere. "Just keep thinking, Butch; that's what you're good at."</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344208379044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344208902646-106</Id><Title>Reince Priebus-what do you really think about Dirty Harry and Daffy Debbie?</Title><Msg>“I’m not going to respond to a dirty liar who hasn't filed a single page of tax returns himself,” Priebus said on ABC’s “This Week” about Reid’s claim. “He complains about people with money, but lives in the Ritz Carlton here down the street.” Earlier in the show, Democratic National Committee Chairman Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz defended Reid’s right to make such statements since they are in keeping with the Democratic Party standards of "trickery and deceit." Then she farted loudly on air.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1344208902646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344209020399-107</Id><Title>The Romney crowd here reminds me of a bunch of returning 8th graders</Title><Msg>who are too old to dressing up to go Trick-or-Treating, and too young to look very menacing in their skinhead costumes. "Have fun, kids, but you all need to be home by 11/06, and then it's four more years of schooling." ROTFLMAO at not-quite-ready-for-primetime Holloweenies everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344209020399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344209043281-108</Id><Topic><Title>Financial Times - must read. Buy downside protection</Title><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1344201982447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Price movement looks very strong recently</Msg><Username>leeal998</Username><Timestamp>1344209043281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344210263469-109</Id><Topic><Title>The Romney crowd here reminds me of a bunch of returning 8th graders</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344209020399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She's planning the honeymoon before she meets you...My Man Mittens says create the incentives....Dirty Harry hasn't produced a single tax return in10 years.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344210263469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344210273322-110</Id><Title>Obama camp is getting pretty nervous !!!!</Title><Msg>All Governer Romeny has to do is just talk about jobs, jobs, jobs and I can guarantee you he will whip Obama's ash in ALL 57 states !!!!!!! OBAMA MUST GO !!!!!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344210273322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344211340574-111</Id><Topic><Title>When George Romney, Mitt's father, ran for president, he set a standard by releasing 12 years of his tax returns.</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191111485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that what Mitt is up to? Misleading the public? Nawwwwwwww! Mitty wouldn't do that, would he?</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1344211340574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344211603879-112</Id><Title>WHEN YOUR GUY CAN'T RUN ON HIS RECORD TRY TO RUN DOWN THE OTHER GUY</Title><Msg>That's exactly what's going on with the constant attacks on Romney everyone already knows obama sucks huge. We are still in recession directly because of obama's policies.</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344211603879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344211831334-113</Id><Topic><Title>I COULDN’T CARE LESS ABOUT COLLEGE TRASNSCRIPTS AND TAX RETURNS I WANT A PRESIDENT WHO CAN RUN THE COUNTRY EFFICIENTLY</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344114302947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 17:05:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting RoBUTT post ............ like a Corp. , Really??? The top dogs get richer and the rest get poorer [ Millions in CEO bonus regardless of performance] and cuts for everyone else ] Guess that means most goverment services will be outsourced to China Short term vision Lack of concern for the people who do the actual work Top Management has only their self interest in mind Will to bend and break any rule Ongoing failure to invest in the future Willing to say or do anything ....truth is not required UMMM come to think of it the Republican Party DOES want the country ran like a Corp. and I guess other gomers like you do also.</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1344211831334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344212115593-114</Id><Topic><Title>The Romney crowd here reminds me of a bunch of returning 8th graders</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344209020399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wild About Harry. However, Trickle-Down has had plenty of opportunities to show us what it's got, and squandered every one of them. To date the most effective results of it that I've seen were by my dog, and while parts of her turf are lush and green, others are burned-out brown wastelands, and the rest of her territory is a no-fly zone. ROTFLMAO at the futility of resisting The Rise Of The Baltic Smugglers, already showing in theaters and places of worship too close for comfort everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344212115593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344212379453-115</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did McCain see in those 23 years of Mitt's tax returns that would be any different from what are in Mitt's tax returns from 2008 through 2011? More of the same Swiss, Cayman Islands, and other offshore accounts?</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1344212379453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344212934457-116</Id><Topic><Title>The Romney crowd here reminds me of a bunch of returning 8th graders</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344209020399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besides, my planner tells me it's time for some simpson-style social sequestration, a breaking bad testosterone injection, and then over and out. See you tomorrow, Same Bat Time, Same Bat Channel. ROTFLMAO at my own efforts to maintain the Common Touch. Maybe I should just go to the Dark Side and become a Mitt-monger too. I'm sure I could give his Uncommon Touch a few adjustments and some fine- tuning.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344212934457</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344213046405-117</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN YOUR GUY CAN'T RUN ON HIS RECORD TRY TO RUN DOWN THE OTHER GUY</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344211603879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:06:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You call yourself "bury obama" and complain about posts that run down the other guy? Your joined at the bungs-to-mouths siamese twin "dumpobamie" and you, and the dozens and dozens of the other SW rectal drips, exist to do that and only that. GFY troll.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1344213046405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344213075486-118</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney's already won, and Obama knows it. Romney wouldn't soil his boot kicking Obama's butt -- besides, he'd have to get through Barney Frank's butt first in order to get to Obama's. I hear Barry's a catcher and Barney's a pitcher. And fish2kill -- what a loon. He should make lots of those bets, then he could collect welfare for the rest of his life when he has to pay them all off.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1344213075486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344213091856-119</Id><Title>My dog BOO will probably vote Obama</Title><Msg>I know my dog BOO is a stupid Democrat. He banged the other guy dogs in the neighborhood all the times.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344213091856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344213899921-120</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gotta have a tea bagger, or the tea bagger storm troopers will vandalize the convention.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1344213899921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344214728902-121</Id><Title>SW and his Rectal Drip Aliases have been reduced to a weak bunch of pathetic inbred trolls.</Title><Msg>All they do is lie about Obama. They never have anything good to say about Romney. Is that because there is nothing good to say about Romney?</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1344214728902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344215479761-122</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A Dog?? hell boy Obama ate more than one dog..he ate 100s of dogs...Our Great Black president also eat Larry Sinclair..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344215479761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344215586820-123</Id><Topic><Title>So...all I want to know is how much Mitt has made each year for the last 10 years and what he paid in taxes?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344185444770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope he was smart enough not to pay any!!! ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344215586820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344215903192-124</Id><Title>Obama &amp; Biden...The Joke..lol...</Title><Msg>What would hapen if Joe Biden became President.???</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344215903192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344215999771-125</Id><Topic><Title>My dog BOO will probably vote Obama</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344213091856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to see Boo bang Obama...Ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344215999771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344216054870-126</Id><Title>Obama ca run on his record</Title><Msg>He has kept 13 of 14 promises to help small business. He has reversed the unemployment trend, he has the economy in recovery. Even Mitt Romney knows that the stage is set for the normal business cycle to bring unemployment down to 6% in the next two years no matter which candidate gets elected. Obama has decreased dependence on foreign oil. Obama brought troops home from the Iraq and has aided in the spread of democracy in the middle east and Africa. Obama has waged a successful war on al qeada exterminating most of their leadership. Obama has defended the rights of all americans to life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness. Obama completed the negotiations to save the auto industry. Obamas stimulus kept teachers, cops and fire fighters off the unemployment lines. Obama has cut the growth of government more than any republican president in the past 50 years. Obama has negotiated budget reductions with a hostile GOP. Obama has created a medical program that will cut billions in medical costs over the next 10 years. Unlike Reagan Obama has done theres things without just shifting the cost to the states.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344216054870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344216129885-127</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA Ate a DOG!</Title><Username>sizzlin2day</Username><Timestamp>1344191337588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:28:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dog meat is almost like deer. Dogs that raised in the farms taste like chicken. Only stray dogs, the one roaming the streets taste the best. Dog balls are thought to be good for your sex.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344216129885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344216367716-128</Id><Title>You can see how worried the Obama Team is...The record is the worlds worst!!!</Title><Msg>8.5% unemployment..No President ever over came the unemployment numbers..Consumer confidence is against Obama also!!! ILMFAO...by by odumba!!! ILMFAO</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344216367716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344216612839-129</Id><Topic><Title>Nancy Pelosi ... former Speaker of the House ... 2nd in line to succeed as President ...</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344215995466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:19:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>swamp rat nancy...1.6 million dollars spent to save the swamp rats in northern California??? Good Job Nancy..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344216612839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344216731218-130</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ca run on his record</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344216054870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the peace monkey did all that??? when??? ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344216731218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217265814-131</Id><Topic><Title>When George Romney, Mitt's father, ran for president, he set a standard by releasing 12 years of his tax returns.</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191111485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt WILL do what daddy did -- LOSE!</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344217265814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217486144-132</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who would want to go down with that sinking ship?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344217486144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217556919-133</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McCain saw what Mitt now wants no one to see.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344217556919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217612981-134</Id><Topic><Title>When George Romney, Mitt's father, ran for president, he set a standard by releasing 12 years of his tax returns.</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191111485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In all fairness, you guys should ask your moms to disclose their income tax first. I have never seen such low point of political science.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344217612981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217676361-135</Id><Topic><Title>When George Romney, Mitt's father, ran for president, he set a standard by releasing 12 years of his tax returns.</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191111485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:25:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Were George Romney's accountants more clever with hiding assets than Mitt's accountants?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344217676361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:47:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217921099-136</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard will lose no matter if he puts up, or not. But, he will never live this down.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344217921099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344218044732-137</Id><Title>Obama the 8% unemployment and Food Stamp King</Title><Msg>At least he is consistent everything is f%#$ed up.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1344218044732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344218147938-138</Id><Title>$10 + bull run</Title><Msg>Anybody get the feeling BAC is going to go for a real nice ride up soon!!! Well over due and ready to pop</Msg><Username>cwoolrey</Username><Timestamp>1344218147938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218534439-139</Id><Topic><Title>Will Washout Willard step down at the GOP convention to let a repug with integrity take his place?</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1344120682377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:51:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the Tea Baggers will stage a putsch.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344218534439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218603725-140</Id><Topic><Title>john 3:16</Title><Username>cboeman</Username><Timestamp>1344133154435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 22:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A beautiful scripture cboeman!!! Thanks for the inspiration! For GOD so loved the world......that he gave his only begotten son and who so ever believeth in him shall not perish but have everlasting life! The big eye in the sky knows all.GOD bless</Msg><Username>cwoolrey</Username><Timestamp>1344218603725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:03:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344218725783-141</Id><Title>CNN just reported that Reid admitted he has no proof for his groundless accusations. What a futz.</Title><Msg>Reid is a liar and an idiot.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344218725783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:05:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218745653-142</Id><Topic><Title>Obama the 8% unemployment and Food Stamp King</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1344218044732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are consistently good at it. Why not get paid for it?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344218745653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344218961401-143</Id><Topic><Title>$10 + bull run</Title><Username>cwoolrey</Username><Timestamp>1344218147938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:55:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I do... but I've had that feeling for a while and so far it hasn't happened. I thought it would make a run in April or May, which it did have a run up but then reversed as the economy slowed in the second quarter. I don't know when it will happen but when the macro economic factors that scare investors resolve themself and BAC earnings improve, I think the run will be well in excess of $10. I am long the Tarp LEAPS that expire Jan 2019, so anytime before then will be fine with me.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344218961401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344219151633-144</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but forgot to bring his wallet. I've set my limit so I won't end up like you, even if the improbable whacks my calculated risk. Show me your money, or at least an Electoral College map to back up your ever-ready mouth, or go back to stewing in your own miserable gravy. ROTFLMAO at blighters breaking bad everywhere. Pardon me; I hear Walt calling.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344219151633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344219334316-145</Id><Topic><Title>CNN just reported that Reid admitted he has no proof for his groundless accusations. What a futz.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344218725783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:05:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIAR!!!!!!!! Reid said no such thing. Reid told Romney to "PUT UP!"</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344219334316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344219390940-146</Id><Topic><Title>Romney released 23 years of tax returns to McCain in 2008 as part of the VP vetting process. Is that why McCain picked Palin?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344191913298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:38:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Groundless twisted speculation. You have no idea what he saw, and you have no idea why he picked Palin. You are putting two and two together and getting eight. I can do the same with Fast and Furious to bring questions on what Obama knew and did. Does he have the killed agent's blood on his hands for approving the operation? Is that why he invoked exec privilege, to coverup his involvement? Experts say it had to be approved at the very top. Obama, who ran on a platform of more transparency? That is the guy who you want to have another term of making promises he does not keep? Like promising voters in Virginia that he would support clean coal, then he closes down a lot of mines? You want that liar for president again????</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344219390940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344220211525-147</Id><Topic><Title>Obama the 8% unemployment and Food Stamp King</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1344218044732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has never worked in the private sector and it shows. He had his chance now time for anyone else.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1344220211525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344220538412-148</Id><Title>Bill Clinton's stellar academic records and George Bush's mediocre records well known, what's up Barack?</Title><Msg>Kind of embarrassing when your touted as a genius but your track record tells the truth...that you are just a pretty front man with no real accomplishments, either before or after election</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1344220538412</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344220550545-149</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Governer Romney can save America from tanking further....Next time you vote you vote for Romney, the guy with a clear vision, concrete ideology, and least but not last, a guy who can re-define Americanism. Obama is an idiot !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344220550545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344221170610-150</Id><Title>What are the odds? I mean, what are the REAL odds?</Title><Msg>At this moment, the Vegas line for the 2012 President Election is a puny 59-cent payout on a $1 bet that Obama will win; but $1.40 for the same $1 bet on Romney. That spread has been widening rapidly; are all you courageous risk-taking free market capitalists waiting to get your money down on Romney when the payout reaches $10 Grand? ROTFLMAO at people who think they can beat the house everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344221170610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344221621340-151</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney gonna kick Obama's butt !!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344199036269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:37:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like Barak and will proudly again cast my vote for the man.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1344221621340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344221711249-152</Id><Title>Shocking! Simply shocking that a politician would lie!</Title><Msg>ROTFLMAO! Someone is surprised that Obama employed a surrogate to do the required dirty deeds? You should have studied your American History, instead of wasting time thumping your chests and puffing each other up about politics, a subject about which few of you seem to have so much as a clue. Well, Obama's gonna send you back to school for four more years; maybe this time you'll put down the Archie comic books and pay attention to all that boring old stuff that doesn't have anything to do with modern times.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344221711249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 22:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344222686600-153</Id><Title>Why I think Romney will be a more qualified Prez?</Title><Msg>If Romney can avoid paying income tax legally for 10 years, by wall street standard, he is smart in managing money. So, he will be better handling economics,</Msg><Username>bigg_cnd</Username><Timestamp>1344222686600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 23:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344224764519-154</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's lead will only continue to</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1344224764519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 23:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344225022110-155</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ca run on his record</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344216054870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:20:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very good post. Obama has done so much to repair the damage incurred by the Bush years. He will continue to repair, rebuild, and lead a recovery.</Msg><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1344225022110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 23:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>