<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349240412045-1</Id><Topic><Title>COME ON GUYS THE ELECTION IS OVER - GOP AND MITTEN LOST</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349181054362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 08:30:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right. Why flog a dead horse? GOP and Mitten are losers. They can't win! WHY WASTE TIME?</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349240412045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349240929354-2</Id><Topic><Title>How Romney loses on one simple question</Title><Username>fringnatical</Username><Timestamp>1349225068629</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His problem is chronic. He speaks before he thinks... always! He is a time-bomb ready to self-destruct. Obama needs to do nothing but smile- flash that winner's smile!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349240929354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349241106134-3</Id><Topic><Title>Biden -- Middle Class has been 'buried the last four years'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349224472948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:34:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is Biden voting for Romney?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349241106134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349243090008-4</Id><Title>new video of obama speech released of Obama screamng racism and class warfare</Title><Msg>Do we really need another 4yrs of this crap?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349243090008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 01:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349245447115-5</Id><Title>It all makes sense now. I was wondering how Joe Biden could effect such a convincing Southern Black dialect with his "Put Y'all back in chains" comment</Title><Msg>He learned from the master, a Columbia Professor that gets in front of a Black audience and all the sudden sounds like a Bro from the hood. Oh to be a fly on the wall during those voice lessons in the Oval office, it must have been priceless "No Joe it isn't YOW its Y'All" Say it with me now....."</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349245447115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349245605364-6</Id><Title>Social Security predicted to go BANKRUPT sooner than forecasted........its time for Obama's lack of leadership to GO!!</Title><Msg>reporting on the accelerating depletion of that program's Trust Fund. As recently as 2008, the Trust Fund's doomsday was projected to be as far away as 2041. But over the past several years that collapse date has inched forward and now sits at 2033. Unfortunately, even that projection looks like it's a bit too optimistic. It turns out that there's a very real risk that next year's report will move that date even closer. What Happened? Since the Trustee's Report was written in April, some news has emerged about the investments in the Trust Fund putting a drag on the returns. Every year, Social Security rolls over its maturing long-term Treasury bond holdings, picking up new ones to replace the ones that are expiring. Because of exceptionally low interest rates, Social Security is earning less interest on its new bonds than it did on its old ones. That lower interest, along with the fact that the program now takes in less in taxes than it spends in benefits, means the Trust Fund is on even shakier footing. What's a Few Billion Among Friends? Take a look at the scary trend line that shows the annual interest lost when the old long-term bonds matured or were sold versus the annual interest on the new long-term bonds: Every year since 2010, the new long-term bonds being bought by Social Security pay substantially less interest than the old long-term bonds that are maturing. That red line is getting deeper, and the 2012 total is nearly $5.4 billion in annual interest foregone because the new bonds pay that much less than the old ones. That amounts to $5.4 billion less available for paying benefits or for reinvestment. That's a $5.4 billion deeper hole the program faces next year than it would have if rates had stayed steady. And that's just from one year. So What? Since 2010, the total annual income foregone due to lower interest rates has exceeded $10.5 billion. Since this only counts the long-term bonds that Social Security is using -- not the short-term certificates that get traded much more frequently -- those numbers add up to create a whole world of pain. It's a huge deal, because Social Security is already paying out more in benefits than it takes in as taxes. The only reason the Trust Fund is still growing at all is because of the interest it generates on the Treasury bonds it holds. With interest rates so low and net interest received dropping as a those old bonds mature, that "net interest" kicker is rapidly losing steam. The sooner it runs out of gas, the sooner the Trust Fund starts actively shrinking, starting something of a death spiral as the stockpile depletes. From the perspective of a potential recipient, this hastens the need for you to prepare for the Trust Fund's collapse. Every downward revision in the year the Trust Fund will expire hurts your chances to get ready in two ways. For one, the closer date gives you that much less time to prepare. For another, if you aren't already preparing, then you've already lost the time that had passed since the last revision. In other words, assume for the sake of discussion that the 2013 Trustees' Report moves the Trust Fund's anticipated run-dry date a year closer -- to 2032 rather than today's expected 2033. If you did nothing to prepare in 2012 because you had 21 years before the issue struck, imagine waking up when the next report is published to find that you've lost not one year, but two. What Will You Do About It? Think it can't happen? Take a look at the table in this article along with the graph above in the one you're reading now. Ask yourself what's more likely: that the ugly trend that has already established itself will continue, or that these very serious issues will somehow, almost magically, solve themselves. With around two decades left, you still have time to prepare. But your chance to let time and the magic of compounding work for you to cover for Social Security's shortfall is rapidly running out. So get moving now, or prepare for a really scary income gap when you are looking to retire. (THE ARTICLE SAYS INCHED FORWARD I WOULD SAY LOSING 8YRS IN 4 IS NOT INCHING ITS POSSIBLE IF INTEREST RATES STAY LOW SOCIAL SECURITY COULD GO BANKRUPT IN JUST 10YRS!!!!!)</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349245605364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349246733637-7</Id><Title>Could California be the first state to go Bankrupt?</Title><Msg>Governor Jerry Brown’s proposed $50 billion tax-increase initiative won’t solve California’s budget problems. Neither will anything else on the state’s ballot in November, nor will more cuts to child care, courts, parks, college and welfare programs repeatedly slashed by the state Legislature. Solving California’s budget woes requires addressing five root causes: unfunded health-care promises to retired employees, excessive incarceration rates, a boom-and-bust revenue system, underfunded pension commitments and fast-growing spending on Medicaid. Except for alterations to Medicaid (which requires agreement from the federal government for material changes), the Legislature and governor have all the power they need to address these causes. They just need to use it. This article looks at the role of retiree health care, technically known as “other post-employment benefits.” Visible state spending on these benefits grew at a 12 percent annual rate from fiscal year 2001-02 to 2011-12, but there is even greater invisible spending.</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349246733637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349246770395-8</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security predicted to go BANKRUPT sooner than forecasted........its time for Obama's lack of leadership to GO!!</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349245605364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let social security go broke...let this country go straight to hell...any country that would vote for a god dam socialist fool that the socialist media panders too deserves to fall...your no better that the god dam Romes go to hell Mers!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349246770395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349247010957-9</Id><Title>Obama Does NOTHING but want to raise spending in the face of Medicare going BANKRUPT in 2016-2020...Social Security going BANKRUPT in 2023-2030</Title><Msg>Talk about the wrong man for the wrong time</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349247010957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349247147320-10</Id><Title>Trustees: Medicare Will Go Broke in 2016, If You Exclude Obamacare's Double-Counting</Title><Msg>The Trustees of the Medicare program have released their annual report on the solvency of the program. They calculate that the program is “expected to remain solvent until 2024, the same as last year’s estimate.” But what that headline obfuscates is that Obamacare’s tax increases and spending cuts are counted towards the program’s alleged “deficit-neutrality,” Medicare is to go bankrupt in 2016. And if you listen to Medicare’s own actuary, Richard Foster, the program’s bankruptcy could come even sooner than that. Here’s how the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services summarize the findings, which carry the formal title “2012 Annual Report of the Boards of Trustees of the Federal Hospital Insurance and Federal Supplementary Medical Insurance Trust Funds” : [Medicare Hospital Insurance Trust Fund] expenditures have exceeded income annually since 2008 and are projected to continue doing so under current law in all future years. Trust Fund interest earnings and asset redemptions are required to cover the difference. HI assets are projected to cover annual deficits through 2023, with asset depletion in 2024. After asset depletion, if Congress were to take no further action, projected HI Trust Fund revenue would be adequate to cover 87 percent of estimated expenditures in 2024 and 67 percent of projected costs in 2050. In practice, Congress has never allowed a Medicare trust fund to exhaust its assets. The financial projections for Medicare reflect substantial cost savings resulting from the Affordable Care Act, but also show that further action is needed to address the program’s continuing cost growth. The Trustees, by saying that Medicare will go bankrupt in 2024, instead of 2016, are simultaneously saying that the program will increase the deficit by several hundred billion dollars. This is precisely the insight that Charles Blahous, one of the Medicare Trustees, explained in his recent report on the program. Think of it this way: if supporters of the Affordable Care Act came clean, they would say one of two things: (1) Medicare is going bankrupt in 2016, but the CBO scores the ACA as deficit neutral; or (2) Medicare is going bankrupt in 2024, and Blahous’ score of the ACA as increasing the deficit by $300-500 billion is accurate. Which path will they choose? As Chris Jacobs notes, President Obama has admitted that, “You can’t say that you are saving on Medicare and then spending the money twice.” That is, Chuck Blahous is right. Medicare actuary Richard Foster splashes cold water on the Trustees’ report If you want to get a sense of how Medicare’s finances look when viewed with real-world accounting assuptions, head to Richard Foster’s “Statement of Actuarial Opinion,” which begins on page 277. “In past reports, and again this year, the Board of Trustees has emphasized the strong likelihood that actual Part B expenditures will exceed the projections under current law due to further legislative action to avoid substantial reductions in the Medicare physician fee schedule,” Foster writes. What he means is that Medicare’s reimbursements to doctors are scheduled to drop by 31 percent on January 1, 2013. Only then is Medicare solvent until 2016/2024. If Congress passes another of its numerous “doc fixes,” Medicare’s insolvency will be even closer at hand. The optimistic insolvency estimate from the Trustees will require “unprecedented changes in health care delivery systems and payment mechanisms,” without which Medicare fees “are very likely to fall increasingly short of the costs of providing those services.” “For these reasons, the financial projections shown in this report for Medicare do not represent a reasonable expectation for actual program operations in either the short range…or the long range,” writes Foster. I wrote about this problem last March: how calculations of Medicare’s solvency assume drastic reductions to Medicare’s fee schedules, reductions that would cripple the ability of retirees to gain access to medical care. If we can’t even be honest about Medicare’s finances, how can we hope to ever reform the program? Follow Avik on Twitter at @aviksaroy. UPDATE 1: Chris Jacobs makes the following relevant points at his Freedom on Call blog: Insolvency One Year Closer: Contrary to predictions made in this space this morning, the insolvency date for the Medicare Hospital Insurance Trust Fund remains at 2024 – despite the 2% sequester cuts scheduled to take effect beginning in January. In other words, if not for the sequester cuts insisted on by Congress, Medicare’s financial stability would have deteriorated even further. As it is, we’re still one year closer to Medicare running out of IOUs to cash in to pay its bills (see #3 below). Obama Economy Making It Worse: As the Associated Press noted, “Social Security’s finances worsened” – and Medicare’s finances did not improve, sequester notwithstanding – “in part because high energy prices suppressed wages, a trend the trustees see as continuing. The trustees said they expect workers to work fewer hours than previously projected, even after the economy recovers.” President Obama’s poor economic record is not only harming workers today, it will harm future generations – seniors in current entitlement programs that are less secure, and children and grandchildren forced to pay the bills for skyrocketing spending – for decades to come. Deficits as Far as the Eye Can See: The report once again confirms that the Medicare program is already contributing to the federal deficit, will continue to do so throughout the coming decade, and forever thereafter. Since 2008, the program has run cash flow deficits; this year’s deficit is expected to total $28.9 billion. The only thing keeping the program afloat financially is the sale of Treasury bonds in the Medicare Trust Fund – and the redemption of those paper IOUs increases the federal deficit. Funding Warning: For the seventh straight year, the trustees issued a funding warning showing that the Medicare program is taking a disproportionate share of its funding from general revenues, thus crowding out programs like defense and education. While in theory this development should prompt the President to follow his statutory requirement to submit legislation remedying this funding shortfall, the White House has previously refused to do so – relying instead on a signing statement by President Bush to ignore the need for Medicare reform (and also breaking the President’s campaign promises in the process). Unrealistic Assumptions: For the third straight year since the passage of Obamacare, the report features a statement of actuarial opinion by the non-partisan Medicare actuary (pages 277-279 of the report), who says “the financial projections shown in this report…do not represent a reasonable expectation for actual program operations.” The actuary will again issue an alternative scenario for Medicare’s unfunded obligations that he views as more realistic, because the major source of Medicare payment reductions in Obamacare may not be sustained over a long period of time. Double Counting: The actuary also previously confirmed that the Medicare reductions in Obamacare “cannot be simultaneously used to finance other federal outlays and to extend the [Medicare] trust fund” solvency date – rendering dubious any potential claims that Obamacare will extend Medicare’s solvency. As Speaker Pelosi admitted last year, Democrats “took a half a trillion dollars out of Medicare in [Obamacare], the health care bill” – and you can’t improve Medicare’s solvency by taking money out of the program. Massive Tax Increases: Today’s report again confirms that Medicare’s finances are also being bolstered by the extension of the health care law’s “high-income” tax – which is NOT indexed for inflation – to more and more individuals over time. Page 30 of the report notes that “by the end of the long-range projection period, an estimated 80 percent of workers would pay the higher tax rate.” As JEC recently reported, these tax increases are part of the $4 trillion in “revenue enhancements” over the next 25 years taking place thanks to Obamacare. When Democrats talk about raising taxes to reduce the deficit, keep in mind that they have already raised taxes in a way that will harm middle-class families over time – and that those tax increases were used not to reduce the deficit but to pay for new and unsustainable entitlements. Seniors Losing Coverage, Part I: Table IV.C1 of the report notes that millions of seniors will lose their current Medicare Advantage plans – enrollment is projected to fall from 13.5 million this year to 9.7 million by 2017. However, thanks to the waiver/demonstration program announced by the Administration, and criticized by the Government Accountability Office in a report this morning, enrollment in Medicare Advantage will not begin falling until after the President has completed his re-election campaign. Seniors Losing Coverage, Part II: Table IV.B10 of the report re-stated prior projections that enrollment in employer-sponsored retiree drug plans will fall from 6.8 million in 2010 to a mere 800,000 by 2016 – a drop of nearly 90%. This rapid decrease in enrollment occurs thanks to provisions in Obamacare that raise taxes on employers who continue to offer retiree drug coverage.</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349247147320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349247781599-11</Id><Title>when the American people find out that the media lead them down the road to doom the media companys will pay....yes abc nbc cbs and msnbc socialist SOBs!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>you messed with the Americans...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349247781599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349248270236-12</Id><Topic><Title>when the American people find out that the media lead them down the road to doom the media companys will pay....yes abc nbc cbs and msnbc socialist SOBs!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349247781599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree they will have done something the soviet union and now the terrorists haven't been able to do destroy America from within. They know the bankruptcies loom but the radicals who want social upheaval are winning. They want to destroy what's left of America's Judeo Christian base and rule of law we were founded upon. There is still hope but with each passing election chance at real change and the continued mounting debt, hope fades....</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349248270236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349249967491-13</Id><Topic><Title>when the American people find out that the media lead them down the road to doom the media companys will pay....yes abc nbc cbs and msnbc socialist SOBs!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349247781599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm glade there is someone else that understands</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349249967491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349251039094-14</Id><Topic><Title>Could California be the first state to go Bankrupt?</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349246733637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cal is the state of the queers...so I hope all the MFers eat chit and die...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349251039094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349261424107-15</Id><Title>This Election, Remove And Replace Republicans In Congress..The Destroy America For An Election..</Title><Msg>The Republicans have done 1,000 times more damage to this country than Osama bin Laden, The (R) after the name means Remove and Replace. The do nothing Republicans in Congress are the only reason why this country is slow to recover. A Romney president will tax the middle class to death, retired will pay more for medical care, the rich will get richer, more people will lose their homes to wall street investors.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349261424107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349263910431-16</Id><Topic><Title>OK Democrats show your support of Eric Holder</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1327706104000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-01-27 18:15:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Osama Bin Laden had kept his head buried, he would have been better off than he is today...</Msg><Username>therwnjneedhelp</Username><Timestamp>1349263910431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349264492414-17</Id><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Msg>Republicans in Congress are holding back voting on bills that would create more than 5 Million Jobs. They will continue to destroy this country. Remove and Replace All those Republicans NOW, the future of this country depends on it. President Obama wants every American working and keeping their homes, Republicans want lower home values and stop paying unemployment. Republicans will remove our Mortgage tax deduction, kill Medicare, kill Medicaid and kill our young children in another war with Iran next. Republicans destroyed this country and put it 11 Trillion dollars in debt, President Obama has to pay $1 Trillion more every year to pay for things passed by Bush and his republicans. We made a big mistake in 2010 and we Need Change, Vote out Republicans in Congress and move this country forward.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349264546376-18</Id><Title>Living on cradle to grave family money is no way to go through life Mitt!</Title><Msg>It puts you so out of touch with us "rabble" out here on the fruited plain!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1349264546376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349264567384-19</Id><Topic><Title>A lady came up to me today and told me to vote for Obama so I can get my free Obama-phone</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349235710874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and a bottle of thunderbird</Msg><Username>drunken_derelict_99</Username><Timestamp>1349264567384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349264803598-20</Id><Topic><Title>Could California be the first state to go Bankrupt?</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349246733637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If California made it through Bush and his Enron 1,000 percent increase in power costs, they are not going bankrupt now. California still has debt from Enron, if Republicans win this election, California should go bankrupt on all those Republicans holding their debt.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264803598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267007523-21</Id><Topic><Title>Legality of Romney's Offshore Investments Questionable</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349123704843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Investors maintain offshore accounts to avoid paying taxes. Romney has accounts in the Cayman Islands, Switzerland, Belgium, Bermuda, and who knows where else? No knows where else because he refuses to disclose his records.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349267007523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349267184384-22</Id><Title>Anyone adding to their short on the pop at the open?</Title><Msg>thoughts??</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349267184384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349267209696-23</Id><Title>All the law suits involving country wide ,actions before I invested or even knew. Why should I be responsible for that debt.</Title><Msg>Before I lost 40,000 If I sell. Should have came with a warning Before I invested.Investors from 2005 thru 2008 have a chance of getting my money. Exactly where does fair begin and being robbed end. Is anyone in the same boat.</Msg><Username>horsence</Username><Timestamp>1349267209696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267488516-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney, a Friend of the Middle Class?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349120376296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 15:39:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another NEO-NAZI COWARD making threats.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349267488516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267712541-25</Id><Topic><Title>A lady came up to me today and told me to vote for Obama so I can get my free Obama-phone</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349235710874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:41:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate the liberal networks worse than Obama</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349267712541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267757433-26</Id><Topic><Title>OK Democrats show your support of Eric Holder</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1327706104000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-01-27 18:15:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder and Obama should be thrown in prison</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349267757433</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267822634-27</Id><Topic><Title>Trustees: Medicare Will Go Broke in 2016, If You Exclude Obamacare's Double-Counting</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349247147320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:52:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama doesn't care his goal is to destroy the US by pushing us into a debt crisis and then declare himself dictator after the collapse</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349267822634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267833547-28</Id><Topic><Title>The only thing missing from the Romney campaign is the death knell</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1348613659336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's lead in the big number swing states easily gives him another four years.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349267833547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267896411-29</Id><Topic><Title>when the American people find out that the media lead them down the road to doom the media companys will pay....yes abc nbc cbs and msnbc socialist SOBs!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1349247781599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The liberal networks should be sued and real Americans should take their place</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349267896411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349267909169-30</Id><Title>The national debt was $10.7 trillion when Obama took office and has increased by nearly 50 percent in less than four years.</Title><Msg>This is what socialism does for you...Obama's "just put it on my bill" attitude toward spending tax payer monies (Czars, Comrade Valarie Jarrett's full security detail, Michelle's staff, ad infinitum) is the major problem. Count of class warfare in 2013 when Democrats attempt to fund all this crap by taxing the 53 percent of people who pay no INCOME TAX and raising taxes on the taxes the 47 percent pay via (just take your pick): Tax his land, Tax his wage, Tax his bed in which he lays. Tax his tractor, Tax his mule, Teach him taxes is the rule. Tax his cow, Tax his goat, Tax his pants, Tax his coat. Tax his ties, Tax his shirts, Tax his work, Tax his dirt. Tax his tobacco, Tax his drink, Tax him if he tries to think. Tax his booze, Tax his beers, If he cries, Tax his tears. Tax his bills, Tax his gas, Tax his notes, Tax his cash. Tax him good and let him know That after taxes, he has no dough. If he hollers, Tax him more, Tax him until he's good and sore. Tax his coffin, Tax his grave, Tax the sod in which he lays. Put these words upon his tomb, "Taxes drove me to my doom!" And when he's gone, We won't relax, We'll still be after the inheritance TAX!! Accounts Receivable Tax Building Permit Tax CDL License Tax Cigarette Tax Corporate Income Tax Dog License Tax Federal Income Tax Federal Unemployment Tax (FUTA) Fishing License Tax Food License Tax Fuel Permit Tax Gasoline Tax Hunting License Tax Inheritance Tax Inventory Tax IRS Interest Charges (tax on top of tax), IRS Penalties (tax on top of tax), Liquor Tax, Luxury Tax, Marriage License Tax, Medicare Tax, Property Tax, Real Estate Tax, Service charge taxes, Social Security Tax, Road Usage Tax (Truckers), Sales Taxes, Recreational Vehicle Tax, School Tax, State Income Tax, State Unemployment Tax (SUTA), Telephone Federal Excise Tax, Telephone Federal Universal Service Fee Tax, Telephone Federal, State and Local Surcharge Tax, Telephone Minimum Usage Surcharge Tax, Telephone Recurring and Non-recurring Charges Tax, Telephone State and Local Tax, Telephone Usage Charge Tax, Utility Tax, Vehicle License Registration Tax, Vehicle Sales Tax, Watercraft Registration Tax, Well Permit Tax, Workers Compensation Tax. COMMENTS: Not one of these taxes existed 100 years ago and there was prosperity, absolutely no national debt, the largest middle class in the world and Mom stayed home to raise the kids.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349267909169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267981495-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Does NOTHING but want to raise spending in the face of Medicare going BANKRUPT in 2016-2020...Social Security going BANKRUPT in 2023-2030</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349247010957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:50:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His plan is working great. Obama wants to cause a debt panic and then declare himself dictator just like Chavez did. Watch and see</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349267981495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349268068261-32</Id><Topic><Title>Social Security predicted to go BANKRUPT sooner than forecasted........its time for Obama's lack of leadership to GO!!</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349245605364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 02:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its all a part of Obama's plan. He wants turmoil and suffering and then declare himself dictator amid the chaos</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349268068261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268210930-33</Id><Title>How do democrat pollsters operate? Example - pollster</Title><Msg>for John Edwards admitted under oath that he cherry picked data that would help Edwards in ’08 to keep campaign donations coming in – even though he knew Edwards nomination was dead in the water. This explains how they show polls giving 0bama a slight lead using only 160 people across America. LOL</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268210930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349268220531-34</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrite Mitt the Chickenhawk</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1348393494190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 05:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt's father, George, did not serve during WWII, and none of Mitt's five sons, all of age, ever served. it pays to be a family of privilege.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349268220531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268348096-35</Id><Title>Univision continues coverage of Fast &amp; Furious scandal. While</Title><Msg>the mass media tries to hide the deadly program, Univision is digging and investigating why more than 2,000 Hispanics were murdered under 0bama &amp; Holders decision to provide illegal weapons to Mexican cartels knowing full well that innocent Hispanics would be murdered. Univision wants answers and those responsible to get justice. Hoorah for Univision!</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268348096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268515774-36</Id><Title>*Warning* If Obama wins he will never leave office *never*</Title><Msg>His goal and plan is to push the US into a debt panic and collapse. He will declare himself dictator amid the chaos and people will go along with it out of fear and starvation. I am telling you Obmaa is the reincarnation of Stalin</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349268515774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268687673-37</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268687673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268687907-38</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268687907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268688673-39</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268688673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268688732-40</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268688732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268709104-41</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268709104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268709446-42</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268709446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268709587-43</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268709587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268709913-44</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268709913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268710141-45</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268710141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268710441-46</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268710441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268710763-47</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268710763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268711085-48</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268711085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268711532-49</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268711532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268711864-50</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268711864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268711972-51</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268711972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268722163-52</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268722163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268722497-53</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268722497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268722803-54</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268722803</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268722892-55</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268722892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268723194-56</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268723194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268723360-57</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268723360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268723616-58</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268723616</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268724142-59</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268724142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268724419-60</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268724419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268724646-61</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268724646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268724835-62</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268724835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268725117-63</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268725117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268725422-64</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268725422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268725656-65</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268725656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268726021-66</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268726021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349268727510-67</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268727510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349268919453-68</Id><Topic><Title>Univision continues coverage of Fast &amp; Furious scandal. While</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268348096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Univision is exposing the coverup ordered by the White House and Attorney General Holder.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268919453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269045847-69</Id><Topic><Title>The national debt was $10.7 trillion when Obama took office and has increased by nearly 50 percent in less than four years.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349267909169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:38:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama has to pay $1 trillion more per year to pay for things passed by Bush and his republicans, Why don't congress cancel everything passed under Bush?</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349269045847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269059849-70</Id><Topic><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $15</Title><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349268727510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:52:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>next stop 11.25-11.75 area</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349269059849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269160411-71</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is time to right the mistake of the 2010 elections, those republicans must go!</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349269160411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269190491-72</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Admits middle class has been "buried" last 4 yrs</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349234139604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he is the smart one of the pair</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349269190491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349269370133-73</Id><Title>"bry345" REPORTED TO YAHOO</Title><Msg>STUPID AS</Msg><Username>dancingjoos</Username><Timestamp>1349269370133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269392652-74</Id><Topic><Title>IT'S A SHAME THAT AMBASSADOR STEVENS HAD TO DIE TO HIGHLIGHT THE UTTER INCOMPETENCE OF OBAMA</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349212743796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems and muslims are one in the same</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349269392652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269418463-75</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $6.75...Up again.......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings......Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues…..Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions</Title><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348494154477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:42:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incredible chart. It looks like it's heading to $10+ before expected record 1Q earnings per guidance in about a month. Analysts average target is $16/share</Msg><Username>jonny.deener</Username><Timestamp>1349269418463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269444586-76</Id><Topic><Title>Legality of Romney's Offshore Investments Questionable</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1349123704843</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will never show 2009 Tax Returns, He must have taken the swiss bank account amnesty. Romney hides his money from paying taxes and people want this guy to be our president??? We will lose our Mortgage deduction if Romney were president, no way..</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349269444586</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269558356-77</Id><Topic><Title>This Election, Remove And Replace Republicans In Congress..The Destroy America For An Election..</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349261424107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will take the next 2 elections to get rid of those republicans, remove and replace congress is a must.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349269558356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349269654218-78</Id><Title>Libyan Embassy officials asked numerous times for extra security prior to our U.S. Ambassadors murder. But</Title><Msg>the White House and Hillary Clinton denied their motions. And those few security officials there were not allowed to be armed under orders by 0bama and the State Dept. The body count piles up under Obama's pro-jihadist policy. The attack on our embassy was an act of war. The slaughter of our US ambassador and three diplomats was an act of war. The President blamed America. The President blamed the Constitution. Obama blamed the first amendment. This is high treason. The enemedia exalts treason as patriotism, while demonizing freedom lovers and patriots. America, it is past midnight. “Based on information provided to the Committee by individuals with direct knowledge of events in Libya, the attack that claimed the ambassador’s life was the latest in a long line of attacks on Western diplomats and officials in Libya in the months leading up to September 11, 2012,” “Multiple U.S. federal government officials have confirmed to the Committee that, prior to the September 11 attack, the U.S. mission in Libya made repeated requests for increased security in Benghazi,” “The mission in Libya, however, was denied these resources by officials in Washington.” The committee noted 13 “security threats” in Benghazi, including an attempt to assassinate the British ambassador to Libya.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269654218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269724951-79</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCAN SUPPORTERS SHOULD GET A BRAIN TRANSPLANT</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349229806780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 22:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans have alzheimers, they forget who destroyed this country and who in congress are holding back this country now... Republicans need better medication</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349269724951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269773144-80</Id><Topic><Title>Univision continues coverage of Fast &amp; Furious scandal. While</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268348096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The wall of secrecy is cracking....</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269773144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269781420-81</Id><Topic><Title>The best way to take down Romney is to let him keep talking</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1348660771141</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 07:59:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...as stupid says</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349269781420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269895059-82</Id><Topic><Title>Libyan Embassy officials asked numerous times for extra security prior to our U.S. Ambassadors murder. But</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269654218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:07:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You think 0bama &amp; Hillary refused security because the Ambassador was gay? Hmmm</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269895059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269931130-83</Id><Topic><Title>This Election, Remove And Replace Republicans In Congress..The Destroy America For An Election..</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349261424107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a must. The nation will never have an opportunity to heal from the damage caused by Republicans unless they are removed from both houses.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349269931130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269960403-84</Id><Topic><Title>"bry345" REPORTED TO YAHOO</Title><Username>dancingjoos</Username><Timestamp>1349269370133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:02:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck with THAT! Yahoo's "Customer Service Team" is as do-nothing as bry345 is prolific. ROTFLMAO while you're at it, ask them why they think we need to see a comprehensive listing of all the chowderheads we've put on "Ignore".</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349269960403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270112304-85</Id><Topic><Title>Liar Tea Baggers NEVER post about anything about Romney. Are they ashamed of their liberal republican candidate?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348559143486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 03:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The funded campaign to demean Obama has failed. He will be re-elected.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349270112304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270174207-86</Id><Title>BAC to $15</Title><Msg>BAC toi $15</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270174207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270201422-87</Id><Title>BAC to $16</Title><Msg>BAC to $16</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270201422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270354448-88</Id><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Msg>You gotta check out this article which provides some technical information . I wanted to share this with everyone Copy and Paste the link to your browser. --- y.ahoo.it/6iS/y</Msg><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>26</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270362093-89</Id><Title>lets put it this way Whom would you intrust with your retirement funds</Title><Msg>Romney or Obama?</Msg><Username>winkdog</Username><Timestamp>1349270362093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270398828-90</Id><Title>BAC to $17</Title><Msg>BAC to $17</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270398828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270466734-91</Id><Topic><Title>Libyan Embassy officials asked numerous times for extra security prior to our U.S. Ambassadors murder. But</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269654218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:07:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is the mass media hiding from the People?</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349270466734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270512951-92</Id><Title>BAC to $18</Title><Msg>BAC to $18</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270512951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270523199-93</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Baggers call themselves tea baggers because...? Look it up in the online Urban Dictionary</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1348292396602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perverted goons</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1349270523199</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270530146-94</Id><Topic><Title>"bry345" REPORTED TO YAHOO</Title><Username>dancingjoos</Username><Timestamp>1349269370133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:02:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet he is scared!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349270530146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270541082-95</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270541082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270541583-96</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270541583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270541620-97</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270541620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270541938-98</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270541938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270542211-99</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270542211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270542322-100</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270542322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270542507-101</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270542507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270543022-102</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270543022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270543401-103</Id><Title>BAC the boring bank.....on the way to $19</Title><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270543401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270625465-104</Id><Topic><Title>*Warning* If Obama wins he will never leave office *never*</Title><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349268515774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't say much for the citizenry of that were the case, would it?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349270625465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270682040-105</Id><Title>Yahoo probably pays bry345 to clean up the board from the political garbage</Title><Msg>IMHO</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349270682040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270867676-106</Id><Topic><Title>BAC to $17</Title><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270398828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you are bald and grey, and your gonads are shriveled up.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1349270867676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349270954642-107</Id><Topic><Title>Libyan Embassy officials asked numerous times for extra security prior to our U.S. Ambassadors murder. But</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349269654218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:07:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Big problem is the Host Country Provides Security for any Embassy property, Libya Failed to do that job. Right now the FBI can't even get to that Embassy to investigate the killings of 4 Americans. Stop all the money we send to any country that can't protect Americans, the worthless people we have in Congress would never stop sending them our Tax Money.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349270954642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271089279-108</Id><Topic><Title>Liar Tea Baggers NEVER post about anything about Romney. Are they ashamed of their liberal republican candidate?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348559143486</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 03:45:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Healthcare or Romney Healthcare, it's all the same</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349271089279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271211480-109</Id><Topic><Title>This Election, Remove And Replace Republicans In Congress..The Destroy America For An Election..</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349261424107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress could have put an end to everything passed under Bush and get rid of the extra 1 trillion dollars per year that was added to the U.S. budget.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349271211480</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349271354082-110</Id><Title>Half of Congress is Democrat. The senate is controlled by Democrats you fool</Title><Msg>watch Msnbc too much and listen to libtard propaganda. Harry Reid should resign in disgrace and democrats should be taken to prison for illegally ramming through Obamacare</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349271354082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271448564-111</Id><Topic><Title>Univision continues coverage of Fast &amp; Furious scandal. While</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349268348096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are outside the tightly controlled obama run media in america</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349271448564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271481317-112</Id><Topic><Title>*Warning* If Obama wins he will never leave office *never*</Title><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349268515774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People do desperate things when fearing violence and starvation</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349271481317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349271519466-113</Id><Title>WOW... BAC crashed. I only show 5 posts then all the rest "topic hidden"</Title><Msg>not only has bac crashed but tis board is crashed also</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1349271519466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:38:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271775045-114</Id><Topic><Title>*Warning* If Obama wins he will never leave office *never*</Title><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349268515774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:48:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they did, then why would he never leave office? Think about what you are saying. They would throw him out, right?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349271775045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271846315-115</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo probably pays bry345 to clean up the board from the political garbage</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349270682040</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:24:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what a good job he does!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349271846315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349271863854-116</Id><Title>Fox News: ALL of the swing states have turned BLUE . . . , AND, Obama continues to gain.</Title><Msg>We saw it on Fox, so it must be true. RFLMFAO!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349271863854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272137172-117</Id><Topic><Title>REPUCAN SUPPORTERS SHOULD GET A BRAIN TRANSPLANT</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349229806780</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 22:03:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>War with Iran is for sure if Romney gets in. Republicans have no value for the lives of Americans</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349272137172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272154545-118</Id><Topic><Title>Lemming dumpobamie can't stop barking at the moon. Hard to stop lying? Denial? Loser syndrome?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1349203361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama continues to gain. dumpobamie continues to lie.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349272154545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272174106-119</Id><Title>What happened to Glenn Beck? Haven's seen him for a while.</Title><Msg>Does anyone know? I've heard that they fixed his brain, and he has nothing to say now.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349272174106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272257571-120</Id><Title>Investors have lost more money on NY Atty Gen political aspiration than MBS</Title><Msg>These guys would happily destroy billions in investor wealth just to make a name for themselves. Attorney Generals from both political parties have done it .. it's Pathetic!</Msg><Username>tenmilevol</Username><Timestamp>1349272257571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272288680-121</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lying is an obsession with the baggers. They can't stop.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349272288680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272295889-122</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those Tea Party Republicans are Holding Americans Hostage, they destroy America, we will destroy their keystone pipeline, Anything republicans vote for , Americans can destroy.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349272295889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272359871-123</Id><Topic><Title>BAC to $17</Title><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270398828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this months earnings will put it over 11.</Msg><Username>slegermark</Username><Timestamp>1349272359871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272415222-124</Id><Topic><Title>Hey LOSER waste of meat Tea Baggerss: HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA!!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349191482034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:24:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They live to lie.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349272415222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272490202-125</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to Glenn Beck? Haven's seen him for a while.</Title><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349272174106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His mother killed herself jumping off a boat, his half brother killed himself knowing is was half of Glenn Beck, We are all waiting for Glenn to kill himself, Go on Fox, DO IT LIVE</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349272490202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272506056-126</Id><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Msg>Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349272506056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272546999-127</Id><Title>TO MANY PUKES PIRATES POSTING HERE OUTTA OF HERE!</Title><Msg>ONE EYE ROMNEY</Msg><Username>dancingjoos</Username><Timestamp>1349272546999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272573491-128</Id><Topic><Title>Lemming dumpobamie can't stop barking at the moon. Hard to stop lying? Denial? Loser syndrome?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1349203361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liar dumpobamie needs a cure. Anybody got a cattle prod?</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349272573491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272647026-129</Id><Title>WS=organized crime all the QE money vanishing</Title><Msg>wheres it going? any guesses? it's going in someones pockets lol the naked short front run is on..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1349272647026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272735747-130</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to Glenn Beck? Haven's seen him for a while.</Title><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349272174106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He still has a vetry loyal following and he is making more money than he ever did by streaming direclty to them.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349272735747</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349272793726-131</Id><Topic><Title>Homeland Security on guard for "Right Wing Extremists"</Title><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346207519429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bagger goon roaches are making threats. Get ready to step on them.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349272793726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273139147-132</Id><Title>Rabid goon Tea Bagger roaches are making threats. Be ready to stomp them.</Title><Msg>Obama's victory may push the rapid Tea Bagger roaches over the edge. Be ready to eradicate them.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349273139147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273218647-133</Id><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Msg>Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight.</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349273218647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273422762-134</Id><Topic><Title>Lemming dumpobamie can't stop barking at the moon. Hard to stop lying? Denial? Loser syndrome?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1349203361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody got a gag?</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349273422762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273526276-135</Id><Topic><Title>BAC to $17</Title><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1349270398828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like you are now beatle juice..move out of your mothers house are you ashamed..</Msg><Username>mrggecko</Username><Timestamp>1349273526276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273551805-136</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clever Boy! You got the idea! Obama WILL be around until 2016!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349273551805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273787986-137</Id><Title>CRAP! FRIGGIN JPM NOTE PUMPING BAC IS GOING TO KILL MY SHORT..I"M COVERED</Title><Msg>LOSERS</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349273787986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273917949-138</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News: ALL of the swing states have turned BLUE . . . , AND, Obama continues to gain.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349271863854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shell shocked dumpobamie remains in denial ... Obama wins AGAIN!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349273917949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273933154-139</Id><Title>oboma blames sex tape</Title><Msg>msnbc reports oboma has blamed a leaked sex tape of him and barney frank and rachel madcow for causing the recent violence in the mideast.</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1349273933154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273939545-140</Id><Title>JPM WON'T STOP PUMPING BAC UNTIL IT HITS $10</Title><Msg>UNFAIR MANIPULATION</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349273939545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274091274-141</Id><Topic><Title>Lemming dumpobamie can't stop barking at the moon. Hard to stop lying? Denial? Loser syndrome?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1349203361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumpobamie: got any threats to add to your twaddle?</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349274091274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:21:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274121521-142</Id><Title>Did you just see that huge Oct 10 call buy! whoa</Title><Msg>some big whale building a huge position</Msg><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349274121521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274262278-143</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks! nice share.</Msg><Username>baileylvf466701</Username><Timestamp>1349274262278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274335392-144</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Baggers will either go down or up in flames. Either way..., let them BURN!</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349185997883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want to borrow my lighter?</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349274335392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274581630-145</Id><Topic><Title>Homeland Security on guard for "Right Wing Extremists"</Title><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346207519429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 22:31:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HA HA...All the lefties will tossed out of the Gov't in January...it'll take a year to clean out all the cockroaches</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349274581630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274606580-146</Id><Topic><Title>Crack Money over at PZE....she's smokin</Title><Username>computerfixuper</Username><Timestamp>1349111392215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 13:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This company just did a 2 for 1 split. should have bought</Msg><Username>computerfixuper</Username><Timestamp>1349274606580</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349274693740-147</Id><Title>Anybody know how much BAC would go up if FHFA limits BAC mortgage liability</Title><Msg>thoughts?</Msg><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349274693740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:31:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274849001-148</Id><Topic><Title>This Election, Remove And Replace Republicans In Congress..The Destroy America For An Election..</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349261424107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 06:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The much needed changes proposed by Obama will be much easier to implement with a Democrat house and senate.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349274849001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349275295269-149</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>informative indeed.</Msg><Username>edelmiravmf82024</Username><Timestamp>1349275295269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349275361209-150</Id><Title>Bullish retail charts: DECK BBBY WSM</Title><Msg>Retail expected to be up 4% yoy. GLTA</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1349275361209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349275533718-151</Id><Title>Dr. Barbara Bellar – Obamacare Summed Up in One Sentence</Title><Msg>We’re going to be gifted with a healthcare plan we are forced to purchase, and fined if we don’t, which puportedly covers at least 10 million more people, without adding a single new doctor, but provides for 16,000 new IRS agents, written by a committee whose chairman says he doesn’t understand it, passed by a congress that didn’t read it but exempted themselves from it, and signed by a president who smokes, with funding administered by a treasury chief who didn’t pay his taxes, for which we will be taxed for four years before any benefits take effect, by a government which has already bankrupted social security and medicare, all to be overseen by a surgeon general who is obese and and financed by a country that’s broke. So, what the blank could possibly go wrong?</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349275533718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349275688987-152</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Baggers will either go down or up in flames. Either way..., let them BURN!</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349185997883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up to now, I didn't know who I would vote for. Thanks for the insite. Tea Baggers here I come. See you at the unemployment line!</Msg><Username>m.inally</Username><Timestamp>1349275688987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276020974-153</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are looking for some new short term opportunities that are poised for growth, this is the newsletter for you!!!</Msg><Username>vargasboris55</Username><Timestamp>1349276020974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276066650-154</Id><Title>tv ads</Title><Msg>when will do something about so many tv ads?</Msg><Username>dickkim</Username><Timestamp>1349276066650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276107512-155</Id><Title>Who's dumber?..Felix "Fartaway" Faraway or Joe Biden?</Title><Msg>The specimen we study, mostly Democrats, have declared a tie as to who is dumber, Fartaway or Joe. Both have room temperature IQ's, the specime said.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1349276107512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276249387-156</Id><Title>Stock Alerts $BAC $AONE $AXPW $AUMY $FB</Title><Msg>............</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349276249387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276350776-157</Id><Topic><Title>Who's dumber?..Felix "Fartaway" Faraway or Joe Biden?</Title><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1349276107512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:55:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another illiterate white trash fool's attempt at humor. Try again later when you have completed the 3rd grade, fool.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349276350776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276387940-158</Id><Title>rumor</Title><Msg>3rd qtr earnings .37 per share</Msg><Username>sly_foxx_93</Username><Timestamp>1349276387940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276544467-159</Id><Title>Who said, "I'm voting Republican, the Democrats left a bad taste in my mouth"?</Title><Msg>Monica Lewinski.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349276544467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276607282-160</Id><Topic><Title>Did you just see that huge Oct 10 call buy! whoa</Title><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349274121521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oct 20 $9's and $10's running hot, eh?</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349276607282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349276659166-161</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he wants to help the middle class .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349274411836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumpy, like the sheep that you are,being lead to slaughter you believe all the right wing #$%$. The work requirement is still being enforced but the program is being tried at a state level for some states.</Msg><Username>acerdaprod</Username><Timestamp>1349276659166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277064242-162</Id><Topic><Title>Did you just see that huge Oct 10 call buy! whoa</Title><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349274121521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought 100 contracts(call) at 24 cents yesterday. I wish I had bought 500 contracts instead. As soon as the S&amp;P hits 1,450, this stock will be ready to fly. BAC is coiled up for too long. It will spring to action soon!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349277064242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277091957-163</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he wants to help the middle class .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349274411836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...check it out, fool. Then get a life, FOOL!</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349277091957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277190391-164</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good info.</Msg><Username>racquelnfw8261</Username><Timestamp>1349277190391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277311925-165</Id><Title>BAC settlement rumour with gov. must be true...calls are being scooped up like candy</Title><Msg>$10 very soon</Msg><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349277311925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277678070-166</Id><Title>Republican attempts to keep registered Democrats from voting FAILS.</Title><Msg>One of the more obvious Republican dirty tricks have failed. Their attempts to block registered Democrats from voting in Pennsylvania and Mississippi have been thwarted by the courts.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349277678070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277831084-167</Id><Topic><Title>BAC settlement rumour with gov. must be true...calls are being scooped up like candy</Title><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349277311925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:15:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweeeeet! Only a fool would not scope up some shares at 50% discount from book value. Banks are making huge profits!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349277831084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277894398-168</Id><Title>BAM!! Sabrient rates BAC strong BUY..NICE</Title><Msg>go bac!</Msg><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1349277894398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349277904258-169</Id><Topic><Title>IT'S A SHAME THAT AMBASSADOR STEVENS HAD TO DIE TO HIGHLIGHT THE UTTER INCOMPETENCE OF OBAMA</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349212743796</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:19:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YUP!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1349277904258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349278018337-170</Id><Topic><Title>The only thing missing from the Romney campaign is the death knell</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1348613659336</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:54:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most damage done to Romney is when he opens his mouth. The debates will put him out of his misery.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349278018337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349278213098-171</Id><Title>The most damage done to Romney is when he opens his mouth. Bring on the debates!</Title><Msg>The more Romey opens his mouth, the more Obama gains in the polls.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349278213098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349278499587-172</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>haydeerjz96669</Username><Timestamp>1349278499587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349278499624-173</Id><Topic><Title>What happened to Glenn Beck? Haven's seen him for a while.</Title><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349272174106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be nice.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349278499624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349278678568-174</Id><Title>Why would anyone use the screen name "Bury Obama?" Could they be a racist neo-nazi?</Title><Msg>Could they be a white trash fascist fool?</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349278678568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349278763589-175</Id><Title>12 years ago Bush promissed cars that will run on water.</Title><Msg>My wife said it's a stupid idea because humidity will go up. But where are they? Takes 12 years to build a car? You just can't trust republicans.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349278763589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279074753-176</Id><Title>ARO ISPOPPING. CROSSING MOVING AVERAGE. $14 SOON WATCH</Title><Msg>Aro is popping crossing today moving average. Big new highs are coming soon. It will cross 14 today</Msg><Username>byuzorro</Username><Timestamp>1349279074753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279160779-177</Id><Title>HOW CAN OBAMA WIN GVEN HIS HORRIBLE JOB PERFORMANCE??</Title><Msg>Obama can win because the USA now has more takers than doers. The USA is an Entitlement country like the lazy Italians.</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1349279160779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279500417-178</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>romanroman79</Username><Timestamp>1349279500417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279583304-179</Id><Title>Shorts...</Title><Msg>In case if have not receive the memo, you have until 10 a.m. to cover. This is your last warning.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349279583304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279622915-180</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he wants to help the middle class .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349274411836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep helping middle class by giving more money to banks. Why cant he give stimulus to the taxpayers just like Bush used to.</Msg><Username>repreja</Username><Timestamp>1349279622915</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279794873-181</Id><Title>YOU are middle class,vote that way unless you are stupid and uninformed.</Title><Msg>Get rid of all GOP in nov</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349279794873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280282526-182</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cut it with the garbage, you don't even know what the hell a small cap stock is.</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1349280282526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349280506862-183</Id><Title>Only a racist, fringe-right goon would call himself "Whitest White."</Title><Msg>The board is infested with neo-nazi #$%$.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349280506862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280729885-184</Id><Topic><Title>7.75% yield, government backed preferred</Title><Username>instantwinbutton</Username><Timestamp>1349194445084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 12:14:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>instantwinbutton</Username><Timestamp>1349280729885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280929188-185</Id><Topic><Title>$9 line</Title><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349187979153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:26:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like the way the intraday action has been shaping up today. Bid now $9.07. There's no "moon shot" urgency about the rise, just slow and gradual. A good sign. And the $9 line appears to be (finally) forming up as support. An even better sign. And there's even fairly large volume on the Oct 20 $9 &amp; $10 Calls. Along with this all the TA is signaling a buy side turn, so it seems all the stars are now lining up if'n yer a buyer. Let's see how the rest of the week goes.</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349280929188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349280991661-186</Id><Title>NEED EVERYONE TO SHORT HERE</Title><Msg>SHORTTTTTT!</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349280991661</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281040218-187</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts...</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349279583304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In about 44 minutes, shorts will begin to move from PV (Palo Verdes, CA) to SUV. lol</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349281040218</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281078225-188</Id><Title>LISTEN TO ME...SHORT HERE AND MAKE MONEY</Title><Msg>SHORTTTTT</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281078225</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281222991-189</Id><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Msg>WHY BOTHER</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281378841-190</Id><Title>WHY BUY BAC IF YOUR MAX UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Msg>SHORTING IS BETTER</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281378841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281488654-191</Id><Topic><Title>Only a racist, fringe-right goon would call himself "Whitest White."</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349280506862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:08:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's more a case of the few fringe-right minority being too loud and repetitive on a terrorist mission. Soon they will have to stop after a landslide win by the President. Take it easy... and look at it as entertainment. They serve as catalyst for decent folks to stay alert and aware that there are such low lives who have nothing else to do but reveal the evil they represent. Dogs bark when the caravan goes forward.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349281488654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281710861-192</Id><Topic><Title>WHY BUY BAC IF YOUR MAX UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281378841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm both trader and investor. BAC is good for traders as well as for holding it and lt. Being flexible and nimble is the way. Make the best of what the market is giving you at this time. GLTA</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349281710861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281734724-193</Id><Topic><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never? Never speak in absolutes. It tends to spoil yer verbal performance metrics. HEH!</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349281734724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281896164-194</Id><Topic><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And btw... never say never. It only gels your mindset and could even cause you to do the wrong thing at the wrong time. Hang loose and maximize the opportunity at this time. Life happens only in the present.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349281896164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349282350410-195</Id><Topic><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not the greatest idea man......should be the new title and user ID for that matter. No worries notgreatestideaman. Go get yourself a XL GMCR Morning burst coffee and relax.LOL IMHO</Msg><Username>cwoolrey</Username><Timestamp>1349282350410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282441273-196</Id><Title>Bank of america will bring better.</Title><Msg>numbers every quarter for 4 years, starting this quarter. Wait and see and forget the phantasies about shorts that will hold the stock down...</Msg><Username>zissi022000</Username><Timestamp>1349282441273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282546554-197</Id><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Msg>After suffering through a four year campaign of hate spewing and outrageous lying, the intelligent and patriotic American voters have chosen the high road. President Obama will be re-elected.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282835356-198</Id><Title>Wells Fargo seen as potential suitor for Ohio's Fifth Third Bank</Title><Msg>Wells Fargo seen as potential suitor for Ohio's Fifth Third Bank San Francisco Business Times by Mark Calvey Wells Fargo &amp; Co. may be a potential buyer of Cincinnati-based Fifth Third Bancorp, analysts say. Wells (NYSE: WFC) of San Francisco could be interested in expanding its Midwest presence with the purchase of Fifth Third, (NYSE: FITB) Richard Bove, an analyst with Punk, Ziegel &amp; Co. told the San Francisco Business Times. Other reports see U.S. Bancorp (NYSE: USB) and Wachovia (NYSE: WB) as potential suitors for the Cincinnati bank. Some have cited Bank of America Corp. (NYSE: BAC) as a possible acquirer, but that's doubtful because the Charlotte, N.C., bank is bumping up against the cap that restricts banks holding 10 percent of national deposits from making big bank acquisitions that would push its share of national deposits even higher. BofA is free to capture a larger percentage of national deposits through internal growth. Wells Fargo CEO Dick Kovacevich told investors last month that he does see his bank participating in a megamerger. Fifth Third would definitely boost Wells Fargo's Midwest branch territory, which is rather thin with 24 branches in Michigan, 39 in Indiana and 14 in Illinois. It has one branch in Ohio. That compares with 851 branches in California, making it the state's second-largest bank after BofA. Fifth Third's Chicago and Florida markets could be attractive to Wells Fargo, not to mention the Cincinnati bank's strong sales culture.</Msg><Username>sachs1960</Username><Timestamp>1349282835356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283530674-199</Id><Topic><Title>WHY BUY BAC IF YOUR MAX UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281378841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like brother Bluto said "why not"! Don't do it sir notsuchagreatide.LOL @ U</Msg><Username>cwoolrey</Username><Timestamp>1349283530674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349283699355-200</Id><Title>Romney to disclose 10 years of tax returs.</Title><Msg>Of his butler.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349283699355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283761897-201</Id><Topic><Title>HOW CAN OBAMA WIN GVEN HIS HORRIBLE JOB PERFORMANCE??</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1349279160779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:46:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMERICA IS OVER!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1349283761897</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283852062-202</Id><Topic><Title>YOU are middle class,vote that way unless you are stupid and uninformed.</Title><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349279794873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stats clearly show significant shifts in net worth from the middle class to the rich and powerful over the past decade or two. Yet so many in the middle class believe, as an article of faith, that it's the poor and powerless that are taking their wealth.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1349283852062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283914948-203</Id><Topic><Title>Republican attempts to keep registered Democrats from voting FAILS.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349277678070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's next? The Republicans are good at smearing, slinging mud, and doing any and all things dirty. Will they save the "best" dirt for last? What turd will they try to dump next?</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349283914948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349283926732-204</Id><Title>Romney agrees that taxing rich is good.</Title><Msg>Especially if you tax them less.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1349283926732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283935795-205</Id><Topic><Title>WHY BUY BAC IF YOUR MAX UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281378841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't even break 9.10. shorts control this baby</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349283935795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284071707-206</Id><Topic><Title>The most damage done to Romney is when he opens his mouth. Bring on the debates!</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349278213098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:30:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let the GaffeMeister live up to his name.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349284071707</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284231237-207</Id><Topic><Title>I'm IN oct 5 calls</Title><Username>ryanmilliron</Username><Timestamp>1348843144816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Selling today at .61 for 32% profit on the $8.50 calls expiring friday. I think we'll have a small pullback tomorrow, so i'll try to get a new position tomorrow-</Msg><Username>ryanmilliron</Username><Timestamp>1349284231237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349284343306-208</Id><Title>The far right jackals eat their own.</Title><Msg>At some point the far right has to turn on Romney hard. Otherwise his loss is a rejection of their agenda for which he's been a pretty faithful water carrier.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1349284343306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284357062-209</Id><Topic><Title>YOU are middle class,vote that way unless you are stupid and uninformed.</Title><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349279794873</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is weak and can't be Pres. of the U.S. He can only be leader of the top 1% who call themselves America's makers.</Msg><Username>toomuchspin4322</Username><Timestamp>1349284357062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284590648-210</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>dickersonh73</Username><Timestamp>1349284590648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:16:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284597100-211</Id><Topic><Title>WHY BUY BAC IF YOUR MAX UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281378841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAC failed to break through $9.11 several times. If the market starts to turn red, it can go to $8.88 again. Longs really need BAC to break through $9.11 today.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349284597100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284704854-212</Id><Topic><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I can say to you greatestideaman is that you are a fkin idiot,</Msg><Username>jesusisntcoming</Username><Timestamp>1349284704854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:18:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284730022-213</Id><Topic><Title>The far right jackals eat their own.</Title><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1349284343306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:12:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It may work both ways. The Republican moderates will blame the far right for alienating the rational and the undecided, and the fringe-right dog s*h*i*t* eaters will blame the moderates for not being truly "conservative," i.e., in their narrow view: neo-nazi.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349284730022</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349284974458-214</Id><Topic><Title>BAC WILL NEVER CROSS $9.50 AGAIN..SHORTS WON'T LET IT..SO YOUR UPSIDE IS 40 PENNIES</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349281222991</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOING OVER IT THIS WEEK</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349284974458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349284978208-215</Id><Title>up up up and awayyyyyy</Title><Msg>up up up and awayyyyyyyyyyyy</Msg><Username>midnight_riderssss</Username><Timestamp>1349284978208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285047016-216</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP...2NIGHTS DEBATE...</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349285047016</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285103567-217</Id><Title>AVERAGING UP OUR SHORT POSITION..CAN'T SEE IT GOING OVER $9.50</Title><Msg>PRETTY SAFE</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349285103567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285511572-218</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Baggers will either go down or up in flames. Either way..., let them BURN!</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349185997883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tide has turned. Swing states have turned blue, voter ID laws modified to allow registered voters the right to vote without Republican interference, The polls show Obama continuing to gain, and the relentless attack on Obama and his family to demean their character has FAILED.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349285511572</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285569277-219</Id><Title>Buying BAC looking for $14.50</Title><Msg>Looked at my long term charts which says BREAKOUT. Looking for $14.50. Only fools would short at this technical breakout or not cover their shorts if they are already short.</Msg><Username>star.maker09</Username><Timestamp>1349285569277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285621110-220</Id><Topic><Title>My father was a great republican</Title><Username>schuey9999</Username><Timestamp>1349148938980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn yourself in to a mental health expert.</Msg><Username>toomuchspin4322</Username><Timestamp>1349285621110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285799160-221</Id><Title>LEAPS - Preferreds</Title><Msg>The Jan 2014 Leaps are looking especially good right now. With the lawsuits getting settled and QE3 picking up the toxic mortgages - BAC is poised for growth in 2013 - even if the Dems win the election. I'm heavy into the out-of-the-money Jan2014 12 calls. Anyone out there holding BAC preferreds? I need some dividend plays and would love to know the best BAC preferreds out there....thoughts? Happy Investing!</Msg><Username>roachmeister01</Username><Timestamp>1349285799160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285844650-222</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News: ALL of the swing states have turned BLUE . . . , AND, Obama continues to gain.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349271863854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wins. Every swing state is now blue or turning blue with Obama gaining.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349285844650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285933228-223</Id><Topic><Title>I CAN'T BELIEVE CONSERVATIVES ARE DEFENDING TAX CHEATER ROMNEY</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349212278235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody ever accused conservative people of being smart, just knuckle draggers.</Msg><Username>toomuchspin4322</Username><Timestamp>1349285933228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349286743518-224</Id><Topic><Title>I CAN'T BELIEVE CONSERVATIVES ARE DEFENDING TAX CHEATER ROMNEY</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349212278235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney paid $1.9 million in taxes last year. Obama paid $162 thousand in taxes last year. ..thus Romney is fiscally over 10 times better for us than Obama :-)</Msg><Username>roachmeister01</Username><Timestamp>1349286743518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349286755675-225</Id><Topic><Title>Hey XTrader</Title><Username>marvinthemartiansdog</Username><Timestamp>1347393386594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened to tardx? Did he have to change his name? LOL LOL LOL</Msg><Username>zipzter</Username><Timestamp>1349286755675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349286944275-226</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>steffanieisc10076</Username><Timestamp>1349286944275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349286979879-227</Id><Topic><Title>HEY TRADERX</Title><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1345652048244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-22 12:14:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL LOL LOL</Msg><Username>zipzter</Username><Timestamp>1349286979879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287071854-228</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing this to us please. Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>flynnacosta69</Username><Timestamp>1349287071854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349287125401-229</Id><Title>bac will be 10+ after earnings</Title><Msg>ben is fattening up all the big banks to hasten recovery.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1349287125401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287201725-230</Id><Topic><Title>Traderx ..FSLR rise up daily and BAC going to $8 not head to $4.40</Title><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1344526445755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 11:34:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>another great call by the resident fool traderx...shorted FSLR LOL The stock that went on to double a few days later. brilliant</Msg><Username>inowhourviv</Username><Timestamp>1349287201725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287335621-231</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>traderx is a clown</Msg><Username>atdabeach48</Username><Timestamp>1349287335621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:02:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287420402-232</Id><Topic><Title>BRAZENTARD</Title><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1340117359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-06-19 10:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is this #$%$ that used to post 100 times daily? new name?</Msg><Username>udumfck50</Username><Timestamp>1349287420402</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287788143-233</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he wants to help the middle class .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349274411836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obummer wants to help then he should resign today and take the drunk biden with him.jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349287788143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349287809928-234</Id><Topic><Title>I CAN'T BELIEVE CONSERVATIVES ARE DEFENDING TAX CHEATER ROMNEY</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349212278235</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't cheat on his taxes. why do you people think if you tell a lie often enough it becomes the truth?</Msg><Username>bouch84</Username><Timestamp>1349287809928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288373549-235</Id><Title>Greece is the word...</Title><Msg>Greece held a new round of talks with foreign lenders to bridge differences over 2 billion euros of disputed austerity cuts, with time running short to clinch a deal before a meeting of euro zone ministers next week. Athens has been haggling for weeks over 12 billion euros of cutbacks that its European Union and International Monetary Fund lenders have refused to sign off on over fears that some of the proposed savings are unlikely to materialize. The IMF wants Greece to cut its debt further to make up for going hugely off-track from the terms of its bailout, while Europe is resisting the option of a new debt restructuring and instead prefers to give Athens more time to get back on track, officials have told Reuters So now what? The Greeks aren’t buying the plan and have taken to the streets to protest. One protestor held a banner saying: "They handed 200 billion to bankers but cut down on medicine, treatment and benefits for the disabled." Yes, the European central planning experiment has gone awry! And guess what, it’s going to get worse. Good morning Spain and Ireland, welcome to your future.</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349288373549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288555730-236</Id><Title>I LOVE HIGH FREQUENCY TRADERS</Title><Msg>I love them because Wall Street hates them The same Specialists who rig the market every day, are those who condemn them I don't care if they do thousands of trades every day, because when they do, it creates liquidity and makes it harder for the Specialists to rig stock prices.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1349288555730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:22:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349288712208-237</Id><Topic><Title>Fed busy printing money ..... says there is low risk of inflation</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349288176612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:16:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!!</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349288712208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288712838-238</Id><Title>Oil $50: Pros analysts Oil at $50 Credit Suisse analysts Oil at $50</Title><Msg>Oil $50: Pros analysts Oil at $50 Credit Suisse analysts Oil at $50 --- the analysis argues that demand would fall along with trading activity and that any recovery would be “halting fragile and painfully slow.” The report points to the fall in oil prices witnessed in 2008, when Brent prices plunged from a record high level in the space of a few months. The analysts Oil at $50</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1349288712838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349288749899-239</Id><Title>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Title><Msg>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel Based on Sanford C. Bernstein estimates of the marginal cost of oil production, the geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now. Reminding the market that a strategic cushion exists—without necessarily deploying it—provides a check on that premium rising even further. Sweet Crude Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel. That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline. Sanford Bernstein geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline.</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1349288749899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349288843424-240</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says he wants to help the middle class .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349274411836</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:26:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! Obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!! obama wins again!!</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349288843424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349288982101-241</Id><Topic><Title>Fox News: ALL of the swing states have turned BLUE . . . , AND, Obama continues to gain.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349271863854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:44:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's over. Everyday Obama gains, Romney loses.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349288982101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289087423-242</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>alixibr05157</Username><Timestamp>1349289087423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289199516-243</Id><Title>SHORTS..WE NEED TO KEEP BAC UNDER $9.15 AT THE CLOSE OR FACE TECHNICAL BREAKOUT TO $9.80</Title><Msg>KEEP SHORTING</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349289199516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289233310-244</Id><Topic><Title>Hey LOSER waste of meat "dumpobamie": HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA, HA!!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349191756452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:29:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know how thick dumpo is. It may take awhile for reality to sink in. His life's work has just been dashed. He spent the last four years of his waste of meat life slamming Obama for nothing. LMAO !</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349289233310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289397668-245</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama continues to gain.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349289397668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289477901-246</Id><Title>PUT UP 50K SHARES SHORT AT 9.08..DOING MY PART..HELP OUT</Title><Msg>KEEP IT UNDER 9.15</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349289477901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289565443-247</Id><Topic><Title>Lemming dumpobamie can't stop barking at the moon. Hard to stop lying? Denial? Loser syndrome?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1349203361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:42:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's try explaining it to him very slowly so he can understand. O B A M A H A S W O N ! Now, give a few weeks to sink in.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349289565443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289632338-248</Id><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Msg>If Mitt Romney is that insecure that he needs his wife to hold him up because he is under such pressure now, what will an insecure Mitt Romney do if the U.S. was under attack??????????????? Mitt Romney has never had a hard day in his life, Being President, All days are hard. Mitt Romney's 3 am Call at the White House may be answered by his wife, she has bigger nuts than he will ever have.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289671047-249</Id><Title>IF BREAKS 9.08 WILL SHORT MORE AT 9.13..NEED TO STAY UNDER 9.15 AT ALL COSTS</Title><Msg>HELP ME OUT SHORTS</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349289671047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289689811-250</Id><Title>SEC Must Act Now to Protect Investors From High Frequency Trading: Saluzzi</Title><Msg>"I know it when I see it" Supreme Court Justice Potter Stewart famously wrote in 1964 while attempting to define precisely what was - or wasn't - to be considered hard core pornography. It's a quip that's not only stood the test of time but has been applied to all sorts of different circumstances over the years, the latest of which coming on Capitol Hill, where a gaggle of lawmakers, regulators and investment industry players are trying to tackle one of the most contentious and dangerous problems facing our capital markets now. I am referring to "high frequency trading" (or HFT) and the ongoing debate over what to do about it that has raged since the Flash Crash rocked the markets in May of 2010. While individuals and institutions have knocked high frequency traders, called them names, and blamed them for all sorts problems, veterans like Joe Saluzzi, co-founder of Themis Trading and author the book "Broken Markets" says you have to "define the problem before you fix it." To many of us, 100 trades per day would be considered high frequency, let alone 100 trades per second. Which is why applying a speed limit would have very different impact on individuals and the markets. After all, HFT is not illegal, it's just annoying. "It's very difficult to fix but we do know what the problems in the market are," Saluzzi says, adding that the root cause of the problems is market structure issues. "The dominant force in the market is scalpers and they're all looking for that big institutional order, where the host is me and my big institutional order and the parasites are just going all around me trying to pick me off all day long." As for fixes, on the one hand, Saluzzi says you have a debate that is still dominated by the big brokerage firms and exchanges, which he says are now all for-profit businesses -like NYSE Euronext (NYX), Intercontinental Exchange (ICE), and Nasdaq OMX (NDAQ)- that are catering to the needs of their biggest (e.g. most active) clients. But with the integrity of our capital markets at risk, and HFT volume accounting for a larger and larger percentage of trading activity, Saluzzi and many others like him say the time for action is now. "The SEC needs to step in and protect the interest of the long term investors," he says, "Who of long-term versus short-term and capital formation become an issue the SEC must protect the long term investor."</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349289689811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349289947938-251</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bubble Boy still has a place in France if the US is attacked again.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1349289947938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349289997491-252</Id><Title>Is the TWEEDLE DUMB_NEY vs. TWEEDLE DUMB_MA DEBATE ON TONIGHT?</Title><Msg>I think most persons would rather be at jury duty! Tonight would be a great night for Wednesday night football!</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1349289997491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349290703963-253</Id><Topic><Title>IF BREAKS 9.08 WILL SHORT MORE AT 9.13..NEED TO STAY UNDER 9.15 AT ALL COSTS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349289671047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:41:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Help you out of your what? No thanks.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349290703963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349290975485-254</Id><Title>AONE AONE AONE AONE AONE AONEAONE AONE AONE AONE AONE AONEAONE AONE AONE AONE AONE AONEAONE AONE AONE AONE AONE AONEAONE AONE AONE AONE AONE AONE</Title><Msg>Aone aone aone aone aone aoneaone aone aone aone aone aoneaone aone aone aone aone aoneaone aone aone aone aone aoneaone aone aone aone aone aone</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349290975485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291138566-255</Id><Title>Will BAC ever get back to the 10's by next year...</Title><Msg>I really doubt it... get ready to cash in...</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1349291138566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291319797-256</Id><Topic><Title>My father was a great republican</Title><Username>schuey9999</Username><Timestamp>1349148938980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LLR!! Aren't Republicans the opposite of smart? Do you really trust these quacking ducks?</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349291319797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291464310-257</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>joettatsm277654</Username><Timestamp>1349291464310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291517592-258</Id><Topic><Title>BRAZENTARD</Title><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1340117359000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-06-19 10:49:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say BOTH!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349291517592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291624862-259</Id><Topic><Title>Why would anyone use the screen name "Bury Obama?" Could they be a racist neo-nazi?</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1349278678568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt he must be the village fool!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349291624862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291911125-260</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nazi's were national socialists. Like the democrats. Adolph 'was a man who passed a law on the most humane way to cook a lobster at the same time as he prepared for the annihilation of an entire race'. You really need to be more careful how you assign your derogatories. That one points back at you.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1349291911125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:18:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291928493-261</Id><Title>A sesson closing question</Title><Msg>You think the Algo's and HFT's will let the pps close north of $9 today?</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349291928493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292373893-262</Id><Title>I lost my virginity, but I still have the box it came in.</Title><Msg>As with most toys, much of the value is dependant on whether you have the original box in good condition or not.</Msg><Username>milesed17smom</Username><Timestamp>1349292373893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349292457764-263</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>dorthyxgm719</Username><Timestamp>1349292457764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:27:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292594530-264</Id><Title>LPTN</Title><Msg>SAN DIEGO, CA--(Marketwire - Oct 3, 2012) - Lpath, Inc. ( OTCQB : LPTN ), the industry leader in bioactive lipid-targeted therapeutics, has initiated the dosing of iSONEP™ in its Nexus Phase 2 study, with several wet-AMD patients treated since September 21, 2012. In the double-blind, multi-site trial, Lpath plans to dose 160 subjects who have not responded completely to a VEGF inhibitor (either Lucentis® or Avastin®). These subjects will be randomized into four arms: (1) VEGF inhibitor alone; (2) combination of a VEGF inhibitor and iSONEP (lower dose); (3) combination of a VEGF inhibitor and iSONEP (higher dose); and (4) iSONEP alone (higher dose). Endpoints to be studied include changes in best corrected visual acuity (BCVA), retinal thickness, and lesion size. The Nexus trial will also investigate iSONEP's ability to flatten Pigmented Epithelial Detachments (PEDs), a complication of wet AMD that does not respond well to anti-VEGF treatments. "We are seeing strong enrollment momentum in our Nexus study," said Scott Pancoast, Lpath's president and chief executive officer. "Our Nexus study seeks to determine how iSONEP can best be used to benefit wet-AMD patients. Whether as first-line single agent, as first-line in combination with anti-VEGF therapies, or as second-line, a drug that can provide additive benefits in the treatment of wet AMD would have a significant market potential." In the Phase 1 trial, where subjects with wet AMD received a single injection of iSONEP, a positive biological effect was observed in most patients, almost all of whom had failed to respond to treatment with Lucentis and/or Avastin. One such positive effect was a significant reduction (30%+) in the size of the choroidal neovascular lesion in many of the subjects, all of whom were not responding well to treatment with the VEGF inhibitors at the time they were enrolled in the study. Significant reduction in lesion size with a single injection is not typically observed with VEGF inhibition. One of these subjects experienced a 100% reduction in lesion size as of Day 45. This subject did not have to be re-injected with the "standard of care" (i.e., with Lucentis or Avastin) for the entire 12-month monitoring period following the iSONEP injection. Another subject who had undergone 16 prior treatments of Lucentis and Avastin without much response was administered the highest dose of iSONEP studied (1.8 mg.). This subject experienced not only a 100% reduction in lesion size by Day 15, but also a complete elimination of retinal swelling. Like the other subject, this subject also did not have to be re-injected with Lucentis or Avastin for the entire 12-month monitoring period following the iSONEP treatment. These extended times to re-treatment suggest that any benefit derived from iSONEP may be durable, a particularly important attribute in this market. Lpath hypothesizes that such distinctive benefits are due to powerful anti-angiogenic, anti-inflammatory, and anti-fibrotic mechanisms of action of iSONEP, which binds to and neutralizes the bioactive lipid, S1P. In various animal models of disease, iSONEP was shown to substantially reduce inflammation and angiogenesis in the eye (Campochiaro et al., Journal of Cellular Physiology, January 2009) and significantly mitigate ocular fibrosis (Grant et al., Experimental Eye Research, March 2009). Lpath entered into an agreement with Pfizer Inc. ( NYSE : PFE ) in 2010 that provides Pfizer an exclusive option for a worldwide license to develop and commercialize iSONEP. Lpath and Pfizer have collaborated extensively on design and goals of the Nexus Phase 2 study. About Lpath San Diego-based Lpath, Inc. ( OTCQB : LPTN ), a therapeutic antibody company, is the category leader in bioactive lipid-targeted therapeutics, an emerging field of medicine that targets bioactive signaling lipids for treating a wide range of human disease. Lpath's ImmuneY2™ drug-discovery engine has the unique ability to generate therapeutic antibodies that bind to and inhibit bioactive lipids that contribute to disease. The company has developed three drug candidates, two of which -- iSONEP™ for wet AMD and ASONEP™ for cancer -- have completed Phase 1 clinical trials. The third candidate is an anti-LPA antibody that holds promise in neuropathic pain, neurotrauma and other disease conditions. For more information, v</Msg><Username>captjerome1</Username><Timestamp>1349292594530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292854315-265</Id><Title>ME AND THE MM'S ARE KEEPING A LID AT 9.08..SORRY LONGS</Title><Msg>WE CAN'T LET IT GET NEAR 9.15</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349292854315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349292860077-266</Id><Topic><Title>A sesson closing question</Title><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349291928493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:18:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349292860077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292949296-267</Id><Title>what jackass shorted today???BWAhahahahah</Title><Msg>10 bucks in three weeks</Msg><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1349292949296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292961292-268</Id><Title>KEEP SHORTING PEOPLE ,,CAN'T LET IT GET TO 9.15 FOR 2 MORE DAYS</Title><Msg>JUST 2 MORE DAYS</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349292961292</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293201998-269</Id><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Msg>HELP OUT</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293233800-270</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On BAC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>frenchzimmerman95</Username><Timestamp>1349292043146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:20:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am really helped and greatful to u for giving such a great information.</Msg><Username>larsens83</Username><Timestamp>1349293233800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293265888-271</Id><Title>When the Chips are Down...</Title><Msg>When the chips are down... we independents, have to vote for who can be more TRUSTED without regard to party or ideology. Romney does not come across as one that I can trust. Why? He is not guided by a deeper sense of high principles. And that shows through his flip-flops. A rich fellow who grew up in comfort and ease does not really understand the plight of most of those who are challenged to make ends meet let alone challenging times of the middle class in our nation. Our nations strength and well-being is largely dependent on our middle class citizens. With a small minority of super rich 1% and the widening gap between them and the rest of the nation... we have almost become like a third world country. Our nation's greatness is founded on a fair distribution of the national wealth everybody doing their fair share and no priviledged class at the top for the 1%. Romney's life career was based on solely his pursuit to make MORE money... almost always holding money above people to reach his financial goal. I'm not surprised he can't connect with the people. Whatever he says... the facts of his life are that his character was formed without learning the tough lessons of life during which one forms abiding good and high principles. His flip flopping is proof that he lacks high principles to guide him. SORRY, I CAN'T TRUST THE MAN. Accordingly, I have no choice. Good luck!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349293265888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293508051-272</Id><Topic><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try longs...almost made a run at 9.15...too little too late</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293508051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293531157-273</Id><Topic><Title>ME AND THE MM'S ARE KEEPING A LID AT 9.08..SORRY LONGS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349292854315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9.08, what lid?? time to take you out!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349293531157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293620073-274</Id><Topic><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead of fixating price levels out of thin air, I suggest for your own health to invest what is more comfortable for you. The market can do anything! I would not put myself in a straight-jacket like you do. My comfort comes first before gambling! Though I wish you GL!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349293620073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293793041-275</Id><Topic><Title>When the Chips are Down...</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349293265888</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch out Romney is equipped with zingers. He thinks these are cool: 1. I am rubber you are glue... 2. So is your mama.... 3. My tax privacy is an my right, voting for everyone not so right.</Msg><Username>a_pig_about_money</Username><Timestamp>1349293793041</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293902902-276</Id><Topic><Title>ME AND THE MM'S ARE KEEPING A LID AT 9.08..SORRY LONGS</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349292854315</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wish there was lid on this can of worms. Your losses will be endless. Sorry shorty</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349293902902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293963125-277</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On BAC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>frenchzimmerman95</Username><Timestamp>1349292043146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:20:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love getting french zimmered. BAC a good bet here.</Msg><Username>trust_this_stock</Username><Timestamp>1349293963125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294057961-278</Id><Topic><Title>SHORTS..WE NEED TO KEEP BAC UNDER $9.15 AT THE CLOSE OR FACE TECHNICAL BREAKOUT TO $9.80</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349289199516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:33:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"we" Talking to your imaginary friends again?</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349294057961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:54:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294242889-279</Id><Topic><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPOKEN LIKE A LOSER LONG. I PLAY TO WIN</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294242889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294247505-280</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those people" -- Mitt Romney</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349026868340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Those people" will not let an out of touch snob become presidnent.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349294247505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294247588-281</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those people" -- Mitt Romney</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349026868340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Those people" will not let an out of touch snob become presidnent.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349294247588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294280669-282</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On BAC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>frenchzimmerman95</Username><Timestamp>1349292043146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:20:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes because 4,5,6,7, and 8 were terrible entries Do you report on last week's weather as well?</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349294280669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349294302065-283</Id><Title>SHORT POSITION INTACT...SEE YOU TOMORROW</Title><Msg>THANKS</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294302065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349294378938-284</Id><Title>DON'T TRY TO PUMP UP THE PRICE TOMORROW MORNING..WE'LL JUST SHORT MORE</Title><Msg>AND MORE AND MORE</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294378938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349294827459-285</Id><Title>Covered my short</Title><Msg>Covered my trade costs and some beer money. Lokk like it may be going higher</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1349294827459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294875464-286</Id><Topic><Title>Covered my short</Title><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1349294827459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*Looks</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1349294875464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294958360-287</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those people" -- Mitt Romney</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349026868340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm... That kind of talk disqualifies a candidate for president immediately! He is doomed! Also he may put another nail in his coffin in the debate tonight... especially trying to explain/justify his infamous statement about his dismissal of the 47% of voters!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349294958360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295011316-288</Id><Topic><Title>DON'T TRY TO PUMP UP THE PRICE TOMORROW MORNING..WE'LL JUST SHORT MORE</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294378938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Young man, you need to understand that the investment/trading activities of the fine women and men on this board have NO effect on the PPS of one of the largest financial insitutions in the world. None whatsoever.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349295011316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:10:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295033981-289</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has weathered a never ending attack by the storm trooper Gesapo-like far right. The disinformation and misinformation constantly hurled at Obama by the neo-nazi extremists has failed to take root anywhere except in the weak minds of those who thrive on racism and fascism. Flippant 1 needs to do some homework. Start with one of your nazi heroes: propagandist Joseph Goebbels.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349295033981</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295073722-290</Id><Topic><Title>DON'T TRY TO PUMP UP THE PRICE TOMORROW MORNING..WE'LL JUST SHORT MORE</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294378938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:59:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, wake up and smell the money. You are definitely on the wrong side of the trade.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1349295073722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295329835-291</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Baggers call themselves tea baggers because...? Look it up in the online Urban Dictionary</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1348292396602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perverts do what perverts do.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349295329835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:15:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295371229-292</Id><Topic><Title>Covered my short</Title><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1349294827459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349295371229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295399800-293</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>lauriemyz111</Username><Timestamp>1349295399800</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295554782-294</Id><Topic><Title>SHORT POSITION INTACT...SEE YOU TOMORROW</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294302065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see BAC gaping up tomorrow- barring negative news from Europe. If you add on good employment numbers on Friday, 9.50 is not out of the question by weeks end. You will elarn the hard way on this one.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1349295554782</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295659705-295</Id><Topic><Title>SHORT POSITION INTACT...SEE YOU TOMORROW</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349294302065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So by position intact you mean your head is still sufficiently up your bum. Good to know</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349295659705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295846602-296</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OUTSTANDING POST! Within the first few sentences, it became apparent to me that an anti-Obama and anti-Islam storm was a-brewin', another fatuous, twist-and-shout revivalist operation a-fixin' to blow through town and raise a stink, so I almost blew off reading the rest of it. I'm glad I stuck around for the punchline, though: "Washington Times Communities"(!) For those not in on the joke, the Washington Times was founded by the Rev. Sun Yung Moon as a broadsheet &amp; mouthpiece for his Unification Church. ROTFLMAO still, the Washington Times has at least as much credibility as Tom Cruise, L. Ron Hubbard, The Book of Mormon, Romney, and Ryan.....put together.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349295846602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295855947-297</Id><Topic><Title>My father was a great republican</Title><Username>schuey9999</Username><Timestamp>1349148938980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That'd be 'tenet', not 'tenant'. Is Mitt Robme your father?</Msg><Username>venturian321</Username><Timestamp>1349295855947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296033310-298</Id><Topic><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be the difference between someone that makes money and someone that makes money and then loses money. I think sometimes people confuse stressing over the stock market with knowledge about the stock market. Like somehow wasting countless hours guessing the price tomorrow is a job.</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349296033310</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296102901-299</Id><Topic><Title>Covered my short</Title><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1349294827459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:07:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well thank God. The markets and everyone here were waiting on your signal.</Msg><Username>tradejunky</Username><Timestamp>1349296102901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296417242-300</Id><Topic><Title>HUGE MONEY AT STAKE..CANNOT LET IT BREAK ABOVE 9.15</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1349293201998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:40:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sounds just like Traderx. Oh he's not around anymore after making a fool of himself many times over and losing his imaginary riches. He had imaginary "connections" with MMs too. Perhaps you are better suited to yahoo fantasy trading.</Msg><Username>finviz20</Username><Timestamp>1349296417242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296572907-301</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are on some other planet -- I think it's Uranus. You name-dropping propagandists just cannot accept that the insult your hurling is perfectly descriptive for your own party, platform, intolerance, strong-arm tactics, and horrific results. You've decimated black families in the past 40 years, you've destroyed the education system, you've destroyed personal ambition, and you just continue on your little path of destruction. Well, now you are going to be stopped.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1349296572907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296792541-302</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you're not calling Obama a national socialist, you're calling him a communist. You don't know your mouth from your b_u_n_g_h_o_l_e_.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349296792541</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296801590-303</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be a member of The Birch Society</Msg><Username>slowpoke66</Username><Timestamp>1349296801590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349296854088-304</Id><Title>Does the Repug Lie Machine blame Bush for 9/11like they blame Obama for Libya?</Title><Msg>Do they blame FDR for Pearl Harbor? Do they ever say anything that is remotely accurate?</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349296854088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297099337-305</Id><Topic><Title>A sesson closing question</Title><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349291928493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:18:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like the answer is...yes? ;-)</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1349297099337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297122631-306</Id><Topic><Title>My father was a great republican</Title><Username>schuey9999</Username><Timestamp>1349148938980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:35:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was he also a member of The John Birch Society?</Msg><Username>slowpoke66</Username><Timestamp>1349297122631</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297497691-307</Id><Topic><Title>"My job is not to worry about those people" -- Mitt Romney</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349026868340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people behind Mr. Romney's closed doors are members of The John Birch Society</Msg><Username>slowpoke66</Username><Timestamp>1349297497691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298499879-308</Id><Title>Profile of 0bama supporters - They all fit into one or more:</Title><Msg>Felons/criminals Illegal aliens Uneducated or brainwashed into progressive robots of the State Able-bodied welfare recipients Able-bodied fraudulent workman’s comp. recipients Securities Fraud enablers of Wall St. Union thugs and organized crime operatives Government workers who work less hours and get paid much more than private sector workers at the same jobs.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298499879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298568721-309</Id><Title>Univision continues coverage of Fast &amp; Furious scandal. While the</Title><Msg>mass media tries to hide the deadly program, Univision is digging and investigating why more than 2,000 Hispanics were murdered under 0bama &amp; Holders decision to provide illegal weapons to Mexican cartels knowing full well that innocent Hispanics would be murdered. Univision wants answers and those responsible to get justice. Hoorah for Univision!</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298568721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298580483-310</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could not care less about wash times...everything in print is true &amp; i will love to hear from u what your feeling is about what happened in Libya to Ambassador Stevens &amp; why Obama &amp; Hillary declined to give him protection that he asked for many weeks before.</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349298580483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298610350-311</Id><Title>Libyan Embassy officials asked numerous times for extra security prior to our</Title><Msg>U.S. Ambassadors murder. But the White House and Hillary Clinton denied their motions. And those few security officials there were not allowed to be armed under orders by 0bama and the State Dept. The body count piles up under Obama's pro-jihadist policy. The attack on our embassy was an act of war. The slaughter of our US ambassador and three diplomats was an act of war. The President blamed America. The President blamed the Constitution. Obama blamed the first amendment. This is high treason. The enemedia exalts treason as patriotism, while demonizing freedom lovers and patriots. America, it is past midnight. “Based on information provided to the Committee by individuals with direct knowledge of events in Libya, the attack that claimed the ambassador’s life was the latest in a long line of attacks on Western diplomats and officials in Libya in the months leading up to September 11, 2012,” “Multiple U.S. federal government officials have confirmed to the Committee that, prior to the September 11 attack, the U.S. mission in Libya made repeated requests for increased security in Benghazi,” “The mission in Libya, however, was denied these resources by officials in Washington.” The committee noted 13 “security threats” in Benghazi, including an attempt to assassinate the British ambassador to Libya.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298610350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298678064-312</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Baggers call themselves tea baggers because...? Look it up in the online Urban Dictionary</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1348292396602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 01:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am confused, since homosexual sex is the norm in the democratic party and tea bagging is what some homosexuals like to do. Why do you refer the Tea Party members as tea baggers? Does that mean you do not approve of tea bagging democrats? So sucking sack is bad? I thought you had big tent for all. Oh that's right you're the party of the double standard and corruption like we have never seen before. Oh wait isn't this the BAC stock board? Yep the one you #$%$ holes infest.</Msg><Username>chipin_at_it</Username><Timestamp>1349298678064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298916746-313</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>sorayamha404</Username><Timestamp>1349298916746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299118072-314</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was collateral damage according to 0bama. obama knew the threats were real and refused to protect Stevens possible because he was gay. Gay and muslims do not mix. Just like when obama never kisses his wife in public. It is against muslim law.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349299118072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299356269-315</Id><Topic><Title>Profile of 0bama supporters - They all fit into one or more:</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298499879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>democrats are the takers or destructive, and Conservatives are the makers who are productive.</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349299356269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:22:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299357919-316</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he was always against same sex marrige but to try and save his election he flipped...this mutant Obama must go in November</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349299357919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299645072-317</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals still think appeasement works. Have they not learned that failed mindset leads to death? Even after all history shows that it fails time and time again? Maybe in their video game minds, they think they are correct. LOL You can't appease or rationally deal with terrorists, especially muslim terrorists...</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349299645072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349299793392-318</Id><Title>BAC PRINTING AFTER HOURS ABOVE HIGH OF THE DAY...NEXT RESISTANCE 9.75 AREA</Title><Msg>Then 52 week high of 10.10...off to the races tomorrow</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349299793392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299874460-319</Id><Topic><Title>Profile of 0bama supporters - They all fit into one or more:</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298499879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good list. A few more: Race Card Players, i.e. Sharpton, Jackson &amp; ilk Mass Media Hollywood Degenerates--Madona Sexual Degenerates, Gays Muslims Communists Socialists</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1349299874460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299969695-320</Id><Topic><Title>Going Long On BAC Who Is With Me?</Title><Username>frenchzimmerman95</Username><Timestamp>1349292043146</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:20:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's huge and instantly!</Msg><Username>clemonsantoinette47</Username><Timestamp>1349299969695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349300117116-321</Id><Title>That stock is going to $10!</Title><Msg>HPQ</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1349300117116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349300256273-322</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Obamas kissing and see what you get. Then put your head back up your backside where it usually resides. Tell us just how much real information you have about security in North Africa and all you know about the activities that day Stevens died.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349300256273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349300414434-323</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is probably still against it but as president realizes it is a matter of liberty for others even if it isn't his favorite thing. His personal opinion has little to do with what he has to do as president.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349300414434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349300482786-324</Id><Title>Bank of America Corp S&amp;P Recommendation SELL Price $8.93 (as of Oct 2, 2012) 12-Mo. Target Price $8.00 Invest</Title><Msg>I was astounded to read this they were previously Hold Target Price 9...</Msg><Username>luisfloreshn</Username><Timestamp>1349300482786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349300513471-325</Id><Title>Bank of America Corp S&amp;P Recommendation SELL Price $8.93 (as of Oct 2, 2012) 12-Mo. Target Price $8.00 Invest</Title><Msg>I was astounded to read this they were previously Hold Target Price 9...</Msg><Username>luisfloreshn</Username><Timestamp>1349300513471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349300643473-326</Id><Title>The arrogance of Obama will be his and our downfall...</Title><Msg>This Community Organizer has become very full of himself and very arrogant especially when he compared himself to the insults to Mohammed...</Msg><Username>luisfloreshn</Username><Timestamp>1349300643473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349300831691-327</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Repug Lie Machine blame Bush for 9/11like they blame Obama for Libya?</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349296854088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes they would blame FDR for Pearl harbor. FDR was a democrat you know. 9/11 they blame on Clinton. The recession on Barney Frank, Katrina on the weather channel and global warming on cattle flatulence.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349300831691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:47:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349301616951-328</Id><Title>Stockguru 7 provides proof Obama is not Muslimor gay</Title><Msg>"Gay and muslims do not mix. Just like when obama never kisses his wife in public. It is against muslim law." quote stockguru7 Now google Obama kissing and see how many public kisses you can find.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1349301616951</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349301633818-329</Id><Topic><Title>Profile of 0bama supporters - They all fit into one or more:</Title><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1349298499879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, when the Reoublican Nazi Party loses the election, are you going to leave the country? Come on , take the RoButt pledge, so we can get rid of the Pee Party, the Klan and the NeoNazis that make up the RNP's so called base, ir is that Basement?</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1349301633818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349301773026-330</Id><Topic><Title>Does the Repug Lie Machine blame Bush for 9/11like they blame Obama for Libya?</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1349296854088</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:40:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and they would be right... FDR boxed in Japan so they had no access to raw materials..causing military solutions Clinton dismantled the CIA so we lost our inside knowledge of 9/11 terrorist activities. Barny Frank opened the flood gates for easy loans to financial dumb bells who thought they could get something for nothing... and continue to vote for democrats. Obama represents all of the above....</Msg><Username>sinfuel</Username><Timestamp>1349301773026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349301901230-331</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>deborautf7201</Username><Timestamp>1349301901230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349302500493-332</Id><Title>Why should they lend?</Title><Msg>In the last two months we had approached two local banks for a line of credit to have the option to buy a house locally with leverage. We're not mentioning any bank's name other than to say one was regional, the other national. We have an 800 credit score a home paid-for, and in one of the banks is deposited more than we were asking for a loan. Both turned us down by continually asking more and more info.. Why? No need to lend, the bail-out money and U.S. bond interest is small, but steady with that bail-out money. Don't believe us? Try it!</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1349302500493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:15:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349302673324-333</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pressure for Mitt Romney is not having change for a $100 dollar bill. Romney's gold digger wife feels pressure when she has a hang nail.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349302673324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349302750440-334</Id><Title>Bloomberg California Muni Bankruptcies a Growing ‘Disease,’ Kotok Says</Title><Msg>America's GREECE(California) IS Totally SCREWED!!!!!!!!!!!!!! I Wonder what State is going to need a Bailout First, Californian, Illinois or Michigan and ALL Run by FRICKING "*****LIBERALS*****"!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Watch How RETAIL Sales Collapses in October and set the Stage for the NEXT Budget Nightmare for State Taxpayers!!!!!!!!!!! Refinery problems send California gas prices skyrocketing California Gasoline Jumps a Second Day to Record on Exxon Flare California Gasoline at Record High on Exxon Upset, Pipeline Shut California Muni Bankruptcies a Growing ‘Disease,’ Kotok Says California Cities in 'Conga Line' For Fiscal Trouble Calif. bond debt eats up bigger chunk of General Fund California's bond indebtedness is estimated to jump to nearly 9 percent of the state's General Fund, costing each Californian about $2,400 a year to pay it off. California’s Ballyhooed Recovery? Oh Dude! AND SO Much MORE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! California IS Totally SCREWED!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Read ALL About IT Where "The REAL News Matters" Reelecting Obama Guarantees America's Greece(California) WILL Need a Taxpayer Bailout in the NEXT 2 YEARS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1349302750440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349303136160-335</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They never had all the democrats vote for anything, Blue Dog Dems are Republicans with a D after their name. Thank God for Republican Arlen Specter, without him, we would not have that great healthcare program from President Obama. Thank you Mr. Specter, you are a true American.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349303136160</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349303382976-336</Id><Title>Pimco's Gross warns: Bonds will be 'burned to a crisp' if US fails to tackle debt</Title><Msg>Pimco's Gross warns: Bonds will be 'burned to a crisp' if US fails to tackle debt Large tax increase looms at year-end "fiscal cliff" By Andrew Taylor The Associated Press US Debt Soars To $16,159,487,013,300.35, +$93 Billion; Or How To Kick Off Fiscal 2013 Average American household now owes $137,000 as share of national debt READ All About IT Where "The REAL News Matters" Reelecting Obama WILL Be the Greatest Mistake the American Middle Class could DO to Itself!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1349303382976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349304326043-337</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, we remember Obama has both a democratic-controlled House and Senate for 2 years while he played golf and traveled, where were those bills then?</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1349304326043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306282615-338</Id><Topic><Title>You should view this profile (BAC)</Title><Username>alishagzx063071</Username><Timestamp>1349270354448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:19:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>mintazdr016688</Username><Timestamp>1349306282615</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306303027-339</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You obviously have never signed the front of a paycheck. I have, Mitt Romney has, it takes Big nuts with all the risk to employ people. You must be a taker with NO CLUE. Did you go smoke pot with the protesters on Wall Street? And don't insult me, I am a female!</Msg><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1349306303027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349306362713-340</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My feeling about what happened to the Ambassador and his escorts? Deep regret and sorrow. However, keep in mind that Stevens had historically and regularly eschewed escorts and heavy security in favor of approachability and openness and close interaction with the Libyan people and their culture outside the embassy's enclave. He did not subscribe to or succumb to the bunker mentality that is so prevalent in diplomatic circles; in fact, these very characteristics played a large part in his naming as ambassador. Also, as regrettable and possibly foreseeable as this tragedy may have been, it in no way should eclipse the far larger and sustained daily body count we're been running up in Iraq and Afghanistan, or the ones we HAVEN'T been running up in Syria and Libya. In fact, during the Vietnam War, 4 American deaths in a single day would have been a GREAT day. I'd love to know how many of our citizens died there under easily foreseeable circumstances. How about exploring some alternate perspectives on this matter? After all, if this incident had occurred on Bush's watch, you'd be defending his vision and courage, not excoriating him and screaming for his head or declaring him unfit to lead. Did the original article by any chance mention if the heartfelt regret expressed by Dr. Elsaadi was tainted by originating in the mind of an Islamist? Just wondering, because early on, the qualifier "radical" was used in front of "Islamist", but towards the end of the article it has devolved to this: 'No more "diversity." No more "multiculturalism." No more "understanding." No more "root causes." No more political correctness. No more "sensitivity." This does not work with Islamists, because like leftists, they do not have one. They hate for the sake of hate.' Note that the modifier "radical" has become conspicuous by its absence. This is precisely the kind of underhanded, deceptive journalism that the Washington Times is famous for. ROTFLMAO every word they print is true, but after the Times has combined them to make sentences like these, the truth of them has pretty much evaporated.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349306362713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349306388325-341</Id><Title>CHRISTOPHER STEVENS blood is on the mon///key boy hands as well as hillarys</Title><Msg>trai///tors are are running the USA.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349306388325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349307480293-342</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt is a self made man all he had to start with was money and connections.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1349307480293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349307635399-343</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No need...Mormney and Rethuglicans demean and insult females every day.</Msg><Username>neondros</Username><Timestamp>1349307635399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349307840363-344</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349272506056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. Romney will self-destruct. I think Obama should not attack him at all. Or if he does, he should handle him with kid gloves. Just allow him... as Romney has no doubts while he delivers untruths with #$%$-sureness and knee-jerk reaction. The fact checkers will be at work and the media will point it out soon. Romney is reactive and sorely lacks deeper thinking and reflection when he knows 40 million folks are watching him... conditioning that is in his development and character makeup. However, Obama should be respectful... in behavior and through his body language. I never liked Al Gore's 'invading' into GWB space in their debate and voted for GWB- only once in 2000!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349307840363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349308082170-345</Id><Title>IF YOU DON'T HAVE A BUDGET....YOU'RE OUT ....COUNTRY CAN NOT BE ALLOWED TO GO BK</Title><Msg>I have nothing against OBAMA but if you run the country for 4 years withouit a BUDGET the COUNTRY will go BANKRUPT . It is as simple as that</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349308082170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349308172049-346</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paris, we do know from your many previous posts you're among the blind followers of the GOP! Have a nice day!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349308172049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349308605147-347</Id><Title>ATTD distribution agreement announcement, 2200% GAINS POSSIBLE ,READ</Title><Msg>ATTD distribution agreement announcement, 2200% GAINS POSSIBLE ,READ DISTRIBUTION AGREEMENT ANNONCEMENT WITH WALMART STORES ANY DAY NOW. Attitude Drinks, has recently announced record orders and expanded distribution of their recently launched Phase III Energy Recovery drink and brand, and has made tremendous progress as of late, by increasing that distribution to the likes of Walgreen's in Florida and Sam's Mart Stores in the Carolinas and Georgia. ATTD is expected to pull in tens of Millions. Analyst suggests ATTD is ready for a MASSIVE BREAKOUT. This Stock price has the potential to 5cents to 20cents. And buying the stock for nothing at 0.0006 will bring unbelievable profit. Buying 1 million shares@ 0.0009, cost= $900. Sell 1 million shares@ 1 cent = $10,000 or 5 cents= $50,000 With 2200% gains, ATTD can turn around your losses and bring your trading account back positive.</Msg><Username>agreenview</Username><Timestamp>1349308605147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349308822630-348</Id><Title>When will BAC announce a dividend to its loyal share holders?</Title><Msg>Sure would be a nice XMAS gift this year.</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349308822630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349309065973-349</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Made A Big Mistake In 2010, Tea Party Congress Holding America Back, No Jobs</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349264492414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Fireunder...do you pray to Marx or Olinsky?</Msg><Username>sasnik9</Username><Timestamp>1349309065973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:04:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349309150712-350</Id><Topic><Title>When will BAC announce a dividend to its loyal share holders?</Title><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1349308822630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:00:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing more then .01 cents this year. I do think that in 2013 we will see some movement on a request to raise the div. I suspect it will go to .04 cents or .12 per year. That will keep 10.00-11.00 as a floor with maybe a small 2 billion at thier descreation buyback( real reason is kick shorts in the #$%$ when they dump).</Msg><Username>tax1099nc</Username><Timestamp>1349309150712</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349309555397-351</Id><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Msg>I hope after the election, this administration investigate this Cayman Island thief and put him in jail for cheating uncle sam.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349309753256-352</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just received your first email. It's very informational. Love it.</Msg><Username>espinoza.flynn43</Username><Timestamp>1349309753256</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349310089427-353</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA &amp; HILLARY CLINTON ARE AT FAULT FOR CHRISTOPHER STEVENS DEATH...</Title><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1349223551735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 20:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. I call.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349310089427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311568144-354</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349272506056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama just needs to keep his eagerness to explain in check. State his position, and then lay off the nuts-and-bolts detailed explanations. Romney, on the other hand, needs to fill in a few details on what his latest shake of the Etch-a-Sketch has failed to display. ROTFLMAO why am I thinking of Muhammed Ali and the Rope-A-Dope strategy right now?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349311568144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311691406-355</Id><Topic><Title>Pimco's Gross warns: Bonds will be 'burned to a crisp' if US fails to tackle debt</Title><Username>ppedroli</Username><Timestamp>1349303382976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:29:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ romney is not the president. yet. he cannot possibly be a "problem."</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349311691406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349311704237-356</Id><Title>LET THE DEBATE BEGIN!</Title><Msg>I remember seeing a very interesting bumper sticker on an old beat-up (beetle) Volkswagen car that read "When I grow up I wanna be a Cadillac". I laughed loudly! Actually that must have been at least 20 years ago. Mr. Romney made me remember that... The mind is a wonderful thing. That bumper sticker was so funny given how unrealistic was the statement based on reality. So is Mr. Mitt Romney's situation... as a candidate for president of the U.S. Mr. Romney, why don't you stick to reality and spare us, our nation and your family the trouble of confirming formally how unfit and unprepared you happen to be! You can't become a Cadillac, Mr. Romney!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349311704237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349311743203-357</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are a big time Kool-Aid drinker! You have a nice day also young man!</Msg><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1349311743203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349312478479-358</Id><Title>Go Romney</Title><Msg>Tired of the Libertards leaching off of the hard workers in this country.</Msg><Username>supersoaker30</Username><Timestamp>1349312478479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349312527420-359</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought that was one among the many privileges of the super rich 1% enjoys. It is a fact that the politicians enact the laws so that to protect their riches and make them richer.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349312527420</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349314146977-360</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I followed your reports since last week. Nice work.</Msg><Username>nash.summers56</Username><Timestamp>1349314146977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314661152-361</Id><Title>Obama is getting smashed in this debate. Romney has taken him to the matt 36 of the 37 minutes</Title><Msg>stay tuned</Msg><Username>retiringat49</Username><Timestamp>1349314661152</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314902964-362</Id><Title>romney is in complete control - what a great leader he will be</Title><Msg>obama is getting hammered!!!</Msg><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1349314902964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:41:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349314964290-363</Id><Title>bring on Biden - Ryan is ging to rip him to shreds</Title><Msg>hahahahahah</Msg><Username>retiringat49</Username><Timestamp>1349314964290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349315256325-364</Id><Title>Curious George</Title><Msg>I can't help but think of curious George when I see obama</Msg><Username>jmpinsonn</Username><Timestamp>1349315256325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315431846-365</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hhmmm - please tell me why Romney is getting criticized for the Cayman Island tax break when the Clintons did the same thing. please get your facts straight!</Msg><Username>retiringat49</Username><Timestamp>1349315431846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349315598464-366</Id><Title>ROMNEY IS KICKING BOZO'S A</Title><Msg>This president is out of his league. His lack of business sense is stunning</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349315598464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315636264-367</Id><Topic><Title>BIG TROUBLE FOR ROMNEY:Wife Said Mitt Is Having A Very Hard Time Right Now</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349289632338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:40:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what debate are you watching - Obama is like a kindergardener wetting his pants</Msg><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1349315636264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349315726026-368</Id><Topic><Title>THROW IN THE TOWEL, Obama!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1349313935170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amen - obama is pooping in his pants</Msg><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1349315726026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349316376365-369</Id><Topic><Title>Curious George</Title><Username>jmpinsonn</Username><Timestamp>1349315256325</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good thing they aren't having a coconut picking contest</Msg><Username>jmpinsonn</Username><Timestamp>1349316376365</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349317726609-370</Id><Title>NOW I GET IT OBAMA IS DELUSIONAL</Title><Msg>The guy is out of his liberal socialist racist mind</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1349317726609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349317843179-371</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe as they are investigating turbo tax cheat geitner and investigating Gun Running POS Eric Holder and investigating Obamie for turning down more security requests from the now murdered ambassador. Get a clue</Msg><Username>constantenergy43</Username><Timestamp>1349317843179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349318325230-372</Id><Topic><Title>What BAC Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>beckivory125</Username><Timestamp>1349267772072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:36:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read your comments with interest - thanks for continuing to post.</Msg><Username>atkinsw85</Username><Timestamp>1349318325230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349318633709-373</Id><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Msg>Ho-hum. Both candidate looked polished and professional, and neither made any egregious gaffes in content, presentation, or their reactions to each other's statements. The Colorado independent voters' reactions also were neutral or positive for the most part during both candidates' remarks, with only the slightest occasional slip just below the neutral line for either.. In short, they were both full of platitudes and lofty ideals, only somewhat evasive about answering the questions, and both performed well overall. However, this debate took place in what was supposed to be Romney's wheelhouse: the economy, and the repeal of ObamaCare. He really needed to score a game-changer, and I didn't see it happen. The next debates will be in Romney's discomfort zones, foreign policy and military budgets, goals and philosophies. If everyone sticks to their well-rehearsed scripts, I expect Romney will either turn in a par performance, or slip just a little from tonight's performance. Bottom line: barring a surprise knockdown punch from Romney, Obama will be re-elected. I still call it around 53-47 in the popular vote, but Obama will collect more than 300 Electoral College votes when it's all over. Now, let's all resume the bickering.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349318820220-374</Id><Title>President Obama Talks With Real Numbers, Romney Just Makes Plans With No Numbers</Title><Msg>This country will be in big trouble if we listen to another Republican like Romney, The Republicans destroyed this country and put us in debt to the tune of 11.5 Trillion dollars and Romney will continue with the Republican plan, the rich get richer and poor get poorer. Romney needs to work on math because nothing he said adds up, it is all to confuse voters.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349318820220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349319021054-375</Id><Title>ROMNEY DESTROYED DUM////BAMA</Title><Msg>what a performance by romney. five stars plus!</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349319021054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319021082-376</Id><Topic><Title>Go Romney</Title><Username>supersoaker30</Username><Timestamp>1349312478479</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:01:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're tired, take a nap. After you've rested, look up the difference between 'leaching' and 'leeching'. ROTFLMAO I suppose you can always blame your teachers and the lousy job they did instructing you about such distinctions.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349319021082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319255379-377</Id><Topic><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need real numbers, Romney talks a good talk but he knows his 7 Trillion dollar plan must be paid for and we still do not know how. President Obama did not talk over Romney but at some times, he should have. President Obama's plan for the next 10 years does cut 4 trillion dollars but without a Congress to agree, the plan will be lost. The format tonight was better for Romney because he was able to state his plan without any numbers to back that plan up, it did sound good until you ask, how is he going to do that? I give the first debate to Romney because he gave his dream and not a plan that would ever come true in real life and numbers.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1349319255379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319311093-378</Id><Topic><Title>romney is in complete control - what a great leader he will be</Title><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1349314902964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 21:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting view. I sure saw no evidence of it in the crawl line of Colorado undecided voter opinion; nobody scored big or stumbled big. If you have any specific examples, tell us. As far as your opinion, I think you've had it for a long time, and you hardly reflect the swing voters who will decide this race. ROTFLMAO waiting for foreign policy approach and American manufacturing policies to get some air time.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349319311093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349319606839-379</Id><Title>OBAMA has the same old IDEA and promises so the net effect will be INCREASING DEFICIT AND HOMONGOUS DEBT</Title><Msg>He didn't even mention the "GO FORWARD "SLOGAN because it will open up another topic of FORWARDING DEFICIT and DEBT. ROMNEY presented new IDEAS which LOOKS MUCH BETTER while maintaining part of OBAMACARE and NO CUTS on MEDICARE WHICH WILL FURTHER PRESERVE THE MEDICARE. OBAMA will only preserve the MEDICARE for at least 8 years with cuts of 716 billion dollars to FUND the OBAMACARE and raising TAXES every year.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349319606839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349319778509-380</Id><Title>dumb///ama is a fraud. a con artist.</Title><Msg>dumb///ama is a fraud.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1349319778509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319810148-381</Id><Topic><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Obama missed taking an easy shot at Mitt when Romney remarked that Obama was entitled to a house and a car, but not to the facts. I was waiting for him to say: "We all know Romney has many houses and cars; the trouble is that we don't know from one day to the next which one he's going to be living in and driving." I still call it too close to a draw to give either an edge.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349319810148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349319978849-382</Id><Topic><Title>This pretty much says it all....and from a educated person of color...Mychal Massie is a respected writer and talk show host in Los Angeles.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1347063125976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:12:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*****</Msg><Username>dons_st</Username><Timestamp>1349319978849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320039606-383</Id><Topic><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>four more years of obummer and a dem majority in the senate and US will see a deficit north of 20 trillion. You are truly dreaming if you think obummer has any intentions if lowing the deficit. He is a tax and spend liberal, period.-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349320039606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320056236-384</Id><Title>Obama smoked bad weed tonite</Title><Msg>He looked like a stoned head....slurred speech....incoherrent....and looking at his finger nails all the times.... What an idiot !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349320056236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320173504-385</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA has the same old IDEA and promises so the net effect will be INCREASING DEFICIT AND HOMONGOUS DEBT</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349319606839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The TV CAMERA keeps on focusing their BACKS how their posture is.......OBAMA all the time standing on his left leg with his right leg bent on the knee...A BAD SIGN .....LIKE TELLING ...... "I WANT TO STEP OUT OF HERE BECAUSE I HAVE NO LEGS TO STAND ON...... ON THIS DEBATE" and ROMNEY was in FULL ATTENTION WITH BOTH STRAIGHT LEG......</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349320173504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320397772-386</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA has the same old IDEA and promises so the net effect will be INCREASING DEFICIT AND HOMONGOUS DEBT</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349319606839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:00:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REPLAY THE VIDEO AND SEE THE DIFFERENCE...ROMNEY VERY PRESIDENTIAL STANDING ON BOTH LEGS.... WHILE OBAMA WAS STANDING ON ONE LEFT LEG FOR ALMOST 1 1/2 HR. ....It is like saying I want to jump out of here.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349320397772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320417956-387</Id><Title>Romney</Title><Msg>Mitt just told Osama and the American people that Government will not solve the problem, but is the problem. Us Americans in the free market competing will create more jobs and opportunity than any ridiculous socialist big government could even fatham....... period. Now lets get Romney in office and get to work on building this Great Nation back up !!!!!</Msg><Username>niceicenick</Username><Timestamp>1349320417956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320671209-388</Id><Topic><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are you saying...... Romney is wrong for having multiple cars and houses... Are you jealous ??</Msg><Username>niceicenick</Username><Timestamp>1349320671209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320708671-389</Id><Title>Romney showed Obama to be the Incompetent boob that he is. Obama will get to play even more golf after November</Title><Msg>Congrats Romney backers and the American people</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349320708671</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349320738073-390</Id><Topic><Title>Romney</Title><Username>niceicenick</Username><Timestamp>1349320417956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P[lay the video of the debate and fast forward it and you will notice that the PBS camera keep focusing on how they stand (camera focused on their backs) OBAMA for 1 1/2 hr was standing on his left leg with the right leg bent on the knee......like telling " can't wait to get out of here" while ROMNEY was in full attention standing on both LEGS STRAIGHT........VERY VERY PRESIDENTIAL</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349320738073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320944115-391</Id><Title>Romney won and this is why</Title><Msg>Both men told us how bad things have been the last 4yrs and what a mess we are in and what they want to do to fix it but the fact is only one man has had a record these last 4yrs and that is Obama. Where have you been mr president? You can't deny you have been president these last 4yrs or are you trying to deny that too?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349320944115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321047511-392</Id><Title>Romney KNOCKED OUT Obama !!!!</Title><Msg>Hee hee LOL stupid Democrats must be weeping by the river of Babylon !!!! What a bunch of social parasites !!!!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349321047511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321165117-393</Id><Topic><Title>Obama smoked bad weed tonite</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349320056236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to cut him some slack the only interviews he allows are to hollywood reporters and adoring liberals. He has never actually been asked a tough question in 4yrs and he well is new at this.</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1349321165117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321378103-394</Id><Title>The Liberal Media should be thrown in Prison for Corruption and Collusion with the Obama Campaign</Title><Msg>Romney looked more presidential than Obama. They have told us how crazy and out of touch Romeny is. I say throw the entire press corps in prison</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349321378103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:29:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321526689-395</Id><Topic><Title>1st Debate - impressions</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349318633709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 22:43:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. I was drawing a parallel between his full complement of residences and vehicles, and the full complement of sets of facts that he switches between on an almost-daily basis. Every day there's a different Romney citing a different set of facts, often in direct conflict to the ones he cited the day before.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1349321526689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:32:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321661426-396</Id><Title>ROMNEY "whoops" NOBAMA !! NOBAMA KNOWS NOTHING !!!!!</Title><Msg>....GOODBYE NOBAMA !!!!!!!!!!!!! About time !!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1349321661426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321684198-397</Id><Topic><Title>Obama smoked bad weed tonite</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349320056236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tonite we saw what a US president should be. Sadly i am talking about Romney and not obummer. GO ROMNEY!!!-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349321684198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349321713094-398</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You pathetic piece of garbage. You are just PO'd that Obama got spanked tonight. Romney's tax returns were audited 100%, he did not break any laws. This is the kind of low-life, spoiled-brat character assassination that liar libs are famous for. You cannot deny that Romney won huge tonight, so you come back with your pathetic totally fabricated liar accusation. You have zero credibility. You make yourself out to be an idiot. You should be sued for slander.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1349321713094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321902892-399</Id><Title>Obama was very uneasy during the DEBATE......FOR 1-1/2 HOUR HE WAS STANDING ON HIS LEFT LEG WITH HIS RIGHT KNEE BENT AS IF HE WAS READY TO JUMP OUT BECAUSE HE HAS NO LEG TO STAND ON.</Title><Msg>While ROMNEY was standing on both LEGS STRAIGHT and very relaxed.......... VERY VERY PRESIDENTIAL. One thing I learned in PUBLIC SPEAKING ....ALWAYS STAND STRAIGHT and YOU WILL BALANCED YOUR THOUGHTS and BRAIN will keep on flowing.... Standing on one leg for 1-1/2 hour especially the left is a sign on uneasiness and fear (as if ready to step out) with your right leg bent on the knee and ready to walk out. Standing on left leg also showed that your right brain was doing the thinking because the right brain controls the left leg and is not the dominant hemisphere. The left brain is considered to be the DOMINANT HEMISPHERE.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349321902892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321971942-400</Id><Title>national debt</Title><Msg>i have figured out how to pay off all of the US Govt. Debt. Just get biden to take back his beer can empties. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349321971942</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322094950-401</Id><Title>Obama would've done better had he</Title><Msg>put out an empty chair</Msg><Username>dn_shapiro</Username><Timestamp>1349322094950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322165862-402</Id><Title>Best Line of the Night: Mr. President you believe the Government should pick winners and losers, well Mr. President you only pick the losers</Title><Msg>and now all of us not just our kids are stuck with this debt</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349322165862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322209654-403</Id><Title>No teleprompter, no place to hide. Obama was revealed as the empty suit that he has always been.</Title><Msg>Obama looked weak, distant like he was daydreaming about being on the View with the all the Lib Ladies fussing over him. That ought to be an eye opener for all of you Obamanoids. He doesn't have a clue, he is a pretty front man with no real substance and totally the wrong plan for this country.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349322209654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322322755-404</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY SHOULD GO TO JAIL FOR CHEATING ON HIS TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1349309555397</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 20:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's it? That is all you have.! You have nothing. Tonite the liberal media could not protect obummer. Obummer did not look very presidential, period, jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1349322322755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322340457-405</Id><Topic><Title>The Liberal Media should be thrown in Prison for Corruption and Collusion with the Obama Campaign</Title><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349321378103</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:29:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have a ton of explaining to do</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349322340457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322514312-406</Id><Title>wow tonight he REVEALED that he is only good for the VIEW</Title><Msg>that is all I can say.....</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349322514312</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322560377-407</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood has been Vindicated. The chair did better than Obama tonight</Title><Msg>God bless Clint Eastwood. The Liberal media should be thrown in prison for collusion with the Obama campaign</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349322560377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322607765-408</Id><Topic><Title>Obama was very uneasy during the DEBATE......FOR 1-1/2 HOUR HE WAS STANDING ON HIS LEFT LEG WITH HIS RIGHT KNEE BENT AS IF HE WAS READY TO JUMP OUT BECAUSE HE HAS NO LEG TO STAND ON.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1349321902892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:38:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney won the debate as it would be in a debating club. That is forgetting all about the real Romney. He certainly was more prepared and also at ease. Let's see in few days if the polls will show a bounce for him. At least a bounce that would erase his lag in states that are crucial for him like Ohio, Florida, etc., etc. If that happens it really means he convinced many undecided and independents. Otherwise it will be bad news for him. As an independent I am not impressed when it comes to substance. The presidency is not going to be won by being just a good debater. It's always easy to tear down those who already have done are doing a job from one who is an outsider saying I will do a better job... especially coming from Romney who is very well on record and one who is a flip flopper.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1349322607765</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322653731-409</Id><Topic><Title>No teleprompter, no place to hide. Obama was revealed as the empty suit that he has always been.</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1349322209654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:43:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama would do well to resign.</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349322653731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322702214-410</Id><Title>3 More Debates Like this and Obama may Lose worse than Walter Mondale</Title><Msg>Could get very ugly for democrats</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349322702214</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:51:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349322805675-411</Id><Title>Throw the Liberal Media in Prison for Collusion with the Obama Campaign</Title><Msg>Romney looked presidential and cleaned Obama's clock not what the Liberal press has been telling us. CORRUPT LIARS!!!!</Msg><Username>broke.obama55</Username><Timestamp>1349322805675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322831886-412</Id><Topic><Title>This pretty much says it all....and from a educated person of color...Mychal Massie is a respected writer and talk show host in Los Angeles.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1347063125976</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:12:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you haven't read "The Communist" by Paul Kengor it is well worth the read; chronicles the life of Frank Marshall Davis, a black Marxist-Leninist of the highest order. Davis is the Frank in Obama's "Dreams" book. Davis was a card carrying member of the Communist Party USA, and a prolific writer, and so radical that he was on the FBIs list to be jailed in the event of a conflict with the Russiians. Davis was transferred from Chicago to Hawaii by the CPUSA to infiltrate the Longshore Workers Union. Davis grew up in Kansas. Stanley Armour Dunham was Obama's maternal grandfather, also grew up in Kansas. Dunham was also a Marxist sympathizer. Obama lived next door to Frank, and soon became under his tutelage. Hope and Change, vilification of anyone successful, etc. all part of the communist teachings expounded by Davis. When Obama when to Occidental he met the founder of the Marxist society John Drew, who described Obama as far left of him. Go to Youtube, type in "Obama Dr. John Drew" and catch what Obama was spewing at that time. Thanks, Babydox</Msg><Username>babydox73</Username><Timestamp>1349322831886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349322894449-413</Id><Topic><Title>Obama would've done better had he</Title><Username>dn_shapiro</Username><Timestamp>1349322094950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and Jim Leher even steered him back on topic and it still didn't help him</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349322894449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349323049353-414</Id><Title>It only Gets Better for the Incumbent Democrats Biden faces Ryan next week</Title><Msg>I think Biden may get so worked up he throws a chair</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349323049353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349323147337-415</Id><Topic><Title>Obama smoked bad weed tonite</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1349320056236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:07:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Obama just showed up like usual and normally the libtards in the media ask him what his favorite food is..you know tough questions like that</Msg><Username>jack_ste56</Username><Timestamp>1349323147337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:59:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>