<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350878664882-1</Id><Topic><Title>Any Obama fans here ?</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350873255909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama whispered to Putin....This is my last election....Wait til I am President again I will be flexible on missiles defense Obama cares more for his job than the livelihoood of America</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350878664882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350879007266-2</Id><Topic><Title>Any Obama fans here ?</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350873255909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Becuase you pathetic dumb-as-rats losers just don't wanna work. That's why voting for Obama is your bare necessity !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350879007266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350879016595-3</Id><Title>I got a great idea...give everybody food stamps??? hell I don't want to pay for food ...ilmfao</Title><Msg>I want a free cell phone..it doesn't have to be an apple..a samsung will do..free gas..free heat and free food stamps...don't worry about my house payment Bank of American can't get me out anyway...ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350879016595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350879193337-4</Id><Topic><Title>Any Obama fans here ?</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350873255909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I shooting my heroin at the moment. Will comment later.</Msg><Username>seezhunter</Username><Timestamp>1350879193337</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350879200389-5</Id><Topic><Title>I got a great idea...give everybody food stamps??? hell I don't want to pay for food ...ilmfao</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350879016595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:10:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can I want to be able to buy my bud lite with food stamps..ilmfao...I guess i'll still have to sell some for my drugs,,,ilmfao...now i'm going to love this socialism..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350879200389</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350879897042-6</Id><Title>Romney can't win!!! the reason is he won't pay for birth control pills for woman!!!! hell mitt spade the%$#@@##$</Title><Msg>i'm got my dog spade...cut dog can't have no pups..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350879897042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350880196253-7</Id><Topic><Title>Any Obama fans here ?</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350873255909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama is my hero...he had sex with more americans than any man in history...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350880196253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:29:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350880419609-8</Id><Title>i'll never vote for another white man....obama is the first president to get corn to $8.49..and my rbob made me 2 million this year....</Title><Msg>obama is my hero...ilmfao...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350880419609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350881315250-9</Id><Title>We had a tough day, not optimal, it's Hillary's fault, it's Obama's fault, it's not Al Qaeda, it is Al Qaeda, it was the video, it was a spontaneous attack, it was planned...</Title><Msg>Well one thing is clear. Obama and his handlers have the smoke machine running full throttle to just get past November 6th. What we know and what is INDISPUTABLE is four innocent and brave Americans died unspeakably horrendous deaths DIRECTLY as a result of a complete lack of adequate security. If Obama is going to take credit 5000 times for killing Bin Laden then guess what? He gets "credit" for Benghazi.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1350881315250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 00:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350882166477-10</Id><Title>Another Sign of Economic Recovery</Title><Msg>Housing Starts At Highest Point Since 2008 In yet another positive economic indicator, the Census Bureau released new data on Wednesday showing energizing news for the housing market. The housing recovery surged in September, fueled by a rate of home building at its highest point since 2008. Housing starts in the U.S. grew by 15 percent from last month as 872,000 homes began construction. Additionally, building permits for privately-owned houses swelled by 11.6 percent relative to August, at an annual rate of 894,000. Mortgage rates are now at record lows, and with the third round of quantitative easing (QE3) announced by the Federal Reserve last month — a plan to buy $40 billion in mortgage-backed securities each month indefinitely — rates will likely remain low in the near future. The latest report from the Department of Commerce is a boon to the labor market, which will likely see construction jobs slowly tick back to pre-recession numbers. Construction employment suffered particularly as a result of the housing bubble that popped in 2007. Last week, JPMorgan Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon released a statement expressing newfound confidence in the recovery. “Importantly, we believe the housing market has turned the corner,” he said. “In our Mortgage Banking business, we were encouraged that credit trends continued to modestly improve.” Prior to the housing report, U.S. banks were already benefiting from the recovery. The Wall Street Journal wrote, “The recent pickup in home prices and the growing sense that housing has finally bounced off a bottom should increase lending activity.” Given the huge contribution of real estate to the gross domestic product—as much as 18 percent—a stabilizing housing market has the potential to have significant effect on jobs and the economy. The strong housing numbers are just the latest recent piece of good economic news; in October alone, unemployment fell to 7.8 percent, jobless claims dropped to their lowest level in four years, and consumer confidence rose to a five year high.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350882166477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882233092-11</Id><Topic><Title>i've said here lately obama would win..the good people of ohio will put him back in...now I can live with it can you??</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350874301925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...do I look like a fool....", you asked. If you look as stupid as you write, no doubt you do look like a fool, IDIOt! You can't be from Ohio. You might live there now, but you are not native to Ohio. I am proud of my state of Ohio and proud to know Ohio will have a major role in re-electing President Obama. Montgomery County is solidly Obama. The early voting polls indicate Obama is the choice for 63% of Ohio's (to date) 400,000 early voters.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882233092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882407887-12</Id><Topic><Title>Intelligence Shows No Planning for Benghazi Consulate Attack</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1350795900939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 01:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The repug liars can't get over the FACTS. They just have to keep spinning lies.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882407887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882507735-13</Id><Topic><Title>The blue states STILL trump the red states. Obama WILL be re-elected.</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1350585744963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 14:42:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the liars at Fox have Obama winning the electoral college vote.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882507735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882527835-14</Id><Topic><Title>Another Sign of Economic Recovery</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350882166477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:02:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A landslide win for president obama is in the making! many of gop rep/obstructionists/tp's will be thrown out of congress.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350882527835</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882662040-15</Id><Topic><Title>How is it that none of you small minded uptight republicans don't get that Obama has won?</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350719228456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 03:47:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No electoral college discussion on this board. Just repugs slinging idiotic lies and slander. The fools don't understand that Obama has won.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882662040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882798741-16</Id><Topic><Title>Another Sign of Economic Recovery</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350882166477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:02:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More good news about Obama's policies affecting the economic recovery.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882798741</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350882823440-17</Id><Title>obanana is a criminal, high treason, impeach now.</Title><Msg>.............</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350882823440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350882920122-18</Id><Title>15 Days Until the Re-Election of President Obama</Title><Msg>We're planning a huge party for the night of Nov. 6 to celebrate.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882920122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350882996724-19</Id><Topic><Title>obanana is a criminal, high treason, impeach now.</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350882823440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:13:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sick fool, go tell your stupid lies to the neo-nazi chat room</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350882996724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350883122801-20</Id><Title>support Romney, vote the criminals out!</Title><Msg>the criminal mon\\\k ey must be got rid of.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350883122801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350883149525-21</Id><Topic><Title>Rose garden statement on Bengazi</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350440402004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And still, the spin from the neo-nazis is a stupid and as idiotic as ever. The truth just does not register with republican fools.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350883149525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350883277442-22</Id><Topic><Title>REPUG LOSERS: does your incessant twaddle-fest assuage the pain of imminent loss?</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1350175751321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big parties planned world wide to celebrate Obama's re-election.</Msg><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1350883277442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350885568145-23</Id><Topic><Title>support Romney, vote the criminals out!</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350883122801</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:18:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we can vote new criminals in!</Msg><Username>dasafwy</Username><Timestamp>1350885568145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 01:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350886352604-24</Id><Title>Bac's earnings will continue to grow with housing market</Title><Msg>Bac will be a little choppy the next couple weeks until we get the election results. All banks should be strong until April. Three reasons: improvement in housing market, continued buying back of bad mortgages, and this is historically the best time of year to hold banks(nov-apr). Once we get approval to raise the dividend this will be a twenty dollar stock</Msg><Username>tonybyford63</Username><Timestamp>1350886352604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 02:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350887383810-25</Id><Title>The Economy is Recovering ... and Romney has Nothing, Zero... Zilch to do with it.</Title><Msg>Spoiler Alert..... He was a "suit" when he started and he is still a"suit" Romney is the pretender of all pretenders the flopper of the highest order.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350887383810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 02:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350890579305-26</Id><Title>If Romney wins, I'm going to start cheating, lying and stealing like he does.</Title><Msg>WTH. I figure if the people in this country vote a known, proven cheat and vulture like Romey in to the Presidency, then why fight 'em. It's easy, and very profitable, to cheat on taxes, hide income, collude with "job makers" (ho ho ) and lie about your motives and intentions. I'll be damned if I'm going to be the last patriotic fool getting fleeced and reamed. Maybe when the system collapses there will be an opportunity for the majority to return to real morals.</Msg><Username>venturian321</Username><Timestamp>1350890579305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 03:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350890997283-27</Id><Title>NTWK $6.0 …..Analyst Target: $16…...Pre-earnings rally to start…... Only 6 PE is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 40 % revenue growth and $1/share net income .…..Two Cloud divisions are growing exponentially …Insiders have purchased 5% of company since 2010 and never sold a share. 4 million share float…. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenue than today.</Title><Msg>Short-term Target: $16 per Upgrade……… Record 1Q 2013 earnings 2 weeks away…….radar this one In 2010 global software provider Netsol Technologies (NASDAQ: NTWK) went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including 2 new high-growth high-margin Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q 2012 CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>makeuiner</Username><Timestamp>1350890997283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 03:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350891208208-28</Id><Title>Buy NCQ as much as you can, like no tomorrow.</Title><Msg>money to be made on this one</Msg><Username>bigappl2011</Username><Timestamp>1350891208208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 03:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350893000540-29</Id><Title>Loser retarded redneck tea baggers don't get Obama has won the electoral college vote</Title><Msg>That means Obama wins re-election.</Msg><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893000540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350893250301-30</Id><Topic><Title>i've said here lately obama would win..the good people of ohio will put him back in...now I can live with it can you??</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350874301925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 22:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A trailer house on a third of an acre does not make a farm, redneck a**s**s** f**u**kkker</Msg><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893250301</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350893352417-31</Id><Topic><Title>Loser retarded redneck tea baggers don't get Obama has won the electoral college vote</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893000540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Acccording to the Vegas pros, Romney gets 303 Electoral votes! Romney 2-1 over the failed politican!</Msg><Username>estero655</Username><Timestamp>1350893352417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350895162396-32</Id><Topic><Title>Loser retarded redneck tea baggers don't get Obama has won the electoral college vote</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893000540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So wrong, so very, very wrong. Obama is a 2-1 favorite. Don't be stupid. Don't bet against the house.</Msg><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350895162396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350896034241-33</Id><Topic><Title>Loser retarded redneck tea baggers don't get Obama has won the electoral college vote</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893000540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hell boy we realize the f--kin jigger is going to win...we also realize that socialism maxism and communism is all around us...we realize the communist party with kill anyone that doesn't bent over to them...see this is about your food stamps and it is about freedom to us...also realize that when push comes to shove you will not fight..your the same people that danced in the streets in the 60 and 70s and call yourself flower child...boy when it comes down to it the tea party will move on you..we showed you socialist we world march on you..we got more ways to get our country back than a fixed voting box..you best remember this..</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350896034241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350896040776-34</Id><Title>Liar Tea Bagger #$%$ never support their candidate. Why? All they do is try to smear Obama.</Title><Msg>Apparently, Romney doe not represent the interests of the Tea Bag neo-nazis, so they do not support him.</Msg><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896040776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350896496901-35</Id><Title>Lying Tea Bag S*c*u*m* do not support moderate Mitt? Why? Is he not neo-nazi enough?</Title><Msg>All the liar tea bag s*c*u*m* do is attempt to slam and smear Obama. Why? Is their candidate not extremist enough? Try to find ONE post that supports Romney by the LIAR tea bags. It cannot be done. They are here to do nothing but LIE about Obama.e</Msg><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896496901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350896865840-36</Id><Title>Early voting turnout 63% for Obama</Title><Msg>The numbers favoring Obama are huge.</Msg><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896865840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:07:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350897992921-37</Id><Topic><Title>How is it that none of you small minded uptight republicans don't get that Obama has won?</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350719228456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 03:47:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple addition is beyond their comprehension. Repugs are know for their incredible stupidity.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1350897992921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350898855188-38</Id><Title>Ever notice how just before every wave of retiring groups, Wall street crooks crash the stock market?</Title><Msg>You have the next wave, beaten up by 2008 but back up a little getting ready to pull the plug on equities and move to cash or bonds....watch out group, better move early, because the Wall street crooks watch the demgraphic shifts! Long term buy and hold only works if you are out when the crooks drain the coffers!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1350898855188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350902546110-39</Id><Title>Obama takes Ohio due to auto bailout.. Game over Mitt.. See ya in church</Title><Msg>Mormon.</Msg><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350902546110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 06:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350903291193-40</Id><Topic><Title>Intelligence Shows No Planning for Benghazi Consulate Attack</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1350795900939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 01:05:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will drop like a rock in polls if he pushes this issue any more, Fox and their worthless will keep their liars coming on to say U.S. intelligence is helping the President?? The President should send a drone to Fox and wipe them out..</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350903291193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 06:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904110586-41</Id><Topic><Title>Early voting turnout 63% for Obama</Title><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896865840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:07:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New polls don't count the already voted. They are only numbers for people who have not yet voted. They also do not include people without home phones.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350904110586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350904286266-42</Id><Title>Obama Adm. is determined to destroy America. And we're letting them do it!!!</Title><Msg>Republican Sen. James Inhofe says the Environmental Protection Agency has delayed action or “punted” on numerous regulations while President Obama tries to “earn votes” for a second term. The Oklahoma senator and ranking Republican on the chamber’s Committee on Environment and Public Works has released a report stating that when the agency approves the roughly one dozen regulations next year in 2013, they will “spell doom” for jobs and economic growth. “The Obama-EPA plans to move full speed ahead to implement this agenda if President Obama wins a second term,” Inhofe writes. “These rules taken together will inevitably result in the elimination of millions of American jobs, drive up the price of gas at the pump even more, impose construction bans on local communities and essentially shut down American oil, natural gas and coal production.”</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350904286266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904394755-43</Id><Topic><Title>Another Republican POS in The House Of Congress, William Joseph Walsh</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350753046292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 13:10:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jackson is much better than Walsh,</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350904394755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904480587-44</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Romney And The Plutocrats Represent Everything Wrong With America Today!</Title><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1350666446721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The (R) after the name means Remove and Replace, dump them and move the country forward.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350904480587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904588772-45</Id><Topic><Title>The Economy is Recovering ... and Romney has Nothing, Zero... Zilch to do with it.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350887383810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 02:29:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has spent a billion dollars on TV ads changing his positions that ought to be worth something and then there is all that redistribution of wealth from his rich donors to advertizing companies and he didn't take his charitable deductions this year so his tax rate wouldn't go below 13%.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350904588772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904687646-46</Id><Topic><Title>Congress Could Save America and Create Jobs We Need, GOP Destroy U.S. To Win Election</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350669789316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans will be voted out of Congress, it is clear to all Americans that Republicans destroyed any chance of growth in the hopes of winning an election, it will not work, Americans are not that stupid.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350904687646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350904914055-47</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the Romney plan to make a perfect family, flush the babies with defects..</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350904914055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350905218576-48</Id><Title>SUPN will fly today - better get in p/m</Title><Msg>FDA approval SPN-804 just announced</Msg><Username>jimfromsavannah</Username><Timestamp>1350905218576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350905271808-49</Id><Title>cannabis play CLNP partners with HEMP to sell HEMP PRODUCTS. 0044</Title><Msg>CLNP $100,000+ revenue for september without hemp products. 400+ million float. sponsors the nascar 79 car. do some DD and check the ihub board.</Msg><Username>lofttee</Username><Timestamp>1350905271808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350905400651-50</Id><Title>Just in.. Obama up big in Ohio.. Game over Mitt... back to church Mitt the Mormon.</Title><Msg>glta...</Msg><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350905400651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350905561460-51</Id><Title>Mitt the Mormon's 5 boys AFRAID to fight for this great country..</Title><Msg>glta...</Msg><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350905561460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350907609631-52</Id><Topic><Title>Just in.. Obama up big in Ohio.. Game over Mitt... back to church Mitt the Mormon.</Title><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350905400651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LDS church uses tax free tithing money to build shopping centers...who picks up the slack for their tax evasion??....the non-mormon americans.....yes we make up the difference as thet get rich..what exactly does the book of mormon say??</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1350907609631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350908055957-53</Id><Topic><Title>Rose garden statement on Bengazi</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350440402004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-16 22:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Urichey, did you get your information from the Romney campaign? ROTFLMAO you neocon lemmings are ready and willing to follow Mr. Magic Panties over the cliff and through the Gates of Hell, aren't you?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350908055957</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350908607949-54</Id><Title>THE CHOICE IS CLEAR A FAILED PRESIDENT OR A CONSISTENTLY SUCCESSFUL BUSINESSMAN</Title><Msg>ROMNEY HAS SUCCEEDED AT EVERY TASK HE WAS HANDED.</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350908607949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350908780206-55</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SACRIFICED AMBASSADOR STEVENS AND 3 OTHERS AS TETHERED GOATS FOR SLAUGHTER</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350695706523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BECAUSE THAT' ALL HE HAS</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350908780206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350909183319-56</Id><Topic><Title>Just in.. Obama up big in Ohio.. Game over Mitt... back to church Mitt the Mormon.</Title><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350905400651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it says - for lazy deadbeats - to get a job .!!!!!!!!!! an they built that shopping center - so you could go to work - Now put your little red shoes - on an go to work .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1350909183319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350909214978-57</Id><Title>VOYING BOOTH EPIPHANIES WILL GIVE ROMNEY A LANDSIDE WIN</Title><Msg>PEOPLE KNOW THINGS ARE VERY BAD UNDER OBAMA!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350909214978</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350909267916-58</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt the Mormon's 5 boys AFRAID to fight for this great country..</Title><Username>scalpelxpert45</Username><Timestamp>1350905561460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:32:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you go hero - if not stop running your jaws .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1350909267916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350909394682-59</Id><Title>VOTING BOOTH EPIPHANIES WILL GIVE ROMNEY A LANDSIDE WIN</Title><Msg>When people stop and think they will vote romney especially if they had to buy gas on the way to he polls</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350909394682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350909720605-60</Id><Topic><Title>BAC has had the highest trading volume for quite some time, so</Title><Username>joannab3</Username><Timestamp>1350822567392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 08:29:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks...I really appreciate the detailed reply.</Msg><Username>joannab3</Username><Timestamp>1350909720605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350910177470-61</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $6.0 …..Analyst Target: $16…...Pre-earnings rally to start…... Only 6 PE is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 40 % revenue growth and $1/share net income .…..Two Cloud divisions are growing exponentially …Insiders have purchased 5% of company since 2010 and never sold a share. 4 million share float…. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenue than today.</Title><Username>makeuiner</Username><Timestamp>1350890997283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 03:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>6 PE for a company growing exponentially and profitably? Gotta get me some of this stuff</Msg><Username>davidmilly79</Username><Timestamp>1350910177470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350910218833-62</Id><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Msg>DISGRACEFUL!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350910489203-63</Id><Topic><Title>VOTING BOOTH EPIPHANIES WILL GIVE ROMNEY A LANDSIDE WIN</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350909394682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YEP PEOPLE AREN'T STUPID</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350910489203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350911073088-64</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will force poor people to have babies they don't want. Even threaten to prosecute for murder. Just as long as it does not apply to them.</Msg><Username>myth_rmoney</Username><Timestamp>1350911073088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350911346676-65</Id><Title>WDAY--strong sell</Title><Msg>short it at will--to 40's</Msg><Username>shortburner2012</Username><Timestamp>1350911346676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350911468196-66</Id><Title>Trickle Down Never Worked</Title><Msg>That rain you feel on your back? Looks like Mitt is up on that balcony. He will tell you it is raining; You know better.</Msg><Username>mitt_is_a_crook</Username><Timestamp>1350911468196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350911533765-67</Id><Title>DOANALD TRUMP CLAIMS BARRACH OBAMA BOMSHELL BEFORE THE ELECTION</Title><Msg>Donald Trump said Monday that he will reveal “very big” news about President Barack Obama by Wednesday but declined to give any hints about his plan, he said on “Fox &amp; Friends.” “Something very, very big concerning the president of the United States,” he said. “It’s going to be very big. I know one thing — you will cover it in a very big fashion.” Trump, who said he will announce the news on Twitter “sometime probably Wednesday,” suggested it could “possibly” impact the election. The businessman, who considered a run for the White House but endorsed former Gov. Mitt Romney, has long been a high-profile Obama birther conspiracy theorist. Read more: .politico</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350911533765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350911707122-68</Id><Topic><Title>VOTING BOOTH EPIPHANIES WILL GIVE ROMNEY A LANDSIDE WIN</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350909394682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT'S OVER!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350911707122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350911827588-69</Id><Title>When Barack lived in NY he was Don Trumps Lover</Title><Msg>Don was the "Bottom."</Msg><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350911827588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350911960598-70</Id><Topic><Title>Sell BAC with PEG Ratio 3.42 &amp; buy GDOT with PEG ratio 0.33?</Title><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1350310196479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:09:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could GDOT be bought out by JPC, PayPal/eBay or its like ... There is only one company with the growth and PEG ratio of GDOT available in pre-paid card business ... so the moment one makes an offer others might follow with counter offers ... Won't it be wise to sell BAC and buy GDOT?</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1350911960598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350912163716-71</Id><Title>GREEDINESS MADE ME LOOK STUPPIIDD!!!</Title><Msg>how about you?</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1350912163716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350912203077-72</Id><Title>You helped pay for Don Trumps Buildings</Title><Msg>Don Trump has been bankrupt FOUR times. Each time he declared bankruptcy the bank had to renegotiate the loan amount so that Don make a profit. Taxpayers and bank customers paid the bill. I mean bill as in $Billions. Don is the kind of person Mitt likes to have around. They almost make him feel honest.</Msg><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350912203077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912216160-73</Id><Topic><Title>When Barack lived in NY he was Don Trumps Lover</Title><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350911827588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turn yourself into the closest mental institution.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1350912216160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912775677-74</Id><Topic><Title>DOANALD TRUMP CLAIMS BARRACH OBAMA BOMSHELL BEFORE THE ELECTION</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350911533765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CAN'T WAIT!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350912775677</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912893784-75</Id><Topic><Title>Congress Could Save America and Create Jobs We Need, GOP Destroy U.S. To Win Election</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350669789316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress is the key, interest rates are so low, I would take all the money I could get to turn this country around. For each 1% rise in GDP removes $1 trillion in Debt, Infrastructure spending must start soon, we are $9 trillion behind in fixing our Schools, Bridges and roads, power lines and more need to be changed before the country goes black.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350912893784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912922065-76</Id><Topic><Title>When Barack lived in NY he was Don Trumps Lover</Title><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350911827588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a 5-day old ID, and a history no mother could love. ROTFLMAO and I'll be YOUR mom tells all her friends she's childless.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350912922065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912979774-77</Id><Topic><Title>When Barack lived in NY he was Don Trumps Lover</Title><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350911827588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Ignore".</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350912979774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350912988515-78</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This sounds like something Hitler would do..</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350912988515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350913179570-79</Id><Title>STEVENS' CALLS FOR HELP IGNORED</Title><Msg>Roughly a month earlier, Stevens had signed a two-page cable, also labeled “sensitive,” that he entitled “The Guns of August: Security in Eastern Libya.” Writing on Aug. 8, the ambassador noted that in just a few months’ time, “Benghazi has moved from trepidation to euphoria and back as a series of violent incidents has dominated the political landscape.” He added, “The individual incidents have been organized,” a function of “the security vacuum that a diverse group of independent actors are exploiting for their own purposes.”</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350913179570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913228934-80</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Romney And The Plutocrats Represent Everything Wrong With America Today!</Title><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1350666446721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush Limbaugh is the drug filled leader of the Republican party, Take that overdose Rush, do it live.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350913228934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913448926-81</Id><Topic><Title>Congress Could Save America and Create Jobs We Need, GOP Destroy U.S. To Win Election</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350669789316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone better vote, vote those republicans out, save this country.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350913448926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913536157-82</Id><Topic><Title>DOANALD TRUMP CLAIMS BARRACH OBAMA BOMSHELL BEFORE THE ELECTION</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350911533765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should be good!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350913536157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913548937-83</Id><Topic><Title>STEVENS' CALLS FOR HELP IGNORED</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350913179570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913548937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913616030-84</Id><Topic><Title>Our Ambassador to Libya is murdered while Obama is busy campaigning!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350910007535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913616030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913654601-85</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SACRIFICED AMBASSADOR STEVENS AND 3 OTHERS AS TETHERED GOATS FOR SLAUGHTER</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350695706523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913654601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913717510-86</Id><Topic><Title>Early CIA report blamed militants for Benghazi attack not a movie or a mob Mr. Obama!! and you knew it!!</Title><Username>frankster1955a</Username><Timestamp>1350782597489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913717510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913730339-87</Id><Topic><Title>Intel Reveals the Attack Lasted for 8 hours but Obama did NOTHING</Title><Username>jackcorso49</Username><Timestamp>1350823539495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 08:45:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913730339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913737245-88</Id><Topic><Title>In just 4yrs you go from Hope and Change to High Crimes by Obama</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350791235536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 23:47:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913737245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913744816-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350780920090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:55:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350913744816</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350913774960-90</Id><Topic><Title>The Romney / Ryan Campaign: Nebulous and Obscure by Design. Nondisclosure, hidden assets, blind trusts, offshore accounts, muddled double speak, flip-flops, vague agendas, shadowy cults, undefined plans, sealed tax records, confidential agreements, indecipherable financial records, four military service deferments, dark schemes, financial dodges, private equity funds....</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1346200994509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a bad enough choice but Tea Party Ryan will never be close to being president, the country can't let this woman hater radical near the White House,, bad choice Romney.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350913774960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350914105344-91</Id><Topic><Title>BAC could blow up today! This is why.</Title><Username>jamesslate42</Username><Timestamp>1350493880197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh huh. I saw that also.</Msg><Username>eliashancock315</Username><Timestamp>1350914105344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350914573477-92</Id><Topic><Title>When Barack lived in NY he was Don Trumps Lover</Title><Username>your_racism_is_showing</Username><Timestamp>1350911827588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:17:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>an to think you poor mommy =- gave you birth .!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1350914573477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350915004084-93</Id><Title>Forbes: best bank dividend stock</Title><Msg>http://www.forbes.com/sites/dividendchannel/2012/10/19/top-ranked-dividend-stock-cac-is-oversold/?partner=yahootix</Msg><Username>flsingleguyon</Username><Timestamp>1350915004084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350915434904-94</Id><Topic><Title>This might be a good reason - BAC</Title><Username>albinaylap834325</Username><Timestamp>1350914616104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>queenmuhhz41395</Username><Timestamp>1350915434904</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350915489086-95</Id><Title>The Mormon calendar ends on December 21'st. Why is Mitt running?</Title><Msg>Interesting.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350915489086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350915705123-96</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SACRIFICED AMBASSADOR STEVENS AND 3 OTHERS AS TETHERED GOATS FOR SLAUGHTER</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1350695706523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350915705123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350915730861-97</Id><Title>When you think Mitt Romney...</Title><Msg>Just think small time Bernie Madoff. With better accountants.</Msg><Username>mitt_is_a_crook</Username><Timestamp>1350915730861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:22:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350915794692-98</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>horrible president</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350915794692</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350915797077-99</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Channel bound?</Title><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1350671555578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:32:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like BAC is still in that channel. PPS got walked to the lower boundary, tagged it then turned and is now at $9.51. Guess it'll ping-pong between the two boundaries until something comes along to change it. And I continue to collect in two-fold fashion whenever it gets around the low end...two parts for the longer term basket, one part for a 10-penny trade. ;-) Highlow American Net'Zen</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1350915797077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916296176-100</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had full knowledge of the event before it happened- just like the Bin Laden murder..</Msg><Username>shortburner2012</Username><Timestamp>1350916296176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916471981-101</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your Pal Bush kept reading "MY Pet Goat" to the kiddies and #$%$ in his pants on the real 9-11</Msg><Username>republicans_are_evil</Username><Timestamp>1350916471981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350916511511-102</Id><Title>Mannkind - MNKD - Potential Blockbuster Drug - Under $2.00</Title><Msg>The announcement that Mannkind has issued a new secondary to raise funds has created a buying opportunity. Mannkind's insulin drug, Afrezza, could receive F.D.A. approval as early as September,2013 if it is granted "priority review" status. With $1.6 billion in tax-loss carry forwards and insulin inventory to produce $10,000,000,000 worth of Afrezza the company in a potential takeover target which may be why Mr. Mann probably decided to convert so much debt to equity at $2.59/share last week. A "big-pharma" partnership could happen at any time. Consider buying a few shares below $2.00 before the approval run-up begins.</Msg><Username>aunttizzy</Username><Timestamp>1350916511511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916552438-103</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is why Bush flew all Bin Ladens relatives home after 911?</Msg><Username>republicans_are_evil</Username><Timestamp>1350916552438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916577945-104</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am starting to think Anne had abortions when it was a girl, boys are the power and pass the family name. I am digging into Anne's past now.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350916577945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916632842-105</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You call yourselves americans . Please lord tell me why we have to protect these Red-Necks who want to elect a draft dodger . Sorry soldiers want OBAMA.</Msg><Username>jpotatohart</Username><Timestamp>1350916632842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350916774258-106</Id><Topic><Title>This might be a good reason - BAC</Title><Username>albinaylap834325</Username><Timestamp>1350914616104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job! Very informative.</Msg><Username>regancfpo542874</Username><Timestamp>1350916774258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:39:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350916969256-107</Id><Title>Is it TIME to start filing OBjections to the CH 11</Title><Msg>Maybe the assets should be divided to the commons!@ Get your pens out!!!! Is the address still in good ole delly???</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1350916969256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350916996782-108</Id><Title>GASX making a nice reversal</Title><Msg>means GASL is a short</Msg><Username>shortburner2012</Username><Timestamp>1350916996782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350917005476-109</Id><Topic><Title>Early CIA report blamed militants for Benghazi attack not a movie or a mob Mr. Obama!! and you knew it!!</Title><Username>frankster1955a</Username><Timestamp>1350782597489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 21:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Republicans question our sources of intelligence, President was able to send drones that killed more than 1400 terrorists and their leaders, our intelligence can't be that bad. Romney is being setup for the debate, he will keep pushing and blaming Obama and Obama will just say the facts and tell Romney to move on.. Romney will keep fighting and get no response from the President after he stated the facts. Look for a Red Faced Romney in the debate.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350917005476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350917117460-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads by a wide margin with early voters</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1350230828939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Did your mouse get stuck on the post button? Living in fantasyland is reserved for the socialist utopian workers' paradise Demcong party. Electoral college tallies have more than 100 toss ups (closer to 125), giving neither candidate the "win" at this point. But what WILL be clear is that the pollsters who live &amp; die by their accuracy will tighten up on reality within the next 5 days. And that's why you now see Romney with a 7 (yes, SEVEN!!) point lead on Gallup now. That will win nearly every state in the country. Liberalism is going to meet its doom. Good riddance. My advice to you - stay away from sharp objects and prescription meds immediately following the election. And if you do decide to drink yourself into a more delusional state than you are in now, please lock the car keys in a drawer or give them to a conservative.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350917117460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350917350060-111</Id><Title>Lots of 10 strike calls being bought for this week.</Title><Msg>Long BAC!</Msg><Username>jdr52683</Username><Timestamp>1350917350060</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350917692815-112</Id><Topic><Title>This might be a good reason - BAC</Title><Username>albinaylap834325</Username><Timestamp>1350914616104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one, I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>yuyhudb10664</Username><Timestamp>1350917692815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350918380795-113</Id><Title>BAC May Be Increasing Dividend?</Title><Msg>Strength of BAC stock may indicate that they may increase dividend by one cent on next declaration and increase it up to five cents on the next declaration - lets hope so!</Msg><Username>acts_111_231_111</Username><Timestamp>1350918380795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350918537442-114</Id><Title>China just signed PGRX for 10 year potash supply contract, worth $2 billions!</Title><Msg>Please look up the newa under PGRX! The insiders recent buyings confirm more business deals are coming from other nations as well! The floating share is low, RSI 80, MFI 50, MCAD K%over pass, all good indicators for the break-out!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1350918537442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350918635246-115</Id><Title>BAC up!!!!..............</Title><Msg>Up today so far in a weak market, as well on last Friday, also up on a big down day(DOW down 205.) Something must be up ????? Maybe dividend increase, reverse stock split, big stock buy back, getting rid of Merrill Lynch or Country Wide Mortg.. etc, etc........!!!!!!!??????</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1350918635246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350918757989-116</Id><Topic><Title>BAC up!!!!..............</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1350918635246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just undervalued. that's all.</Msg><Username>rocketscienc</Username><Timestamp>1350918757989</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350918855183-117</Id><Topic><Title>cannabis play CLNP partners with HEMP to sell HEMP PRODUCTS. 0044</Title><Username>lofttee</Username><Timestamp>1350905271808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 07:27:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>up to .0058 today. 2 weeks till the election.</Msg><Username>lofttee</Username><Timestamp>1350918855183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350918885314-118</Id><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Msg>Look at where we were in 2009 and the what has been done since then. The "buy a new and bigger car or house every year" when you could not afford it or did not need it. Accumulating credit card debt by just saying "charge it" or having sleazy college advisers telling your children who are still children "just sign here, you are 18 now" and they accumulate humongous school loans for mediocre education are a few of the reasons why we are we had to deal with all this mess. We now want to trade in the "president" because the US people have the attention span of a goldfish when it comes to politics and because we can and think that the "new" model is it. It would not happen. We need to stay the course. We need a steady president and steady congress and a steady senate that represent and look out for the well being of all the people in this country. We do not need elections bought by plutocrats.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919142702-119</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this ain't no SPAMMER..this is REAL!!! subscribe now!!!</Msg><Username>burgess_christina611</Username><Timestamp>1350919142702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919464063-120</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The military overwhelmingly wants Romney it is not even close! Why do you think the Democrats are filing suits to block military votes?</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350919464063</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919503369-121</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush did the right thing.</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350919503369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919521700-122</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks legit. Thank you for sharing this</Msg><Username>mckinney_lara552</Username><Timestamp>1350919521700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919599543-123</Id><Topic><Title>BAC up!!!!..............</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1350918635246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will break $10.05 when the dow has an up day. Remember its the close that matters.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1350919599543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:26:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350919795357-124</Id><Title>IRAN NEEDS TO BE DESTROYED</Title><Msg>OR THEY WILL DESTROY US!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350919795357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350919933610-125</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>bates_anne556</Username><Timestamp>1350919933610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350920361244-126</Id><Topic><Title>BAC could blow up today! This is why.</Title><Username>jamesslate42</Username><Timestamp>1350493880197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 13:11:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very good potential</Msg><Username>robinsonjoe816</Username><Timestamp>1350920361244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350920511126-127</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally! I found something informative.</Msg><Username>haynes_jeanette559</Username><Timestamp>1350920511126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350921083931-128</Id><Title>Obama Sent a Drone to Shut me Up!!!</Title><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350921083931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350921089416-129</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>then why... Is GDP at 1.3% lower then we he was elected 8 million more on food stamps 23 million unemployed more than when he started Median income down $4500 Middle class net worth down 45% 17 trillion deby added 4.7 trillion this is what you get for 4.7 trillion? 1 out of every 6 in poverety 3 million more women out ofr work than when he started women in the whitehouse making 17% less than men at the same position You mental midget how is this better oh because gas has doubled because the economy is booming.</Msg><Username>hulteen_mark</Username><Timestamp>1350921089416</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350921124004-130</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350921124004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350921307934-131</Id><Topic><Title>BAC up!!!!..............</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1350918635246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:10:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$14 in the next month, and Roomny will win.</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350921307934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350921408253-132</Id><Topic><Title>BAC might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>hazard.lawrence</Username><Timestamp>1350921034803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This website are on a unstoppable roll right this moment. I don't suspect that they will quit or decelerate at this time.</Msg><Username>jacksondillon81</Username><Timestamp>1350921408253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350921651157-133</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>douglasinthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350916598218</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not bad - it works pretty nice...</Msg><Username>itsacalabreeze</Username><Timestamp>1350921651157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350921799316-134</Id><Title>bac will be $14 next month and</Title><Msg>Roomny will win %100</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350921799316</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350922105643-135</Id><Title>bulls are "playing with bears"</Title><Msg>Looks like bulls are "playing with bears" and can overrun bears at anytime now. Feels like bears lost their power. IMHO Good luck to all</Msg><Username>easytr8er</Username><Timestamp>1350922105643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350922257237-136</Id><Title>can you hear the sound of the shoe shine monke//y boy flushing down the toilet...</Title><Msg>yes you can.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350922257237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350922302550-137</Id><Topic><Title>STEVENS' CALLS FOR HELP IGNORED</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350913179570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:39:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FRY ODUMBA!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350922302550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350922349941-138</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>love_maria569</Username><Timestamp>1350922349941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350922372687-139</Id><Title>GO MITT!</Title><Msg>no to the traitor.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350922372687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350922539141-140</Id><Title>Holy Photoshop! LSU erased Christian football fans' crosses!</Title><Msg>LSU school spokesman Herb Vincent told the site the school altered the image to prevent other students from being offended by the weekly Geaux-Mail newsletter. LSU officials sent out a photo of The Painted Posse, Christian students who paint their bodies with LSU school colors and small crosses for home games, in an email about the LSU game against South Carolina on Oct. 13. The students were shocked to see the photo, which appeared to be otherwise untouched, in the newsletter that went out following the Tigers' 23-21 win over the then-No. 3 Gamecocks. The Tigers are now 7-1 for the season.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350922539141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350922675413-141</Id><Topic><Title>This might be a good reason - BAC</Title><Username>albinaylap834325</Username><Timestamp>1350914616104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:03:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok cool! Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>leolalasj12703</Username><Timestamp>1350922675413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350922849834-142</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the massive heart attack we suffered up to the end 2008 was directly related to the policies of the G W. Bush government. The facts are the facts and we conveniently forget the mess that government left us with. Banks and other financial institutions collapsing, stock market plummeting, 2 unpaid 10 year wars, losing several thousands of jobs a month and a republican senate and congress dripping with the onset of destroying the presidency. Totally forgetting the well being of the American people. Inheriting all this this at the start of any presidency is a crisis. You blame the president for what goes wrong but no respect for what goes right and a lot of things have been going right.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350922849834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923054121-143</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great share. Many thanks</Msg><Username>powers_carol565</Username><Timestamp>1350923054121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923143367-144</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Americans have the little chicken necked big eared dumbo a shot!! he missed?? Now Reggie Thomas go tell the jiggers we the people won't vote for another telepromter jive bass big mouth jigger...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350923143367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923339714-145</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such logic... We need more</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350923339714</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923519227-146</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is what i exactly need at the moment</Msg><Username>young_deborah573</Username><Timestamp>1350923519227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350923557779-147</Id><Title>These boards have outlived their usefulness</Title><Msg>no information at all. spam and poorly expressed political stupidity. absolutely useless.</Msg><Username>miklx</Username><Timestamp>1350923557779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923863385-148</Id><Topic><Title>These boards have outlived their usefulness</Title><Username>miklx</Username><Timestamp>1350923557779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>completely agree with you about the garbage posts on this board. What is your proposal?</Msg><Username>easytr8er</Username><Timestamp>1350923863385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350923908362-149</Id><Title>SHE HAS HAD ENOUGH IF OBAMA'S CONTROL</Title><Msg>Donna, a right wing Tea Party member and strong supporter of Mitt had enough of Obama's contol and called her local radio station to complain. What was she complaining about? Well, according to Donna Obama had required that Deer Crossing be placed on the interstate Hwy. and by requireing the Deer to cross an Interstate Hwy., insteads of a back road with less trafic was placing Americans at risk.....yes. this really happened and gives an excellent insite to the logic of the right wing that Flipper and Jug Ears love to pander to. YOU REALLY WANT THESE NUTS RUNNING THE COUNTRY?</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350923908362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350923935485-150</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined. Heard a lot about these guys</Msg><Username>wright_vickie569</Username><Timestamp>1350923935485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350924293605-151</Id><Title>Ryan's mother benefit from medicare--</Title><Msg>Ryan inherited over $5 million from his parents. Why would he be concern about medicare? Ryan is now and always talk c----. Just like when he ran the marathon in less than 3 minutes. The Ryan/Romney ticket is the sleeziest in the history of America.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1350924293605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924423818-152</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure thing. Been receiving good alerts from them</Msg><Username>mullins_ashley574</Username><Timestamp>1350924423818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924514735-153</Id><Topic><Title>Holy Photoshop! LSU erased Christian football fans' crosses!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350922539141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every true right wing nut knows that if you don't share their virsion of being christian , revised interpertation to support their agenda of hate .you should just accept what they attempt to push down your throat.....heck they do the same thing by calling people anti-american if they don't accept their political agenda. Of course they have no problem with lieing if it supports their limited political views. Just look at who they want for president, a man of no lasting values....guess its a robutt condition or what most call a major case of the #$%$</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350924514735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924585580-154</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this Rush Limbaugh, Reince Priebus, Shaun Hannity, Newt, Donald Trump, Tad Romney, John Sununu or Willard himself? There are so many of you that have corrupted and brought nothing but hate and racism into this country and you all sound so much alike it is amazing how easy it is to be racist and stupid in the good old USA</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350924585580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924605986-155</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll keep that in mind when I buy my next Chevy and just think how the automotive industry was saved. Or when I look at my 401k now and how it was worth half in 2008 and when there was a run on the banks in 2008 and the FDIC raised the limit of insured deposits to 250k and I was able to recoup the money I lost in 2008. That's American strength?</Msg><Username>acerdaprod</Username><Timestamp>1350924605986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924625339-156</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Hillary let Obama throw her under the bus?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350924278028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>simple. she had made a calculation. but as always with the incompetent cow shrillary her calculations will have proven to be wrong. LMAO.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350924625339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924628981-157</Id><Topic><Title>These boards have outlived their usefulness</Title><Username>miklx</Username><Timestamp>1350923557779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we are stuck with the idiots on these yahoo boards... But then all boards have the same idiots..</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350924628981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924677985-158</Id><Topic><Title>US has been brought from the brink, stabalized and we are now moving forward.</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350918885314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama started with 1.3 trillion debt the first year left from Bush and has declined a little each year after, the only other time the yearly debt has declined was during Clintons terms . During Reagan , Bush Sr and Dubya's terms it went up every year ! Now Romney wants to spend more and cut taxes thats how Bush destroyed the surplus.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350924677985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924691470-159</Id><Topic><Title>GO MITT!</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350922372687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:12:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on!!!! Yes, please go mitt,,....go away and take the right wing nut cases with you....go to where your $$$ are ....offshore</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350924691470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924693888-160</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this here.</Msg><Username>graham_natalie576</Username><Timestamp>1350924693888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350924771135-161</Id><Title>Who likes to watch Alan Comes? Who likes to watch Bill Matthews?</Title><Msg>I don't watch them .................</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350924771135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924847772-162</Id><Topic><Title>can you hear the sound of the shoe shine monke//y boy flushing down the toilet...</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350922257237</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You posts serves to demonstrate to the americans with half a brain why we can not allow flipper and the right wing nuts, such as yourself to never have control of the country.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350924847772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924929407-163</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>reeves_catherine585</Username><Timestamp>1350924929407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924961541-164</Id><Topic><Title>BAC might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>hazard.lawrence</Username><Timestamp>1350921034803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. I had not subscribed yet. Doing so without delay.</Msg><Username>camp.colton</Username><Timestamp>1350924961541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350924989612-165</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Sent a Drone to Shut me Up!!!</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350921083931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:51:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way we would want you to be shut up ...ever. You are an ongoing reminder why we can not allow nuts to run the country</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350924989612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925152671-166</Id><Topic><Title>The Mormon calendar ends on December 21'st. Why is Mitt running?</Title><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350915489086</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please answer the question.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350925152671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925157612-167</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama has such a solid lead in the polls .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350924768259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:52:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ is crying for help? LMAO.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350925157612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925292649-168</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads by a wide margin with early voters</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1350230828939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent news. Early voters vote often.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350925292649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925314895-169</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>cross_tara587</Username><Timestamp>1350925314895</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925324413-170</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are mastering the art of buying and stealing elections</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350861788755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:23:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reggie, they have been a master and have the experience as well for decades. Another serious concern must be where those electronic voting machines used that leave no printed record behind. Only those who program know what's really going on inside. It appears to me it may be too tempting for crooks not to exploit such opportunity.</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1350925324413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925375813-171</Id><Topic><Title>IRAN NEEDS TO BE DESTROYED</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350919795357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:29:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess that this shows that the robutt faction supports flipper in his drive to invade another country and thus spend another billion dollars a month for 10 years...bit heck it does allow the rich to get richer and to reduce the lower and missle class by killing them off./////// heck maybe they will find jr.'s wmd's or has that lie been used up to warrent invadeing another country?</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350925375813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350925427945-172</Id><Title>Will Mitt take Ryan with him when he goes back to Mexico after elections?</Title><Msg>I sure hope so.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350925427945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925648559-173</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan's mother benefit from medicare--</Title><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1350924293605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:44:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya gotta love the republican nazi party ...... After all when they continue to get caught in lies all they have to say is that they did not mean it or what i really said was or you heard me wrong and then go on to tell the same lie over and over ........... The robutts eat it up</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350925648559</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:07:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925723734-174</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love it. thanks</Msg><Username>manning_beth588</Username><Timestamp>1350925723734</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350925765726-175</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHOICE IS CLEAR A FAILED PRESIDENT OR A CONSISTENTLY SUCCESSFUL BUSINESSMAN</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350908607949</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes master very clear, very clear indeed if you were born on the Bayou and you are wearing rose colored glasses</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350925765726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350925914110-176</Id><Title>7 out of 10 Romney voters don't know Romney first name.</Title><Msg>#$%$. Not mormons, #$%$.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350925914110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350926058431-177</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this one ROCKS!!!subscribe now!!!</Msg><Username>edwards_katie592</Username><Timestamp>1350926058431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350926227969-178</Id><Title>Ryan and Mitt will build 15 navy ships and 3 submarines a year! Pearl Harbor is safe.</Title><Msg>Germans won't atack it again. Even Al-Qaeda's navy won't try anything.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1350926227969</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350926482645-179</Id><Topic><Title>Hot Stock Picks!</Title><Username>toniapeb63953</Username><Timestamp>1350911559194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 09:12:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is AWESOME!!! two thumbs UP!</Msg><Username>townsend_heather596</Username><Timestamp>1350926482645</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350927295985-180</Id><Title>Wallstreet con job wants banks to rally</Title><Msg>So they can survive and then totally finish of the American working class into slavery. Today and friday proves this is a premeditated slaughter. Dow down 300 points and dropping....but not banks, you know the ones that destroyed this market in the first place.</Msg><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1350927295985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350927338151-181</Id><Topic><Title>Holy Photoshop! LSU erased Christian football fans' crosses!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350922539141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello, Carolune..."Obama draws praise from Chavez, Putin -- and Castro family"...You are in an elite group..it's not so much what Romney can do for America, as it is the utter destruction Obama and his geek freaks will wreak if allowed to run unchained for four more years. Are you sure you want to risk learning to goose-step and speak Arabic while becoming a full fledged socialist under Obama. These are very dangerous people who don't have the financial expertise to make the hard decisions necessary for our Country to regain its' financial footing in 2013. If they were just inept, it would be one thing, but the Obama administration will do ANYTHING for political gain. Obama himself is not the problem..he's never involved in any presidential matters..just likes to spend time on Late Night and rub shoulders with his Hollywood buddies. Realistically ask yourself what Chavez, Putin and Castro have in common with Obama.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350927338151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:35:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350927391189-182</Id><Title>Romney is Leading or Tied in all National Polls</Title><Msg>Great News</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1350927391189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350927511402-183</Id><Topic><Title>Holy Photoshop! LSU erased Christian football fans' crosses!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350922539141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 12:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freedom of Speech is being destroyed by Political Correctness. The self promoted Tolerant have now become the intolerant</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1350927511402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350927516770-184</Id><Topic><Title>BENGHAZI ATTACKED FOR 7+HOURS WHILE OBAMA SLEPT</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350910218833</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last poll of military is 63 to 37 OBAMA . Do your homework before you speak for us.</Msg><Username>jpotatohart</Username><Timestamp>1350927516770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350927567780-185</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Leading or Tied in all National Polls</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1350927391189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares.</Msg><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1350927567780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350927617687-186</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Leading or Tied in all National Polls</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1350927391189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FACT!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350927617687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350927872356-187</Id><Title>If there no elections in Noverber 2012, the Lybya incidend would have hardly been talked about.</Title><Msg>Making what was said and when it was said an issue is strictly a matter of Romney attempting to morph himself as someone who "knows about foreign policy" and really he does not know Jack.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350927872356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350927877116-188</Id><Title>BAC = Absolutely amazing strength in a down market.</Title><Msg>BAC = Absolutely amazing strength in a down market.</Msg><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350927877116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350928542114-189</Id><Title>rOMNEY KILLED BIG BIRD AND RONALD MCDONALD IS RUNNING FOR HIS LIFE!!!</Title><Msg>McDonalds post worst quarter in 9 years??? Ronald McDonald is running the country side hollowing "Where IS The BEEF!!!! Ronald is buying old sick and dying holstiens...Yes Sir my friends Where is the BEEF??? THE DAY OF THAT BIG JUICY T BONE IS GONE FOR EVER...ILMFAO</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350928542114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350928607235-190</Id><Title>WH: Getting rid of unwanted virus</Title><Msg>Uninstalling Obama......... █████████████▒▒▒ 90% complete.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350928607235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350928854811-191</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Leading or Tied in all National Polls</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1350927391189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect it is not as close as the media thinks.</Msg><Username>bidds000</Username><Timestamp>1350928854811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350928902983-192</Id><Topic><Title>WH: Getting rid of unwanted virus</Title><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350928607235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:56:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well it's a little black virus...the worse kind...the kind that doesn't want to go peacefully...oh but he'll go...i just sprayed my pc with roach killer..and the ole bo virus was gone...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350928902983</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350929024105-193</Id><Title>ROMNEY 2END UR TAX/MORTGAGE DEDUCTIONS! VOTE OBAMA 4SURE!</Title><Msg>protect your tax deductions - this jerk Romney does not understand the middle income person</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1350929024105</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350929034761-194</Id><Title>Future</Title><Msg>Without Obama, we hit 20.00 next year.</Msg><Username>bidds000</Username><Timestamp>1350929034761</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350929257870-195</Id><Title>BAC is a mover stock today -- A real Dumpster kinda stock</Title><Msg>time t sell</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350929257870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350929513431-196</Id><Title>OHIO GOING TO ROMNEY TODAY</Title><Msg>SORRY OBAMA MEAT SUCKERS</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350929513431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350929616478-197</Id><Title>BENGHAZI COVERUP SCANDAL JUST WON'T GO AWAY??? WAS BO AND THE MUSLIMS WORKING TOGETHER? I WONDER???</Title><Msg>This isn't just any black boy from chic-ago...this is the messiah..the son of a muslim..trained in maxist ways fron birth...i do know he claims to slept through the hole attack...the next day he flew to las vagas to a fund raiser...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350929616478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350929812536-198</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is a mover stock today -- A real Dumpster kinda stock</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350929257870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No way. The handle is about to burst, fibbs are in tact. Its an easy $12 to $13 play.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1350929812536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:16:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350930070815-199</Id><Topic><Title>JRCC AONE TAGG on fire!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOAD UP AT THESE GIFT LEVELS!!</Title><Username>marketprimping</Username><Timestamp>1350927985458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 13:46:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are you posting this garbage on all boards? Mostly sick.</Msg><Username>kgolesorkhi</Username><Timestamp>1350930070815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350930587758-200</Id><Title>printed money = printed bank value</Title><Msg>I say NO to the US$ and their banks.</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350930587758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350930822837-201</Id><Topic><Title>BAC might be the next SEFE!</Title><Username>hazard.lawrence</Username><Timestamp>1350921034803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 11:50:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without a doubt. I'm thinking about it too. Whoever these guys are on a intense roll right now.</Msg><Username>garyfritch489</Username><Timestamp>1350930822837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350930849889-202</Id><Title>ANY IDEAS ON WHERE IS BURY BIG BIRD AND ROSIE WADE????</Title><Msg>If your a christian you wouldn't kill??? You think pulling the handle for anyone that is pro rosie wade will go to heaven???</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350930849889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350931058011-203</Id><Title>ROMEY TO PAY HIS BACKERS W/YOUR TAX INCREASE! VOTE OBAMA 4SURE!</Title><Msg>don't lose your tax deductions w/Romney!!</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1350931058011</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350931273918-204</Id><Title>MKT TANKS in a few minutes !!! MINUS -350 pts....BEWARE</Title><Msg>............</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1350931273918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350931570842-205</Id><Title>GOOG LOST A 100 DOLLAR SENCE THE 52 WEEK HIGH??? LOOO...ALOT OF MONEY FOR A SEARCH ENGINE???</Title><Msg>I used yahoo and don't like google except google maps...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350931570842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350931748016-206</Id><Title>MKT "wobbling" then *****KABOOM***** and the BROKERS win BIG this YEAR !</Title><Msg>yes sir !</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1350931748016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350931760666-207</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Romney And The Plutocrats Represent Everything Wrong With America Today!</Title><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1350666446721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:07:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree completely!</Msg><Username>mooseonaplane</Username><Timestamp>1350931760666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932017054-208</Id><Topic><Title>MKT TANKS in a few minutes !!! MINUS -350 pts....BEWARE</Title><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1350931273918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody knows that. However, my own Indicator for the larger market picture (LMP) is becoming gradually negative, since Monday, Oct. 8, 2012. The market can do anything.</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1350932017054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:53:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932066077-209</Id><Topic><Title>VOTING BOOTH EPIPHANIES WILL GIVE ROMNEY A LANDSIDE WIN</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350909394682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 08:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i THINK YOU'RE RIGHT!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350932066077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932251344-210</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans are mastering the art of buying and stealing elections</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1350861788755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 19:23:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2008 the headline was: Broward County Voters Give 110% in Florida Primary!.. Precinct D001 had 930 registered voters, the offical vote count was 1028. There is always something wrong in Florida and Ohio when it comes to vote count. A friend of Bush sold new election machines, " paperless ES&amp;S iVotronic touch-screen " These machines lost 18,000 votes in a race that in the end only had a 369 vote margin. That was in Sarasota County's 13th Congressional district race in 2006, they gave the race to the Republican Vern Buchanan without even telling voters how they decided a ract with 18,000 votes missing... Remember, It's not your vote that counts, it is the count of the votes.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350932251344</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932282973-211</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is a mover stock today -- A real Dumpster kinda stock</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350929257870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:07:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ha ha ha ya gotta be jokin ha ha ha</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350932282973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 14:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932581826-212</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all about money, if you are a republican and have enough money and power, like Romney, you can have all the abortions you want and every Republican in Congress will say that was a special case. So, Did Anne Romney Flush the girls to have that all boys (FUTURE LEADERS)????????????????</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350932581826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350932681932-213</Id><Title>HOLD ON TO YOUR "Ace"....DOWN we GO !!!</Title><Msg>Oh yeahhhhhhhh !!!</Msg><Username>purple_man91</Username><Timestamp>1350932681932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350932692145-214</Id><Topic><Title>Fathom this about the terrible obamacare destructive circus</Title><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1349801712312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:55:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>***** More Prog-Crap-Surprises. Hat tip to CNS News: Obamacare Mandate: Anyone Who Works 30-Hour Week Is Now 'Full-Time' :::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::::: Barry's "Kill Your Health" scheme still needs to be deep-sixed with a stake driven through it!</Msg><Username>dons_st</Username><Timestamp>1350932692145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350932707301-215</Id><Title>BAC in the dumspter tomorrow</Title><Msg>Triple top around 9.56. Must go down big tomorrow before another leg up past 9.60 resistance</Msg><Username>getinwill</Username><Timestamp>1350932707301</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:05:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350932811998-216</Id><Title>bac in dumpster right now</Title><Msg>there she goes... to the trash bin...</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350932811998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350933243532-217</Id><Title>ROMNEY JUST REMINDS ME OF SNAKE OIL BARKER AT THE FAIR!!</Title><Msg>JUST DON'T TRUST THIS GUY</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1350933243532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350933249879-218</Id><Topic><Title>The Romney / Ryan Campaign: Nebulous and Obscure by Design. Nondisclosure, hidden assets, blind trusts, offshore accounts, muddled double speak, flip-flops, vague agendas, shadowy cults, undefined plans, sealed tax records, confidential agreements, indecipherable financial records, four military service deferments, dark schemes, financial dodges, private equity funds....</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1346200994509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 20:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney was a bad choice but picking Ryan was crazy bad, Americans hate that boy for holding them hostage many times, the 7% approval rating for Congress tells the whole story.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350933249879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350933322637-219</Id><Title>BAC is the best but don't miss the train,,,</Title><Msg>the banks sector will do the best in the next 3 month, you guys will laugh all the way to the bank.</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350933322637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350933364228-220</Id><Title>if the feds start putting everyone who appears on CNBC in prison</Title><Msg>including most employed @ CNBC Wall Street would start cleaning up a bit..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1350933364228</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350933465600-221</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is the best but don't miss the train,,,</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350933322637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buy,,,</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350933465600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350933640876-222</Id><Topic><Title>Does anybody know why Romney's grandfather moved to Mexico</Title><Username>lookfwd</Username><Timestamp>1350525106224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 21:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney keep his binder of women, could get top dollar in Utah where all Mormons have a binder of women. If anything, rape the one's at Fox, they would not mind as long as Romney wins.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350933640876</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350933688440-223</Id><Title>Next President....Who Cares all useless</Title><Msg>But the tinkerbell parade here thinks they are being included in the team.</Msg><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1350933688440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350933798004-224</Id><Title>Next President....Who cares all useless</Title><Msg>But the tinkerbell parade here thinks they are on the team. Losers galore.</Msg><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1350933798004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934192887-225</Id><Topic><Title>IAM BETTER OFF NOW THAT 4 YEARS AGO UNDER OBAMA DOW IS UP 7500 POINTS MY IRA UP 150%</Title><Username>chavesagain</Username><Timestamp>1350313911941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We answered the Reagan question, We are better off than 4 years ago, 401K's that lost 50% under Bush are now full again, Thanks Obama, just think how much better it would be if we did not have republican terrorists in Congress trying to kill every good thing Obama has done for America???</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350934192887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934206215-226</Id><Topic><Title>Next President....Who cares all useless</Title><Username>jksouth</Username><Timestamp>1350933798004</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:23:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100000000000000000% right</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934206215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:30:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934287550-227</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is the best but don't miss the train,,,</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350933322637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slow growth, if any. GMCR and BBBY are much better plays.</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1350934287550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350934349123-228</Id><Title>Printobama + debtomama is an idiot .</Title><Msg>With money printing and mega debts you can not creating any wealth.</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934349123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934399571-229</Id><Topic><Title>Printobama + debtomama is an idiot .</Title><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934349123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Printobama + debtobama</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934399571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934413623-230</Id><Topic><Title>ANY WOMAN WHO SUPPORTS THE REPUCAN PARTY IS WORSE THAN A BABOON</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1350827296267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 09:48:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True numbers in Ohio, Obama leads Romney by double digits.. Christian vs Mormon Cult</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350934413623</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350934577578-231</Id><Title>Printing $3000B and increasing debt $6000B = $9000B =$30000 per American</Title><Msg>Robert Mugabe from Zimbabwe is an child compare with Obama.</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934577578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350934610660-232</Id><Topic><Title>The resident fringe right pervert trolls KNOW Obama will win the Electoral College vote</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1350177244483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone want to buy Romney/Ryan road signs, I have about 1,000 of them, they are all over the road. Someone drove around and knocked them all down.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350934610660</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350934818211-233</Id><Title>Chapter 11 for the US</Title><Msg>Too much debt and to much printed $</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934818211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350935036519-234</Id><Topic><Title>Dems Prove Trickle Up Economics Doesn't Work</Title><Username>defeatsocialism</Username><Timestamp>1287709896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-10-21 21:11:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since the Commiecrats/Progs, aka Democrats, have been in charge we have seen an over 70% increase in the use of food stamps. The American people have been saddled with a 16Trillion$$$plus debt; they have been saddled with trillion$$$plus deficits to the horizon and beyond; they have been saddled with QE3...$40 Billion per month to infinity. Over 100 million on some kind of welfare scheme. Record numbers on food stamps. Record numbers on the poverty roll. Record numbers not looking for work. Record numbers receiving disability assistance. Obama unemployment rate above 8% longer than any other President since 1948 (adjusted down below 8% the other day since there are now even fewer looking for work). And, Barry's "Kill your Health" scheme has already started with its looting and controlling and its meddling, tinkering, intruding and interfering in every aspect of our lives, our children, our families, our schools, our churches, our doctors, our hospitals, our faith, our farms, our energy sources, our communities, our private property, our health-care and our businesses. Clearly, Obamanomics is killing the USA. Clearly, Commiecrats/Progs, aka Democrats, should never be in charge of anything! November 6, 2012. Fire every Democrat across the USA; get it done!!!</Msg><Username>dons_st</Username><Timestamp>1350935036519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:43:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350935430859-235</Id><Title>Biden's Brother???!!!!</Title><Msg>David Richter, the president of Hill International (HIL), a mid-sized outfit that manages construction projects, was speaking last year at a private meeting with investors when he was asked about the recent success of his newest subsidiary, HillStone International. How was it that HillStone, a newcomer in the business of home building, landed a massive and potentially lucrative contract to build 100,000 homes in war-torn Iraq? Richter didn’t mince words. It really helps, he said, to have “the brother of the vice president as a partner,” according to a person who was present. The “brother” Richter was referring to during the meeting is James Biden, the younger brother of Vice President Joe Biden. Since November 2010, James Biden has been the executive vice president of Hill International’s housing subsidiary despite little if any documented work history in residential construction. And if the company’s projections are accurate, both Hill and Biden are on the verge of a huge payday, beneficiaries, some analysts believe, of James Biden’s connections to the Obama Administration through his older brother. Indeed, the Iraq project may be the most lucrative single development in Hill’s history. Since 2011, Hill, located in Marlton, NJ., has been losing money; the shares were recently trading at $3.82, down about 28% this year on New York Stock Exchange trading.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350935430859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350935673396-236</Id><Title>Spanish Bad Loans Hit New Record in August (10% of Spain feeling the PAIN )</Title><Msg>Reuters October 18, 2012 Spanish households and companies defaulted on their debts in record numbers in August, hurting the country's lenders and highlighting the need for an aid package and bad bank to help the economy out of recession. A property crash left banks with billions of euros in bad debt from real estate developers on their balance sheets but the problems have spread to small businesses and other sectors. Loans that fell into arrears in August increased by 5.3 billion euros ($7 billion) from July, reaching 178 billion euros, Bank of Spain data showed on Thursday. Spain is setting up a bad bank to siphon property assets off lenders' balance sheets and banks are preparing to receive the first funds from a 100-billion-euro credit line agreed with the European Union. But the record loan data raises the question of whether consumer loans should also be transferred to the bad bank and if Spain will take too little of the European cash. The government estimates it only needs 40 billion euros. "The most obvious thing from this data is that the Spanish government should aim for a greater recapitalisation exercise,'' said Gilles Moec, economist at Deutsche bank. "There is a risk of undershooting with the recapitalisation plan as it stands today.'' The setting up of a bad bank is a condition of receiving the European aid, alongside an independent audit of the country's lenders completed in September which pointed to seven banks needing capital in a severe downturn. Spain is also expected to ask for a sovereign aid package in the next few weeks which would open the door for the European entral Bank to start buying its debt to bring premiums down. CONSUMER QUESTION Spain is suffering its worst economic downturn in half a century, marked by high unemployment and deep spending cuts. This has hurt consumers who are now defaulting on their loans in increasing numbers and this also makes the bank problems worse. The country has raised the possibility of including defunct consumer loans in the bad bank, although only in the worst cases, Economy Ministry sources said on Wednesday. Bad consumer loans will not be transferred into the bad bank in the first instance, a source with knowledge of the matter said, but the bad bank has been designed so that non-real estate assets could be included in the future. "At some time in the future they may be included, but it may never happen,'' the source said. ``What you need to cut out is the cyst of the real estate sector, that's what the bad bank has been set up for, that's what has destroyed the banking system.'' The bad bank will be designed to hold up to 90 billion euros of assets, but the government expects the final size to be much smaller. It will be up and running by the end of the year. The Bank of Spain must determine the price at which assets are transferred to the bank, using input from independent auditor Oliver Wyman. The price will be set in the week following Nov. 19 when the legislation governing the formation of the bad bank is passed. Prices must be low enough to attract private investors, meaning the bad bank will be profitable over its 15 year lifespan, but not so low as to precipitate bigger losses for Spain's banks. WRITEDOWNS SQUEEZE EARNINGS Economists say getting the banks back to a healthy position is crucial to Spain climbing out of recession. Most independent forecasts are looking for a drop of 1.5% in economic output next year, far worse than the government's forecast for a 0.5% contraction. Spain's lenders have already made massive write downs on their property investments under two government laws passed this year. The government has forced lenders to set aside 137 billion euros on 307 billion euros of real estate exposure. Write downs on property are expected to continue to squeeze banks' profits in nine-months results. Bankinter, the first Spanish bank to report results this season, posted a halving of 9 month net profit due to writedowns made in the first half. Santander and BBVA, which passed the independent audit with flying colours, still have more writedowns to make to comply with the government legislation.</Msg><Username>mrj.premier</Username><Timestamp>1350935673396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350936096912-237</Id><Topic><Title>Printing $3000B and increasing debt $6000B = $9000B =$30000 per American</Title><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934577578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHAPTER 11</Msg><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350936096912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350936101503-238</Id><Title>BAC = $9.55 close is highest closing price since 9-13-12</Title><Msg>BAC = $9.55 close is highest closing price since 9-13-12</Msg><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350936101503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350936410443-239</Id><Title>Hollywould Hores Panic.</Title><Msg>According to some political experts, Streisand’s message is a sign that liberal Hollywood is starting to panic. “They can read the poll numbers as well as anyone, and their guy is losing ground. Plus, celebrities are nothing if not superficial, and a big part of Obama's appeal to them has been charisma," Matt Philbin, Managing Editor of the Culture and Media Institute, told the Pop Tarts column. "The ‘optics’ of the first presidential debate must have been jarring." Jeff Roe, GOP Political Consultant and founder of Axiom Strategies, concurred that the possibility Obama may be a one-term president is prompting some celebrities to “pull out all the stops to prevent a family-oriented, business-oriented, wholesome individual to the Office of the President.” “When Hollywood liberals begin to panic, you know you are doing something right,” he quipped.</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1350936410443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350936459119-240</Id><Title>$95 million trade at the close?</Title><Msg>Yahoo charts suggests there was a huge (10 million share) trade just before the close. What gives?</Msg><Username>atascaderoguy</Username><Timestamp>1350936459119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350936520506-241</Id><Title>Will hit over 9.65 tomorrow on a BIG up day and ...</Title><Msg>you know what that means will hit the wall at 10</Msg><Username>felixm05</Username><Timestamp>1350936520506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350936582539-242</Id><Topic><Title>ANY WOMAN WHO SUPPORTS THE REPUCAN PARTY IS WORSE THAN A BABOON</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1350827296267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-21 09:48:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Felix Fartaway. You should be ashamed of yourself. If these fine people knew what you do to our mentally challenged son, they would tar and feather you. Now get off this board and go get us some food stamps, you dirtbag.</Msg><Username>milesed17smom</Username><Timestamp>1350936582539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350936623574-243</Id><Topic><Title>Will hit over 9.65 tomorrow on a BIG up day and ...</Title><Username>felixm05</Username><Timestamp>1350936520506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>im with u buttercrud</Msg><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1350936623574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350936742700-244</Id><Title>Felix "Fartaway" Faraway</Title><Msg>Felix Fartaway. You should be ashamed of yourself. If these fine people knew what you do to our mentally challenged son, they would tar and feather you. Now get off this board and go get us some food stamps, you dirtbag.</Msg><Username>milesed17smom</Username><Timestamp>1350936742700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350936804570-245</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will keep the baby boys with blue eyes, perfect family, that is how Romney did it.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350936804570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350937464081-246</Id><Topic><Title>bac in dumpster right now</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1350932811998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like price is going up</Msg><Username>easytr8er</Username><Timestamp>1350937464081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350937614327-247</Id><Title>haha you idiots think romney is going to give you a job? think again your daddy is not hearing you:</Title><Msg>this guy is worse than bush he will not create any jobs he will ship all of the jobs overseas just to make more millions for his rich friends</Msg><Username>fatal9998</Username><Timestamp>1350937614327</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350937659642-248</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. This Country needs to move in a new direction. Thank you for not using vulgar and sexist comments to make your political point. Paris</Msg><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350937659642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350937918030-249</Id><Title>BOTTOM LINE OPTIONS: CHRISTIAN VS MORMON CULT</Title><Msg>keep it up to the church and what you support..</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350937918030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350937970288-250</Id><Title>so far good earnings news...could see another 1% tomorrow</Title><Msg>alot of strenght...bac did not waiver today</Msg><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1350937970288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938070841-251</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry the bad social experiment was called bush and now willard "mitt" romney.</Msg><Username>fatal9998</Username><Timestamp>1350938070841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:34:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938213856-252</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Bag S*c*u*m* do not support moderate Mitt? Why? Is he not neo-nazi enough?</Title><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896496901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They don't like Romney because he is almost as liberal as Obama.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938213856</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938249582-253</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry obama has saved this country from an economic depression. all scholars regardless of party lines have agreed that obama saved this country. now if you look at how bush left the country than yes, that is what you call damage to america.</Msg><Username>fatal9998</Username><Timestamp>1350938249582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938309020-254</Id><Topic><Title>haha you idiots think romney is going to give you a job? think again your daddy is not hearing you:</Title><Username>fatal9998</Username><Timestamp>1350937614327</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this idiots name is WILLARD not MITT you fools get it right.</Msg><Username>fatal9998</Username><Timestamp>1350938309020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350938514398-255</Id><Title>Fifteen days until the re-election of President Obama</Title><Msg>Nov. 6 will be another great day in American history.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938514398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938620399-256</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHOICE IS CLEAR: COMMIE MUZZIE vs CHRISTIAN MORMON</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350938389614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will you lie about after Obama is re-elected?</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938620399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938701077-257</Id><Topic><Title>Loser retarded redneck tea baggers don't get Obama has won the electoral college vote</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1350893000540</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 04:03:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Early voting polls show Obama with huge margins</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938701077</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938841381-258</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leads by a wide margin with early voters</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1350230828939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 12:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like early voter turnout will at least be as big a factor in Obama winning this election as it was in 2008.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938841381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350938856252-259</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHOICE IS CLEAR: COMMIE MUZZIE vs CHRISTIAN MORMON</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350938389614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After it's all over can i have the loser??? Put a choker chain on the jigger and ship him over my way...ilmfao...i'm going to reprogram the muslim and socialist out of him...ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350938856252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350939114449-260</Id><Title>Liar Tea Baggers in a frenzy over Libyan reports. They have to find something else to lie about.</Title><Msg>They lied about the polls when they were heavily favoring Obama. They lied about the jobs report numbers because they could not deal with the truth. And, they want to keep on lying about Libya to prove they can do nothing but lie.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939114449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350939183580-261</Id><Title>Republicans lie like most people breathe</Title><Msg>It just comes natural to them.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939183580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939350058-262</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 week old ID, 160 posts of anti-Obama blather. A classic testicle pirate and sack hijacker and [wait for it]........[wait for it].......IGNORE USER.....[aaahh!]</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350939350058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350939354581-263</Id><Title>Las Vegas odds have Obama winning 2-1. Not smart to bet against the house.</Title><Msg>The house always wins in the end.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939354581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:55:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939475637-264</Id><Topic><Title>Fifteen days until the re-election of President Obama</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938514398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump time</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939475637</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:57:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350939510490-265</Id><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Msg>I am appalled by the personal attacks on this Board. Mitt Romeny raised five boys, has been married to the same woman for 40+ years, has eighteen grandchildren. I present the following facts: - Mitt Romney is a self made man, got a good education and moved on to help others in business and social venues. - He not only gives 10% to his Church, but gives 30% of his income to charity. I know that doesn't compare with the $100 Joe Biden gave to charity last year. - He served his Church, along with all his boys as missionaries in foreign countries to address poverty and civil rights. - He didn't even take a salary as Gov. of MA, that greedy SOB! Wake up and smell the coffee! This is the man that can turn this Country around!</Msg><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939539168-266</Id><Topic><Title>Fifteen days until the re-election of President Obama</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938514398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome to Denial</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350939539168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939638382-267</Id><Topic><Title>Blue states trump red states. Obama Wins Again !</Title><Username>blue_state_of_mind</Username><Timestamp>1349370188288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 13:03:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama mopped the floor with Romney during the last debate. And, the blue state margin STILL give Obama the win for re-election.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939638382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:00:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939838887-268</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about the racist, lying tea bagger attacks on Obama and his family? I guess that doesn't bother you since he's not your candidate. Hypocrite.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939838887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350939906000-269</Id><Title>Obama created a bigger mess in the Middle East !</Title><Msg>Now everyone over there is throwing rocks at US ! Talking about throwing rocks, does anyone here really know why them Muslimies like to throw rocks at one another ?</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350939906000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939928105-270</Id><Topic><Title>Are you one of "those people" that Romney dismisses as unworthy of his concern? "My job is not to worry about those people" -- Mitt Romney</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1349042110360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 47% will rise up to take Mitt down.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939928105</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350939972372-271</Id><Topic><Title>Printobama + debtomama is an idiot .</Title><Username>hitobamaler</Username><Timestamp>1350934349123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about BEN the PRINTER? Buy gas recently? When did America get hijacked by Wall Street? Or is it just the FED?</Msg><Username>dr.market</Username><Timestamp>1350939972372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940037565-272</Id><Topic><Title>Las Vegas odds have Obama winning 2-1. Not smart to bet against the house.</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939354581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:55:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not for a LOSER fool like you.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940037565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940131052-273</Id><Topic><Title>IAM BETTER OFF NOW THAT 4 YEARS AGO UNDER OBAMA DOW IS UP 7500 POINTS MY IRA UP 150%</Title><Username>chavesagain</Username><Timestamp>1350313911941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Obama's policies, the economy is beginning to recover.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940131052</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940278247-274</Id><Topic><Title>The utter stupidity of the right wingers shows a real need for a voter intelligence test.</Title><Username>obama.4more</Username><Timestamp>1350677973016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just look at the ignorant LOSER fool "dumpobamie." Uninformed, ignorant, and stupid.</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940278247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350940376526-275</Id><Title>barack4more should change his name to bagdad bob this person is in serious denial</Title><Msg>Everything is moving Romney's way. That's called momentum and that's what wins elections</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350940376526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940467824-276</Id><Topic><Title>Will dump of dog s*h*i*t* self-euthanize after Obama's re-elected?</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1350511303867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 18:01:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jump, dumpy, jump!</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940467824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940592323-277</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It helps if you have a father who was a CEO who madfe millions. Yes Mitt is a self made man, NOT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1350940592323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350940615590-278</Id><Title>Is "bury obama" a blatant racist inbred white trash tea bagger?</Title><Msg>Or, is he just brain-dead?</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940615590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350940638375-279</Id><Title>we could hit 10 bucks this week..</Title><Msg>not too late to get in</Msg><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1350940638375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940705871-280</Id><Topic><Title>Is "bury obama" a blatant racist inbred white trash tea bagger?</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940615590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the red necks and inmates are in charge of the Republican party's asylum.</Msg><Username>gothedistance723</Username><Timestamp>1350940705871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940771891-281</Id><Topic><Title>we could hit 10 bucks this week..</Title><Username>ceausescu_rules</Username><Timestamp>1350940638375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:17:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is m arket and bac pps baking romney election into the cake?-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1350940771891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350940802384-282</Id><Topic><Title>bury_obama is just another SW rectal drip alias. They all drip from the same A-- hole.</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350671278204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:27:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just one of thousands</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940802384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350941261226-283</Id><Title>The Chase</Title><Msg>for BofA stock is starting.</Msg><Username>lovmayercooch</Username><Timestamp>1350941261226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350941513934-284</Id><Title>The Class War is being lost</Title><Msg>How interesting that Tea Baggers who are largely lower middle class continue to attempt to degrade the President by saying he is starting a class war...... well the class war is true , but these losers can't figure out its the Rich who have declared war on the middle class and they are winning with the help of those whom they are intent to eliminate and move into the poor house plus ensure they die off quick when they reach the point they can no longer work for slave wages. The IRS released a report that found that more 20,000 filers in 2009 with an adjusted gross income above $200,000 didn't owe any taxes that year. The percentage of affluent filers who owed no taxes was five times greater than in 2001. As David Callahan wrote, U.S. tax laws sometime seem to be designed to facilitate tax avoidance by the super wealthy ie. WHO CARES WHAT YOUR TAX RATE IS WHEN THE LAW ALLOWS THE RICH TO TAKE ADVANGE OF SPECIAL PERKS SO THEY PAY AN ACTUAL RATE LOWER THAN EVERYONE ELSE. Combine this with the Republican supported Corp. Welfare, largest increase in the wealth of the wealthy in history while middle class wealth has decreased more than any time in history, Mult. tax breaks that only the wealthy can effectively utlize and increasing CEO pay and workers pay drops EVEN a Tea Bagger should be smart enough to figure out the CLASS WAR IS REAL and the 99% are loseing it.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350941513934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350941816342-285</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHOICE IS CLEAR: COMMIE MUZZIE vs CHRISTIAN MORMON</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350938389614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plese keep posting your insane rants ........ People in america need to be reminded that we can not allow the nuts to assume control. ps also please take the pee party pledge to leave the country when obama wins, we need your spot for someone who does not have $hit for brains</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350941816342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350941905707-286</Id><Title>NEW POLL RESULTS</Title><Msg>9 OF FLIPPERS 10 GRANDMOTHERS SUPPORT OBAMA</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350941905707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350941956183-287</Id><Title>That's a breakout of range for YHOO</Title><Msg>moe</Msg><Username>eatmayercooch</Username><Timestamp>1350941956183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350942007754-288</Id><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Msg>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Msg><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350942033655-289</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POLL RESULTS</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350941905707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:38:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Caro-lie. You are off you meds again. Shame on you.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1350942033655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350942119293-290</Id><Title>Romney will slam-dunk Obama on this tonight!</Title><Msg>“The Libyan rights activist who was highlighted by the Obama administration in news accounts as having not been, ‘publicly associated with the U.S.’ until the Oversight Committee released documents had actually been brought to the U.S. in December 2011 by the State Department and her trip is highlighted on the Internet," Issa said. "President Obama should be ashamed of yet another example where his administration has been caught trying to mislead the American people about what happened in Libya.”</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350942119293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350942156950-291</Id><Title>Take a look at BAC on NASDAQ after hours trading. POP tomorrow?</Title><Msg>Hit a high of $9.60. Lots of volume. Does this mean a ice pop tomorrow morning?</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1350942156950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350942205794-292</Id><Title>Romney gonna smack Obama tonite !</Title><Msg>Dear Governer Romney, please do me a favor. Bite Obama's ear like Mike Tyson if you have to. This loser Obama deserved more beating ! WIN ROMNEY WIN !!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350942205794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350942210277-293</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like a nice leg up in the morning.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1350942210277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350942342690-294</Id><Topic><Title>LIAR ObamaCraps in a frenzy over Libyan reports. They have to find another way to help Dear Leader cover it all up!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350939859290</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dump ......... please keep posting , since it continues to show why the Republican Party is made ip of nuts and should not be allowed in power at any level</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350942342690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350942613955-295</Id><Title>Governer Romney got ALL my support !</Title><Msg>I feel really happy whenever Romney kicked Obama's butt !!! WIN ROMNEY WIN !!!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350942613955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350942870932-296</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gheez - your jealousy is showing chittttt go to work an earn an income - cry baby</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1350942870932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943013656-297</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, he can breed, HE IS a self-made man who took the Million from family to get a start, who said they had tough times and ALMOST had to dip into their trust funds, had a great education paid for by a rich daddy,mission work in that backward foreign country of France where he drove a car and did not ride the bicycle like the lesser people, he did serve as REQUIRED by his Church, BUT YOU ARE RIGHT , HE CAN AND WILL TURN THIS COUNTRY AROUND ...BACK TO THE 1950'S SO WOMEN WILL NOT HAVE RIGHTS, BLACKS CAN NOT VOTE , ETC., ETC. MITT IS THE MAN THAT WILL MOVE US BACK .</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350943013656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943031990-298</Id><Topic><Title>Las Vegas odds have Obama winning 2-1. Not smart to bet against the house.</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939354581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:55:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Makes no sense. Vegas has obummer 2-1 odd favorite. Why? He is a commie socialist with a agenda to destroy our free capital system. Not a optimal pick in my book. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1350943031990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943116317-299</Id><Topic><Title>Is "bury obama" a blatant racist inbred white trash tea bagger?</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940615590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's is not an EITHER / OR answer,,,,,,,,,,, the actual answer is yes to both</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350943116317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943141699-300</Id><Topic><Title>LIAR ObamaCraps in a frenzy over Libyan reports. They have to find another way to help Dear Leader cover it all up!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350939859290</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another fool carrying Murdoch's catheter</Msg><Username>whatgozaround</Username><Timestamp>1350943141699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:59:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943313336-301</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep , America would win the prize for electing another Republican idiot ......... mission accomplished</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1350943313336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350943423271-302</Id><Title>More enlightened Republican leadership</Title><Msg>A candidate for the Arkansas legislature, Charlie Fuqua, says children who don’t demonstrate “respect for parents” should be put to death, the Arkansas Times reports. Fuqua is a former member of the Arkansas legislature and has received support from the Arkansas Republican Party and two sitting members of Congress. Here’s the key passage from Fuqua’s 2012 book, “God’s Law: The Only Political Solution“: 'The maintenance of civil order in society rests on the foundation of family discipline. Therefore, a child who disrespects his parents must be permanently removed from society in a way that gives an example to all other children of the importance of respect for parents. The death penalty for rebellious children is not something to be taken lightly. The guidelines for administering the death penalty to rebellious children are given in Deut 21:18-21'. Fuqua helpfully notes that “This passage does not give parents blanket authority to kill their children.” Rather, parents would have to “follow the proper procedure in order to have the death penalty executed against their children.” Fuqua assures the reader that, in his view, the procedure would “rarely be used.” The threat of death would, however, “be a tremendous incentive for children to give proper respect to their parents." Fuqua, reached by the Huffington Post on the issue, declined to comment. ROTFLMAO the Confederate wing of Al Qaeda has spoken.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350943423271</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943598860-303</Id><Topic><Title>$95 million trade at the close?</Title><Username>atascaderoguy</Username><Timestamp>1350936459119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any guesses?</Msg><Username>atascaderoguy</Username><Timestamp>1350943598860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350943944356-304</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we got a nice positive divergence going on with this stock. Should hopefully float up quite a bit over the next month or two. I'm more than okay with that!</Msg><Username>jomopen11</Username><Timestamp>1350943944356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944016851-305</Id><Topic><Title>$95 million trade at the close?</Title><Username>atascaderoguy</Username><Timestamp>1350936459119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought large trades were common after hours because that's when large investors do their bidding :) my guess</Msg><Username>do_not_try_it_at_home</Username><Timestamp>1350944016851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944151409-306</Id><Topic><Title>BOTTOM LINE, OBAMA LOSES, AMERICA WINS</Title><Username>barryisaliar</Username><Timestamp>1350935727970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 15:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it doesn't matter who wins, wall street always wins! the difference with Obama winning is that little player might have a better chance IMHO</Msg><Username>do_not_try_it_at_home</Username><Timestamp>1350944151409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944360859-307</Id><Topic><Title>Is "bury obama" a blatant racist inbred white trash tea bagger?</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940615590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe a tea bagger when when visiting you mom</Msg><Username>do_not_try_it_at_home</Username><Timestamp>1350944360859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944467194-308</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT HAS OBAMA BEEN PROMISING pUTIN IF HE WINS?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1350944402479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:20:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Canada</Msg><Username>lawcram</Username><Timestamp>1350944467194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944485910-309</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is definitely successful smart and many other good things... but under new republican dogma, he just sold his soul to the devil</Msg><Username>do_not_try_it_at_home</Username><Timestamp>1350944485910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350944698866-310</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow you are an idiot,etc.etc.etc.</Msg><Username>lawcram</Username><Timestamp>1350944698866</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350944743161-311</Id><Title>I am a Democrat but will not be voting for Obama this time</Title><Msg>I believe he knew in hours or at most a day that it was a terrorist attack. I don't fault him for thinking politically at first after all it is the heat of election battle but what I can't deal with is the continued denial and cover-up. This went on for weeks. It makes me think what else is he dishonest about? It should you as well. In my opinion he has lost credibility with the American people</Msg><Username>angry.democrat</Username><Timestamp>1350944743161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350944759905-312</Id><Title>BAC $18- $20 is not out of question.</Title><Msg>before it moves into mid 20's. Banks are basically printing money right now. and more will c ome as economy recovers. Good Day boys</Msg><Username>techxpit</Username><Timestamp>1350944759905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350945507095-313</Id><Title>WHEN ROMNEY WINS I'M GOING TO GO OUT IN THE STREET AND PUNCH A DEMOCRAT IN THE MOUTH</Title><Msg>Just to add injury to insult! I love watching democrats cry!!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945507095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350945604656-314</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder if Mitt ever had to do a real days work in his life ?</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350945604656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350945716987-315</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN ROMNEY WINS I'M GOING TO GO OUT IN THE STREET AND PUNCH A DEMOCRAT IN THE MOUTH</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945507095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will it be a woman or a child ?</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350945716987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350945876181-316</Id><Topic><Title>BAC $18- $20 is not out of question.</Title><Username>techxpit</Username><Timestamp>1350944759905</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. "Good things come to those who wait". And the facts show the economy is recovering, especially housing. If it happened quickly, that would have been aberrational. This is gradual and steady, the way it should be.</Msg><Username>derek.nsai</Username><Timestamp>1350945876181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:44:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350945954254-317</Id><Topic><Title>bury_obama is just another SW rectal drip alias. They all drip from the same A-- hole.</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350671278204</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:27:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>drip, drip, drip.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350945954254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:45:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350945962625-318</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN ROMNEY WINS I'M GOING TO GO OUT IN THE STREET AND PUNCH A DEMOCRAT IN THE MOUTH</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945507095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEMOCRAT MEN CRY BETTER THAN WOMEN</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945962625</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350945966765-319</Id><Title>First thing Mitt will do is spend two trillion on more govermnet !</Title><Msg>and drop all taxes on interest and capital gains so his taxes will be zero .</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350945966765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:46:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946021500-320</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Bag S*c*u*m* do not support moderate Mitt? Why? Is he not neo-nazi enough?</Title><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896496901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same old, same old. All they do is smear Obama.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946021500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946021850-321</Id><Topic><Title>Lying Tea Bag S*c*u*m* do not support moderate Mitt? Why? Is he not neo-nazi enough?</Title><Username>voice_from_the_empty_chair</Username><Timestamp>1350896496901</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 05:01:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same old, same old. All they do is smear Obama.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946021850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946078624-322</Id><Topic><Title>Fifteen days until the re-election of President Obama</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350938514398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:41:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's ready to watch Obama kick Mitt's a** again?</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946078624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946178031-323</Id><Topic><Title>Is "bury obama" a blatant racist inbred white trash tea bagger?</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350940615590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The correct answer is: he is both</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946178031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946297446-324</Id><Topic><Title>Liar Tea Baggers in a frenzy over Libyan reports. They have to find something else to lie about.</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939114449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:51:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to the "birther" issue.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946297446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946308359-325</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN ROMNEY WINS I'M GOING TO GO OUT IN THE STREET AND PUNCH A DEMOCRAT IN THE MOUTH</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945507095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make sure it's a cop that just voted democrat.</Msg><Username>lovmayercooch</Username><Timestamp>1350946308359</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946349350-326</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans lie like most people breathe</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939183580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:53:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946349350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:52:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946376846-327</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN ROMNEY WINS I'M GOING TO GO OUT IN THE STREET AND PUNCH A DEMOCRAT IN THE MOUTH</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350945507095</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:38:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt will be a joke tonight, the Mitt Flopper doesn't have a chance !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350946376846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350946545480-328</Id><Title>Wow Mr. Frank is defending JPM and includes BofA acquisition of Merill Lynch</Title><Msg>Barney Frank cries foul in government's lawsuit against JPMorgan</Msg><Username>dasafwy</Username><Timestamp>1350946545480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350946553812-329</Id><Title>bury_obama = gutless white trash chicken.</Title><Msg>Making threats on a message board takes the courage of a gnat.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946553812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350946638015-330</Id><Topic><Title>Las Vegas odds have Obama winning 2-1. Not smart to bet against the house.</Title><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1350939354581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:55:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vegas odds, Obama 2/5 Favorite Romney 2/1 underdog.. if you put $5 on Obama, you get $7 back if he wins. put $5 on Romney, you get $15 back if he wins.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350946638015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350946734528-331</Id><Title>Liar Tea Baggers: What's the latest on your favorite topic, the "birther" issue?</Title><Msg>Has Sheriff Joe come up with more fabricated evidence lately?</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350946734528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350947032379-332</Id><Topic><Title>I am a Democrat but will not be voting for Obama this time</Title><Username>angry.democrat</Username><Timestamp>1350944743161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:25:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This Benghazi horror would never have happened if we had a good president there was plenty of warning and nothing done about it. Of course Obama would have to attended the security and intelligence briefings. Which he doesn't do</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1350947032379</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350947050700-333</Id><Topic><Title>TAGG ROMNEY SIGNS ABORTION AGREEMENT WITH SURROGATE, AGAINST DEFECTS</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350777692767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-20 20:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next time Anne Romney goes on a TV show I am going to call ahead and see if they can ask some questions about this. I left a question for Mitt Romney, no response.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1350947050700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:04:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350947473180-334</Id><Title>bofa is like obama,,, aint going nowhere.. #$%$</Title><Msg>except foodstamp and fraud gone up</Msg><Username>seanwu733</Username><Timestamp>1350947473180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350947580479-335</Id><Title>The Motley Fool's Informal Poll Results-about 30 seconds ago</Title><Msg>A special thanks to those of you who took our informal poll. To date 33% of you believe Romney will doom your wealth while the other 67% think Obama will bring more harm to your portfolio. Read on for The Motley Fool's take!</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350947580479</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350948305009-336</Id><Title>GOP'rs are WIMPS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>The USSR could blow the US up multiple times. Iran may or may not build a couple of bombs and the GOP is screaming the sky is falling because of it. Talk about nannies.</Msg><Username>waitin_for_read_my_lips</Username><Timestamp>1350948305009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350948350120-337</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you aware that when Mitt's father George died he gave his ENTIRE inheritance to charity. Once again, that greedy SOB!</Msg><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350948350120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:25:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350948540305-338</Id><Title>barney is a fafffgot for the banks</Title><Msg>holeit up demorcrack</Msg><Username>seanwu733</Username><Timestamp>1350948540305</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350948717517-339</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY &amp; HIS FAMILY</Title><Username>parisonr</Username><Timestamp>1350939510490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 16:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats take the cake on this board for nastiness. That alone would make me look askance at voting any of the democrat ticket. But then my democrat friends are great people....perhaps it's BAC democrats. Not really worth thinking about much.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1350948717517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350948746708-340</Id><Topic><Title>British engineers create gasoline from thin air</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1350946651081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:57:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone offering to be POTUS come out and say "We are five days away from fundamentally transforming the United States of America." After 45 months it's plain as day that The WH Occupier and Gang Obama hate the founding concepts established by our Constitution and The Declaration of Independence. There should be no doubts that The WH Occupier and Gang Obama must be given their eviction notice to vacate the premises. They are a menace and a hazard to the well-being of the USA and the American people. November 6, 2012. FIRE The WH Occupier, Gang Obama and every Democrat across the USA; stop empowering traitors; get it done!!!</Msg><Username>dons_st</Username><Timestamp>1350948746708</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350948942815-341</Id><Title>WHO WILL SHOW UP - MITTEN ROMNEY OR JETRO ROMNEY</Title><Msg>Mitten Romney - Is against abortion with no exceptions Jetro Romney - Against abortion but with exceptions Mitten Romney - Against more teachers in our schools Jetro Romney - For more teachers in our schools Mitten Romney - Against equal pay for women Jetro Romney - Against and for equal pay for women Mitten Romney - Sanctioning China for dumping tires in US market is bad for business Jetro Romney - Sanctioning China for dumping tires was my idea in the first place and its good Mitten Romney - Let Detroit go bankrupt and what Obama did for Detroit was bad for America Jetro Romney - I'm on the same page with the President, he did exactly what I suggested he do. Mitten Romney - I will de-fund Plan Parenthood. Jetro Romey - Not really THIS DUDE IS A FREAKING JOKE, ANY WOMAN WHO VOTE FOR THIS BABOON SHOULD HAVE HER HEAD EXAMINED</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1350948942815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350949192596-342</Id><Title>What comes with a Mitt Flopper ?</Title><Msg>Everything but still leaves you empty !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350949192596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:39:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350949392786-343</Id><Title>I can't wait for tomorrow morning, you guys will all laugh...</Title><Msg>best day of the month.</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350949392786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350949465908-344</Id><Topic><Title>What comes with a Mitt Flopper ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1350949192596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:39:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it a big dick up the democrat bass..and yours..</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350949465908</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350949627033-345</Id><Title>BAC = $9.61 in after hours trading</Title><Msg>And it feels so good</Msg><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350949627033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350949706929-346</Id><Topic><Title>Flush the hundreds of SW rectal drip aliases with the "ignore user" function.</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350672172691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:42:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1350949706929</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350949731632-347</Id><Title>No Teleprompter....No Crowley.... BIG PROBLEM .......COUNTDOWN BEGINS</Title><Msg>Just ROBO MEMORIZE the answer. Al Queda on the RUN.......Huh.........except the AL QUEDA FLAG replaced the AMERICAN FLAG in the US EMBASSY in LIBYA, are they on the RUN?</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350949731632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350949988890-348</Id><Title>ROMNEY IS A LYING PILE OF DOG POOP - THIS GUY IS USELESS</Title><Msg>he will lose by a mile and the house and the senate will be in the hands of democrats and not those miserable freaking moronic anti-america and greedy fukkkkkas</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1350949988890</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350950150845-349</Id><Title>Mitt is much better looking than Obama</Title><Msg>And he's white</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1350950150845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350950181265-350</Id><Title>GOP Candidates Proposing a Draft to Fight Iran?</Title><Msg>I wonder if they are talking drafted beer? Must be their cure for unemployment and retirement.</Msg><Username>waitin_for_read_my_lips</Username><Timestamp>1350950181265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350950501106-351</Id><Topic><Title>I am a Democrat but will not be voting for Obama this time</Title><Username>angry.democrat</Username><Timestamp>1350944743161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 18:25:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't fault him so much for that although there is a little negligence there but what bothers me is his deceit after the fact. He would and should have said to the American people look I made a mistake it was not about a youtube video or demonstration within 48hrs after the attack, NOT weeks later and still is in denial. Its always the cover-up. Why don't politicians realize the cover-up is often worse than the event? But he has lost all credibility with me</Msg><Username>angry.democrat</Username><Timestamp>1350950501106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350950682474-352</Id><Topic><Title>WHO WILL SHOW UP - MITTEN ROMNEY OR JETRO ROMNEY</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1350948942815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:35:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me ole lady said she'd whip your black #$%$ up you want to meet her at a walmart parking lot...i've got 50 bucks on her...I told her to cool off your just a crazy ole #$%$ and you wouldn't show up...ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350950682474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350950794353-353</Id><Title>Will Mitt Romney pardon Bernie M?</Title><Msg>After all they are both job creaters. Right???</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1350950794353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350951402453-354</Id><Title>Walter Mitty and Eddie Munster</Title><Msg>What a team. LONG BAC</Msg><Username>ooo_key_doke</Username><Timestamp>1350951402453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:16:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350951762621-355</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like babbling stupidity is the favorite past time of the fringe right dog crap eaters.</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1350679368998</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will all of these liars do after Obama is re-elected?</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951762621</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350951949496-356</Id><Title>Obama will pick up where he left off last week and continue humiliating Mitt.</Title><Msg>"Please continue, Mr. Governor." RFLMAO!!</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951949496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350952095464-357</Id><Title>Worst case scenarios</Title><Msg>If Obama wins again BAC might drop to like 2 bucks ! READ MY LIPS !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350952095464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350952132664-358</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Candidates Proposing a Draft to Fight Iran?</Title><Username>waitin_for_read_my_lips</Username><Timestamp>1350950181265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 19:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where have you been jethro? Iran is cyber attacking our banks trying again and again to cause economic chaos in America why not attack back? Wait a second let's surrender like we did to our space program to Russia, our manufacturing to china. Shall I go on?</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350952132664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350952193863-359</Id><Title>A Commander in Chief with four draft deferments? NO WAY!</Title><Msg>Mitt is a classic chickenhawk. Rich boy with deferments. Talks war but walks chicken.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350952193863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350952198967-360</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could break out in the morning...lets see</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1350952198967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:29:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350952406190-361</Id><Topic><Title>Lest we forget: Republican incompetence responsible for 9/11 terrorist attacks.</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1350678801357</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last thing America needs is another gang of Republican incompetents dropping the ball at every turn.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350952406190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350952519307-362</Id><Topic><Title>The utter stupidity of the right wingers shows a real need for a voter intelligence test.</Title><Username>obama.4more</Username><Timestamp>1350677973016</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zevoter would need several tutors and several cheat-cheats.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350952519307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350952645974-363</Id><Title>Obama is this country's problem</Title><Msg>Toss him out.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350952645974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350952866269-364</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are forecasting a very strong performance from financials in the very near term. Though you might see some fluctuation... Sentiment: Sell your mom and buy BAC NOW !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350952866269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350953226746-365</Id><Title>Tell Vladimir Putin this....</Title><Msg>This is my last election....I will be flexible with missile defense...WHAT A BASTERD !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350953226746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350953292173-366</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is this country's problem</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350952645974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:37:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kick him out in Nov., and don't let the door hit him in the #$%$.</Msg><Username>bidds000</Username><Timestamp>1350953292173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:48:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350953434352-367</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How high do you expect BAC to move?</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350953434352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350953541134-368</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is this country's problem</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350952645974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:37:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to be honest..baracko will be much happyer back with his gay boy friends in the chic-ago bath houses..he'll have larry sinclair and all the gays in rev.wrights church to be with..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350953541134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350953689871-369</Id><Topic><Title>BAC = $9.60 in after hours trading</Title><Username>i_need_the_money_too</Username><Timestamp>1350942007754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 17:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a ton of resistance at 10.....but BAC has been sitting in this real tight trading range for a week....this sometimes favors a large move, so it could go through 10.10. Just have to see, but it could be very interesting</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1350953689871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:54:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350953739677-370</Id><Title>Romnesia</Title><Msg>That fool Romney... he "remembers" Obama saying that if he didn't cut the deficit in half then he'd be a one term president. He also "remembers" Obama saying that he would close Gitmo. Obviously, "somebody" has a problem with their memory...</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitellii</Username><Timestamp>1350953739677</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350953974377-371</Id><Title>Sometime this year, we taxpayers will again receive another 'Economic Stimulus' payment.</Title><Msg>Sometime this year, we taxpayers will again receive another 'Economic Stimulus' payment. This is indeed a very exciting program, and I'll explain it by using a Q &amp; A format: Q. What is an 'Economic Stimulus' payment ? A. It is money that the federal government will send to taxpayers. Q.. Where will the government get this money ? A. From taxpayers. Q. So the government is giving me back my own money ? A. Only a smidgen of it. Q. What is the purpose of this payment ? A. The plan is for you to use the money to purchase a high-definition TV set, thus stimulating the economy. Q. But isn't that stimulating the economy of China ? A. Shut up. Below is some helpful advice on how to best help the U.S. Economy by spending your stimulus check wisely: * If you spend the stimulus money at Wal-Mart, the money will go to China or Sri Lanka . * If you spend it on gasoline, your money will go to the Arabs. * If you purchase a computer, it will go to India , Taiwan or China . * If you purchase fruit and vegetables, it will go to Mexico , Honduras and Guatemala .. * If you buy an efficient car, it will go to Japan or Korea . * If you purchase useless stuff, it will go to Taiwan . * If you pay your credit cards off, or buy stock, it will go to management bonuses and they will hide it offshore. Instead, keep the money in America by: 1) Spending it at yard sales, or 2) Going to ball games, or 3) Spending it on prostitutes or gigilos, or 4) Beer or 5) Tattoos. (These are the only American businesses still operating in the U.S. ) Conclusion: Go to a ball game with a tattooed prostitute/gigilo that you met at a yard sale and drink beer all day ! No need to thank me, I'm just glad I could be of help.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350953974377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:59:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350954410216-372</Id><Title>democrack are lazy,, they sit and let 4 dipolomats got ambush and killed</Title><Msg>they did not do their job.</Msg><Username>seanwu733</Username><Timestamp>1350954410216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350954688041-373</Id><Title>Bank of America Hires $2.5 Billion Adviser From Morgan Stanley</Title><Msg>http://www.businessweek.com/news/2012-10-22/bank-of-america-hires-2-dot-5-billion-adviser-from-morgan-stanley</Msg><Username>shanumer8310</Username><Timestamp>1350954688041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350955319484-374</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO GET SELL BAC AT THIS 9.10 LEVEL!!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1350063556067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy traderx dumdum</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1350955319484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350955388229-375</Id><Title>Romney wanted troops left in Iraq</Title><Msg>However Bush negotiated the withdrawl. "Troop presence,” Romney said in his foreign policy speech at the Virginia Military Institute in Lexington, Va. “The president tried — and failed — to secure a responsible and gradual drawdown that would have better secured our gains.” Obama has touted the removal of troops from Iraq on the campaign trail. His 2008 campaign was built on criticism of the Bush administration's handling of the war, but Iraq and Afghanistan have been discussed sparingly during this year's campaign. Romney, like many Republicans, criticized the Obama administration last year after it announced that all U.S. troops were leaving Iraq at the end of 2011. Republicans argued that the administration should have maintained a U.S. presence there to help maintain security and train Iraqi forces, and that Obama failed in negotiations with Iraqi President Nouri al-Maliki. U.S. troops left at the end of 2011 under the terms of an agreement signed by President George W. Bush. And Democrats point out that al-Maliki refused to give U.S. troops immunity in Iraqi courts, effectively killing any chance of renewing the deal.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350955388229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350955718411-376</Id><Topic><Title>Sometime this year, we taxpayers will again receive another 'Economic Stimulus' payment.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350953974377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:59:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eye likes the cuntclusion.</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1350955718411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956226180-377</Id><Title>Carter</Title><Msg>Isn't being the worst President in our history enough, now he has to go shoot his mouth off again and blame Isreal. Just go to sleep and not wake up!</Msg><Username>jld2734</Username><Timestamp>1350956226180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956261143-378</Id><Title>Obamaroids</Title><Msg>Caused by excessive #$%$ without any experience then lead to failure.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350956261143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956348631-379</Id><Title>Obama is one rude son of a #$%$!</Title><Msg>Obama is one rude son of a #$%$!</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1350956348631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956592991-380</Id><Title>OBAMA IS WINNING THE DEBATE</Title><Msg>ROMNEY WANTS TO START A WAR</Msg><Username>midnight_riderssss</Username><Timestamp>1350956592991</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956924746-381</Id><Title>Romney kicking butt again</Title><Msg>Obama you are unemployed.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350956924746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:48:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956961824-382</Id><Title>None and done.</Title><Msg>Only halfway through this evening's debate, and Mitt's already finished. His foreign policy: try to do what Obama has done, but spend a lot more money doing it. Last debate, most of ObamaCare was fine with Mitt; tonight he wants to axe the whole thing. Say good night, Willard. ROTFLMAO and see if someone will lend you a genuine smile for your closing remarks.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350956961824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350956980650-383</Id><Title>Romney will chase Latinos out of USA</Title><Msg>Screw Romney</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350956980650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957046132-384</Id><Title>Romney wants to Invade Iceland,,,</Title><Msg>Republicans Invaded Iraq,,,,,,,what the hell was that about?</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350957046132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957156646-385</Id><Title>Romney Hates Women,,wants them all Pregnant</Title><Msg>He wants to abolish Planned Parenthood..... He says,,,a Fetus is a Person,,he says,,,,Condoms will be outlawed,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350957156646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957220506-386</Id><Title>Obama talks, talks, and talks yet says nothing</Title><Msg>...and he tends to end blaming someone why it his plan did not work.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350957220506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350957273651-387</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will pick up where he left off last week and continue humiliating Mitt.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951949496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good diagnosis, doc. Halfway over now, and Romney's going down in flames. ROTFLMAO a squadron of F-22s couldn't protect him from Obama's laser-guided missiles.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350957273651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350957350921-388</Id><Topic><Title>None and done.</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350956961824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching on CNN and when he mentioned apology tour his rating dropped well below the line by both men and women. His lie is not being accepted.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350957350921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:55:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957380911-389</Id><Title>America only has one enemy and that is Obama's Socialist Policies</Title><Msg>He is destroying America's capitalist system.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350957380911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350957447323-390</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will pick up where he left off last week and continue humiliating Mitt.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951949496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts are invaluable to our study. Please continue to fart, oops, post.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1350957447323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957478299-391</Id><Title>Is Osama Bin Ladin better off than 4 yrs ago?</Title><Msg>Republicans trained the Taliban</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350957478299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350957520776-392</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will pick up where he left off last week and continue humiliating Mitt.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951949496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Past your bedtime Fishbreath. Please show more respect to your fellow specimen.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1350957520776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957572588-393</Id><Title>9/11 GW Bush Day,,,,Republican Day</Title><Msg>Republicans are Proud of Bush legacy</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350957572588</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957676036-394</Id><Title>The Great Socialist Obama is a miserable failure</Title><Msg>His socialist policies are a huge failure the only thing he has are lies.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350957676036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957789916-395</Id><Title>Four years of blaming others</Title><Msg>He is out, no more Obama socialist policies.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350957789916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350957857356-396</Id><Topic><Title>None and done.</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350956961824</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:49:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney destroying himself with his rambling and no solution or program He just flat lined for 2 minutes. Then Obama kicked his butt.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350957857356</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957896501-397</Id><Title>9:55 - Check out Romney's rapid eye blinking!</Title><Msg>Looks like he's fighting back the tears now. I hope he can still see his ship sailing....without him. ROTFLMAO Obama is now spanking him like a teacher dealing with a kid who hasn't done his homework.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350957896501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957931362-398</Id><Title>Are four americans better off now? an ambassador and three brave americans.</Title><Msg>Obama the failure.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350957931362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957937122-399</Id><Title>GW Bush was a DRUNK,,,he cannot be held Responsible</Title><Msg>he started 2 of americas longest wars....he created the largest deficits he had the worst economic meltdown</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350957937122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350957954461-400</Id><Title>Romney already kicked Obama's butt !!!</Title><Msg>Obama looked like a little chihuahua dog next to Romney. WIN ! ROMNEY ! WIN !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350957954461</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350958036448-401</Id><Topic><Title>will obama use this debate to give his concession speech?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1350957167357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:52:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama the failed president.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350958036448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350958072074-402</Id><Topic><Title>Obama will pick up where he left off last week and continue humiliating Mitt.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350951949496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a big future for your institute.....in self-study programs. ROTFLMAO it should be a late night for you......calling your Vegas bookie to get enough money down on Obama to offset the losing bets you already made.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350958072074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350958171774-403</Id><Title>Half a flip flop is a belly buster</Title><Msg>"While Gov. Romney believes that the continued presence of U.S. forces in Afghanistan should ultimately be decided by the military’s top brass, he cautions that the country should not be making similar commitments in the future. He also stressed that the bulk of the security obligation must lie with the Afghanis themselves. Gov. Romney indicated in an interview with ABC on July 29, 2012, that while he is supportive of President Barack Obama’s Sept 2014 troops withdrawal deadline, he disagrees with the plan to order 23,000 troops out of Afghanistan by Sept. 30. However, he admits that his position could change depending on the counsel of military commanders, while leaving open the possibility of keeping combat troops in Afghanistan beyond 2014 should conditions change." Now he is in full agreement that troops will be out in 2014.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350958171774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350958187745-404</Id><Topic><Title>Carter</Title><Username>jld2734</Username><Timestamp>1350956226180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:37:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What? Obama isn't the worst? ROTFLMAO Mitt isn't having much success running Obama down either. Maybe he should have tried debating Carter instead of the guy who is taking him apart right now.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350958187745</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350958513737-405</Id><Topic><Title>obama is right on one thing, this is the last election he will EVER see</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1350958144057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he is planning on taking over Castro's position.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350958513737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350958650048-406</Id><Topic><Title>gosh the cardinals are going down, but obama is going down faster</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1350957998030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:06:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2 weeks finally Obama is out.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350958650048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350958988850-407</Id><Title>Obama just said, "Governor Romney You Are Right..."</Title><Msg>Obama has to leave office for better ideas.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350958988850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959042133-408</Id><Title>haa,, the china people,,, they pretend to be innocent and good but tricky and dishonest</Title><Msg>gop is leader.</Msg><Username>seanwu733</Username><Timestamp>1350959042133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959181038-409</Id><Title>Obama pulled a Biden</Title><Msg>He tried talking over Romney. His totalitarian regime has got to go. Rude and crude.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350959181038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959451686-410</Id><Title>Romney won this debate and finished very strong</Title><Msg>Hello new President.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350959451686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350959582766-411</Id><Topic><Title>Obama pulled a Biden</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350959181038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney as something to say whereas Obama just says something then blames someone for failure.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350959582766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959598021-412</Id><Title>Romnisia on the Auto industry</Title><Msg>He can't remember he srote this in 2008 In the first paragraph of his 2008 article, Mr. Romney made an unmistakable prediction: “If General Motors, Ford and Chrysler get the bailout that their chief executives asked for yesterday, you can kiss the American automotive industry goodbye. It won’t go overnight, but its demise will be virtually guaranteed.”</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350959598021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350959696123-413</Id><Topic><Title>Romney won this debate and finished very strong</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350959451686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:30:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your an idiot</Msg><Username>kacnkel</Username><Timestamp>1350959696123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959783930-414</Id><Title>Romney closing statements flat lined</Title><Msg>With the group of Florida undecided voters Romney was a total failure tonight. Obama scored much better with the women but had favorable ratings from the men much of the time.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350959783930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350959889877-415</Id><Title>Roomnt was much better. Obama</Title><Msg>go home. ur bad for the usa and the world.</Msg><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350959889877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350960068398-416</Id><Title>romney lost this election the day he picked ryan as a mate!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>you people sit back and watch</Msg><Username>kacnkel</Username><Timestamp>1350960068398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350960173154-417</Id><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Msg>Romney was able to convince China and voters NOT to F with America !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350960439445-418</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the news media is saying obama won!!! you idiot</Msg><Username>kacnkel</Username><Timestamp>1350960439445</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350960553755-419</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES HE DID!!! ILMFAO</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350960553755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350960786966-420</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After November 6th you will feel the pain of living your life without Obama !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960786966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350960813205-421</Id><Title>ROMNEY ROPER DOPED OBAMA....MITT DID WHAT HE HAD TO DO!!!</Title><Msg>He stayed cool under obamas attacks...record on auto bale out...romney told the true..you look it up yourself...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350960813205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350960987848-422</Id><Title>Obama took Romney to school again. Romney learns about ships not found in his bathtub.</Title><Msg>I hope Mitt finally gets that an aircraft carrier has more capability than a canoe.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350960987848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961228400-423</Id><Topic><Title>Roomnt was much better. Obama</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1350959889877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stevens was crying so much he couldn't see which keys he was hitting. Our greatest BAC prognosticator has handed Romney the win (along with Cadaver Krauthammer), and you know what that means....ROTFLMAO Obama 4 more, Romney none and done.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350961228400</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961301579-424</Id><Title>Obama looked Petty, Desperate teenager type personal jabs not presidential...This election is over Romney President Elect</Title><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350961301579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961372300-425</Id><Title>CBS poll gives a huge debate win to Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%</Title><Msg>500 undecided voters rate the instant poll that rated Obama the 2-1 winner.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961372300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961467145-426</Id><Title>Romney Got Obama to Destroy his Likeability. Obama looked upset and bitter</Title><Msg>Romney looked more presidential</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350961467145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961503842-427</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked Petty, Desperate teenager type personal jabs not presidential...This election is over Romney President Elect</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350961301579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree. odumba looked very primitive compared to romney. odumba has no plans or ideas.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350961503842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961510728-428</Id><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Msg>ROMNEY won in tonight's debate ...NO QUESTION ABOUT IT .......what ROMNEY did tonjght is enough to earn the votes of the remaining 7 %.........IN THE SWING STATES.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961545118-429</Id><Topic><Title>CBS poll gives a huge debate win to Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961372300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles 'The Cadaver' Krauthammer called it a resounding Romney victory. Too bad he can't 'win' a few more like this one, but I think it'll do. ROTFLMAO heck, I should call Charles....all these years I felt like we lost in Vietnam; it sure would be nice to hear him tell me I won.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350961545118</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961556575-430</Id><Topic><Title>Obama took Romney to school again. Romney learns about ships not found in his bathtub.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350960987848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama took him to the woodshed and told him not to speak loose and pretend you aren't... R-Money apologized and acted as if he had learned a his lesson. But that animal can't change his spots even though he can pretend he looks different during the confrontation.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350961556575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961637015-431</Id><Title>Obama wins another one. Every poll rates him the winner again.</Title><Msg>The wing dings are trying in vain to mask Mitt's weak performance with the usual slobber and spin.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961637015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961696460-432</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Got Obama to Destroy his Likeability. Obama looked upset and bitter</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350961467145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:04:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO Romney blinked, squinted and grimaced through 80% of the debate. Obama looked like a guy demolishing a juicy steak. Spin boy, your days are numbered. ROTFLMAO the only presidency Mitt will be serving in is a corporate one.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350961696460</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961816848-433</Id><Topic><Title>CBS poll gives a huge debate win to Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961372300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles Krauthammer has been having too many senior/Alzheimer's moments on the KQED program that I watch. However, every now and then he see things in a realistic way and I like those rare moments.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350961816848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961822128-434</Id><Title>I am glad Romney is bring sensitivity back !</Title><Msg>It is impossible for Governer Romney alone himself to rescue America. He will need all the strength of us. Obama is an idiot AND must go PERIOD !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350961822128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350961945029-435</Id><Topic><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO Florida doesn't look much like a swing state anymore....it's Obama's. Same goes for Ohio and PA. Go look at the replay, especially from around 45 minutes in through the 1 hour 10 minute point, and watch Romney whenever Obama had the floor. He looked a lot more like Mole Man than any US President I've ever seen. ROTFLMAO or maybe Obama kicked sand in Mitt's face when no one was looking.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350961945029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350961953081-436</Id><Title>Look at the resident neo-nazi wing dings slobber and spin over Mitt's beat down. Ha, ha!!</Title><Msg>The fools can't handle Mitt's beat down.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961953081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962004245-437</Id><Topic><Title>CBS poll gives a huge debate win to Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961372300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles has been in a wheelchair since a young man. You are ignorant. Charles is measured and reasonable</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350962004245</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962081549-438</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wins another one. Every poll rates him the winner again.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961637015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:07:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean abc,nbc,cbs and msnbc??? Ilmfao...the left wing media of corse...ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350962081549</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:14:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962090102-439</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trashofvietnam, only to midgets like you!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350962090102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962107709-440</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked Petty, Desperate teenager type personal jabs not presidential...This election is over Romney President Elect</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350961301579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama looked angry but brought up silly attacks against Romney that didn't justify his anger. It was almost comical to watch him be so desperate and unconfident</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350962107709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962153317-441</Id><Topic><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NATION'S ECONOMY is the most to be concerned about. Strong NATION'S ECONOMY means a strong MILITARY, A strong nation MEANS a strong leader of the WORLD.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350962153317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962211238-442</Id><Topic><Title>obama is right on one thing, this is the last election he will EVER see</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1350958144057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you misunderstood, it is the last election than he can win for the presidency. Next up, in 2017 he will be Hilliary's Secretary of the Interior or perhaps special envoy to Israel.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1350962211238</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962217361-443</Id><Topic><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama not only looks presidential, he IS presidential. Mitt took a serious beat down.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962217361</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962232002-444</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wins another one. Every poll rates him the winner again.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961637015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:07:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney came up looser tonight.</Msg><Username>edi_kh2000</Username><Timestamp>1350962232002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962266211-445</Id><Title>Romney's Lead Will Continue to Grow</Title><Msg>This election won't be close by election day</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350962266211</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962289917-446</Id><Topic><Title>Carter</Title><Username>jld2734</Username><Timestamp>1350956226180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:37:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Richard Milhouse Nixon was the worst in recent memory.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1350962289917</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962294671-447</Id><Title>Even with more Republicans in the poll</Title><Msg>than democrats the CNN poll says Obama won. 48% to 40%.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350962294671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962308990-448</Id><Topic><Title>CBS poll gives a huge debate win to Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350961372300</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:02:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believed that . Romney was the tonight's looser.</Msg><Username>edi_kh2000</Username><Timestamp>1350962308990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962370725-449</Id><Title>romney set up a trap for odumba and odumba stepped right in</Title><Msg>odumba: pettiness, juvenile aggressiveness, bitterness, the usual drivel and old lies. I have to give it to Mitt. Mitt is a great strategic thinker.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350962370725</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962463539-450</Id><Title>Loser Mitt loses another one. Every poll has Obama the runaway winner.</Title><Msg>Two weeks til re-election.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962463539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962503458-451</Id><Topic><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama did everything to Romney except send him to his room. He left that up to us.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350962503458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962582001-452</Id><Title>FOX NEW CALLS ROMNEY THE WINNER...EVEN IF OBAMA IMPRESSED YOU DID HE IMPRESS THE VOTERS??</Title><Msg>One sure fact is romney didn't lose it...the polls are moving romneys way so by being cool was the way to play the hand...</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350962582001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962610538-453</Id><Topic><Title>Loser Mitt loses another one. Every poll has Obama the runaway winner.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962463539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:21:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If what you say is true, then cite the polls. CNN's poll, which was released just two minutes ago, show it a few % points difference, not a "runaway" by any rational means... but oh, wait I forgot, you are a liar lib, so rational does not apply to you.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350962610538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:23:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962635295-454</Id><Topic><Title>Even with more Republicans in the poll</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350962294671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:18:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every poll give Obama the win.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962635295</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962681934-455</Id><Topic><Title>Even with more Republicans in the poll</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350962294671</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:18:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Fox? What was their number?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1350962681934</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962787863-456</Id><Topic><Title>Loser Mitt loses another one. Every poll has Obama the runaway winner.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962463539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:21:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could say that Obama being the President he does know the stuff, he is intelligent, and he is genuine. R-Money is fake and keeps changing. In this 3rd debate, he poised as presidential and agreed with the President most of the time to look presidential. But few times he tried to insult President's intelligence... but was badly bruised in the process... even the smooth salesman in him could not succeed as his record is out there contradicting himself all the time trying to change color for the debate like a chemelion!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350962787863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962802438-457</Id><Title>Mitt Romney made an Acute Left Turn tonight</Title><Msg>Is he abandonning his Base or Just Lying</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350962802438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962856339-458</Id><Topic><Title>Loser Mitt loses another one. Every poll has Obama the runaway winner.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962463539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:21:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, my aren't you the sore loser. The CBS poll gives Obama 53% to Mitt's 23%. Get yourself a super-size box of Kleenex for the night of Nov. 6. Sore loser like you will be slobbering and sniveling all night.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350962856339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:27:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350962888750-459</Id><Title>Mitt Romney defended Osama...</Title><Msg>Mitt loved Osama....sounded dissapointed...that he was killed</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1350962888750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962945626-460</Id><Topic><Title>Obama just said, "Governor Romney You Are Right..."</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1350958988850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:23:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama failed as a community organizer too</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350962945626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350962992115-461</Id><Topic><Title>FOX NEW CALLS ROMNEY THE WINNER...EVEN IF OBAMA IMPRESSED YOU DID HE IMPRESS THE VOTERS??</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350962582001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right. I was disapointed romney did not kill odumba on libya but admit that Mitt picked a certain strategy.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1350962992115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963042131-462</Id><Topic><Title>Crowley Interrupts Romney, Social Frenzy Erupts on debate #2</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350962175198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:16:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your crash has come... You should call your doctor immediately!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350963042131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963067076-463</Id><Topic><Title>Obama took Romney to school again. Romney learns about ships not found in his bathtub.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350960987848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else does Mitt not know.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350963067076</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963067709-464</Id><Topic><Title>Obama took Romney to school again. Romney learns about ships not found in his bathtub.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350960987848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:56:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else does Mitt not know.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350963067709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963105713-465</Id><Topic><Title>Carter</Title><Username>jld2734</Username><Timestamp>1350956226180</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 21:37:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I kept thinking that Obama looked desperate tonight just like Jimmy Carter in 1980. He had that look of defeat on his face as he watches his lead evaporate and all the momentum with Mitt</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1350963105713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963166476-466</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama sounded like a biting fiesty little chihuahua next to Romney</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350963166476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963193112-467</Id><Topic><Title>Obama looked Petty, Desperate teenager type personal jabs not presidential...This election is over Romney President Elect</Title><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350961301579</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:01:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is Guilty of High Treason</Msg><Username>obama_sucksass</Username><Timestamp>1350963193112</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963196518-468</Id><Topic><Title>Romney kicked Obama's butt again tonite !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1350960173154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:42:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What the libs fail to recognize is how you count a "win." If you count debate points, yes Obama won. Obama was quite good. But if you count points based on what each candidate wanted to sell about themselves, then Romney could have run away with it - time will tell. Romney's agenda was to illustrate that he is not a war monger. If libs had read the strategists BEFORE the debate, they would know that. Romney was reserved and careful to avoid looking looking like a bully that would rush to war. Take note of his comment that we cannot kill our way out of the situation. And, he was softer and less aggressive in attacking Obama - a clear contrast to the first and second debates. If the Repub strategists were correct about the message Romney needed to deliver, and Romney was able to deliver that message (which remains to be seen), then Romney could count this as a win. It all depends on how people perceive his foreign policy after this debate. There IS a difference between winning a debate and winning ground in the election. We'll see.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963196518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963229115-469</Id><Topic><Title>FOX NEW CALLS ROMNEY THE WINNER...EVEN IF OBAMA IMPRESSED YOU DID HE IMPRESS THE VOTERS??</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1350962582001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, right. This a poker game and R-Money is not a candidate for the presidency of the U.S. Sure, FOX sees things too objectively... and every body 'believes' what you post AH!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350963229115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963265777-470</Id><Topic><Title>Romney very PRESIDENTIAL while OBAMA became the aggressive and acted like a hopeless candidate. OBAMA keeps attacking , continue to blame BUSH and has not accepted the blame for the last 4 years.</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350961510728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:05:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those who are already commited to ROMNEY and those commited to OBAMA has made up their minds. What ROMNEY did tonight is to look PRESIDENTIAL and WIN the UNDECIDED VOTES. He LOOKS well mannered LOOKS like a real PRESIDENT and COMMANDER IN CHIEF. OBAMA ATTACKING ROMNEY for the poor education in MASS. well he forgot one thing...he is from CHICAGO WHERE DROPOUTS IS VERY HIGH. EDUCATION in MASS is an envy of other states. being number one in english and math.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1350963265777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350963395355-471</Id><Title>Romney has another bubble in the bathtub moment.</Title><Msg>Obama tutors Romney about the modern U.S. Navy having more capability than the US Navy of 1917. Tonight, Mitt got to learn about submarines and aircraft carriers.</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350963395355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:36:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963416532-472</Id><Topic><Title>Over 30 000 killed in Syria: USA import 5.3% from Syria...Germany &amp; Italy 18% each...Turkey 8.2%..Saudi 7%</Title><Username>flashcrashcoming</Username><Timestamp>1350963275577</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:34:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you contact your president R-Money... He will instantly do what you wish, AH! Contact your doc immediately you seem you have a flashcrashattack, AH!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350963416532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350963544260-473</Id><Topic><Title>Romney closing statements flat lined</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350959783930</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 22:36:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeez, and I thought it was only Clinton and Kennedy who scored with the women (except their wives). On your words, Obama must go both ways since he scored with a bunch of Florida men, too.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350963544260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350963864202-474</Id><Title>Marines surprised by "military doesn't use horses and bayonettes" Obama quote</Title><Msg>Oops, Obama lost on yet another fact check. It seems the military does still use bayonettes, at least in the Marine Corps (or "corpse", as Obama would say). There's another answer we can toss out as ignorant, uninformed Obama -- the supposed "smart" CIC -- shooting first, never aiming, and accidentally targeting his own jackboot.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350963864202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350963876503-475</Id><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Msg>That's what the repub strategists wanted to accomplish, and at least based on this poll, it looks like Romney pulled it off. There is a reason Romney focused most of his time on stating his stand on foreign policy issues and less time attacking Obama than he has in the previous debates. It was very noticeable that he did not let Obama dictate his use of time by getting him to spend all his time defending against Obama's attacks. Dems wanted to paint Romney as a war monger, and it appears to have failed. The repubs out strategized the dems on this one. Obama spent too much of his time attacking Romney. The neutral strategists warned against that. They also warned against the extensive sarcasm, e.g., Big Bir, Romnesia, and now "horses and bayonetts." That sarcastic demeaning insulting tone libs are known for, and I have lampooned on this board, is coming back to bite the liar libs.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964149633-476</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RFLMAO!!! Mitt as Commander in Chief RFLMAO!!! With four draft deferments?!! RFLMAO!!! Whats matter, mrstan, couldn't you find a poll with Romney winning the debate? So you post this ludicrous pile of crap!!! RFLMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1350964149633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964184732-477</Id><Topic><Title>Marines surprised by "military doesn't use horses and bayonettes" Obama quote</Title><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350963864202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, and Obama supporters wonder why the military favors Romney. I believe the Marines are the only arm of the military that still uses bayonettes, and I should not know half what Obama should know about how our soldiers fight. Can you imagine what Marines are saying about our fine commander in chief now?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350964184732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964237234-478</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republican strategists like you are short term thinkers (may be better to say non-thinkers)... and AH's like you think that the majority out there are not aware of the game. Pretending, changing, lying, all through the campaign can't be hidden from the public that is interconnected now with all the hi tech tools. But who am I talking with? I'm just wasting my time with you Mrs. TAN!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1350964237234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350964238853-479</Id><Title>First duty of Romney WH transition staff in November</Title><Msg>Uninstalling Obama......... █████████████▒▒ 90% complete.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350964238853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350964258560-480</Id><Title>Romney geography challenged</Title><Msg>n trying to describe the strategic importance of seeing Assad defeated, Romney stumbled in saying Syria was Iran's "route to the sea." Iran has a large southern coastline with access to the Persian Gulf and the Gulf of Oman. It has no land border with Syria.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350964258560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964359146-481</Id><Topic><Title>Marines surprised by "military doesn't use horses and bayonettes" Obama quote</Title><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350963864202</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to a recent poll of active duty military forces, 82% of them are saying they want their absentee ballots counted so they can get a real CIC.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350964359146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964390187-482</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a CNN poll showing that more than half of the people believe he can be commander in chief. What is so hard about getting that through your thick skull? It does not matter what you think, the "four deferments" you keep lying about isn't being bought by anybody (name which arm of the military Obama served in, smartass). You are a pathetic fool.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350964390187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964494345-483</Id><Topic><Title>Romney geography challenged</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1350964258560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:50:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately for you, the ignorant Obama voters are more challenged and think that Syria is what you put on your pancakes. They were in agreement with Romney because pancakes are a great way to settle the stomach before going to sea.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350964494345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964603128-484</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan wasn't paying attention. Obama had to give Romney a lesson on the modern Navy. That's not a good fit for a Commander-In-Chief.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1350964603128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964625236-485</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah yes, the givoannijay, cosmo, sakkk sukkker, etc, etc, coward that cannot limit his posts to one alias. Your response is SOOO predicable. The majority, Einstein (60%) after this debate believe that Romney can be commander in chief. Doubt that he could be was a major problem for him. So who won? The loudmouth liar lib like you? Or the guy that accomplished what he wanted to accomplish in the voters's eyes? I guess that is too suble for an ape like you. You're no more capable of understanding strategy and seeing through the liar lib noise, than you are at coming up with something more creative than "Mrs Tan" How clever you are! I've not seen that kind of keen since gradeschool. YOU ARE A JOKE!!!!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350964625236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350964714903-486</Id><Topic><Title>CNN poll shows 60% believe Romney can handle being commander in chief</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1350963876503</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:44:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was a 4F for persistent drug use.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1350964714903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-22 23:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>