<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346476322465-1</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this noise about an empty chair?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346451002656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All hat, no horse</Msg><Username>c_bandit_8</Username><Timestamp>1346476322465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 01:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346482863768-2</Id><Title>Not to be outdone, the Dems are countering Eastwood with Bill Cosby</Title><Msg>"See I'm not dead! Zippety Zee Bop vote for Barack de Bop Jellllo Pudding!!!!</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1346482863768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 03:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346489269094-3</Id><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Msg>Check it out on Youtube! Wow!!</Msg><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346489269094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346489622435-4</Id><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Msg>A real man. Full of class and character. Discipline and dignity. Just like the late Charles Bronson or Chuck Norris who were and are incorruptible by the Hollywood PIGS. Compare these folk to the filth of the likes of the unkempt michael moore who escaped from the group home one day and never returned. The Republican Convention was a blessing of encouragement and true hope to change the big mistake in '08.</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346502131252-5</Id><Title>Wall St. crook butt smooching won't get you elected Mitt!</Title><Msg>Come on, tell us your position on regulating the derivatives markets, forcing the banks to disclose their risk in credit default swaps and whether you feel in light of 2008 that there should be some modest forms of regulation on Wall St. banks. Do we need to break up the big banks and make sure there is a firewall between commercial banking and investment banking? Address these issues so we know that you don't intend to let the fox back in the hen house!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1346502131252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346502438749-6</Id><Title>Our Worthless State Department</Title><Msg>Rule of Thumb, Going Dutch, Holding Down The Fort, Handicap -- These are the new words and phrases that our State Department has deemed offensive and we should avoid using. Are you kidding me? Why don't we remove these words from our vocabulary: --Democrats - Liberals - Progressives - Obama - Biden - Pelosi - Reid - Schumer - Kennedy - Rangel - Clinton - Carter - Chavez - Putin - Political correctness - Department of Commerce (failed) - Department of Education (failed) - Department of Energy (failed) - EPA (extreme and needs to be moderated) - ACLU - NEA (cares more about paying bureaucrats and electing anti Americans than the kids) - Unions (bankrupted our companies and now our governments) - AARP (advocating socialism and Democratic policies at expense of bankrupting our kids) I find these words much more offensive and anti American.</Msg><Username>defeatsocialism</Username><Timestamp>1346502438749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346502755874-7</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint Eastwood, Charles Bronson and Chuck Norris real men? Are you #$%$ kidding me? Any man, or woman for that matter, who makes a life out of playing MAKE BELIEVE are not "men/women" in the classic sense. They just play them on TV/Movies. Real men, in this case, are the likes of Neil Armstrong, Chuck Yeager, and all the men and women who serve in our Military (to name one aspect of our society). Actors and actresses? No offense against the breed but they spend their lives accomplishing nothing other than entertaining the rest of us. So it you consider them "real" then I submit you're spending too much time playing the audience and watching their performances and not enough time truly living your life. And that's no life at all. Just sayin'. Highlow American Net'Zen</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346502755874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346503064268-8</Id><Title>BERNANKE WILL CRASH THE MARKETS</Title><Msg>Stimulus. Just another name for more borrowing You saw what happened to the price of Gold as soon as he said "stimulus" was once again in play. I used to think Peter Schiff was some "gold bug" who didn't know what he was talking about. He has many times blamed Bernanke for our financial plight, and he's right. THE DOLLAR WILL CRASH, TAKING DOWN ALL MARKETS,, AND YOUR MONEY WILL BE WORTHLESS.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1346503064268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:37:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346503842185-9</Id><Topic><Title>Our Worthless State Department</Title><Username>defeatsocialism</Username><Timestamp>1346502438749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:27:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I submit finding the opinions and thoughts of others offensive is, in and of itself, anti-American. Democracy...aint it a beeeyatch? HEH!</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346503842185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346503957340-10</Id><Title>A man, Democrat Felix Faraway Fartaway, wandering around a Delmar, Md., poultry farm in a drunken stupor turned off the power to three chicken houses, causing the deaths of nearly 70,000 chickens, sheriff’s officials said. After acts of bestiality with the chickens, Fartaway, a demented Democrat stated that he thought the chickens were Republicans, and that an extraterrestrial power told him to "zap them".</Title><Msg>A man, Democrat Felix Faraway Fartaway, wandering around a Delmar, Md., poultry farm in a drunken stupor turned off the power to three chicken houses, causing the deaths of nearly 70,000 chickens, sheriff’s officials said. After acts of bestiality with the chickens, Fartaway, a demented Democrat stated that he thought the chickens were Republicans, and that an extraterrestrial power told him to "zap them". The property owner who made the grisly discovery found the man, identified as Felix Faraway Fartaway passed out on the floor of the power control shed, wearing only a T-shirt and boxer shorts. “This subject was also lying in a pool of his own urine. A strong odor of alcohol was also coming from the subject,” Wicomico County sheriff’s Lt. Tim Robinson said in a press release.</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1346503957340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346504167773-11</Id><Topic><Title>A man, Democrat Felix Faraway Fartaway, wandering around a Delmar, Md., poultry farm in a drunken stupor turned off the power to three chicken houses, causing the deaths of nearly 70,000 chickens, sheriff’s officials said. After acts of bestiality with the chickens, Fartaway, a demented Democrat stated that he thought the chickens were Republicans, and that an extraterrestrial power told him to "zap them".</Title><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1346503957340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:52:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Daddy, Mr. Fartaway. I know that most animals aren't safe around Democrats, but chickens?</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1346504167773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346504401971-12</Id><Topic><Title>POOR PUKES. NO BOUNCE AFTE THE CONVENTION. BAWAHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA</Title><Username>toodakin</Username><Timestamp>1346498391566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 07:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the Republican convention fades into oblivion, the one thing everybody is still talking about is, of course, the party platform. The convention was so full of opportunities to catch a glimpse of celebrities like John Sununu and Rudy Giuliani that I didn’t get around to the platform until the flight back from Tampa. But it was so worth the wait. Really, I could hardly take my eyes away from it long enough to watch the flight attendant demonstrate how to use a seat buckle. As you’d expect, there were paeans to things Republicans like (phonics, Israel, coal, English, defense spending, transparency for everything except political donations) and denunciations of the stuff they hate (Obamacare, mass transit, the Law of the Sea Treaty, Venezuela, teachers’ unions, Obamacare). But you may be interested to know that the proven methods of improving school performance are high standards, accountability and “renewed focus on the Constitution and the writings of the Founding Fathers.” Some of the recommendations are stunning. Besides the inevitable tribute to the Second Amendment, the platform goes to the trouble of specifically mentioning that Republicans are against limiting the sale of those extra-bullet magazines for guns that maximized the victim count in the mass shootings in Tucson, Colorado and Wisconsin. Please, keep that in mind. Wherever there’s a gun capable of spraying 100 bullets, there’s a Republican platform behind it. But the most startling sentence is in the preamble, where the Republicans announce they are the party with “a positive, optimistic view of an opportunity society where any American who works hard, dreams big and follows the rules can achieve anything he or she wants.” People, do you think the Republican hierarchy really believes that working hard and playing by the rules is a guarantee of big-dream fulfillment? This is a worldview you usually only hear before the first elimination round on “American Idol.” No wonder they don’t like food stamps and unemployment compensation. The platform provides some welcome hints about what the Romney ticket stands for. We do need help on that point because when it comes to actual plans, Romney-Ryan has been pretty opaque. Leaving Tampa, we knew no more about the big Medicare issue than when we arrived. The biggest Republican talking point is that the Obama health care reform will, in the words of Mitt Romney, “hurt today’s seniors.” That’s all about the $716 billion in projected long-term savings, except that Ryan had the same cut in his budget plans and what the heck are we supposed to make of that? Fortunately, Fortune magazine asked the House majority leader, Eric Cantor, that question during the convention, and Cantor was able to clear it all up thusly: “The assumption was that, um, the, the, ah, again — I probably can’t speak to that in an exact way, so I better just not.” So, O.K. The big, if-not-quite-articulated, message in Tampa was that in a free economy, everybody will get what they deserve. There is no need to worry about the vast, growing gap between the richest and the rest, or the shrinking middle class, or the fact that America currently has one of the worst rates of social mobility in the developed world. Untrammeled, the business sector will create plenty of jobs, and the hard-working big-dreamers will jump in, amass wealth and achieve success. You cut taxes, reduce regulation and let the magic happen. It’s that or what Paul Ryan called “a dull adventureless journey from one entitlement to the next, a government-planned life, a country where everything is free but us.” Listening to the convention speeches, it was easy to get the impression that every high-ranking Republican in the country had parents who were truck drivers or convenience store workers who moved up entirely through their own efforts. Also, there were a lot of grandfathers who worked in the mines. Republicans love mines, particularly coal mines. This is partly because of their big donors, but the fact that environmentalists hate coal makes coal mines even more adorable. And the miners themselves are always sympathetic figures because they work hard and play by the rules. As a result, their biggest dreams have been realized, and they are able to spend their lives underground developing chronic pulmonary disease. Shortly before the convention, Mitt Romney had pressed the coal theme with an appearance in Ohio, where he stood with a group of sooty miners whose sad, solemn faces seemed to underscore their concern about big government. Also, some of them later told the news media that they had been required to show up and weren’t paid for the day. The reward will undoubtedly arrive at a later date. (Courtesy of Commenter Gail Collins - No wonder no bounce)</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346504401971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346504509801-13</Id><Title>Sherrieff Joe and County Atty: Andrew Thomas: investigation has closed, NO INDICTMENT and INVESTIGATION has CLOSED</Title><Msg>Arpaio and his top ally, former County Attorney Andrew Thomas---------INVESTIGATION CLOSED.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1346504509801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346504549530-14</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give Clint Eastwood a break... The RNC asked him to speak about ObamaCare and he thought they said ObamaChair.</Msg><Username>daytonnv89403</Username><Timestamp>1346504549530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346505823539-15</Id><Title>WHO THE H IS CLINT EASTWOOD?</Title><Msg>An Entertainment Celebrity, that's who he is. More important than any head of Government. More important than any King or Queen. More important than any Inventor More important than any Company CEO. More important than any Sports Athlete. MORE IMPORTANT THAN ANYONE. THE PUBLIC PLACES THEM ABOVE EVERYONE ELSE. The public knows more, and can name more Entertainment Celebrities than any one in the world. What they say matters most. Don't fight it, because that's the way it is.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1346505823539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346505972970-16</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346489269094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lies are his only HOPE.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346505972970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346507778561-17</Id><Topic><Title>WHO THE H IS CLINT EASTWOOD?</Title><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1346505823539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:23:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course you're correct. Even Snookie, one of the least talented, and ugliest people on the Entertainment scene, I'm sure is as well known a the President by most people.</Msg><Username>scampity2</Username><Timestamp>1346507778561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346509911702-18</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College Poll, 8/31/12: Obama: 332. Romney: 206. Gas Bag-Tea Bag Fest (RNC) affected nothing.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1346446795220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey teacher! Can I borrow your Strunk &amp; White? What do you mean, "What's that"? ROTFLMAO at teachers who won't be earning any merit raises this year....or ever.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1346509911702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346510346747-19</Id><Title>Yahoo and BAC will sink like rocks</Title><Msg>This is related to BAC. It too will sink regardless of what the censors allow.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346510346747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346510579394-20</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint was funny and refreashing to see and hear joking about Obama...with obama people forgot how to laugh...</Msg><Username>valueplay_2000</Username><Timestamp>1346510579394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346512379132-21</Id><Topic><Title>Do you know what is worst than shorts???</Title><Username>dailyfun2007</Username><Timestamp>1346420215754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:36:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorely disappointed, Fish. Forgot there are 366 daze this year, as in many presidential election years? They need to leap ahead for most who can't read.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346512379132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346512990625-22</Id><Topic><Title>How do democrats expect to get away with so many outright lies ?</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346342978232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:09:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Missus stan will not be eating crow that day. It will be a spacial variety of Utah Mountain Chicken, IMHO.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346512990625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346513196285-23</Id><Topic><Title>DOW JONES DOWN OVER 100 POINTS ON RYAN SPEECH</Title><Username>dexter.galileo</Username><Timestamp>1346336970880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:29:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When was it I pointed out the futility of foreign trade and exchange as an economic indicator? At least you seem to have gotten it.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346513196285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346513948650-24</Id><Title>WFEMF - World famous investor Warren Buffett is investing in this company</Title><Msg>WFEMF - World famous investor Warren Buffett is investing in this company. I will be buying more shares of WFEMF soon. Stop losing money on BAC &amp; invest in WFEMF which is only trading at around .25 cents per share and is close to completing a deal with Warren Buffett's multi billion dollar company IMC Warren Buffett values tungsten the way other investors value gold. Which makes sense because tungsten has more primary uses then gold. Tungsten, not so easy to get ahold of. Critical for power generation in 2nd half of the 21st century. Critical for aerospace and spacecraft construction for similar reasons. I must thank the investors who pointed out WFEMF to me as one of the most promising early stage tungsten plays that is entirely run within the boundaries of a civilized westernized nation.</Msg><Username>k_k_909</Username><Timestamp>1346513948650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346514000236-25</Id><Title>Facebook and BAC</Title><Msg>What a pair. Which alleged investment is under-performing the other faster? Both in a dead heat, with Tampa and Utah bringing up the rear!</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346514000236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514006245-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama .... show America your educational records! What are you HIDING?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346507986792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dump take a dump.</Msg><Username>jakedownover</Username><Timestamp>1346514006245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346514014826-27</Id><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Msg>This from one of my friends in Africa this morning. I have friends from Kenya in eastern Africa to Cameroon on the west coast of Africa. They are very interested in the US presidential election. I seldom talk politics with them. They have more fundamental needs in life. But they want to know what is happening with the campaign. Many of them want to come here, seeing escape from Africa as their only chance for a good life. All of them say about the same thing: "Africans are very disappointed with Obama. Africans expected a change of Africa with Obama. Unfortunately this is not the case." Obama walked into the presidency with such arrogance, promising this and promising that, like he was some kind of messiah. Raising everybody's hopes. "I will slow the rise of the oceans, I will heal the earth." What a bunch of crap. He not only disappoints Americans, he disappoints the whole world. He needs to go.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514195839-28</Id><Topic><Title>WFEMF - World famous investor Warren Buffett is investing in this company</Title><Username>k_k_909</Username><Timestamp>1346513948650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just my two cents but once Warren Buffett's company IMC closes the deal and we get financing from the banks, WFEMF will start to look very good for a takeover. I mean in today's markets, what mining company would not be interested in buying a mine that is totally de-risked, fully financed and with an offtake agreement for 100% of production ??? Plus, Woulfe Mining comes with a gold &amp; silver mine, a lead/zinc mine, 11 uranium land title, a moly reserve, ect, ect, ect .... Again, this just my opinion but an opportunity like this, at this price, does not come often in today's market and my guess is that Korea Zinc could be the ones to take us out. They are a local mining company, they have cash and the knowledge and the experience needed to developpe all of Woulfe's assets. They already own over 36,000,000 shares of WFEMF which gives them a 10% advantage over the competition in a takeover battle. Again, I'm just exploring future possibilities. With all that is supposed to happen in the near future I think its important to look at the whole picture cause whoever has the right hindsight will make alot of money. I'm long on this one as I think patience will pay off once the project is fully financed, takeover or production, its a win win situation.</Msg><Username>k_k_909</Username><Timestamp>1346514195839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515054659-29</Id><Topic><Title>Are we to forget nanci pelousy swapping spit with Bashar al-Assad</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346508831692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please, zevoter, don't mention Pelosi before lunch. Just the thought of her makes me lose my breafast. Ms. "We have to pass it to see what's in it." Only to be topped by Barney Frank's, "There is absolutely no sign of a housing bubble."</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515054659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515077423-30</Id><Topic><Title>How do democrats expect to get away with so many outright lies ?</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346342978232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:09:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a single thread, the poor creature misspells 'pathological' twice - in two different ways. As a marine science major, I know a little about piscine pathology, but I've never encountered anything like it. This repetitive self-destructive behavior extends to challenging the universe to debate it, claiming it resides at the top of the food chain even though it dines exclusively on hazanga, asserting that it can school other fish, and making the same flatulent noises every time it opens its mouth. The last time I let it go, I even smacked it with a copy of Strunk &amp; White just to see if it was possible to alter its suicidal tendencies or at least improve its communication, but it's proven to be highly resistant to behavior modification, too. ROTFLMAO at inedible fish to kill everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1346515077423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346515468993-31</Id><Title>Definition: Democratagogue</Title><Msg>A democratagogue or rabble-rouser is a political leader who appeals to the emotions, prejudices and ignorance of the poorer and less-educated classes in order to gain power. Cunning, uncouth, and unprincipled, democratagogues appeal directly to the emotions of the poor and ignorant, pursuing power with ruthless ambition, telling lies to stir up hysteria, exploiting crises to intensify popular support for their calls to immediate action and increased authority.... Hmm, sound familiar? Why, yes it does! Liar libs cornered the market on it! Teflon Obam! Fishy2Smell? Cosmo Sphincter Face? Mrs.Pizzhard? LMAO.... ah, geez, I am having too much fun needling the needle brains. Like shooting fishy in a sphincter full of wizz. C'mon, girls, let's here your best liar responses. I know it is not fair odds, 3 on 1... because you all are unarmed the battle of wits, but there are THREE of you (nyuk, nyuk).</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515468993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515563334-32</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A bit of a misquote isn't it. there is no "I" in it and it is not about "I". Also He wasn't running to be the leader of Africa. He only disappoints if you expected a Messiah. For a man he has done damn well.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346515563334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346515756394-33</Id><Title>How much was tax amnesty worth in 2009</Title><Msg>to Romney? Lets see where all that money comes from.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346515756394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515953878-34</Id><Topic><Title>Democraps tell us we must trust Obama .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346508127846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:02:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, the libs are masochists. They would take four more years of failure just to smugly brag that their man is still in office. Even if it were an indisputable proven fact that the country would be better off without Obama, they'd still vote for him.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515953878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346516160952-35</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College Poll, 8/31/12: Obama: 332. Romney: 206. Gas Bag-Tea Bag Fest (RNC) affected nothing.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1346446795220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beating his head against the wall to try and get some sense in to it is problem not something he would care for. That is all I see you doing.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346516160952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346516513274-36</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"who makes a life out of playing MAKE BELIEVE" Are you talking Eastwood or Obama? Because Eastwood is more real than Obama, and Obama has done more make believe than Eastwood will if he lives another hundred years.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346516513274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516574736-37</Id><Title>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Title><Msg>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel Based on Sanford C. Bernstein estimates of the marginal cost of oil production, the geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now. Reminding the market that a strategic cushion exists—without necessarily deploying it—provides a check on that premium rising even further. Sweet Crude Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel. That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline. Sanford Bernstein geopolitical premium in the Brent price is about $30 a barrel right now That equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516574736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516622686-38</Id><Title>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Title><Msg>Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516622686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:23:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516674085-39</Id><Title>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market</Title><Msg>Oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market. 28-August-12 07:23 am Many analysts say oil prices aren't right due to too much oil in the market. “The economic price for (West Texas Intermediate) oil is in the $50-$60 range,” said Mickey Cargile, managing partner at Cargile Investments, basing his estimate on where he sees supplies locally and in Cushing, Okla., the delivery hub for Nymex oil. “Our range valuation suggests a 20%-30% risk premium price d for potential supply disruption from Iran,” he said. This equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.50 per gallon</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516674085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:24:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346516718402-40</Id><Topic><Title>How do democrats expect to get away with so many outright lies ?</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346342978232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:09:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My, my so thin skinned and easy to upset. Must be a sensitive spot there when you understand you've been made a fool of. Mrs tan, and all the time I thought you were a mimic trying to make people think you were the old excellent banking knowledge poster that use to be here know as Stan. That explains my confusion.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346516718402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516723815-41</Id><Title>OPEC Says Supply Ample, Speculation Driving Price ,</Title><Msg>OPEC Says Supply Ample, Speculation Driving Price , | 28 August 2012 | 06:18 AM ET Oil supply will be more than sufficient to meet demand this year and beyond, OPEC's Secretary General said on Thursday, but added the price of fuel is being driven higher by speculation. "There has been no shortage of oil in the market. Producers have been able to meet consumer needs," Abdullah al-Badri told an energy conference. "We also see this as being the case for the rest of 2012 and the foreseeable future." Oil prices surged in March to $128 a barrel, the highest level since 2008, because of concern about possible supply shortages. Prices have since fallen back and brent crude was trading around $118 on Thursday. "Today the price continues to be driven by excessive speculation," Badri said. OPEC at a meeting in December set a target to produce 30 million barrels per day, settling an argument which broke out in 2011 after Iran and other members opposed a Saudi-led plan to raise OPEC's production ceiling. Output has remained above the target all year as Libyan supply recovered after being virtually shut down during the 2011 uprising against Muammar Gaddafi's rule. The extra oil is filling gaps caused by an unusually large number of supply outages globally, which have also helped support prices. Supply breaks were running at nearly 1.3 million bpd as of early April. The additional supply has also offset a decline in exports from Iran, which is facing stiffening western sanctions over its disputed nuclear energy program. Iranian oil exports were running at between 200,000 and 300,000 barrels per day below last year's level, Maria van der Hoeven, head of the International Energy Agency, told Thursday's conference. Iranian officials have said the country exported an average of 2.2 million barrels a day last year. July supply from the 12-member Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries ran at 31.75 million barrels per day (bpd), the high est since September 2008, which was shortly before it agreed to a series of supply curbs to combat recession and collapsing demand, based on Reuters surveys</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516723815</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:25:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516780344-42</Id><Title>"There has been no shortage of oil in the market"</Title><Msg>"There has been no shortage of oil in the market" OPEC Says Supply Ample, Speculation Driving Price , | 28 August 2012 | 06:18 AM ET Oil supply will be more than sufficient to meet demand this year and beyond, OPEC's Secretary General said on Thursday, but added the price of fuel is being driven higher by speculation. "There has been no shortage of oil in the market. Producers have been able to meet consumer needs," Abdullah al-Badri told an energy conference. "We also see this as being the case for the rest of 2012 and the foreseeable future." "Today the price continues to be driven by excessive speculation," Badri said</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516780344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516808958-43</Id><Title>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Title><Msg>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516808958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516819681-44</Id><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Msg>I don't understand</Msg><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516859748-45</Id><Title>Gas Prices Are “Outrageously High”: Sen. Bernie Sanders Demands Crackdown on Oil Speculation.</Title><Msg>Gas Prices Are “Outrageously High”: Sen. Bernie Sanders Demands Crackdown on Oil Speculation.</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516859748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:27:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516901659-46</Id><Title>equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline Sanford Bernstein</Title><Msg>equates to averages gasoline price of $2.25 to $2.00 per gallon gasoline Sanford Bernstein Oil Value should be $60.00 to $50.00 a barrel</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516901659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346516951428-47</Id><Title>The DOW shot up over a hundred points on Romney speech</Title><Msg>Before settling lower after Bernanke spoke. Mitt is good for the markets.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346516951428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517140069-48</Id><Topic><Title>Definition: Democratagogue</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515468993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fishy? Sphincter? Mrs. Pizzhard? Where are you girls? Stop hiding, stop pulling your skirts up over your heads, come on out to play....</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346517140069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346517162727-49</Id><Title>Equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.25 per gallon</Title><Msg>Equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.25 per gallon 28-August-12 08:42 am This equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.25 per gallon 28-August-12 This equates to gasoline prices to average about $2.00 per gallon</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346517162727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517393962-50</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well thats too much concentrated power then. Those people aren't elected by voters why do they get the right to frame the debate and decide what news to discuss?</Msg><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346517393962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346517581955-51</Id><Title>Left side of Obama's face: "You didn't build that" -- Right side of Obama's face: "You did build that."</Title><Msg>"My statement was taken out of context." WHAT??? In the full unabridged context, you DID say that, Mr. Teflon Obam. I thought teflon was being outlawed... but still seems to be a plentiful supply in the White House.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346517581955</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517740798-52</Id><Topic><Title>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Title><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516808958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And there's absolutely NOTHING that can be done about it. Ah the joys of a Free unfettered Market, eh? HEH!</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346517740798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517803316-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because Bush is a oil guy and oil began its climb right after the Cheney energy meeting.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1346517803316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517835569-54</Id><Topic><Title>How do democrats expect to get away with so many outright lies ?</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346342978232</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:09:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>libertylies, just FYI that I am not responding to you because I have you on ignore. You're simply not worth my time to respond to such idiotic fertilizer. I shoveled enough of that stuff on dairy farms. Besides, my dance card is full with the three stooges, and there's no room for a fourth stooge.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346517835569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517939483-55</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop sipping the Kool and watching American Ido for your deep social commentaryl. Try thinking before you speak you might find it does wonders for your image. That is if you actually CAN think and not be suffering from ossified patterns. Kind'a like very old Clinty baby. What a joke.</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346517939483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517941759-56</Id><Topic><Title>Oil Speculation Imposes “the Most Insidious Tax” on Americans: Leo Hindery</Title><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1346516808958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the government spends too much money and goes into deep debt people ought to have the right to invest in hard assets ...or we could outlaw all markets including companies and put our money in the mattress? Oh but that won't work when the government devalues the dollar to nothing and spends like there is no tomorrow.</Msg><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346517941759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518040252-57</Id><Topic><Title>How much was tax amnesty worth in 2009</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346515756394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:09:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dirty Harry is probably right thats why Romney can't show his taxes, or it would show little the rich pay compared to the middle class.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1346518040252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518065574-58</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College Poll, 8/31/12: Obama: 332. Romney: 206. Gas Bag-Tea Bag Fest (RNC) affected nothing.</Title><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1346446795220</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice! And I'll bet you're a product of home schoolin', too. Just like our rugged Pioneers. HEH!</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1346518065574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518129720-59</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't Obama bring it down in price like he promised? Is he an oil guy too?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346518129720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346518275209-60</Id><Title>With This High of Unemployment and Gasoline Prices I Think there is no way an Incumbent President Wins</Title><Msg>I think people are waiting for the debates to make up their mind they don't care if Romney wins all he has to do is show he can hang with Obama and look Presidential than Obama is unemployed and back to Chicago</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346518275209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518328915-61</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>almost dead, dead, should be dead, clint is the only chance rnc had, a chance, since heston, reagan...actually surprized they didn't see it-</Msg><Username>sheikyermoneymaker</Username><Timestamp>1346518328915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518496758-62</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>US oil production is the highest its ever been and demand is so low gas exports are up 20% but Obama can't control the markets or oil companys and if he tried congress would block him.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1346518496758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346518863046-63</Id><Title>WHO LIKES PRESIDENT O VOMIT??</Title><Msg>CHECK YOUR ASSETS UNDER HIM DOWN!!</Msg><Username>earlh00</Username><Timestamp>1346518863046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346519787788-64</Id><Topic><Title>WHO LIKES PRESIDENT O VOMIT??</Title><Username>earlh00</Username><Timestamp>1346518863046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:01:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Mathews likes him he gets a tingle down his leg but later that was learned his depends failed him again</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346519787788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346520050664-65</Id><Title>Know them by the content of their character</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan lies AGAIN "I had a two hour and fifty-something" marathon, Ryan said last week an interview. "I hurt a disc in my back, so I don’t run marathons anymore." But Ryan confirmed to Runner's World that he has only run one marathon, the 1990 Grandma’s Marathon in Duluth, Minnesota, which he finished in just over 4 hours. I GUESS HE IS JUST ATTEMPTING TO BE A GOOD REPUBLICAN AND HAS ADOPTED THEIR VALUES: LIE CHEAT STEAL WELL AT LEAST FLIPPER PICKED SOMEONE WHO IS HIS EQUAL</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1346520050664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346520246190-66</Id><Topic><Title>The DOW shot up over a hundred points on Romney speech</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346516951428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:29:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy big , so you can lose your #$%$ next week</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1346520246190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346521029090-67</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Robutt Post rateing - 1 Out of a max. 5 ................... you got in some of the requirements a. Slamed Obama based on fictional information b. You proved that the 7th grade was the best 4 years of your life However you FALIED to include the other rcritcal RoBUTT post items and lies, for example: a. He was born in Kenya b. You failed to use the word Socialist [ ya, I know you have no idea what it means, but thats true of most of the Republican Nazi party] c. You failed make a racial slur SO IF YOU WANT TO BE A REAL ROBUTT POSTER AND NOT GET KICKED OUT OF THE REPUBLICAN NAZI PARTY YOU MUST QUICKLY CORRECT YOUR ERRORS ....... IT MIGHT HELP IF YOU GET YOUR PEE PARTY BUDDIES TO FORWARD THEIR POSTS, AND KKK &amp; NAZI WEBSITES SO YOU CAN REPEAT THE LIES BETTER.</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1346521029090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346521321687-68</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to thank the republicans for giving him the opportunity to make a fool of himself just like they did with ryan.</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1346521321687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346522917680-69</Id><Title>Will the Greek Columns be flown in from Hollywood this time for the Obama Convention Speech?</Title><Msg>What do you think?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346522917680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346525770467-70</Id><Title>Same jerks on the line</Title><Msg>See Freeh promoted to an alleged law firm to expand his business base? Sandusky and MFGlobal weren't good enough clients? Suggest an empty chair next to Clint would have been sufficient...</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346525770467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346525938205-71</Id><Topic><Title>libertylies what is obama charging for pardons?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346516518633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My guess is that he's charging about as much as Clinton charged to let people stay in the Lincoln bedroom.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346525938205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346526313924-72</Id><Topic><Title>The DOW shot up over a hundred points on Romney speech</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346516951428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:29:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DOW has been shooting blanks since Bush and Obama kept feeding Bernake ammo. Mitt will surely keep the same approach, so I predict DOW to keep shooting up to Fifteen-year past levels? Hard to keep going up at zero gravity. Might get there again.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1346526313924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346527121308-73</Id><Topic><Title>Know them by the content of their character</Title><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1346520050664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he was talking about how long his mouth has run non-stop. Surprisingly little attention has been given to Ryan's hypocritical attack on the $716 billion that mean old Obama eliminated from Medicare (Ryan proposed the same cut in HIS budget plan) or his repeated flat-out lies about not seeking or obtaining federal handouts for his district. I expect both of these deficiencies will be corrected in Charlotte next week. Romney and Ryan are muy sympatico in so many respects, I'm ROTFLMAO waiting for Ryan's heretofore unrevealed high school hairdressing exploits to hit the wire.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1346527121308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346527848976-74</Id><Title>I lookked at State Electorial Votes like "Wargames" movie No matter what ROMNEY LOOSES! :-) :-)</Title><Msg>The republicans are in a massive denial. The game is up, the rig is up. People are tired of having been fleeced, by the rich and super rich. Now lets take away all Social Security and Medicare and give more tax breaks to the rich, so they can """""HOARD""""more money and not spend it into the economy. Wake up America. Please.God Bless America. Hope we never go the wealth concentrated way of the Spanish Empire. Republicans are a "Cancer" to the system.</Msg><Username>electronicsguy1212</Username><Timestamp>1346527848976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346528479870-75</Id><Title>"I'D RATHER SHOWER AT PENN THAN VOTE FOR OBAMA."</Title><Msg>No question about it!!</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1346528479870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528539681-76</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the Media Claim Corruption when the gas prices went up with Bush but now they are silent with Obama?</Title><Username>stockking_profit</Username><Timestamp>1346516819681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:26:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so if its a republican in charge its corruption but if its a democrat its just the markets and you can't control that? How convenient and absurd.</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346528539681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346529026302-77</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have africans friends, yea sure. You lying pile dog mess</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1346529026302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346533501661-78</Id><Topic><Title>** This Board Is Loaded With Vile RePOOPlicans...Dumb TURDS**</Title><Username>wiggleszpa2</Username><Timestamp>1346532818232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:53:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. They hate high school drop outs, minorities who aren't smart enough to get a job, immigrants who took the risk to come here illegally so they could get some food to eat and a competent doctor to deliver their babies, all government workers because they think they are lazy, all lawyers because they think all they do is sue the producers of society and take 50%, union members because they think shareholders should earn more profits than the workers, drug users because they don't understand addiction and hopelessness, #$%$ sexual men because they don't understand why men want to put their pecker in another man's mouth or anal opening, etc etc. I can't stand the intolerance.</Msg><Username>liberalsgreat</Username><Timestamp>1346533501661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346534084087-79</Id><Topic><Title>Will the democraps have a debt clock at their convention?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346528802625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they`ll have a big flag with a hammer&amp;sickle on it.</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1346534084087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346534887959-80</Id><Topic><Title>Will the democraps have a debt clock at their convention?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346528802625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he will declare war on any white man over 30. For some reason we don't count in Obama's world of payoffs. We are the evil, the oppressors of all other groups according to Obama</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346534887959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346535501634-81</Id><Title>Is Bac smarter than we think?</Title><Msg>Can Bac benefit from stalling on all of these mortgage back securities litigation?Example waiting for housing mess to improve and buying these back on pennies on the dollar and re bundling it?</Msg><Username>sbacchus2003</Username><Timestamp>1346535501634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535687424-82</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All americans got to go and see the movie "2016-obama" its about everyones as well as everyones children future.....</Msg><Username>jpdyanni</Username><Timestamp>1346535687424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535974634-83</Id><Topic><Title>obama's new campaign slogan FORE!</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1346533120241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:58:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on how he conducts himself I'm guessing he averages about 4 mulligans, 3 foot wedges and two penalty waivers per round.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1346535974634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346536331371-84</Id><Title>3 Things I love,,,, other gay men,,,,obama,,,,,and my democrat party</Title><Msg>Let the party begin in charloote baby!!</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346536331371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346537774319-85</Id><Title>Republicans will LOSE!</Title><Msg>No bounce from their convention, a horrible indicator for them. All of the polls have Obama leading and gaining. Swing states lead for Obama keeps gaining. And every electoral college poll shows Obama winning.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346537774319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346538078865-86</Id><Title>All of the repug / tea bag slobbering on this board is for nought. LMAO!</Title><Msg>Every objective indicator shows Obama gaining.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346538078865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538100824-87</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans will LOSE!</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346537774319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yay! we gonna win go obama!</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346538100824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346538226820-88</Id><Title>Obama claims GOP ideas are "outdated". That must mean that his ideas are "modern". I'll take outdated ideas that work over modern ideas that fail.</Title><Msg>The millions of people that have dropped out of the work force or are now making 30K a year when they used to make 80K a year are tired of modern ideas too.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1346538226820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538278655-89</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's lead in the polls is gaining. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Obama as well</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345051811501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:30:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Florida's polls indicate Obama is gaining thanks to Mitt and Gov. Scott. LMAO!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346538278655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538669154-90</Id><Topic><Title>Frenzied far-right KKK Tea Baggers are inciting each other to violence.</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345051593938</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fringe idiots like the sack sucking tea baggers on this board will hope-fully self destruct when Obama is re-elected</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346538669154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:31:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346538700877-91</Id><Title>Obama drops probe of Sheriff Joe</Title><Msg>The federal government has closed a criminal probe of alleged financial misconduct by Arizona lawman Joe Arpaio and no charges will be filed, the U.S. Attorney's Office said on Friday. Maricopa County authorities were informed on Friday that federal prosecutors had likewise declined to bring charges in connection with allegations that the sheriff's office had misused county credit cards or misspent money from jail facilities excise taxes. In addition, the U.S. Attorney's Office declined to prosecute two former officials of the county attorney's office who were accused of wrongfully prosecuting a local judge.</Msg><Username>bob13890</Username><Timestamp>1346538700877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538795737-92</Id><Topic><Title>Draft Dodger. Tax Dodger. Prsident Willard...Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!! NEVER!!!!!!!</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345054005115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:06:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The draft-dodging candidate by default as commander-in-chief? Never is right!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346538795737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:33:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538825624-93</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Africans are very disappointed with Obama. Africans expected a change of Africa with Obama. Unfortunately this is not the case. Obama walked into the presidency with such arrogance, promising this and promising that, like he was some kind of messiah raising everybody's hopes.. What a bunch of crap. He not only disappoints Americans, he disappoints the whole world. He needs to go."</Msg><Username>bob13890</Username><Timestamp>1346538825624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538957701-94</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint made my day. Loved the empty chair with the teleprompter in front of it.</Msg><Username>bob13890</Username><Timestamp>1346538957701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346538991803-95</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Bag lepers need to be eradicated before they spread their insidious disease</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1345047285699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In two months time, the tea bagging sack suckers will be nothing but a national joke!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346538991803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539144914-96</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans will kick out fringe right perverts</Title><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1339950252000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-17 12:24:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking forward to the end of the GOP. The Grand Old Pile of s**h**i**t**!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539144914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539313399-97</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a joke. Community organizer pretending to lead a nation. No budget in 3 years and 7 months. DISMAL FAILURE!!! He is incompetent and could not lead ants to a picnic. FACT!!! Go ahead and vote for him if you want $7.00 per gallon gasoline.</Msg><Username>iam4braves247</Username><Timestamp>1346539313399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539330579-98</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is the clear choice for 0.0001% of Americans.</Title><Username>obama.4more</Username><Timestamp>1344448743947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 13:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After Nov. 6, Romney will be remembered like his father. Another wannabe that failed.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539330579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:42:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539426644-99</Id><Topic><Title>3 Things I love,,,, other gay men,,,,obama,,,,,and my democrat party</Title><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346536331371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barney Frank is going to be speaking I am so exicted!</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346539426644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539489393-100</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Bag jokers dye their hair orange...</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1343159842844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:57:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They dye their hair orange to look good riding in Mitt's clown car.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539489393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346539627042-101</Id><Title>Tea Bag sack suckers: Take your perversions somewhere else!</Title><Msg>You boys need to start your own chat room.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539627042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539854240-102</Id><Topic><Title>When the French were in dire need of Mormon missionaries, Willard answered the call.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1343136596014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 09:29:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He supported the Vietnam war from his Paris, France residence as the four men who took his place did his fighting for him. What a coward!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539854240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539924467-103</Id><Topic><Title>WFEMF - World famous investor Warren Buffett is investing in this company</Title><Username>k_k_909</Username><Timestamp>1346513948650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WFEMF is a Strong Buy! Expecting powerful news in the near future on Woulfe Mining.</Msg><Username>k_k_909</Username><Timestamp>1346539924467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346540029456-104</Id><Title>Hey Obama !!!</Title><Msg>Hope &amp; Change SUCKS !!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1346540029456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346540170534-105</Id><Topic><Title>Wayward Willard. The worst repug candidate for president EVER!</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1343282391770</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 01:59:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From here on in...look for Willard's support to drop and keep on dropping.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346540170534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346540460848-106</Id><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan gonna whip Obama &amp; Biden's #$%$ !!!</Title><Msg>READ MY LIPS!!!....LANDSLIDE BABY.... ALL 50 STATES !!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1346540460848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346540546184-107</Id><Topic><Title>3 Things I love,,,, other gay men,,,,obama,,,,,and my democrat party</Title><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346536331371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i marched with ows and the gay pride parade. My 2 fav politicans are Obama and Barney Frank I am so excited to get to hear both of them next week especially as a proud qweer</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346540546184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346540555069-108</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea go waste your money watching what that black indian dude put together.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1346540555069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346540623607-109</Id><Title>Chickenhawk Willard: Fruit does not fall far from the tree.</Title><Msg>What is troubling about Romney is that not only did HE manage to get several deferments, but his father did not serve in WW II, when HE was of age, either -- moreover NONE of Romney's FIVE healthy sons have served in the military. That's O-for-7 for the Romneys. Can anyone say "Chickenhawk?"</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346540623607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541024851-110</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is the clear choice for 0.0001% of Americans.</Title><Username>obama.4more</Username><Timestamp>1344448743947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 13:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's polls show Obama pulling away.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541024851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541054138-111</Id><Topic><Title>Chickenhawk Willard: Fruit does not fall far from the tree.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346540623607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is one sorry dude. I am thinking of joining my man in the military next year that way we can always be together and thanks to Obama we don't have to hide it we can be proudly gay and open about it as we share a bunk. Thankyou Obama</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346541054138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541080381-112</Id><Topic><Title>Draft Dodger. Tax Dodger. Prsident Willard...Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!! NEVER!!!!!!!</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345054005115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:06:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you imagine veterans voting for the coward Mitt?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541080381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541133565-113</Id><Topic><Title>Chickenhawk Willard: Fruit does not fall far from the tree.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346540623607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you serve in the military? I did and was proud to serve my country. If you served maybe you have a right to judge others. If not, you need to keep your mouth shut. FACT!!!</Msg><Username>iam4braves247</Username><Timestamp>1346541133565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346541352093-114</Id><Title>A lot of my fellow gays and qweers will be in Charlotte next week I am so excited!</Title><Msg>Look for me in the crowd when Barney frank speaks</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346541352093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541481358-115</Id><Topic><Title>Definition: Democratagogue</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515468993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is that fishy sphincter wizz trio?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346541481358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:18:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541520208-116</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans will LOSE!</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346537774319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The inevitable re-election of Obama is only a matter of two months and a few days.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541520208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346541630501-117</Id><Title>The loser republicans will be talking to their chairs on Nov.7 and whining, "We shoulda nominated Newtie."</Title><Msg>".... or anybody but Mitt."</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541630501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:20:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346541712643-118</Id><Title>The no convention bounce is a BIG deal. The undecided voters were not at all moved by the republican lies.</Title><Msg>The voters are wise to republican lies.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541712643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346541899166-119</Id><Title>This Message board does not discuss anything useful</Title><Msg>I think teenagers hang out here</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346541899166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541944204-120</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Bag sack suckers: Take your perversions somewhere else!</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539627042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A tea bag party follows a circle jerk.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541944204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542014313-121</Id><Topic><Title>This Message board does not discuss anything useful</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1346541899166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful? like a turd from Tulsa?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346542014313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346542111503-122</Id><Title>Romney is gaining in the polls. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Romney as well</Title><Msg>Obama's machine is getting scared. His lead in swing states is diminishing after the GOP convention, and in one swing state it is a dead heat. Start lying faster, liar libs, the truth is catching up with you.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346542111503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346542117802-123</Id><Title>Romney is gaining in the polls. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Romney as well</Title><Msg>Obama's machine is getting scared. His lead in swing states is diminishing after the GOP convention, and in one swing state it is a dead heat. Start lying faster, liar libs, the truth is catching up with you.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346542117802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542188530-124</Id><Topic><Title>After three years, and several deferments from military service, Missionary Mitt failed to convert any of the heathen French to Mormonism</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1343243065542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 15:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't heard any spin from the repug liars on this issue. I guess they don't want to talk about it.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346542188530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542189790-125</Id><Topic><Title>After three years, and several deferments from military service, Missionary Mitt failed to convert any of the heathen French to Mormonism</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1343243065542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 15:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I haven't heard any spin from the repug liars on this issue. I guess they don't want to talk about it.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346542189790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542582514-126</Id><Topic><Title>A lot of my fellow gays and qweers will be in Charlotte next week I am so excited!</Title><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346541352093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:15:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>doesn anyone know what day he speaks i will be there mon morning</Msg><Username>jcs_gaylover2</Username><Timestamp>1346542582514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542655800-127</Id><Topic><Title>The no convention bounce is a BIG deal. The undecided voters were not at all moved by the republican lies.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541712643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The republicans hired Dirty Harry to talk down to the voters. The voters are proving to be a lot more intelligent than imaginary rogue cops that talk to chairs: thus, NO BOUNCE.</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346542655800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346542724253-128</Id><Title>ANYBODY but SCOTTRADE.....Bunch of ROOKIES !!! that KNOW NOTHING !!!</Title><Msg>Clocsed my account for placing "low" limit orders...illegal ????</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1346542724253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346542895741-129</Id><Title>As Romney continues to slide in all the polls, look for the Republican lie machine to overheat</Title><Msg>They have the best liars on staff, but the voters are not buying what they are selling.</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346542895741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543069872-130</Id><Topic><Title>Chickenhawk Willard: Fruit does not fall far from the tree.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346540623607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:03:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chickenhawks breed freely in the Republican camps. It's their legacy.</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346543069872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543300290-131</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's lead in the polls is gaining. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Obama as well</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345051811501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:30:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Fox spin can change the facts. Romney is slipping.</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346543300290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543573820-132</Id><Topic><Title>When Willard loses the election, will he once again pick up the mantel of Mormon missionary and reach out to the underclass denizens of Beverly Hills?</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1343272551303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 23:15:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll become just another persona non grata</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346543573820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543574247-133</Id><Topic><Title>When Willard loses the election, will he once again pick up the mantel of Mormon missionary and reach out to the underclass denizens of Beverly Hills?</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1343272551303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 23:15:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll become just another persona non grata</Msg><Username>ooo_mau_mau</Username><Timestamp>1346543574247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346544095526-134</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Bag sack suckers: Take your perversions somewhere else!</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1346539627042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do the Republicans embrace these perverted low-life lying inbreds?</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346544095526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346544618581-135</Id><Title>Lying perverted inbred Tea Bag Repugs have relegated themselves to the status of diseaese ridden vermin. They are a threat to patriotic Americans.</Title><Msg>Their messages of hatred, bigotry, racism, fascism, non-stop lying, perversion, and all things un-American need to be eradicated like disease ridden vermin.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346544618581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346545115388-136</Id><Title>RYAN IS A LYING WEASEL, ROMNEY IS JUST PLAN OLD ROBOT THAT LIES</Title><Msg>These two jokers think they can get to the White House by feeding BOLD FACE lies to the voters. NO CHANCE LITTLE MAN AND MR. ROBOT. My lord Romney is as stiff as a board and as fake as a $3 BILL.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1346545115388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346545218459-137</Id><Topic><Title>After three years, and several deferments from military service, Missionary Mitt failed to convert any of the heathen French to Mormonism</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1343243065542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 15:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never a response from any liar repubublican on this. Are they ashamed? I doubt it. It would take having integrity to be ashamed of this.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346545218459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346545429714-138</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's inevitable re-election will keep the USA secure</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1340249528000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-20 23:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No terrorist attacks on the US on Obama's watch.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346545429714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346546119121-139</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's inevitable re-election will keep the USA secure</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1340249528000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-20 23:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>due to the military and intelligence laid down before him.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1346546119121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346550855685-140</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood said it best. The President is an employee of the American people. When an employee doesn't do the job you gotta let him go.</Title><Msg>It's time to give Mr. Obama a new opportunity.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1346550855685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346551218687-141</Id><Title>Romney - please win so I can get a job</Title><Msg>Obama has abandoned the jobless</Msg><Username>yournameshouldbemud</Username><Timestamp>1346551218687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551354675-142</Id><Topic><Title>Lying perverted inbred Tea Bag Repugs have relegated themselves to the status of diseaese ridden vermin. They are a threat to patriotic Americans.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346544618581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:10:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is only one way to deal with disease. Eradicate it.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346551354675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551455944-143</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's lead in the polls is gaining. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Obama as well</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345051811501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:30:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just over two months, and the re-election parties will begin</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346551455944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551509496-144</Id><Topic><Title>The no convention bounce is a BIG deal. The undecided voters were not at all moved by the republican lies.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541712643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:21:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No amount of spin can save the repugnant republicans. They are doomed to lose.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346551509496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551547758-145</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he will get off the banks backs so this country can grow again.</Msg><Username>nextinbreed</Username><Timestamp>1346551547758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346551769460-146</Id><Title>Liar Repugs are doomed</Title><Msg>Their cause is lost. No bounce in the polls. In fact, Romney has slipped. It's over for the repugs.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346551769460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551919213-147</Id><Topic><Title>The loser republicans will be talking to their chairs on Nov.7 and whining, "We shoulda nominated Newtie."</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1346541630501</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:20:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt by default. What a sorry way to find a nominee. The last man standing gets to run for president. What a farce!</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346551919213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346551962125-148</Id><Title>GIVEN THE CURRENT GOP LEADERSHIP AND THE INFLUENCE OF TEA BAGGING FOOLS</Title><Msg>I fear for my country. The day Obama took office, Ryan, Gingrich, Cantor and other Repucan leaderships help a meeting a few blocks from the inaugural celebrations site to discuss how to make Obama fail. This clearly demonstrates how rotten the GOP leadership is. One would think, these treasonous GOP leaders will as a minimum work with the new President for a year before they do anything to undermine his Presidency. Senator O'Connell openly declared that his priority is to make Obama fail, not help America recover from the failed leadership of Bush, rather to bring down an American President. These criminals followed through with that plan, even allowing our credit rating to fall one grade level during the debt crisis, which they engineered. The President has a job bill at the hill as we speak, a bill that will help generate a minimum of 1 million jobs, but GOP leaders will have none of it, because any good economic news will prevent these lying, greedy and corrupt baboons from taking over our government. THIS IS A SAD COMMENTARY. I feel sorry for GOP supporters, because they are low information voters and they are in most part fools.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1346551962125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552241811-149</Id><Topic><Title>Draft Dodger. Tax Dodger. Prsident Willard...Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!! NEVER!!!!!!!</Title><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1345054005115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:06:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a pathetic choice. All the other nominee wannabes had to drop out due to lack of funding.</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1346552241811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552497403-150</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not providing free sheet cleaning for the clan.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346552497403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346552833397-151</Id><Title>COME ON REPUCANS, TELL THE TRUTH, YOU GUYS DON'T LIKE ROMNEY</Title><Msg>unfortunately that is what corporate America imposed on you losers....hahahahahahaha. During the Primary, you guys went from Donald (theidiots) Trump, to Bacmann (crazy lady), then Cain( 999), then Gingrich, finally settled with Willard Romney. He was your least favorite candidate. TELL THE TRUTH.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1346552833397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346552910390-152</Id><Title>Ryan lies about Marathon time</Title><Msg>And gets caught again. Talked like he ran many and claimed he did it in under three hours. His time was 4 hours 10 seconds and he only ran one ever. You think he could remember the time of the only marathon he ever ran. He'll lie about anything but I guess that is his job as Romneys hatchet man.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346552910390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346553692751-153</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hasn't provided free health care to illegals like Reagan did,</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346553692751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346553769502-154</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't handing out free reload machines for NRA members.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346553769502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346553837391-155</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>promised the oil companies they would lose some subsidies.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346553837391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346554531264-156</Id><Topic><Title>Is there ANY group Obama hasn't pandered to yet in his quest for votes ?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346551230877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recipients expanded food stamp rolls Obama didn't. Did not gut work requirements for welfare. That is a lie Yes he extended unemployment benefits as well he should with the help of congress. did not give amnesty to young immigrants, only temporary so you stretch the truth did not give GM to UAW. they were owed money from unfunded plans.and they agreed to pay cuts as part of the dea for which they got stock. Better than going bankrupt and the government having to pick up all those pensions and unemployed. again you stretch the truth What huge tax increases are scheduled? There were not billions to any solar companies which have gone bankrupt again you lie And yes he was convinced that his view on gay marriage was not consistent with his obligation to provide equal rights for all citizens and changed his position.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346554531264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346554723448-157</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Congress to IMPEACH HOLDER ....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1346553852275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:44:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and now you call for impeachment after he wins. There sure is no time for any impeachment of anyone before the elections.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346554723448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346556347540-158</Id><Title>Go Ahead Liberals - Make My Day! Ha Ha Ha Ha</Title><Msg>Obama becomes history on November 6</Msg><Username>oceansorcas</Username><Timestamp>1346556347540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346557362580-159</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is gaining in the polls. Most of the swing states, including Ohio and Florida, are gaining for Romney as well</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346542117802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's fishycosmowizzard?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346557362580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346557388307-160</Id><Topic><Title>Definition: Democratagogue</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346515468993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's fishycosmowizzard?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346557388307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346557399035-161</Id><Topic><Title>What Africans think of Obama</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346514014826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where's fishycosmowizzard?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346557399035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346557740867-162</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489622435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost dead and he could still kick your sorry #$%$</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1346557740867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>