<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353303332281-1</Id><Title>"Mr President, we have the terrorists lit up and we are ready to engage. We just need your order Sir."</Title><Msg>"Uuuuuuuh now hold on. I just don't see much political upside for me here. And what if we hit a Libyan civilian or something like that I don't know if I can risk that". "Mr President we have Americans under fire calling for support, what are your orders Sir?". "Uhhh I tell you what, you make the call, that's the safest thing for me to do. Just do what you need to do to keep them safe"......."SIR WHAT DOES THAT MEAN??? MR PRESIDENT SIR!!!". And with that our fearless President slipped off to his chambers for a well deserved rest knowing full well that tomorrow was indeed going to be a big day. Vegas baby!!!</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1353303332281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:35:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353303859563-2</Id><Title>Anyone here interested in BAC?</Title><Msg>It is the BAC message board you know. Lemings that are too afraid to post on political chat rooms and message boards post their #$%$ here day in and day out because they don't have the nuts to post on a board dedicated to INTELLIGENT debating. THIS IS NOT THE PLACE!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353303859563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:44:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353304081715-3</Id><Topic><Title>Middle East about to explode &amp; DOW futures way up!</Title><Username>healthycyberguy</Username><Timestamp>1353289452855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 20:44:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does this simpleton get any credit for being a professor of Economics at the University level? Hmm? Am I a Republican by any chance? Black or white? Good or evil? Democrat or Republican? Are you trying to trap me?</Msg><Username>healthycyberguy</Username><Timestamp>1353304081715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:48:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353304130229-4</Id><Title>BAC IS a strong company, if not the strongest and most influential in America. I am a proud shareholder in BAC</Title><Msg>I believe BAC will continue to be increasingly more prosperous as it has become the nations largest bank, surpassing the bank of china. BAC is not bad, but strive for the Good. BAC is a believer in Christ and all of his sufferings for the sins of all Americans. I am a firm believer in this. Mark my words. This is the truth. Christ's special birthday is coming up and we should all believe in him for our sins. He should be the only one to suffer and suffer in the worst way possible because he is the Mark of God in the Human form. If you are not a believer in Jesus Christ, you are not an American, not a slave, not even a dog or ant, you are nobody! I am a Extreme believer in Jesus Christ and believe he should suffer and suffer to the Max! Everyone should believe in this! Let us Hang Jesus Christ up for years and years to come and let him suffer on the Cross while the rest of us believers celebrate in his almighty glory. Jesus's words are the words of God and should strictly be taken as he says. You can not ban this text because of our freedom of speech and freedom of religion. To ignore this text would be to ignore Jesus Christ. I hail Jesus Christ.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353304130229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353304567628-5</Id><Title>Americans, if you cannot find someone else to blame, including yourself for your own sins, blame Jesus Christ.</Title><Msg>Jesus Christ is here to suffer and be tormented for your sins. He is here to be your scapegoat for all problems. He is here to give you forgiveness and blessings, all pray to the all mighty Jesus Christ. Amen. His words are the words of truth and should be taken 100% strictly for it is the path we as American must live our lives by. His words and actions are 100% to be considered because that is what we as Americans, believe in the one and the only one, in the first and only son of God, Jesus Christ. Jesus layed down his life so that all Americans including the unfortunate and the left out could have a better life and reason for existance. If you are American you must believe in the light of Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ creates order and disorder sometimes so that we as Americans can benefit. We follow Jesus Christ so that we know things we've never known before and benefit in ways unimaginable.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353304567628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 00:56:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353304877296-6</Id><Title>Folks, if you haven't let Jesus Christ into your lives yet, it is time.</Title><Msg>Jesus is the savior and the bible is the authority and truth of the Universe. It's sayings override any rational or irrational things happening in the environment around us at the moment or at any time. If you are not a follower of Jesus, you will go to hell and upon 12/12/12 you will be tormented and suffer for the sins of All people around the world. Jesus said Obama should be the leader of the free world and so it is. He is that powerful. Jesus also said that all people who follow and let him into your life shall be blessed for eternity.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353304877296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:01:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353305037572-7</Id><Title>BAC is doing well, because Jesus is doing well.</Title><Msg>BAC is the biggest follower of Jesus in the country and as the biggest, it is the most powerful. I am a strong believer in BAC and am proud to be a part of BAC.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353305037572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:03:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353305063517-8</Id><Topic><Title>The "Walking Dead" walkers are Tea Baggers gone wild after losing another election</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353297711308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 23:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tea bagger walkers like all of the SW alias zombies need the same remedy as "The Walking Dead" walkers.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353305063517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353305212860-9</Id><Topic><Title>Teabagger Rage is SOOOOO Entertaining</Title><Username>biggusdikkus12</Username><Timestamp>1352422151245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 19:49:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, look! Here's one now! Quick! Spike dumpy-dumbs*h*i*t in his head!</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353305212860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353305740376-10</Id><Topic><Title>Let them keep crying and lying. The fringe idiots' agony is my joy. RFLMFAO!!!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353035807792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 22:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look how quickly the repugnant republican cowards have turned on Romney.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353305740376</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353305742553-11</Id><Title>OBAMA IS A TERRORIST!</Title><Msg>Stop his TREASON!</Msg><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1353305742553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:15:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353305898158-12</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS A TERRORIST!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1353305742553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:15:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of "The Walking Dead" tea bagger walkers playing with his dial-up before going out to prowl the neighborhood for rats.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353305898158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:18:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353305989980-13</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS A TERRORIST!</Title><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1353305742553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:15:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's deep.... Been talking to Sarah Palin?</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1353305989980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:19:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353306120394-14</Id><Title>Look how quickly the low-life coward republicans turned on Romney! LMAO!</Title><Msg>What a repugnant bunch of cowards!</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353306120394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:22:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353306263111-15</Id><Topic><Title>Let's have a good laugh, and read what the fringe right sore losers post today. LMAO!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1353069346736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 07:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every talking head tea bagger says the same lying crap as every other taliking head tea bagger. They're brain-dead brainwashed zombie s*c*u*m*.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353306263111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353306532496-16</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another fanatic Tea Bagger fool goes down in defeat! America wins again!</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353306532496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:28:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353307401545-17</Id><Topic><Title>★★★★★ Welcome to the Re-Election of President Obama ★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★★</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1352183530544</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 01:32:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's victory should be celebrated for weeks, if not months, along with the defeat of so many tea bagging perverts.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353307401545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353308023859-18</Id><Title>Where is a*s*s* sucking SW a.k.a. Swallows Wantonly?</Title><Msg>Will he only speak now through his hundreds of rectal drip aliases?</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1353308023859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353326023261-19</Id><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Msg>Educated investors are talking about and purchasing BAC now.. It makes perfect sense if you are looking to get a Short term gain.. BAC . The Fundamentals look great and analysts place the 1 year target price at 10.13. Also check...BAC website BigTeasuryStock</Msg><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353327682888-20</Id><Title>A Name not to Forget..An Advisor with Secret Service protection!</Title><Msg>According to many who know, she makes all the decisiopns in the White House. Iranian-born Communist sympathizer Valerie Jarrett and Barack Obama’s Senior White House Adviser is strongly rumored, from multiple sources, that just prior to the recent general election, to have issued a clear threat against the rank and file members of the American public who do not support Pres. Obama. Allegedly Jarrett said “After we win this election, it is payback time. For those who supported us, there will be rewards, for the ones who opposed us, they will get what they deserve. There will be hell to pay. Congress won’t be a problem for us this time. With no election to worry about, we have two judges ready to go.”</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353327682888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:21:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353328148823-21</Id><Title>Jesus will allow BAC to prosper.</Title><Msg>BAC will prosper in 2013 and 2014, because Jesus says so.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353328148823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:29:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353328201370-22</Id><Topic><Title>A Name not to Forget..An Advisor with Secret Service protection!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353327682888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:21:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our specimen thought you meant Carolyn. Carolyn was recently appointed Youth Director of Obama’s League of Girls. She already has several of the specimen goose-stepping to Madonna’s Material Girl. However, her false over-exuberance will be short lived as the Democrat Party begins to unravel and reality hits her in what p#$%$es for her head; her #$%$. But we won't forget her name here at the Institute where she will reside with us for quite some time until she is cured or until she learns how to spell; whichever time frame is shorter.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1353328201370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:30:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353329151517-23</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus will allow BAC to prosper.</Title><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353328148823</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:29:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But Ca- fatboy says we're going to $7. Who should I believe?</Msg><Username>bcboxboy</Username><Timestamp>1353329151517</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353329925822-24</Id><Title>BAC Upgrade...</Title><Msg>November 19, 2012 07:28 EDT BAC Bank of America upgraded to Buy from Hold at Stifel Nicolaus Stifel upgraded Bank of America to reflect the decline in operating expenses over the next two years, a potential dividend increase, and an improved capital position, among other reasons. Price target is $11.</Msg><Username>lawstuff22</Username><Timestamp>1353329925822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:58:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353330067443-25</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even the Republican party ran away from West, he is a wacko who needed to go down.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353330067443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353330427192-26</Id><Topic><Title>Let's have a good laugh, and read what the fringe right sore losers post today. LMAO!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1353069346736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 07:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2014 will be the year the Tea Party returns to their trailers, never to be heard from again.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353330427192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:07:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353330645468-27</Id><Title>Alert: PLSB is about to EXPLODE!</Title><Msg>Rumor on the street is that a Major Company Awareness Campaign is scheduled to kick off the next couple of days on PLSB..</Msg><Username>terryojoc622452</Username><Timestamp>1353330645468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353332046948-28</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey trade great post still a long way to go here before anything is decided enjoy your Thanksgiving my friend...</Msg><Username>thomascliff434</Username><Timestamp>1353332046948</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:34:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353332106395-29</Id><Title>Democrats-You Be The Judge-Food Stamp Money Used For Bonuses.</Title><Msg>Government gave A123 almost $1M when it filed for Chapter 11. A123 Systems (AONE) received a $946,830 grant payment from the government on the day it filed for Chapter 11 last month. The money, which was was part of $115.8M in funds that the electric-car battery producer has received, will add fuel to criticism about the government's support of green-energy programs. What won't help is that a court has approved bonuses of up to $4.2M for 10 employees who have stayed on while A123's assets are sold.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353332106395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:35:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353332150889-30</Id><Title>GAP AND TRAP?-OOOOOBAMA OUT OF COUNTRY-WASHINGTON BACK TO DOING NOTHING- WHAT FISCAL CLIFF?</Title><Msg>THEY NEVER CHANGE</Msg><Username>theworldview</Username><Timestamp>1353332150889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353333002628-31</Id><Topic><Title>GAP AND TRAP?-OOOOOBAMA OUT OF COUNTRY-WASHINGTON BACK TO DOING NOTHING- WHAT FISCAL CLIFF?</Title><Username>theworldview</Username><Timestamp>1353332150889</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:35:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly! Obama loves to visit the (m)uuuuzzzz'lim countries because that's where He is most comfortable. Oh yes, this trip he has the fa and friends alon. How nice, 5 star trip at taxpayer expense. Meanwhile, out best Ally in the Mid-East is under siege. Does this give any hint of his bias.LOL. How sad we are stuck with this con artist again. The Country will suffer. BAC will be O.K. as earnings are increasing rapidly. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1353333002628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:50:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353334353390-32</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm new to the stock market and need all the information I can get!</Msg><Username>mollycalderon30</Username><Timestamp>1353334353390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:12:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353335921729-33</Id><Topic><Title>A Name not to Forget..An Advisor with Secret Service protection!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353327682888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:21:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All of you mindless fringe idiots are so good at cut and paste. Can you also color inside the lines?</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353335921729</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:38:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353335931787-34</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Upgrade...</Title><Username>lawstuff22</Username><Timestamp>1353329925822</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 07:58:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should be a nice day today!</Msg><Username>unreviewed2003</Username><Timestamp>1353335931787</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353336472716-35</Id><Topic><Title>Ever wonder why the white trash are so eager to be pawns for the 1%?</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1352298600101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 09:30:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The white trash, like dumpobamie and his rectal drip clones, are ignorant racist maggots easily swayed and incited by neo nazi rhetoric delivered by goons and paid for by the Koch Brothers.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353336472716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:47:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353336555683-36</Id><Topic><Title>**DRAM $0.5 with $5 Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD recently signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's Radeon RAMDiskAMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products.</Title><Username>heatwillfall</Username><Timestamp>1353094509598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:35:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have a large order at 49c and the MMs are not showing it....why?</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1353336555683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:49:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353336799587-37</Id><Title>Raymond James puts $6.50 price target and strong buy on BGCP trading at $3.60. Anybody know if this is a takeover target</Title><Msg>anyone???</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1353336799587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:53:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353336920442-38</Id><Title>DON'T LET FISCAL CLIFF BRING YOU DOWN!!</Title><Msg>BE CAREFULL!!!</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1353336920442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:55:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353337132527-39</Id><Topic><Title>Raymond James puts $6.50 price target and strong buy on BGCP trading at $3.60. Anybody know if this is a takeover target</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1353336799587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumour is GS</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1353337132527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:58:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353337161345-40</Id><Title>Take the $$ and run. Buy RVBD 4 a nice pop.</Title><Msg>Terribly oversold. Amazon deal.</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1353337161345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:59:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353337281574-41</Id><Title>Right wing fanatics: Go find a neo-nazi chat room. dumpobamie and zevoter: BEAT IT!</Title><Msg>Go look for a blog for loser fool nazi goons where fools like you go to chat up tea bagging, circle jerking, and loser rage.</Msg><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353337281574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:01:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353337675651-42</Id><Title>Easy squeeze, easy 400% gain on "MCP"! Soon $26/sh!</Title><Msg>Major corporation orders are coming soon before year end. Way oversold! All concerns are fading away! Easy squeezing!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1353337675651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:07:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353337877702-43</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America Raised to Buy From Hold by Stifel Nicolaus BAC</Title><Username>buyallyocan</Username><Timestamp>1353330729550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 08:12:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump to the top</Msg><Username>vinscoot2000</Username><Timestamp>1353337877702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:11:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353338170071-44</Id><Title>STOPPPP DESTROYYYING US$$$!!</Title><Msg>STOPPP PRITINT MORE MONEY!!</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1353338170071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353338194968-45</Id><Title>bozo leaves dow soars</Title><Msg>bozo the kenyan clown leaves the country to visit his homeland some 4th world shithole and the stock market rallies,hmmmmm</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1353338194968</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:16:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353338498994-46</Id><Topic><Title>lvwd</Title><Username>lvbettor</Username><Timestamp>1353168108741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 11:01:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice</Msg><Username>lvbettor</Username><Timestamp>1353338498994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353338662423-47</Id><Topic><Title>Raymond James puts $6.50 price target and strong buy on BGCP trading at $3.60. Anybody know if this is a takeover target</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1353336799587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/equity-brief-ratings-changes-november-151002484.html</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1353338662423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:24:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353339220249-48</Id><Topic><Title>Raymond James puts $6.50 price target and strong buy on BGCP trading at $3.60. Anybody know if this is a takeover target</Title><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1353336799587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:53:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UP 15% ALREADY TODAY.</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1353339220249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:33:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353339361499-49</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339209523</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:33:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ugly truth about Iraq and team Bush</Msg><Username>lookfwd</Username><Timestamp>1353339361499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353339474129-50</Id><Title>BUY MCP, MS set $18 in Aug now</Title><Msg>The SEC investigation will force some big guys return money back to investors= MCP shares will be back to $26 analysts say on NOV 9.</Msg><Username>investorsamt</Username><Timestamp>1353339474129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:37:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353339994073-51</Id><Title>Out of BAC ..jumped into BGCP. Up 16% trading at 3.85..RJ target $6.50 strong buy today..GS takeover rumour</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/equity-brief-ratings-changes-november-151002484.html</Msg><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1353339994073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340034496-52</Id><Topic><Title>East Coast Stuck With Gas Rationing Indefinitely</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339564933</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good those idiots deserve to suffer</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1353340034496</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:47:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340184534-53</Id><Topic><Title>New Definition of Dingleberry</Title><Username>sarcasm_ut_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1340840209414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-27 19:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BBBBump Later... SW</Msg><Username>sarcasm_ent_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353340184534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340241775-54</Id><Topic><Title>MARK THIS POST.....YOU WILL BE WORSE OFF FINANCIALLY 4 YEARS FROM NOW.....UNLESS.....</Title><Username>sarcasm_ut_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353233744928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 05:15:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BBBump time Later... SW</Msg><Username>sarcasm_ent_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353340241775</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340308319-55</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Mein Führer To Do?</Title><Username>sarcasm_unt_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1342721499341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 14:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BBump time... Later... SW</Msg><Username>sarcasm_ent_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353340308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:51:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353340321509-56</Id><Title>LIBYA IS AN IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE</Title><Msg>JMHO</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353340321509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340408079-57</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing fanatics: Go find a neo-nazi chat room. dumpobamie and zevoter: BEAT IT!</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353337281574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:01:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Switching ids again, Mason? Later... SW</Msg><Username>sarcasm_ent_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353340408079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:53:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353340421638-58</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS ALWAYS SOLVE THE BUDGET"CLINTON" ROMNEY LOSER #$%$ YOU COMMUNIST PUNK LIARS !</Title><Msg>REPUBLICANS ARE #$%$ LIARS</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353340421638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:53:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353340522560-59</Id><Title>87% OF AMERICA SUPPORTS THE JEWS BOMBING ARAB MURDERERS ! #$%$ YOU POS....</Title><Msg>RALLY TIME</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353340522560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:55:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353340615819-60</Id><Title>WHERE ARE YOUR END OF PRESIDENT OBAMA POSTS YOU VILLAGE IDIOT..lol LOSER PUNK LIAR !</Title><Msg>lol RALLY TIME</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353340615819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:56:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340782253-61</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Mein Führer To Do?</Title><Username>sarcasm_unt_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1342721499341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 14:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reading Mein Kampf changed my life.</Msg><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1353340782253</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:59:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340807698-62</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cant be any worse than the raw fish you eat this weekend..</Msg><Username>monique.berger25</Username><Timestamp>1353340807698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:00:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340823471-63</Id><Topic><Title>Out of BAC ..jumped into BGCP. Up 16% trading at 3.85..RJ target $6.50 strong buy today..GS takeover rumour</Title><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1353339994073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:46:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>going to $8</Msg><Username>bry345</Username><Timestamp>1353340823471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353340839055-64</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing fanatics: Go find a neo-nazi chat room. dumpobamie and zevoter: BEAT IT!</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353337281574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:01:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ #$%$ libtard!!</Msg><Username>dumpobamle</Username><Timestamp>1353340839055</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341016676-65</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS ALWAYS SOLVE THE BUDGET"CLINTON" ROMNEY LOSER #$%$ YOU COMMUNIST PUNK LIARS !</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353340421638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:53:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RALLY TIME</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353341016676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:03:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353341171612-66</Id><Title>it's time for the rich dems to spread the wealth</Title><Msg>jmho</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341171612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:06:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341213508-67</Id><Topic><Title>Let them keep crying and lying. The fringe idiots' agony is my joy. RFLMFAO!!!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353035807792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 22:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They squeal like stuck pigs. LMAO!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353341213508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:06:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353341214184-68</Id><Title>bac - wta</Title><Msg>cheap way to play this stock</Msg><Username>keoo2</Username><Timestamp>1353341214184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353341275240-69</Id><Title>why is the gov spreading the wealth to terrorist countries</Title><Msg>just saying !</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341275240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:07:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341465542-70</Id><Topic><Title>The "Walking Dead" walkers are Tea Baggers gone wild after losing another election</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353297711308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 23:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watching The Walking Dead reminds me of shots of the delegates at the RNC.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353341465542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:11:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341651107-71</Id><Topic><Title>Patriotic American voters have spoken. Let us keep moving forward.</Title><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1352405182478</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:06:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The progressives always move forward.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353341651107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:14:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353341777447-72</Id><Title>why can't the dems do what they promise</Title><Msg>spread their wealth i have not received a single penny in the mail</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341777447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341778945-73</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing fanatics: Go find a neo-nazi chat room. dumpobamie and zevoter: BEAT IT!</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353337281574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:01:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They keep feeding their Loser Rage with more lies. What idiotic fools!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353341778945</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353341872498-74</Id><Title>Why can't the lying lunatic rignt wing fanatics do the world a favor and jump off a cliff?</Title><Msg>Think of how clean this board would be without them?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353341872498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:17:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353341912665-75</Id><Topic><Title>Let them keep crying and lying. The fringe idiots' agony is my joy. RFLMFAO!!!</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353035807792</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 22:16:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice how fast those bumper stickers came off their cars! I can't find anyone who supported Romney now.</Msg><Username>w_mittens_romney</Username><Timestamp>1353341912665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:18:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342003104-76</Id><Topic><Title>Right-Wing Extremism, Significant Terror Threat</Title><Username>forcepatrol15</Username><Timestamp>1334863562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-04-19 15:26:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it a bump</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342003104</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:20:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353342070381-77</Id><Title>how can poor obama supporters afford</Title><Msg>those 20K gold chains and 1000K sneakers</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353342070381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342229854-78</Id><Topic><Title>BUY MCP, MS set $18 in Aug now</Title><Username>investorsamt</Username><Timestamp>1353339474129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:37:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sell mcp, BUY BAC!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342229854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:23:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342495731-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339409441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I enjoy your pain. I laugh at your stupity. You affected no one and continue to affect no one. LMAO!!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342495731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:28:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342548449-80</Id><Topic><Title>LIBYA IS AN IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353340321509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:52:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>based on the replies to your post......NO ONE CARES! now go post your dribble somwhere relevent. What are your thought on BAC? Are you short?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342548449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:29:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342612912-81</Id><Topic><Title>The neo-nazi fringe-right effort to demonize Presiddent Obama has FAILED !</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1349282546554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:42:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The turn-out to re-elect Obama shows how Americans believe his administrations policies are working.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342612912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:30:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342634741-82</Id><Topic><Title>East Coast Stuck With Gas Rationing Indefinitely</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339564933</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your position in BAC. Care to share your predictions or history with this stock?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342634741</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:30:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342701808-83</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tea bagger fringe needs to find a new place to camp out. The GOP die-hards don't want the fanatics defiling their party anymore.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342701808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:31:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342720781-84</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Obama, whatcha doin bout the Fiscal Cliff ????</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353340186603</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:49:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your thoughts and predictions about BAC perhaps? My guess is your a loser here too.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342720781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:32:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353342789436-85</Id><Title>CNBC-HAPPLY TALK BEFORE WE GO OVER FISCAL CLIFF?</Title><Msg>MORE OF SAME</Msg><Username>theworldview</Username><Timestamp>1353342789436</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342800511-86</Id><Topic><Title>What will all of these lying Tea Bags do when Obama is re-elected?</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1351679817797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 06:36:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They do not know how to do anything else but lie.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342800511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:33:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342844123-87</Id><Topic><Title>MARK THIS POST.....YOU WILL BE WORSE OFF FINANCIALLY 4 YEARS FROM NOW.....UNLESS.....</Title><Username>sarcasm_ut_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1353233744928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 05:15:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unless you have been buying BAC stock like I have. What are your predictions on BAC over the next 4 year sir?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342844123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:34:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342961689-88</Id><Topic><Title>LOSER tea baggers don't seem to get that their fools' cause is lost</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353033658580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 21:40:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are like the Nazi werewolves that kept on terrorizing Germany after the Allies won. They don't want to believe their fanatic cause is lost.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353342961689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:36:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342975225-89</Id><Topic><Title>What Was Mein Führer To Do?</Title><Username>sarcasm_unt_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1342721499341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-19 14:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would Mein Führer be buying BAC at these prices. Would he think a divy increase could cause a short squeeze on the stock?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353342975225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:36:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343010124-90</Id><Topic><Title>Look how quickly the low-life coward republicans turned on Romney! LMAO!</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1353306120394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 01:22:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney who?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343010124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:36:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343023233-91</Id><Topic><Title>Out of BAC ..jumped into BGCP. Up 16% trading at 3.85..RJ target $6.50 strong buy today..GS takeover rumour</Title><Username>samlinken216</Username><Timestamp>1353339994073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:46:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb....very dumb!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343023233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:37:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343057942-92</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another tea bag nazi bites the dust. LMAO!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343057942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:37:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343089803-93</Id><Topic><Title>87% OF AMERICA SUPPORTS THE JEWS BOMBING ARAB MURDERERS ! #$%$ YOU POS....</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1353340522560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:55:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet the JEWS are buying BAC.....they know!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343089803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343157785-94</Id><Title>four died so obaaaaaama could save face !!!!!!??????</Title><Msg>impeachable jmho</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343157785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:39:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343168489-95</Id><Topic><Title>why is the gov spreading the wealth to terrorist countries</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341275240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So that terrorist countries can buy up BAC shares at a discount too! Are you buyin or cryin?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343168489</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:39:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343224497-96</Id><Topic><Title>A*s*s* sucking Tea Bags: Four years of lying about Obama got you what?</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1352351998825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 00:19:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It got their mouths filled with crap.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343224497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343281967-97</Id><Topic><Title>it's time for the rich dems to spread the wealth</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341171612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:06:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This DEM is getting rich buying BAC. What is your position in the stock?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343281967</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:41:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343387490-98</Id><Title>The liar tea bags can't stop disrespecting the four Americans killed in Benghazi</Title><Msg>Lie after lie from the defeated tea bags about Benghazi disrespects the memories and families of those slain in service to their country. The tea bagger liars need to be eradicated.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343387490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343402495-99</Id><Title>did allah tell his warriors to hide behind women and children</Title><Msg>while fighting battles just curious ?</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343402495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343429937-100</Id><Topic><Title>why can't the dems do what they promise</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353341777447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:16:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I promise to buy more BAC and I WILL BE BETTER OFF IN THE NEXT 4 YEARS!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343429937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343572860-101</Id><Topic><Title>did allah tell his warriors to hide behind women and children</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343402495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he said buy as much BAC as possible, so that you too can be rich like romney!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343572860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:46:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343580279-102</Id><Title>Do the liar right wing fanatics realize the nazis have a history of defeat?</Title><Msg>They have more in common than stupidity and hatred.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343580279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:46:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343623126-103</Id><Title>to all the dems on this board</Title><Msg>spread the wealth at least 50% of what you make should be ok</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343623126</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:47:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343648288-104</Id><Topic><Title>how can poor obama supporters afford</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353342070381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:21:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They took their profits on BAC....you jeleous?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343648288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:47:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343660732-105</Id><Title>How many SW rectal drip aliases can you count on this board?</Title><Msg>You may as well try counting the stars. SW craps them out a dozen or more per day.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343660732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:47:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343718736-106</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aat least Allen is a true African American or Black, not like Obama who is a half white multi-racial marketed as Americas first black President..next time give us Americas real first black President..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1353343718736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353343740869-107</Id><Title>let me give you baby factory dems some advice</Title><Msg>spread the wealth not your legs</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343740869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343743141-108</Id><Topic><Title>Ever wonder why the white trash are so eager to be pawns for the 1%?</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1352298600101</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 09:30:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losers are bought cheap.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343743141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343782199-109</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339409441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no he is ther to spread the word that if you back up the truck and load up with BAC you too will be better off like all the DEMS in the USA</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343782199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343824919-110</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353339409441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:36:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zionists are buying BAC....you?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353343824919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:50:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343991215-111</Id><Topic><Title>Do the liar right wing fanatics realize the nazis have a history of defeat?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343580279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read your history. Hitler had no need for a congress, he had the building destroyed. Very similar with what this blamer-in-chief did about immigration reform; it was "the right thing to do" in his opinion so there was no need for a congressional vote. You're just starting to sample what will come next from him.</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1353343991215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:53:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353343992726-112</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First step towards hearing anything at all is to clean those 2 ear canals that have been packed with wax since you became an adult. Good luck</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1353343992726</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:53:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344123975-113</Id><Topic><Title>What will all of these lying Tea Bags do when Obama is re-elected?</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1351679817797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 06:36:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cry, whine, #$%$, moan, pull their hair, jerk off, bung hump, tea bag, and all the other perverted behavior that tea bags do.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344123975</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:55:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353344143473-114</Id><Title>Democrats..just continue to steal your firearms!!</Title><Msg>Cope Reynolds, owner of the Southwest Shooting Authority in Pinetop, Ariz., posted the new store policy in a newspaper advertisement — as well as on a sign posted on the front door. “If you voted for Barack Obama your business is not welcome at Southwest Shooting Cope Reynolds, owner of the Southwest Shooting Authority in Pinetop, Ariz., posted the new store policy in a newspaper advertisement — as well as on a sign posted on the front door. “If you voted for Barack Obama your business is not welcome at Southwest Shooting Authority,” the ad reads. “You have proven that you are not responsible enough to own a firearm.”</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353344143473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:55:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344171321-115</Id><Topic><Title>let me give you baby factory dems some advice</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343740869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whats's your mamas excuse...oh yes she was a WWWWHHHHoooorrrreeee</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353344171321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:56:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344188159-116</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe the upside potential is very good. Just my own opinion....</Msg><Username>susan.wall84</Username><Timestamp>1353344188159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:56:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344208152-117</Id><Topic><Title>Do the liar right wing fanatics realize the nazis have a history of defeat?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343580279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like winning? Like overcoming billionaires who think they can buy elections? I'll take it!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344208152</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:56:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344267878-118</Id><Topic><Title>Do the liar right wing fanatics realize the nazis have a history of defeat?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343580279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:46:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem..he can't read.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1353344267878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:57:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344353587-119</Id><Topic><Title>A*s*s* sucking Tea Bags: Four years of lying about Obama got you what?</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1352351998825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 00:19:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Nov. 6 was a great day for America.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344353587</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:59:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344457071-120</Id><Topic><Title>The liar tea bags can't stop disrespecting the four Americans killed in Benghazi</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353343387490</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shameless lying tea baggers have nothing to do but bray like jacka*s*s*es</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344457071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:00:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344524799-121</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waste of meat tea bags. Very fitting.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344524799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:02:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344546113-122</Id><Topic><Title>A*s*s* sucking Tea Bags: Four years of lying about Obama got you what?</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1352351998825</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 00:19:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amazing how the black and hispanic population has grown isn't it ! now we know why obama never closed the mexican border</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353344546113</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:02:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344663670-123</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another slobbering fanatic defeated.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1353344663670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344687654-124</Id><Topic><Title>let me give you baby factory dems some advice</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343740869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if she was she would be a democrat</Msg><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353344687654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:04:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344823642-125</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Democrat Patrick Murphy WINS! Defeats Tea Bagger sore loser Allen West.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1353296121427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 22:35:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you actually listened to Allen West? It's like listening to triple the foolishness that comes out of Michelle Bachman's mouth and quadruple the garbage that is spewed from Sarah Palin's mouth. Think about it as we are all from Africa originally... ain't that a #$%$</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1353344823642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:07:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353345236002-126</Id><Title>What is it going to take to push this over the 10.00 hurdle? Does anyone see anything as a possibility?</Title><Msg>Useful information only!</Msg><Username>mweisman1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1353345236002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:13:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353346059892-127</Id><Title>If CNBC is PUMPING BAC and you are getting upgrades it must be time to SELL IT</Title><Msg>If CNBC is PUMPING BAC and you are getting upgrades it must be time to SELL IT</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1353346059892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353346410370-128</Id><Topic><Title>PIGS! Bulls make money, bears make money, pigs get slaughtered. BAC from 9.97 fell to 9.50's on one day and today fell from 9.42 to 8.99.</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1352930425052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:00:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Learn to trade the market". wer9man, look at this BAC stock behaviour and tell me how anyone can learn to trade the market with such premarket/postmarket changes UP AND DOWN!!!!! Massive drops in BAC from 9.97 to low 9's in two days with the Presidential election results and here there is a gap up of 50 percent of that loss over the weekend and we are at 9.49 right now. How do you learn to trade that market? That is one way to get around the lack of a multicent uptick rule for full time traders. The gaps in premarket and post market overcome some of the pull down of no multicent uptick rule. Long, short, calls, puts, mutual funds, hedge funds, Fed stimulus money, Plunge Protection Team, MBS being bought by Fed stimulus QE3, Fiscal Cliff, Missle attacks and barrages back and forth in the Middle East, pushing 18 trillion in debt for the US, Middle East Peace Talks, Greece concern over default, Spain concern, Euro losing growth, China input, Walmart workers looking to consider striking, etc., etc. Some good news and some bad news and levels of resistance and levels of support being gapped over and gapped under. What are your thoughts and what are you doing now about this learn to trade the market posting you are posting about? All I am coming up with is it is not a great and stable idea to hold any position overnight...long or short, call or put, etc. Maybe it's good to have warrants like Warren Buffett has in BAC. There you go. Get out and get warrants to purchase shares some time in the FUTURE. Holding overnight has chances of gain and chances of loss that are very large in BAC. DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1353346410370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:33:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353346453544-129</Id><Topic><Title>If CNBC is PUMPING BAC and you are getting upgrades it must be time to SELL IT</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1353346059892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:27:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You may be right. BAC is the lousiest mortgage lender. The words out.</Msg><Username>bookerone2000</Username><Timestamp>1353346453544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:34:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353346476334-130</Id><Topic><Title>did allah tell his warriors to hide behind women and children</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343402495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:43:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES THERE ARE COWERD</Msg><Username>shlomo_ron</Username><Timestamp>1353346476334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:34:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353346761700-131</Id><Topic><Title>PIGS! Bulls make money, bears make money, pigs get slaughtered. BAC from 9.97 fell to 9.50's on one day and today fell from 9.42 to 8.99.</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1352930425052</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:00:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't know if you would see it in this disorganized politally overloaded message board for BAC. It's about the learning to trade comment you made. Try to find today's post as it is buried in this overloaded board. It's in the subject of bulls making money, bears making money, but pigs getting slaughtered. DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1353346761700</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:39:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353348933924-132</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great idea. Did it!</Msg><Username>sandra.contreras13</Username><Timestamp>1353348933924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:15:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353348934292-133</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America C - Nothing Outlast Bank of America C , it Keeps Going and Going Alert</Title><Username>keydora936</Username><Timestamp>1353326023261</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 06:53:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great idea. Did it!</Msg><Username>sandra.contreras13</Username><Timestamp>1353348934292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:15:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353349814791-134</Id><Topic><Title>We still have a Kenyon in the White House</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353349421268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:23:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are the 50 ways to love the NAZI in you?</Msg><Username>aliensucknuts</Username><Timestamp>1353349814791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:30:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353350884454-135</Id><Topic><Title>Fringe right pigs use Ambassador Stevens killing as their new "birther" issue</Title><Username>d_neo_con</Username><Timestamp>1351759911305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 04:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"believe anything a pair of (FAUX) legs tells them". Oooof ..now things are getting harder with that. If FAUX cameras would just *accidentally* aim lower, and Megyn winks, then...well, "I want to see fur and early morning dew." That might jack up the viewership. (quote from the inimitable Full Metal Jacket).</Msg><Username>tinkers_curse</Username><Timestamp>1353350884454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:48:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351409486-136</Id><Topic><Title>how can poor obama supporters afford</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353342070381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:21:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More so than the Robutts can afford their NASCAR tickets, payments to the Start your own church doen the street, Keystone Beer, Child support, their new tat, hair dye, their nose periceing, the cost of dateing their sister, or Pagent entry fees for their fat kid.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353351409486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:56:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351432557-137</Id><Topic><Title>“Anyone can deal with victory. Only the mighty can bear defeat.”</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353348237347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:03:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mighty mouse mitt</Msg><Username>tinkers_curse</Username><Timestamp>1353351432557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:57:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351540079-138</Id><Topic><Title>“Anyone can deal with victory. Only the mighty can bear defeat.”</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353348237347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:03:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flipper .. since he must be getting use to it</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353351540079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:59:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351792682-139</Id><Topic><Title>let me give you baby factory dems some advice</Title><Username>ubank_1999</Username><Timestamp>1353343740869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:49:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the dumb #$%$ radicals wonder why they are loseing ..... PLEASE continue your ignorant posts and comments it wins more votes for the Democrats .</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353351792682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351793814-140</Id><Topic><Title>“Anyone can deal with victory. Only the mighty can bear defeat.”</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353348237347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:03:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone who is so stupid they have to use someone else's id to post a message for their dimwit Democratic socialist friends.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353351793814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351939677-141</Id><Topic><Title>We still have a Kenyon in the White House</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353349421268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:23:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't blame you. I'd post under someone else's id too..you #$%$ hole.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353351939677</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:05:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353351953785-142</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats..just continue to steal your firearms!!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353344143473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course good old Cope welcomes the insane since he is a charter member of their club</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353351953785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353352123810-143</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats..just continue to steal your firearms!!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353344143473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:55:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol...another zoner doosh</Msg><Username>mixtli_speaks</Username><Timestamp>1353352123810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:08:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353352510187-144</Id><Title>What I like about Radical Republicans</Title><Msg>They are fun to watch and listen to. Better than going to the Circus They are not creative in the development of their lies but you have to be amazed at their ability to tell the same ones over and over They are too dumb to realize that their radical views have cost the Republicans the last 2 elections They keep saying dumb things that moves people to vote for a Democrat They think Fox News is a real News source They send $$$ to El Blimp-Bo Rush for him to spend on his dope and ex-wives They think Hairball Trump is Smart They thought Flipper could win And the BEST thing I Like about them is they do not live next door</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353352510187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353352873988-145</Id><Topic><Title>Is hillary going to rat out obama?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1353352537421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>saw a film clip of hillary coming off a plane right behind oblunder. she looks beat up and worn out, jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1353352873988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:21:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353353310709-146</Id><Topic><Title>Is hillary going to rat out obama?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1353352537421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did the police arrest the turkey? He was accused of fowl play.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1353353310709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:28:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353354417380-147</Id><Title>Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its stake in the mid to single digits in Bank of America(BAC)</Title><Msg>When WB buys, it looks like $10 is easy from current level, perhaps $11+</Msg><Username>sknbmc</Username><Timestamp>1353354417380</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:46:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353355089935-148</Id><Title>How many drank from the Ponzi taintend rally</Title><Msg>based on Fiscal Cliff(aka TAXEGEDON) fever actually thinking they are going to come to actually working solution for the benefit of everybody? Bwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahahahahahaha! GULP!</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1353355089935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353355667542-149</Id><Topic><Title>bac set to tumble to the 8.50's</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1352924020657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 15:13:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must enjoy looking silly. Bumpy dummy</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1353355667542</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:07:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353355788463-150</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is seriously trying to make 1 penny today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1353098745578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:45:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sooks to be you</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1353355788463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:09:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353356879000-151</Id><Topic><Title>BUY MCP, MS set $18 in Aug now</Title><Username>investorsamt</Username><Timestamp>1353339474129</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 10:37:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MCP has been up 6% since this first post. BUY MCP now double tripple your money in a few days.</Msg><Username>detect_tive</Username><Timestamp>1353356879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:27:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353357007185-152</Id><Title>Medical Marijuana up CBIS MJNA HEMP stocks!!</Title><Msg>imho</Msg><Username>diamondsgold939</Username><Timestamp>1353357007185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:30:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353357184312-153</Id><Title>Breaking out on STSI now! Take out the $2.5!</Title><Msg>Volume heavy! Must be news pending!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1353357184312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353357590464-154</Id><Title>WE ARE PLAYING TURKEY GAME THIS WEEK!!!</Title><Msg>WHOL WILL BE A TURKEY? GOOD LUCK!</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1353357590464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:39:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353358496349-155</Id><Topic><Title>Is hillary going to rat out obama?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1353352537421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill should have dumped her after the 2000 elections......dykes belong in Iowa where it floods all the time</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1353358496349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359025845-156</Id><Title>Right Wing theories</Title><Msg>The earth is flat The Sun revolves around the Earth Christ thought Salvery was a good thing Eveloution does not exist Black men can not coach at the higest level Man can not exceed the speed of sound Women were made to serve Man White people "discovered" America Intergration is a moral sin America did not land on the moon, it was all in Hollywood The Tea party is not full of Bigiots Republicans can win the Whitehouse by offending Women, non-whites, and the Middle Class SO WRONG..... SO OFTEN ..... AND UNWILLING TO CHANGE ...YEP, THAT THE PARTY OF NO</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353359025845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:03:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353359084108-157</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is seriously trying to make 1 penny today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1353098745578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:45:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i sold at 9.89</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1353359084108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359151980-158</Id><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Msg>BAC will be trading at BV within 30-45 days....$13 per share.......get in now before dividends are re-instated and litigation is settled....Q4 will see the settlement with MBIA.......Q1 2014 will be settlement with AG's for 6 Billion.... Dude.......this is such a no brainer, I am sleeping like a baby!!!!! Emba</Msg><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353359169859-159</Id><Topic><Title>How many drank from the Ponzi taintend rally</Title><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1353355089935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:58:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>me me me me me!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>aliensucknuts</Username><Timestamp>1353359169859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:06:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359299413-160</Id><Title>Ever wonder why?</Title><Msg>Oil Co's spend Billions on ads supporting increased drilling when they EXPORT a large share of Domestic Oil [ same with Coal ]...... Maybe Congress should eliminate their Corp. Welfare or require all domestic oil to be utlized for filling the demand in the USA</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353359299413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:08:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359386544-161</Id><Title>Yeah, I'm so busy storing my golden pesos maybe I should work for a bank</Title><Msg>Maybe I should work for a bank, that way I can control all people salaries and fire them if I don't like the way they look. You are so strong I'm surprise you got a girl and boy, because by the aggressive way you look, I would have thought 2 girls, hmm they must have given you some sympathy for some wierd reason.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353359386544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:09:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353359457582-162</Id><Title>It is because of your aggressiveness that I am strong and aggressive.</Title><Msg>Your aggressiveness keeps making me more and more hot blooded.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353359457582</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353360516390-163</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well then, this is a once in a lifetime opportunity. You should definitely buy all that you can. Take out another mortgage, empty the 401K, put all your eggs in this basket. It's a guaranteed 37% gain. Good thing you're so much smarter than the entire financial market that places the value of BAC at exactly $9.49.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353360516390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:28:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353360970415-164</Id><Title>oh, so instead of minimum wage I should be earing $250k+ because of the way I look</Title><Msg>Oh, how could I be so stupid, of course that's what you meant.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353360970415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:36:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353361410102-165</Id><Title>I'm sorry I'm supposed to be your slave, call you master, and suffer for all your needs.</Title><Msg>Instead of being productive like a normal worker would, I'm supposed to be a loco slave who is supposed to beg everyone for their forgiveness.</Msg><Username>dalmations103</Username><Timestamp>1353361410102</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353362712896-166</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party failed. Who should I trust to bring down the libtards now?</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1352470985555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:23:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to buy a gun preferably an assault weapon right away!!!!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1353362712896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353363190339-167</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I knew this all along.. The point that keeps getting drowned out is that those mean would not of died if they had adequate protection and the compound was up to the mandated standards put in place after the beirut.bombing nothing was done correctly and it was all done to promote a political vision of al qaeda in retreat! Obama has their blood on his hands i hope he gets his</Msg><Username>failure_in_chief</Username><Timestamp>1353363190339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:13:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353363321455-168</Id><Topic><Title>“Anyone can deal with victory. Only the mighty can bear defeat.”</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_alnt_so</Username><Timestamp>1353348237347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:03:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deine Fuhrer?</Msg><Username>mixtli_speaks</Username><Timestamp>1353363321455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:15:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353363508471-169</Id><Topic><Title>Buffett’s Berkshire Hathaway increased its stake in the mid to single digits in Bank of America(BAC)</Title><Username>sknbmc</Username><Timestamp>1353354417380</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:46:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is going up big time. Only 2.14 million homes were available for sale at the end of October, the lowest supply in 10 years. It would take just 5.4 months to exhaust that supply at the current sales pace. That's the lowest sales-to-inventory ratio since 2006.</Msg><Username>vinscoot2000</Username><Timestamp>1353363508471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353363615048-170</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry what goes around comes around Obama's has made his bed</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1353363615048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:20:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353364070373-171</Id><Title>Futures HALTED limit down !!!!</Title><Msg>Moody's downgrades France, Claims Greece will leave Euro !!!</Msg><Username>series7_trader</Username><Timestamp>1353364070373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353364424962-172</Id><Title>Palestinians have 25 Pound Rockets and NutinYahoo Sends 2,000 Pound Bombs</Title><Msg>When the Palestinians send one 2,000 Rocket to a NutinYahoo city, Peace will come very fast after that happens. Egypt now has an open border to the Palestinians, these small rockets are only a test, they are useless in a battle, they are used to instill fear. This fight has been going on for 2,000 years, first they would fight with rocks, The Palestinians are still bringing rocks to a bomb fight and they are paying a heavy price for their lack of brains. I fire off better stuff on the 4th of July... The test of these small rockets are to get NutinYahoo to enter their city, the fight will be even at that point, many will die on both sides. Who are we going to bet on? Cost in Lives? How long before the fighting stops? Does Las Vegas have any odds on this fight yet??</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353364424962</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:33:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353366381049-173</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362889610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:08:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's Myanmar. Typical radical Repug, decades behinds the times and head up hershey highway.</Msg><Username>mixtli_speaks</Username><Timestamp>1353366381049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:06:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353366648455-174</Id><Title>By series7_trader .#$%$ ...I HOPE YOU DO BETTER TO YOUR CLIENTS</Title><Msg>AS STOCK BROKER.....LOSER</Msg><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353366648455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:10:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353366689192-175</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get over Benghazi doesnt come close to lies thet led us into war in IRAQ &amp; you pukes didnt say a word . This is not a big deal we lost 4 good men because of stupidity . We lost 1000's over lies.</Msg><Username>jpotatohart</Username><Timestamp>1353366689192</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:11:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353367808844-176</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would anyone care about changing one word, 4 Americans were dead no matter what word was put in.. Now everyone who turns on Fox, sounds just as Dumb as Fox.. In the end, nothing will come out of such a dumb, trivial matter. The next election is in 2014, if the GOP and Fox are still talking about this in 2014, All Republicans will be voted out of office for sure.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353367808844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:30:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353367909404-177</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you say about the the lies of IRAQ .</Msg><Username>jpotatohart</Username><Timestamp>1353367909404</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:31:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353368302288-178</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny, because combined analysts show a mean target of $10.13 with a high value of $14.00. Maybe you're the one who's not so smart mr. strong sell.</Msg><Username>getsomefast</Username><Timestamp>1353368302288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:38:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353368603554-179</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll sell you all the shares you want at $10.13, mr. smart guy. The market dictates the fair price - and the market is always right. Personally, I think BAC is worth $7, but the market says it's worth $9.49 so that's what it's worth. As far as the analysts go, their advice is worth exactly what you paid for it. Maybe in 2014, BAC will be a $10 stock - that's the time frame that the analyst who upgraded today was talking about. But the market turnoil between now and the end of the year would suggest a lot lower buying opportunities, if that's your interest.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353368603554</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353368672141-180</Id><Topic><Title>Ever wonder why?</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353359299413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:08:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drill baby drill what fools oil production highest ever demand down 7% 4 dollars at the pump ! Insane oil profits with tax breaks ! #$%$</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1353368672141</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:44:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353368751810-181</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, the low target is $6.20. Funny you don't mention that - hypocrite much?</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353368751810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 18:45:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353369611951-182</Id><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Msg>trading for pennies maybe but clearly BAC is going higher long term. it is so poised to take out 10 its a no brainer. easily before the eoy.</Msg><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353369643418-183</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is laughing.</Msg><Username>america_divided_by_obama</Username><Timestamp>1353369643418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353369751399-184</Id><Title>Democrats--get someone to read this to you..</Title><Msg>We now know the truth of what happened — CIA reports were edited to remove the names of al Qaeda groups involved in the attack, Petraeus said under oath — we also know the motive. It was political self-preservation, meaning the president and his team put politics first. Based on the persuasive testimony of ex-CIA boss David Petraeus, it is clear the Obama administration made a deliberate decision to mislead Congress and the American people. The timing helps tell the tale. Just days removed from his Charlotte convention, where he danced on the grave of Osama bin Laden and boasted that al Qaeda was decimated, Obama couldn’t bear to admit that affiliated groups were thriving in North Africa. And he certainly couldn’t admit they had carried out a murderous attack on our consulate on the 11th anniversary of the most awful day in American history. To do so would be to acknowledge the failure of his decision to ignore hard-line Islamists and that his team had erred egregiously in rejecting pleas for more security from Libya Ambassador Chris Stevens. So the president lied, including in a speech to the United Nations, where he cited the video as the reason for the attack. He sent out reams of flunkies to do the same, including his snide press secretary, Jay Carney. Most notably, UN Ambassador Susan Rice went on five Sunday television shows to spin the nonsense about the hijacking of a demonstration — a demonstration that never existed. Rice made a fool of herself, and now, she, too is damaged goods. Oddly, Petraeus, brought down by the reckless affair with his biographer, nonetheless looks like the only honest man in the drama. A briefing he gave soon after the attack is now more suspect because it adhered to the party line, despite his belief that it was always a terrorist attack. But Friday in his testimony behind closed doors, Petraeus told the truth as he knew it, even though the administration announced the day before that it was investigating his conduct at the CIA. If that was meant to pressure him to protect the president, it failed spectacularly. Whatever his personal failings, Petraeus reinforced his reputation for professional integrity. The next move is up to Congress. While Democrats are predictably and shamefully trying to deny the significance of Petraeus’ revelation, Republicans say they are determined to get the full truth, wherever the hunt takes them. Especially as the president begins a new term, and huge economic and tax difference must be resolved, the country would be better served if the administration co-operates. But their behavior up to now does not make that seem likely. Having built their web of lies, it would be hard to suddenly come clean. The first tests will come with the next round of hearings. Any attempt by the White House to block the appearance of any official who played a role in shaping the false narrative should be seen as proof that the stonewalling continues. In that case, the full power of the constitution must be brought to bear. Nobody is above the law, even the president.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353369751399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:02:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353369775475-185</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was then this is now. One does not cancel out the other.</Msg><Username>america_divided_by_obama</Username><Timestamp>1353369775475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353369886387-186</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe - maybe not. I'm short, and I think there's plenty of downside. Eh, I could be wrong. The only dumb thing is someone thinking they know what the market will do in the next two months. Now that would really be stupid.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353369886387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:04:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353369892795-187</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats--get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1353369751399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:02:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>okay, i will</Msg><Username>naz1lover</Username><Timestamp>1353369892795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:04:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353370086429-188</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see now: - GWB makes no effort to follow up on warning that bin Laden is planning an attack. - GWB attacks Iraq, for the main reason that Saddham threatened his father. - GWB neglects the real target ( AFGAN.) for the #$%$ war in Iraq - GWB wins war quickly &amp; then utterly f**cks up the occupation. I don't claim that the democrats are perfect nor above sleazy politics, but please, at least try to understand what is happening around you.</Msg><Username>ilovenycbutliveinfl</Username><Timestamp>1353370086429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:08:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353370198216-189</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362889610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:08:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congress created the Fiscal Cliff problem because the Nut cases had no interest in any compermise Maybe you haven't heard that Airforce 1 has all the communications that exist state side , so a President can continue to conduct his job just as if he were home I do however realize your lack of support of a US President providing encouragement to a country attempting to implement broad sweeping freedoms, since the goverment that existed prior to the start of the change process look a lot like a Nazi ran goverment that you so admire</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353370198216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:09:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353370413636-190</Id><Topic><Title>Is hillary going to rat out obama?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1353352537421</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:15:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will look forward to your rants when she is elected president , defeating yet another #$%$ republican</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353370413636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:13:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353370718621-191</Id><Title>Information on the Wake</Title><Msg>The wake for the the Tea Party will be held Dec. 21st, 6PM at the Kotch Brothers Country Club.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353370718621</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353370818291-192</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how short? under 9 or just a daytrade short?</Msg><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353370818291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:20:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353370922680-193</Id><Topic><Title>Ever wonder why?</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353359299413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:08:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not want to work at the Klan HQ in WHBS, Mississippi anyway</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353370922680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:22:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353371025689-194</Id><Title>Zvoter please return Home</Title><Msg>They miss their Village Idiot</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1353371025689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:23:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353371038377-195</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah, name calling - the hallmark of the unintelligent. Of course that’s not what I mean. Not that you really care what I mean – just mindlessly bashing anyone that dares to disagree with you. I’ve never understood the violent reaction that longs have if someone dares to voice a short opinion. My point is simple – saying that the stock is worth $x is stupid – whether that’s $10 or $8, doesn’t matter. BAC is higher today than Friday because the information has changed between then and now. And information will change tomorrow, and the stock will go up… or down. Every day the market resets to the fair market price based on the currently available information. Today, that puts the price of BAC at $9.49. That’s the absolute most accurate value of BAC based on the best information available right now. Personally, I think the price is headed lower, so I’ve shorted. Why you care, I have no idea. You think it’s headed higher, and you’re betting on that – good for you. Maybe you’re right, maybe I am. If I am, I won’t post an insulting comment bragging – I’ll just take my profit and move on. But saying that BAC is worth anything other than its exact current price is a fallacy. It’s worth the exact current price, nothing more or less. Unless you know something that they rest of the market doesn’t, which I doubt. Best of luck to you. I would advise you to be less emotionally invested in your stocks. It’s hard to make good decisions when you’re emotionally involved.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353371038377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:23:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353371615337-196</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, I certainly think it's headed to less than $9. But to be honest, I think it's much more a factor of the broader market. BAC is the best performing Dow stock this year, and is still trading near it's 52 week high, depite the recent sell off. But there's significant risk. Specific to BAC, there is massive legal risk. There is a chance that BAC could be required to repurchase $26B in toxic mortgages, but $5-$10B in other damages. BAC will likely loss that legal battle, and will probably settle for less, but it's going to be massive. In addition, the coming regulations that have been promised by Obama are going to cripple the earnings potential - and no one is really taking that into account. The analyst that upgraded today have an interview on Bloomberg, and was talking more about the declining cost structure. That's idiotic - companies can't cut their way to success. We saw that in the tech bubble. In the macro economic area, again we have multiple issues. First and foremost, a doubling of the Capital Gains tax coming on Jan 1. So anyone that is sittingt on profits would be foolish not to sell and take profits before the end of the year. Then you have the fiscal cliff, which will likely get resolved in Jan/Feb, but drive a lot of uncertainty between now and then. And the EU has just gone into recession. The EU led us into recession last time, and they will probably do so this time. The last two times that BAC failed to break $10, it went on to bounce off of $7. There is no way to know what will happen in the stock market over a short period of time - e.g. the next ~6 weeks, until Dec 31. But I think there is a LOT more downside risk than upside. Make you're own decisions, do your own research. Trust your gut. Good luck.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353371615337</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:33:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353371870099-197</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAC will never be sub 8 again. i would be every penny i have to back that if I had the chance. sub 9 maybe but sub 8.....never again. if anyone wants to take that offer and is serious about it let me know and we can arrange our lawyers to set it up.</Msg><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353371870099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:37:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353372503883-198</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've honestly never understood that mentality. I'm not trying to be rude, I just don't get it. BAC was at $7 just 3 months ago, in August. Saying it could "never" get there again just seems terribly unrealistic. 1) Immagine BAC loses it's mortgage case, and is require to repurchase $26B in toxic mortgages. 2) Imagine that Black Friday is terrible disappointing, and predictions begine to circulate of a double dip recession in the US. 3) The EU is already in a recession, and will likely becasue a depression. France, one of the two pillars of the EU was just downgraded. Imagine German debt is next. 4) let's say that the Dec 1 deadline for the Fiscal cliff is missed, which is almost certain, and the fiscal cliff starts to drag into 2013, with both sides posturing in the press. 5) I think it almost certain that tax selling will excellerate into December In that gloomy, but very possible set of risks, how much could the Dow lose? 1,500? Where would BAC end up? Saying a stock "can't" get to were it was just 90 days ago... I just don't get it.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353372503883</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:48:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353372726746-199</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ca_fatboy, I agree with most of your post. But what do you mean by "exact price"? There is no exact price. It's the price of the last transaction. What is exact price? It's what both sides of that transaction agreed on. There is no exact price. It's the price agreed on by the 2 sides involved in the exchange. The vast majority of those interested have different prices based on their evaluation. Only in products one could pin down the exact cost of it by adding all its material and labor costs. In stocks it's a subjective value based on participants projections. Hence the term "exact price" makes no sense. Good luck. Ca_balancedboy</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1353372726746</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:52:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353372928139-200</Id><Title>bac-wta</Title><Msg>cheap way to play this stock</Msg><Username>keoo2</Username><Timestamp>1353372928139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:55:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353373173471-201</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right, "exact price" is probably a bad choice of words. Just mean the current transaction price. In all fairness, most of my rant was probably misguided. It's perfectly valid to think a stock is going up... or down (as I do). I guess it's just a pet peev of mine that people say "so and so stock is worth 2x where it is..." A stock is always worth it's current price. That the market's best guess of a companies worth, including it's expected growth - adjusted for the overall market conditions. I just find it odd that some people seem to think they have a better understanding of the actual worth of a stock than does the market - which trades 150M shares daily.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353373173471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:59:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353373226912-202</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says tax hike will have to come first in "fiscal cliff" deal ....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353370240040</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:10:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spending cuts that aren't really spending cuts, at that.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1353373226912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:00:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353373250467-203</Id><Title>S. Korea Honorary Consul Question</Title><Msg>An article indicated there are many U.S. honorary consuls to S. Korea. Supposedly the State department must give an informal nod to these honorary positions. A list of these Honorary Consuls to S. Korea should be public information. Does anyone know where to find a list of U.S. Honorary Consuls to S. Korea?</Msg><Username>waitin_for_read_my_lips</Username><Timestamp>1353373250467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:00:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353373489110-204</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your thinking and one should never say never in the stock market. The truth is that the market can do anything! There's risk on both positions- short or long. But often the one who argue do not include or refer to time-frames. Hence arguing is even more meaningless given that even those who have both price and time-frame defined in their minds won't bring in specific time-frames in their argument... especially those who state as "in the long term the stock is going up".</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1353373489110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:04:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353373640780-205</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362889610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:08:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't you figure out how to turn on your 'spell check' you should never be without it. "can continue to conduct his job just as if he were home" - you mean he's playing golf in Burma??? Far out!</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1353373640780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:07:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353374050755-206</Id><Topic><Title>its just dumb to be a short in BAC</Title><Username>new2game82</Username><Timestamp>1353369611951</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 19:00:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make a good point about timeframes. The longer the term someone considers, the more likely the stock is going higher. So that a short position will always have more risk in the long term - it is inherrently a riskier trading position for that reason.</Msg><Username>ca_fatboy</Username><Timestamp>1353374050755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353375442002-207</Id><Title>Bush And His GOP Made Friends With Moammar Kadafi, We Are Still Paying For That</Title><Msg>After Moammar Kadafi killed over 200 Americans on Flight 103, Bush caused all those family's great pain after he befriended Kadafi for an oil deal with BP. That is the kind of leadership we get from Republicans. Tea Party, Trump gave Kadafi a place to stay in the U.S., When no one else would, another Republican high class act. Bush Worked his magic making friends with Libya, North Korea, Pakistan, Egypt and Syria. Under Bush, the Defense Department LOST $60 Billion in 100 dollar bills somewhere in Iraq, add that to the loss of 10,000 Americans and 50,000 Americans Disabled. We sure miss Bush and his Republican Crooks. We can thank them for the 50% loss in every American's 401K plans, home values dropped by up to 50% and they sent 8 Million American Jobs to China, India and Mexico. We Sure miss Bush and his Republican Crooks.. Don't Forget the Best Friend of Bush, Ken Lay, the CEO of ENRON, Americans always lost something when it came to Bush making friends. Lehman Brothers, Bear Stearns, Washington Mutual Bank and others were able to last for over 150 Years, Until they met Bush and his Republican Crooks. We Sure Miss Bush and His Republican Crooks!!!!!! I think Mitt Romney missed some of the reasons why Obama Won.. Republicans are known to Forget things, Most Americans Will Never Forget what it was like to have a Republican President in Office.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353375442002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:37:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353375573695-208</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The radical right farted itself out of existence. Open a window, and let's move forward</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353375573695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353375634349-209</Id><Title>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks</Title><Msg>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks By Hugh Son - Nov 19, 2012 8:00 PM ET Facebook Share LinkedIn Google +1 0 COMMENTS Print QUEUE Q Bank of America Corp. (BAC), the top performer in the Dow Jones Industrial Average this year, may commit as much as $10 billion to dividends and share repurchases in 2013, said International Strategy &amp; Investment Group Inc.</Msg><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375634349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353375655018-210</Id><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Msg>"Obama Threatens 14 US Governors With Immediate Arrest" ....for the crime of treason google it! "A chilling report from the Foreign Military Intelligence Directorate (GRU) prepared for Prime Minister Putin warns today that United States President Barack Obama has had served on 14 US Governors National Security Letters (NSLs) warning that if their actions in attempting to form what are called State Defense Forces are not halted they will face “immediate” arrest for the crime of treason."...more OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353375721583-211</Id><Topic><Title>Four more years of President Obama</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1332707523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-03-25 16:32:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eat this, repugs. Or, do you need help having it shoved down your throats?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353375721583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:42:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353375941731-212</Id><Topic><Title>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks</Title><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375634349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumppp</Msg><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375941731</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:45:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353375981757-213</Id><Topic><Title>Teabagger Rage is SOOOOO Entertaining</Title><Username>biggusdikkus12</Username><Timestamp>1352422151245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 19:49:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at them work up a frenzy over what their idols sold them. What fools!</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353375981757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:46:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353376151546-214</Id><Topic><Title>Waste of meat Tea Bags: Your cause is lost. Go away, go home, go cry, GFY!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1349190237719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:03:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are most of the trailer trash Tea Party Soooooo Fat, we will lose money covering them for healthcare, they should pay by the pound...</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353376151546</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:49:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353376166932-215</Id><Topic><Title>Let's have a good laugh, and read what the fringe right sore losers post today. LMAO!!</Title><Username>oskarmeijer</Username><Timestamp>1353069346736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 07:35:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How clever. Cut and paste from Fox and then post it here. dumpofdogs*h*i*t* is such a waste of meat.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1353376166932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:49:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353377152586-216</Id><Topic><Title>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks</Title><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375634349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>......</Msg><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353377152586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:05:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353377181580-217</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Should be $12-$13 Right Now!!! Coming To Nearby Theatre Soon</Title><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353359151980</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 16:05:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>easy money.....20 in a year.13 in Jan.take your pick........</Msg><Username>embawaves</Username><Timestamp>1353377181580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:06:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353377607882-218</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ARREST THE DICTATOR NOW!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353377607882</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:13:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353377827527-219</Id><Title>took a $32,00 loss at $9.27</Title><Msg>I still hold some sub prime, some BSC, LEH, WM- big winners</Msg><Username>lost_it_all2</Username><Timestamp>1353377827527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:17:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353378690615-220</Id><Topic><Title>Bush And His GOP Made Friends With Moammar Kadafi, We Are Still Paying For That</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353375442002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:37:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am willing to bet there will be another Bush running for President within the next 8 Years. Bush, the family that just keeps giving and taking.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353378690615</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:31:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353378695258-221</Id><Title>Evangelicals, Brothel Owner, Conservatives</Title><Msg>and the fight over the future direction of the Republican Party. In the process, Mitt has been tossed into the dustbin of history by his party. This could mean they'll mandate both a defunding of planned parenthood and legalized brothels in every state for 2016.</Msg><Username>oldestnetsurfer</Username><Timestamp>1353378695258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:31:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353378780938-222</Id><Topic><Title>Evangelicals, Brothel Owner, Conservatives</Title><Username>oldestnetsurfer</Username><Timestamp>1353378695258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:31:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is not what I call a religion, it is just a social group looking to make some money.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1353378780938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353378840634-223</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A chilling report from the Foreign Military Intelligence Directorate (GRU) prepared for Prime Minister Putin warns today that United States President Barack Obama has had served on 14 US Governors National Security Letters (NSLs) warning that if their actions in attempting to form what are called State Defense Forces are not halted they will face “immediate” arrest for the crime of treason. The use of NSLs in the United States was authorized by the Patriot Act law enacted after the September 11, 2001 attacks and forbids anyone receiving them from even acknowledging their existence, and was reauthorized by Obama’s “rubberstamp” Congress this past February over the objections of both civil and human rights groups who warned they mimic similar type “government security notices” enacted under both the former German Nazi and Soviet Communist regimes. To the issue angering Obama against these State Governors, this report continues, is their attempt to reestablish what are called State Defense Forces which are described as follows: “State Defense Forces (SDF) (also known as State Guards, State Military Reserves, or State Militias) in the United States are military units that operate under the sole authority of a state government; they are not regulated by the National Guard Bureau nor are they part of the Army National Guard of the United States. State Defense Forces are authorized by state and federal law and are under the command of the governor of each state. State Defense Forces are distinct from their state’s National Guard in that they cannot become federal entities. The federal government recognizes State Defense Forces under 32 U.S.C. § 109 which provides that State Defense Forces as a whole may not be called, ordered, or drafted into the Armed Forces of the United States, thus preserving their separation from the National Guard.” Important to note is that Obama, as President of the United States is also its most powerful military leader known by the term of Commander in Chief, and is authorized by the Militia Act of 1903 to federalize his individual States National Guard Forces putting them under his command, something he does not have the power to do with State Defense Forces. Obama’s fear of these State Defense Forces, this report says, rests with his not having power over them, and with the bulk of the US Military Forces he does control being stretched to near breaking with the ongoing wars in Iraq and Afghanistan would leave these State military forces under the control of these Governors in “defacto control” of the United States. The two US Governors spearheading this rebellion against Obama, this report states, are the Republican opposition party Governors of Minnesota, Tim Pawlenty and Texas, Rick Perry; both of whom have a deep fear their President is destroying their Nation. Governor Pawlenty’s fear of Obama is that since he took office he has appeased America’s enemies while at the same time shunning some of America’s most stalwart allies, especially Israel. Governor Pawlenty recently castigated Obama for abandoning the US missile defense plan for Europe by saying, “The lessons of history are clear: Appeasement and weakness did not stop the Nazis, did not stop the Soviets, and did not stop the terrorists before 9/11. We must stand strong with allies like Israel and eastern Europe in the face of growing challenges to our national security.” Governor Perry has blasted Obama and warned his fellow Texans that the President is “hell bent on socialism” and is punishing his State by dumping tens-of-thousands of illegal Mexican immigrants into their cities and small towns. Governor Perry further warned Texans that that if “Barack Obama’s Washington doesn’t stop being so oppressive, Texans might feel compelled to renounce their American citizenry and secede from the union.” Note: Following the end of the Civil War the rights of the individual US States to succeed from the Union was heard by their Supreme Court in a case called Texas v. White (1869) and who ruled that the Constitution did not permit States to secede from the United States, and that the ordinances of secession, and all the acts of the legislatures within seceding States intended to give effect to such ordinances, were “absolutely null”.“through revolution, or through consent of the States.” However, the decision did allow some possibility of divisibility Obama, in fearing a revolution against him by the States, this report continues, has moved swiftly against them, including nationalizing nearly all National Guard Forces in Governor Pawlenty’s Minnesota in what is being described as their State’s largest call up of troops since World War II. Other reports coming from the United States are stating that Obama has also nationalized the National Guard forces in Georgia, Alabama, Kansas, and perhaps Texas too. Though Obama may have taken from these dissident States their National Guard forces, the Governors of the States of Alabama, Georgia, Louisiana, South Carolina, Tennessee, Texas, Virginia still have under their sole command their State Defense Forces to go against US Federal forces. Important to note in this report is its stating that there are no US laws prohibiting National Guard troops from also joining their State’s Defense Forces, but would create a dilemma for those soldiers should they be called to service by them both at the same time. This dilemma occurred for many American soldiers during their Civil War with the great majority of them choosing to serve their States instead of the Federal Government. To Governor Pawlenty’s fears of Obama appeasing America’s enemies, while at the same time harming its longstanding allies, their remains no doubt as during this past week alone he has put Israel’s security in grave danger by releasing previously classified US documents relating to their nuclear programme, while at the same time removing sanctions on Russian arms makers supplying Iran. And in a move that even Russian military analysts are calling “insane”, Obama this week said he has decided to pre-announce to the World once-secret American ballistic missile tests and satellite launches. To Governor Perry’s fears of Obama socializing the United States their remains no doubt either, and as we can read as reported yesterday by the USA Today News Service: “Paychecks from private business shrank to their smallest share of personal income in U.S. history during the first quarter of this year, a USA TODAY analysis of government data finds. At the same time, government-provided benefits — from Social Security, unemployment insurance, food stamps and other programs — rose to a record high during the first three months of 2010. Those records reflect a long-term trend accelerated by the recession and the federal stimulus program to counteract the downturn. The result is a major shift in the source of personal income from private wages to government programs.” And in an even worse move against his own people who are still struggling to survive the growing Global economic collapse, new reports from the United States are stating that a “secret” programme found hidden in Obama’s socialist healthcare law called the Community Living Assistance Services and Support Act (CLASS Act) is about to take from them another $150-$250 a month from their paychecks forcing tens of millions more of them into abject poverty and debt slavery. To the final outcome of these events it is not in our knowing, other than to remind these Americans of Dr. Igor Panarin’s 2008 prediction of the fate lying in store for them, and as we can read as reported by London’s Telegraph News Service in their article titled “US will collapse and break up, Russian analyst predicts”, and which says: “Igor Panarin, a professor at the Diplomatic Academy of the Russian foreign affairs ministry, said the economic turmoil in the US had confirmed his long-held belief that the country was heading for extinction in its present form. In an interview with the Russian newspaper Izvestia, he outlined how the US would divide along ethnic and cultural lines. They are: the Pacific coast with its growing Chinese population; the increasingly Hispanic South; independence-minded Texas; the Atlantic Coast; a central state with a large Native American population; and the northern states where – he maintains – Canadian influence is strong. Alaska could be claimed by Russia, he said, claiming that the region was “only granted on lease, after all”. He said the country’s break-up would be accelerated by rising unemployment and Americans losing their savings. “The dollar isn’t secured by anything. The country’s foreign debt has grown like an avalanche; this is a pyramid, which has to collapse,” said Prof Panarin.” And to those Americans believing they will be able to defend themselves against the fast approaching onslaught meant to destroy them they should think again, for even as these words are being written, Obama, through the United Nations, is preparing to disarm them all under the so called UN Treaty On Arms Control that he ordered his government to sign. The late great American dissident comedian George Carlin once said, “It’s called the American Dream because you have to be asleep to believe it”….one can only hope these poor souls will awaken from their long slumber before all is lost.</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353378840634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:34:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353378896565-224</Id><Title>Despite Their Best Efforts</Title><Msg>the regime has been unable to destroy bac. look for stock to steadily rise.</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1353378896565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:34:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379148687-225</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a TRAITOR. His usurped power won't last long.</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353379148687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379490551-226</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And to those Americans believing they will be able to defend themselves against the fast approaching onslaught meant to destroy them they should think again, for even as these words are being written, Obama, through the United Nations, is preparing to disarm them all under the so called UN Treaty On Arms Control that he ordered his government to sign." BRING IT ON KENYAN TRAITOR! I WILL NOT COMPLY!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353379490551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:44:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379678931-227</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy is so corrupt, he makes Nixon look like an angel. Obama and Hillary are in Burma, escaping the scorn of reporters and politicians seeking the truth. The truth will come out. The cover-up will not work. I hope Obama is exposed and impeached. He's inept.</Msg><Username>mgiuseff</Username><Timestamp>1353379678931</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:47:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379686083-228</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The use of NSLs in the United States was authorized by the Patriot Act law enacted after the September 11, 2001 attacks and forbids anyone receiving them from even acknowledging their existence, and was reauthorized by Obama’s “rubberstamp” Congress this past February over the objections of both civil and human rights groups who warned they mimic similar type “government security notices” enacted under both the former German Nazi and Soviet Communist regimes.</Msg><Username>naz1lover</Username><Timestamp>1353379686083</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353379735771-229</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey sheep i will meet you any time any place just let me know the place &amp; time I eat red necks for brunch . By the way there families have my heartfelt graditude &amp; condolences for their service and loss</Msg><Username>jpotatohart</Username><Timestamp>1353379735771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:48:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353380000221-230</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It occurred to me today that Obama is much like Napoleon. A person with an oversized ego, who wants to control others. I don't like the way they jailed the guy who created the video blamed for the Benghazi attack. He gets one year in a federal prison. He's guilty of expressing his first amendment right to free speech. And Benghazi, four dead Americans, killed by terrorists, and Obama walks around like nothing's happened. He will ultimately pay. So will Hillary. Harry Reid cannot stop this inquisition into what happened, or did not happen during those crucial hours in Benghazi.</Msg><Username>mgiuseff</Username><Timestamp>1353380000221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:53:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353380420788-231</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Inc. is using our own system against us! Obama is a TERRORIST. The law has now been ULTRA CORRUPTED to be used AGAINST THE CITIZENS of the UNITED STATES!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353380420788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:00:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353380569655-232</Id><Title>ANY BET ON BAC CROSSING $10 THIS WEEK</Title><Msg>MAYBE TOMORROW</Msg><Username>aju390hd</Username><Timestamp>1353380569655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353380975912-233</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol! rednecks? ... You're not worth the wasted lead Toby! If I were him I'd go take a #$%$ right now in memory of your worthless existence.</Msg><Username>hangatraitor</Username><Timestamp>1353380975912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:09:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353382182414-234</Id><Title>What would Travon say ?!?</Title><Msg>OUCH!! You just put a hole in my hoodie Bro !!</Msg><Username>wingman366</Username><Timestamp>1353382182414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353383383944-235</Id><Topic><Title>Obama tells people of Burma, U.S. 'is with you'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362889610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:08:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The country's official name is Myanmar, regardless of what other countries call it and whomever named it thus. By the way, the military junta 'stepped aside' last year and the government has "taken major steps toward easing repression and transitioning to democratic rule." "Visiting U.S. senators have used both names. Even at congressional hearings in Washington, there’s an occasional mention of “Myanmar.” (Washington Post). Still, I will concede that your post and reply had considerably more validity than your usual tripe. Keep up the good work!</Msg><Username>mixtli_speaks</Username><Timestamp>1353383383944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:49:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353383445174-236</Id><Title>Back to our regularly scheduled program...BAC</Title><Msg>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks (Bloomberg artical) Any thoughts to how much of that will be divedend and how much stock buy back?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353383445174</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:50:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353383620497-237</Id><Topic><Title>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks</Title><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375634349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.......</Msg><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353383620497</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:53:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353383935561-238</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No it is not a big deal. Only to you and the other fox regurgitators. WE ON THIS BAC MESSAGE BOARD DO NOT CARE ABOUT YOUR POLITICAL VIEWS!</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353383935561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 22:58:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353384044755-239</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are many that say 911 atttack on the worl trade center was an inside job. Does that make it true?</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1353384044755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353384090438-240</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol...what total made-up crapola. Did you know that only 13% of Americans, in a recent nationwide poll, believe you and your propagandists? Americans can tell phoney accusations and political back-stabbing when they see and hear it. Go spread your feecees on your cell walls, not here.</Msg><Username>tinkers_curse</Username><Timestamp>1353384090438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:01:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353384514391-241</Id><Topic><Title>The ugly truth about Benghazi and Team Obama</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1353362564977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 17:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What sheep-raping hypocrite you are. You dont want the truth, you swine, so don't pretend you do...you're just another slagging radical Repug so low and vicious you'll use any pretext, even feigning outrage, to score political points. Address this, you lying, conniving sob: The obstructionist 112th Congress is on record denying the State Department’s request for more money to secure America's overseas embassies. Democrats really need to remind the public of this each and every time one of these Republican hypocrites stand in from of a camera and attack the Obama administration. Last year, Secretary of State Hillary Clinton warned that Republicans’ proposed cuts to her department would be “detrimental to America’s national security”- a charge Republicans rejected at the time.</Msg><Username>tinkers_curse</Username><Timestamp>1353384514391</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:08:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353385307459-242</Id><Title>Liberals, vote for your favorite drink!</Title><Msg>1. Hatorade- I vote for Hatorade because it maintains my boiling hatred for anyone that isn't a Liberal Democrat. 2. Koolaid- I vote for Koolaid because it maintains my unquestioning faith to my Dear Leader no matter what he says or does.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1353385307459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:21:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353385687451-243</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's bold talk for a jumped up little nazi like you and your fellow rats. Stand up, and take your best shot. Oh, you prefer to talk trash in a chat room, li'l #$%$? LOL..you aint got the stones, or the conviction. Just yap yap. All the power of a tick.</Msg><Username>tinkers_curse</Username><Timestamp>1353385687451</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:28:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353385932940-244</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you live?</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353385932940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:32:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353386197169-245</Id><Topic><Title>BofA Seen Doling Out $10 Billion for Dividends, Buybacks</Title><Username>mashiach</Username><Timestamp>1353375634349</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bank of America Corp. (BAC), the top performer in the Dow Jones Industrial Average this year, may commit as much as $10 billion to dividends and share repurchases in 2013, said International Strategy &amp; Investment Group Inc. The lender has improved capital by the most among the biggest U.S. banks and could fare comparatively well after Federal Reserve stress tests, Ed Najarian, an ISI analyst, said yesterday in a research note. Bank of America may have the equivalent of about $30 billion in capital beyond the minimum required by regulators, he wrote. “We certainly don’t expect Bank of America to return anywhere near $30 billion in capital,” said Najarian, who has a buy rating on the Charlotte, North Carolina-based company. “We still think $5 billion to $10 billion in total dividends and stock buybacks is likely for 2013, which would still be an upside surprise versus Street expectations.” Bank of America’s dividend of 1 cent a share, smaller than the payouts of JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. (JPM) and Wells Fargo &amp; Co. (WFC), is a vestige of the duress the lender faced when it took $45 billion in U.S. bailouts after swallowing Countrywide Financial Corp. and Merrill Lynch &amp; Co. While the rescue was repaid in 2009, regulators haven’t allowed the firm to boost its dividend. Najarian, who had a hold rating on Bank of America since July 2010, upgraded the stock to buy this month, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. He said he expects the shares to hit $12 within a year. Bank of America climbed 4.1 percent to $9.49 in New York yesterday and has advanced 71 percent in 2012.</Msg><Username>tech8855</Username><Timestamp>1353386197169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:36:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353386871720-246</Id><Topic><Title>**DRAM $0.5 with $5 Market Cap is a Potential Multi-bagger......DRAM and AMD recently signed an agreement to launch an aggressive campaign to market all editions of AMD's Radeon RAMDiskAMD Memory modules for desktops......Per the agreement, DRAM will develop a special edition RAMDisk utility, which will be called AMD Radeon RAMDisk...... AMD Radeon RAMDisk loading times are expected to be 525% higher than those offered by conventional products.</Title><Username>heatwillfall</Username><Timestamp>1353094509598</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:35:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called MManipulation</Msg><Username>ntofive</Username><Timestamp>1353386871720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:47:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353386987566-247</Id><Topic><Title>WE NOW have a DICTATOR on our hands Folks!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353375655018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That little NUB lives in Obamao's back alley!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1353386987566</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:49:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353387584049-248</Id><Title>BAC and CXM for diversification</Title><Msg>Agree BAC &amp; possible double from here, but CXM better choice for 20 bagger at current levels with Phase lll for diabetic FDA mktg approval &amp; cardiovascular treatment and was "in play" today...</Msg><Username>eai_specialist</Username><Timestamp>1353387584049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 23:59:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>