<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343535489167-1</Id><Title>Wuss Willard won't win. No way!</Title><Msg>Who will all of the lying tea baggers bash once Obama is re-elected?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1343535489167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 00:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343537032704-2</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I explain it as the shorts collectively covered, took their profits, and then let off of shorting in order to allow the market to get back to a higher nicely shortable level again for double the profit another time around. That nonsense did not get stopped in its tracks until the SEC put into effect a functional uptick rule later in the 1930's. I don't think we will see much SIGNIFICANT improvement here again until a MULTICENT uptick rule is enacted again!!!! DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343537032704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 00:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343537458317-3</Id><Topic><Title>Wuss Willard won't win. No way!</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1343535489167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 00:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ODUMBA IS A BEAT MAN...I'VE GOT $5000 BET ON IT..LOL</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1343537458317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 00:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343556354616-4</Id><Title>Vets Treated like Disposable Trash</Title><Msg>The Vets should have equivalent health insurance to those of Congress members. Instead, they are offered subpar healthcare at VA clinics and hospital. The VA still has yet to transfer all Vets files to electronic files. A Vet can die by the time the VA finds his file.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343556354616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 06:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343563471891-5</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next week's meetings will supply enough catalysts to easily bring BAC back to $10. A beaten down stock with the latest "profitable" earnings has not other ways to go but up!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1343563471891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343565403249-6</Id><Topic><Title>does BAC own property at Circle 8, Bolgia 2? ROFLMFO</Title><Username>ekonprophet</Username><Timestamp>1343505898249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 16:04:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAC once had title to the place, but wrapped that dump in mortgaged-based securities and then dropped it on Countrywide. Have you seen their new digs near the 9th Street Bridge To Nowhere? They've even erected a toll booth. ROTFLMAO at desperate souls everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1343565403249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343565881930-7</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have something there! Good luck! DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343565881930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343566414726-8</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THERE SHOULD BE A MORATORIUM and FREEZE placed on those sophisticated complex derivatives and just stop the nonsense. This could easily be done through global accords. Case in point. Remember when the guy who invented "pyramid selling" was voted Business Man of the Year? Guess what, not long after that, the technique was made illegal. Just work on making complex opaque derivatives "illegal" and freeze them with a global moratorium where they are. That would have been better than all these bailouts and exponential growth to trillions of dollars of soverign debt growth. DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343566414726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343568876355-9</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"10K shares at 7.71 average and I am in no hurry. I would like the chance to buy more under 8.00 an preferably below my current average" You are not making any sense. BofA is already some 50 cents below your current average and under $8, so why are you not buying? Because you are full of it or just a plain idiot. Or perhpas both.</Msg><Username>clueless345</Username><Timestamp>1343568876355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 09:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343572182634-10</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think all the bank should be forced to divest there trading branches and put many of the old glsseagle act back into place. You want volitality buy a broker stock. Want slow steady increase in stock price and div buy a bank. That was the 1980's. Even the old Citi CEO is saying that down. I like BAC ( avergae below 7.00 a share) becouse they are working on the BALANCE SHEET. Under 7.00 the are a huge buy. We still could see as low #$%$50 a share if the markets really tank but I just dont see the 3.5-4.00 that some shorts are talking ( yes..3.50 a share !). They were right from 2007 thru 2010. With a few good plays in 2011 and 2012.) The 200 day average is now way down to 7.30 a share ! grief.</Msg><Username>tax1099nc</Username><Timestamp>1343572182634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343573019365-11</Id><Title>Will goup .40 this week</Title><Msg>BAC cut ATM machines at gas stations and other non profit locations. This will be the year BAC hits over $10.00. Weak hands are almost out of the stock and long term investors are buying. This stock Is for the long term investor and not the short term investor. If you can't take the ups and downs put your money in a safe CD. DD.</Msg><Username>catspaw33129</Username><Timestamp>1343573019365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343573343989-12</Id><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Msg>Consumers will not pay a credit card price for goods and services. Instead, consumers will revolt and go back to paying bills with cash. BAC stands to lose millions of dollars. Wise investors are aware of this, and this is one more reason why BAC stock has not taken off.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343574488531-13</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thats why cc volume is up 25%... note that del are down 25%... go figure.</Msg><Username>george.murphy3</Username><Timestamp>1343574488531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343576914377-14</Id><Title>QE3 PURE POLITICS AS STOCKS SURGE $1.5 TRIL ON QE2 EXCESS CASH</Title><Msg>I am always amazed that stock prices can easily surge trillions of dollars on HOPES of the Fed Res printing more free money via QE3 when the current trillion plus dollar stock surge proves there is a ton of EXCESS cash FLOODING the world already. World banks printed over $16 trillion in the past few years (this is equal to the total US economy), yet the jobless rate in US is 8.2% and 25% in some parts of Europe. Housing prices hardly budged over this time period. So what is the purpose of printing more money via QE3? Pure politics, if Bernake implements QE3 he will establish a new role for the Fed Res to manipulate US elections. Bernake already manipulates: interest rates, FX exchange rates by buying Euros and weakening the US dollar, stock market through buying bad mortgages at full price and easy money policy to banks that don't pass that benefit onto the public, buying $2 trillion US treasuries aka buying US debt and now manipulating election outcomes. Wow, is this still America?</Msg><Username>raebeht</Username><Timestamp>1343576914377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343579728533-15</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consumers do not know cash....</Msg><Username>sinfuel</Username><Timestamp>1343579728533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 12:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343580197405-16</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 PURE POLITICS AS STOCKS SURGE $1.5 TRIL ON QE2 EXCESS CASH</Title><Username>raebeht</Username><Timestamp>1343576914377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:48:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are two important things that keep the world go round; real estates and stocks. Real Estates will continue to depreciate if people's wealth (stocks) does not improve. Although it might sound artificial, the printing of money should ( "has to" might be better words) help create confidence and jobs for millions of suffering unemployed. Our current market is in the game of manipulations and the manipulations (to control inflation from going out of control again) will "eventually" put the world economy back in equalibrium. All and all, the government has no choice but to help the stock markets go up to keep real estates from dropping further. And letting dead beats( most of these people have nothing to contribute to the economy, financially) live for free and decreasing the balances of their mortgage is farthest away from fixing the real problem. Anways, if people's wealth can not be recouped from their 401k, IRAs and other private funds in stocks, then "the only choice" is to declare a nuclear war to clean up the mess we have created for ourselves based on greed. That of course, should not happen. Therefore, it is time for the stock market to "consistently" go up. Too many people have lost their life savings, spouses (due to divorces) and morality. We can no longer afford to bring home casualties if we let greedy and corrupted politicians ruin the world. Next Monday could be your last chance to own BAC at a huge discount because the future always depend on the success of banks. Own some BAC while interest rates are still low. Because when they go up, your bank stocks will quadriple in value!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1343580197405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 12:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343581126344-17</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong again! In this economy, people are more dependent on credit cards. They need it to pay their other bills by making minimum payments (banks win). Unlike real estates, they have to pay on time or their credit cards will close permanently; giving them no other chances to find a new start (like finding a job, buying time to save their house or rental housings). Good luck spreading negativtity around the world. If not already, you will be the first to be forgotten.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1343581126344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 12:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343581438131-18</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, really? Millions??? Let me see, for a company with BAC's size, how small of a fraction of a part of a percent is that? IT IS NOTHING!!! It is your hapless speculation. No, I take that back, it is not even speculation, it is a BAC hater fabricating a reason to bash, and it is not a factor for where BAC pps is. It is the economy, the fiscal cliff and the EU - every expert says that, nobody who knows anything says the stupid stuff you say.THE BOTTOM LINE IS THAT CREDIT CARD FEES WILL NOT HURT BAC ONE BIT BECAUSE 1)THE CONSUMERS WHO HAVE NO CASH AND LIVE ON CREDIT WILL CONTINUE TO DO SO AND HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO PAY THE FEES, AND 2) THOSE WITH MONEY WHO PAY OFF THIER CC BILLS EACH MONTH WON'T CARE ABOUT THE SILLY FEE. GOOD FOR BAC IF THEY LOSE MORE DEADBEAT CUSTOMERS AND KEEP CUSTOMERS THAT PAY THEIR BILLS. THIS WILL INCREASE BAC PROFITS!!!! CREDIT UNIONS ARE ALREADY FEELING THE HURT FROM DEADBEAT CUSTOMERS WHO HAVE LEFT COMMERCIAL BANKS.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343581438131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 13:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343581521819-19</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Barron's this weekend: "Market fundamentals, including earnings, are mixed, but hope for stimulus is high now, says Michael Yoshikami, chief executive officer of Destination Wealth Management. "QE3 is coming," he adds. Indeed, there is a strong dread among institutional investors in particular of being out of the market ahead of such easing moves." QE3 can happen, and it will.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343581521819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 13:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343586071359-20</Id><Title>The QE's are the Fed's rather pitiful attempts to offset</Title><Msg>a little of the demand lost to crashed home equities. Like spitting into the wind. Meanwhile, the Republicans in Congress refuse to allow any meaningful fiscal stimulus, beyond that which was necessary to bail out bank managements and creditors. The U.S. is Japan in '95 and, in the end, our stock market will perform about like their's has. We pretty much followed Keynesian theory though the '90's. Remember how Clinton and the Republican Congress were paying down the deficit during the good times. Then that became politically inexpedient for the right who incurred gov debt to cut taxes and wage silly wars during the housing boom and now refuse to borrow, even at negative real interest rates, to mitigate the bust. Turns out that Maynard was a smart guy.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1343586071359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 14:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343597565339-21</Id><Topic><Title>Sister In Law Hasnt paid her BAC mortgage in 5 years in NY....still no foreclosure</Title><Username>lawyerreviews9</Username><Timestamp>1343530757182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is exactly what is wrong with the economy. You have a bunch of dead beats that are living for free, while hard working people are still struggling to pay their bills on time. All these dead beats are better off than the ones that are responsible, that is just not right! I may end up voting for Romney is this #$%$ keeps up. The banks need to forclose and get it over with, period!</Msg><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1343597565339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 17:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343601870957-22</Id><Title>THE SUPREME COURT IS COMPLETELY POLITICAL</Title><Msg>It is amazing how each Supreme Court member, is always telling the American Public how politics does not enter into their decisions. If that was true, then most rulings should be 9-0 for, or against any legal issue brought before it. I can see 8-1, or 8-2 because the law can be construed somewhat differently between the members BUT 5-4, ON ALMOST EVERY CASE? IF THEY ARE LOOKING AT THE SAME LAW, WITHOUT PREJUDICE OR POLITICAL JUDGEMENT, THEN THE OUTCOME SHOULD BE THE SAME FOR ALMOST ALL OF THEM. THEY ARE AS FARCICAL AS THE CONGRESS OR THE PRESIDENT.</Msg><Username>collieman83</Username><Timestamp>1343601870957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 18:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343602810443-23</Id><Topic><Title>Vets Treated like Disposable Trash</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343556354616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 06:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead of giving Vets what Congress has, how about give Congress what the Vets have? I think if Congress had the same as the Vets, they would fix the VA and provide Vets with better quality care. Vets deserve the best.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343602810443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 19:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343603913102-24</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday traderx asked fans shorted at $7.11, today hsi fans are crying</Title><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1343317032897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tardx is a pathetic lying poser with no life, no money, and no brains. I feel sorry for him really. Trust me his 100 dollar option bet was made way before 7.11 and he will lie his way out and be foolish enough to think he is believed.</Msg><Username>inowhourviv</Username><Timestamp>1343603913102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 19:18:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343604285825-25</Id><Topic><Title>traderx and brazentrader are the same person...</Title><Username>kds5862</Username><Timestamp>1343168605369</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:23:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except if the price rips up then brazentardlez is suddenly long LOL. The fun and lies never end with our resident blind squirrel!</Msg><Username>ispyafake11</Username><Timestamp>1343604285825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 19:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343607738461-26</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Stands to Lose Millions over Credit Card Ruling</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343573343989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:49:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's a heap of cash</Msg><Username>lenelifty</Username><Timestamp>1343607738461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 20:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343609678961-27</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qe1 an 2 has a lot to do with the markets recovering pps. if romney wins i expect financials to do much better as over regulation will be slowed and if the senate also goes republican then i expect the rise will be quick and hard. if obummer is re-elected then i am afraid bac and financials are doomed to muttle thru another 4 yrs. a lot at stake in this election. jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1343609678961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 20:54:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343609704669-28</Id><Topic><Title>Shhhhh! Heh, heh, heh! I was at Park City, Utah, and I donated a trillion dollars to Mitty's campaign...</Title><Username>dawgeeeeedawg</Username><Timestamp>1341835324449</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-09 08:02:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The trailer trash fund contributed some surplus Velveeta and some food stamps.</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1343609704669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 20:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>