<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343473909459-1</Id><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Msg>When fanny and freddy come to court with their bundles. There will be a lot of houses from 2006 that mortgages had been made on for 2 years or more and then the owners lost their jobs.I hope bac will contest this hard. Bac did the gov. a favour buying C. W. It seems to me that now this beat up bank needs some help.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343475236945-2</Id><Topic><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sem to know a lot BACon. i was curious why do they have asset being placed in their name by the bank of NY mellon??? i was also curious about the name- is bac= bacon =a slaughtered pig??? and do they want bac to fail for a reason???</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1343475236945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343475316785-3</Id><Topic><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>was this another civil war matter- teach them good Ole boys not to mess with wall street?</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1343475316785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343476475562-4</Id><Title>BAC has the San Fernando Valley Cramps</Title><Msg>"It spells Rolaids."</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343476475562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343476598318-5</Id><Title>Yahoo's IP Blocking Does not Work</Title><Msg>One only need to use a proxy server which generates endless IP addresses.</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1343476598318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:56:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343477196008-6</Id><Title>Flipper</Title><Msg>Flipper once again proved that he has no business running a Kool-Aid stand much less than a country. He proved he has NO ability in international affairs. He states something and then flips 180 degrees since his people let him know it was a #$%$ remark. He says he should be President since he has Business experience, but all he did was use his Dads Millions to buy a Co. that even he says he made no decession on, even though he was owner and CEO [ so either he lied or was responsible for closing American Plants to send them offshore]. He lobbied for millions for the Games in Salt Lake and managed nothing. He spends more on a horse than most Americans make in a year. He was able to afford the best in treatment for his wifes MS , but wants everyone who is not rich to die if they become sick. He hides his millions offshore so that he pays less tax than a worker at Burger King. He refuses to release tax records , but since it would prove he is a crook you can't blame him for that. He panders to a radical base who has more in common with the Klan than anything else, he degrades women who have the brains and will to be successful, he thinks blacks are subhuman, but this is due to his religion that tought him this was true. He biggest donors are crooks with ties to the Mob in China. He thinks its ok that people can buy assult wepoons and massive amounts of ammo on the internet with no controls and takes the insane position that #$%$ happens when people are killed by a nut case who was able to purchase enough arms to supply a small army. Of course his toothless /brainless bases thinks he is the guy for the job, but of course they also think its ok to marry your sister,. So Flipper who has no lasting values, who has no concept of what the average American faces, who only cares for the Rich and himself, and is the choice of the Republican Nazi party and their Pee Party Base. His OWNERS are spending a Billion $ to try and get him elected, but are worried that Americans may not be a dumb as they once thought and are able to see what Flipper really is a pampered Rich boy willing to sell out to the higgest bidder.</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1343477196008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343478209182-7</Id><Topic><Title>Article About BAC's Future Prospect Updated</Title><Username>Neil_Hollands_Uncle</Username><Timestamp>1334606444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-04-16 16:00:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the best article about Bank of America out there right now. Really hits the points regarding what should affect BAC's stock price going forward. It's a tug-of-war!</Msg><Username>luvfloydc</Username><Timestamp>1343478209182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343478327801-8</Id><Topic><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jim. quit scaring them... it is time to let them decide.. it is sad they will probably chose the carrot that always proceeds them.. but Now it is their decision... it always has been</Msg><Username>franklincarter95</Username><Timestamp>1343478327801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343480151271-9</Id><Topic><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't interesting that Sandy Weill came to the revelation that the big banks need to be broken up so that their not to large to fail. Isn't he the same one that pushed for repeal of Glass Stegal (S) so the big banks could get more speculative when he headed up Citi? Boy that worked out well. What a mess.</Msg><Username>bookerone2000</Username><Timestamp>1343480151271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343484982806-10</Id><Topic><Title>Reverse stock split 1-2 ?</Title><Username>gordon939</Username><Timestamp>1237419195000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2009-03-18 19:33:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I acknowledge your above message but don't understand how reverse splits are indicators of bullishness for the stock. Could you explain more??</Msg><Username>lucky.ecv13</Username><Timestamp>1343484982806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343486430268-11</Id><Topic><Title>Flipper</Title><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1343477196008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:06:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He panders to a radical base who has more in common with the Klan than anything else." This is the most disturbing thing about Mitt. He needs to condemn the lying Tea Bagger / KKK / Birther elements, but embraces their nazi stupidity instead.</Msg><Username>urbansquall</Username><Timestamp>1343486430268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 10:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343488391016-12</Id><Topic><Title>explain why S&amp;P cuts all ratings on Canadians Banks but not US Banks lately??</Title><Username>sushibn</Username><Timestamp>1343478281170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:24:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple, the ratings agencies do not know what they are doing.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1343488391016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343488574791-13</Id><Topic><Title>Flipper</Title><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1343477196008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:06:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flipper was a good choice. He has no chance of winning.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1343488574791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343490099779-14</Id><Title>Student Loan Debt up 275% since 2010</Title><Msg>and Obama wants even more. Sound familiar? Obama worked for Acorn pushing people into homes who couldn't afford them and well we know how that ended.</Msg><Username>ralph6741</Username><Timestamp>1343490099779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343492671316-15</Id><Title>the plan</Title><Msg>The more Obama can enslave people in poverty the more secured voters he hands over to the Democratic party…that’s the plan…this is the inter circles strategy and will be the death blow to the Republican party if accomplished . Straying off the teleprompter gave people the chance to see the real Obama. In 09 when Steve Job’s of Apple sat down with Obama and discussed getting Apple’s production back to American soil, Jobs came out of that meeting and said “he doesn’t have a clue”. Obama thought he could get another out of touch elitist to spew the same nonsense, “ spread the wealth” which translates into “ bring me all your money and I’ll decide how is spent and who it is spent on”.. What Obama failed to realize was that Steve Job’s started in his parent’s garage and worked long hard hours building a business. Apple was on the brink of bankruptcy in 1999, Steve came back as CEO and burned the midnight oil and history was made. Steve Job’s knew it took hard work to become successful and he was not about to let some community organizer convince him otherwise. It’s about being competitive and right now we are not competitive. HOPE IS GONE…AND WE NEED A CHANGE.</Msg><Username>frank55rea</Username><Timestamp>1343492671316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343496150433-16</Id><Topic><Title>Flipper</Title><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1343477196008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:06:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without them he has no chance. Republicans are a dead party without the fringe right. Just a bunch of rich guys trying to find some votes they can by with social issues.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1343496150433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 13:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343499861166-17</Id><Topic><Title>Article About BAC's Future Prospect Updated</Title><Username>Neil_Hollands_Uncle</Username><Timestamp>1334606444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-04-16 16:00:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Written by an unknown person with no professional qualifications. It may be a good summary, but it is not original, just someone compiling what they've read from real experts on both sides of the BAC issue.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343499861166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343504105440-18</Id><Topic><Title>THE GDP FALLS AND THE MARKET BOOMS</Title><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1343433096556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 19:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a good memory old timer, LOL</Msg><Username>barackobammy</Username><Timestamp>1343504105440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 15:35:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343504906672-19</Id><Title>ROMNEY NOW HAS A 4% LEAD OVER OBAMA</Title><Msg>DON'T YOU JUST LOVE IT!!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1343504906672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 15:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343507446402-20</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY NOW HAS A 4% LEAD OVER OBAMA</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1343504906672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 15:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No student who cannot find a job is going to vote for Mr. O.</Msg><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1343507446402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 16:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343509615242-21</Id><Topic><Title>How would you rule?</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343473909459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope the lawyers for bac convince the courts that two wrongs will not make it right.I am long but if they do not treat us fairly a precident will be set, and the rest of the vultures will smell blood. DESPITE what the gov.says Iam sure there will be more money coming and half will go to towards housing.GL</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343509615242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 17:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343514520264-22</Id><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Msg>QE3 won't happen at all. Look up interest rate swaps and tell me how QE3 can come in? If money comes out of the bonds and into stocks, yield of the bonds will rise. If yields the bonds, the bonds value goes down. Therefore, the balance sheets of the banks would be destroyed because they would lose values on their bond holdings. Also, there is 300 trillion of interest rate swaps that would be destroyed if yield rise dramatically causing the end game. How can QE3 come? I don't see it.</Msg><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343515506413-23</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you listen to cnbc,they are expecting it soon.I believe it will happen and I also believe it will be a huge world wide coordinated event. A lot of gold stocks jumped this week as they expect also.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1343515506413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343515930877-24</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your point and I tend to agree. A short term fix for a long term disaster.</Msg><Username>waitingtilldawn</Username><Timestamp>1343515930877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343519904569-25</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes it can, and it will.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343519904569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 19:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343527126945-26</Id><Title>The story of pathetic lending practices of B of A</Title><Msg>I am purchasing a home. It is a duplex and I applied for a loan with Bank of America (James McKibban is my loan officer - he is at 949.302.6620). They sent an appraiser to the property and after he did the appraisal he apparently called the officer and said, hey, this is not a true single family residence, I am not qualified to do this appraisal. So, James emails my real estate broker and says, we need a new appraisal. My broker emails back and says, what, the guy just completed the gig, what are you talking about. James says, I will get back to you. So one of James's assistants emails my broker a few days later and says, we need a new appraisal, to which my broker responds, there was already and appraisal done, and my broker also emails James asking if there is a problem. James responds (and this is the money email) that there is no problem, the loan is moving right along. Well, there were some other small problems (I will detail those in a separate email, but suffice it to say thta Ms. Stephanie Gallegos of the Plano Fulfillment Center m - 972-244-4555 is not up to her job when it comes to documents), and i actually had to get a rep from Mr. Moynihan's office involved. This woman - she should be made CEO - got the doucment problem cleared up (her name is Tywanna Levine). With the document issued cleared up, James informs us that there is a problem, that 3 days before closing, there is no appraisal. We (my broker and I) call James and he abruptly quits working, tells us to call someone else, he cannot take the abuse. So we get Sam Cruz involved. This is on Thursday morning, with the closing to take place Tuesday. Sam tells me flat out, there is no appraisal in the file, that James cancelled the first one, and never ordered a second (well, really first, appraisal). At this point, I involve another rep from corporate and the story will continue tomorrow, but if you are a BAC stockholder, I just think you should know why BAC is not making any money off of its lending, while Chase, Wells Fargo, Citibank, and City Nationaly Bank are eating its breakfast. It is due to employees not doing the most basic part of their checklist, like having an appraisal at the ready well in advance of the close. To Be Continued ....</Msg><Username>sellbullion</Username><Timestamp>1343527126945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 21:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343527640020-27</Id><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Msg>This is here at 7.31 rather than 9.71 or 10.00 or ?15.00 because it has been shorted down here and scared longs selling down to here. There is no sound reason why it was 9.71 last year Q2 post reporting with 10 plus billion dollar reported Q2 loss and only 7.31 a share this year Q2 post reporting with 1.4 billion dollar operating income gain!!!! Total nonsense. H E L L O......??????? TIME SOMEBODY REALIZED THIS BAC IS BEYOND RIPE FOR A SHORT SQUEEZE ! DYODD JMHO</Msg><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343528446547-28</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy and hold! I love it! I got 10K shares at 7.71 average and I am in no hurry. I would like the chance to buy more under 8.00 an preferably below my current average.</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1343528446547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:20:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343530757182-29</Id><Title>Sister In Law Hasnt paid her BAC mortgage in 5 years in NY....still no foreclosure</Title><Msg>Guess they dont have the note??BAC seems to be giving away free houses. we need to break up the big banks.</Msg><Username>lawyerreviews9</Username><Timestamp>1343530757182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343531202733-30</Id><Topic><Title>QE3 CAN'T HAPPEN!!!!</Title><Username>tobigtofail</Username><Timestamp>1343514520264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 18:28:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>QE3 BUYS bonds...that is the point of QE. To supress real interest rates. U got it all #$%$ backwards.</Msg><Username>lawyerreviews9</Username><Timestamp>1343531202733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343532818512-31</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'd better make a study of markets. Just one example. How do you explain that after the 1929 crash, the stock market regained 50% of the loss in the next year, with many companies getting back to there highs, even though their earnings kept on falling? History is replete with the stock market, and stocks doing just the opposite of the economy.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1343532818512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343533069578-32</Id><Title>Questions for SW…………</Title><Msg>I see your dumpobamie is out now? Is buckydoodle now your favorite? Where's zevoter? C'mon man, break out a few more that you can converse with your self even more! Me thinks you may have "multiple personality disorder", SW... you may want to get yourself checked out by a qualified health care professional soon. In order for to be taken seriously, SW, you need to answer a few questions, otherwise everything you post will be taken as nonsense: How long have you been pretending to be a veteran? (You know, your "kingofvietnam" id...) Is that why your kweer life partner left you? Did he notice your fudge chute was always full of Masonberry jam? How many browsers you got open? How many trousers you got open? How many of your ids are currently signed in to yahoo at this moment? How many of those ids are you using to converse with yourself? How do you spell "loser""? How do you get dumpobamie to lick all of that splurt off of your face? How can you spend all day licking my crack? And...what's the difference between a "bung diving crack licker" and a "skinflute player"? And finally, given all the above, how can ANYTHING you post ANYWHERE be taken seriously, SW? LMFAO Later... SW_FuxRatz</Msg><Username>sw_fuxratz</Username><Timestamp>1343533069578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343533689306-33</Id><Topic><Title>HOW STUPID IS THIS? BAC $9.71 last year with 10.3 billion Q2 loss and $7.31 this yr with 1.4 billion Q2 GAIN!!!</Title><Username>bluesky_there_to_here</Username><Timestamp>1343527640020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 22:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem with ALLLLL the banks is that they have a QUADRILLION hole in derivatives off balance sheet. Fiat money is going down. Bitchez!</Msg><Username>lawyerreviews9</Username><Timestamp>1343533689306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>