<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344744161399-1</Id><Topic><Title>Biden to Ryan: "Congessman Ryan, you're no Jack Kennedy!"</Title><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1344743316478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 23:48:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and I predict that 'Voodoo Economics' is going to be making the rounds again, too. ROTFLMAO at a guy who's interested in getting over on old ladies being compared to ANY Kennedy.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344744161399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344744783735-2</Id><Title>I'm Watching Fox News... Ha ha ha!</Title><Msg>Funny how they seem energized... all of below ave. intelligence in these U.S.A. It's interesting to see what happens to human beings who are brought in an affluent society and the generations that grow in easy conditions. It's interesting to watch the human species under various conditions and circumstances and see how they react.... and had it not been than the U.S. was bringing in the best motivated from AROUND the WORLD... it would never be the best nation in the world! Human species are what the conditions happen to be where they're born. No challenge when things are too easy and their motivation is not challenged. I know that from my own offspring who lack all motivations when I came specifically to this country for growth in all areas of what I seeked in my utterly poverty stricken upbringing and dire conditions abroad. America still can go on if they continue the smart policy of sucking all the motivated minds from around the world. But if it fails to do that... the road will be tough and downward in the years to come. I happen to know both given my own circumstaces and what I have experienced in my own life rising from utter poverty to a quite satisfactory life with a son born in affluence here in the U.S., who at age 39, is still dependent on my own income for his livelihood. The human condition is quite clear and alive here in my own life!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344744783735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745227763-3</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Watching Fox News... Ha ha ha!</Title><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344744783735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I meant to say is that these GOP fellows pushing their agenda on Fox News are a misguided group and they are up against a great tide of REALITY that sloganeering and lies are not going to work... like it used to... for many decades! They are going to face the reality that times are a changing... flag waving and lies and sloganeering are not working like they used to... just a decade ago... Truth will emerge much faster in our modern day reality than they were used to like before. These folks are not only slow learners... but they are NO LEARNERS!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344745227763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745443531-4</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama has been Prez for 4yrs his policies should have worked by now instead of this stagnation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344720382124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comparing the times like that is a sign of ignorance of the reality of the times. You must be a blind follower of party... it doesn't matter what party for that matter. A mental dwarf, I should add!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344745443531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745542364-5</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama has been Prez for 4yrs his policies should have worked by now instead of this stagnation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344720382124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The economic conditions were far far worse then. There were no emerging markets back then to carry us. The only growth has been emerging markets the last few years or the economy would be even worse. Obama's economic policies have been a complete and utter failure.. Gdp under reagan 83-84 approx 7% Obama 2% Job growth: So in 15 months in 1983-84 job growth was 4,655,000, while in the comparable 15 months in 2011-12 it was 2,475,000, just a little more than half as many, and while the nation’s population has risen 33%, from 236,348,000 in 1984 to 313.417,000 today (according to the Census Bureau).</Msg><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745542364</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:25:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745696363-6</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Watching Fox News... Ha ha ha!</Title><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344744783735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you should know about dependency then. This welfare state built on borrowed dollars is destructive to the human spirit and has a nasty endpoint in terms of crippling debt</Msg><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745696363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344745781427-7</Id><Title>Obama has created an Government Run Enslaved Society</Title><Msg>Your gov't support check is in the mail</Msg><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745781427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344745859603-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has created an Government Run Enslaved Society</Title><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745781427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know what you're talking about, ah!</Msg><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344745859603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344746206814-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has created an Government Run Enslaved Society</Title><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745781427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the numbers, more people on government assistance than at any point in US history and all on borrowed dollars. "The federal government administers nearly 80 different overlapping federal means-tested welfare programs," the Senate Budget Committee notes. However, the committee states, the figures used in the chart do not include those who are only benefiting from Social Security and/or Medicare. Food stamps and Medicaid make up a large--and growing--chunk of the more than 100 million recipients. "Among the major means tested welfare programs, since 2000 Medicaid has increased from 34 million people to 54 million in 2011 and the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP, or food stamps) from 17 million to 45 million in 2011," says the Senate Budget Committee. "Spending on food stamps alone is projected to reach $800 billion over the next decade." The data come "from the U.S. Census’s Survey of Income and Program Participation shows that nearly 110,000 million individuals received a welfare benefit in 2011. (These figures do not include other means-tested benefits such as the Earned Income Tax Credit or the health insurance premium subsidies included in the President’s health care law. CBO estimates that the premium subsidies, scheduled to begin in 2014, will cover at least 25 million individuals by the end of the decade.)" This is not just Americans, however. "These figures include not only citizens, but non-citizens as well," according to the committee.</Msg><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344746206814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344751195209-10</Id><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Msg>Great leader, like Romney makes wise choices. Paul Ryan reminded me of President Ronald Reagan. Fiscally disciplined and belived in a Stronger America. Watch out for China as those SOBS already intended the entire Pacific belongs to them.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344762124865-11</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama has been Prez for 4yrs his policies should have worked by now instead of this stagnation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344720382124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Volker got us out of stagflation then Reagan tripled the national debt. Tax Cuts or Tax Redistribution? When all was said and done, the total tax burden imposed on the American people from all sources—state and local taxes, federal income and capital gains taxes, and payroll taxes—remained basically unchanged throughout the 1980s. In the end, Reagan's reputation as a tax-cutter far outran his actual performance. Reagan's tax policies did, however, redistribute the tax burden significantly, even if they failed to reduce it overall. By cutting income taxes, which are paid at a higher rate by the wealthy, while increasing payroll taxes, which are paid at a higher rate by the working poor and middle class, Reagan shifted the tax burden down the income scale. During the 1980s, the total effective federal taxation rate for the poorest one-fifth of American families actually increased by more than 16%. By contrast, the effective taxation rate for the wealthiest one-fifth of families fell by 5.5%, and the richest one percent of Americans saved even more: their tax rate fell by 14.4%.25 Small-Government Values vs. Big Government Spending Reagan's failure to truly reduce taxes for most Americans was mirrored by a failure to restrain government spending. Reagan ran for office in 1980 as a harsh critic of "tax and spend" liberalism, vowing as president to shrink the size of the government by slashing federal spending. Once in office, however, Reagan found it impossible to deliver on his promises. The largest chunk of the federal budget went to pay for Social Security and Medicare, which provide retirement income and health care for the elderly, and which are the two most popular government social programs in American history. While Reagan had long criticized both, he found it politically impossible to dismantle them. After Social Security and Medicare, the next largest government expense was the military—and Reagan, a staunch Cold Warrior, never considered cutting defense spending and instead increased it substantially. "Defense is not a budget item," he told planners at the Pentagon. "You spend what you need."26 With Social Security, Medicare, and defense all off the table, there just wasn't much left to cut; those three programs, combined with unavoidable payments on the national debt, accounted for fully 85% of the federal budget during Reagan's presidency. Congressional Democrats had little interest in slashing away at the remaining 15% (which included many liberal social programs instituted by Franklin Roosevelt's New Deal and Lyndon Johnson's Great Society), and Reagan never really went to the mat politically to try to force them to do so. As a result, total government spending continued to rise. "Mortgaging Our Future and Our Children's Future" Reagan's presidency produced huge annual federal budget deficits of more than $100 billion —the equivalent of about $200 billion today. It was an ironic result for a man who had spent his entire political career criticizing deficit spending by the government. "For decades we have piled deficit upon deficit," he said in his first inaugural address, "mortgaging our future and our children's future for the temporary convenience of the present. To continue this long trend is to guarantee tremendous social, cultural, political, and economic upheavals." Yet the national debt tripled under Reagan's watch, reaching a staggering $2.7 trillion by the time he left office. Ironically, the government's gargantuan deficit spending during the 1980s ended up providing exactly the same kind of Keynesian stimulus to the national economy that Franklin Roosevelt's New Deal had provided during the Great Depression.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344762124865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 05:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344762261453-12</Id><Topic><Title>So Obama has been Prez for 4yrs his policies should have worked by now instead of this stagnation</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344720382124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:26:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagans answer was a large dose of borrowed money. Deregulation gave you the savings and loan crisis just like it gave you the banking crisis and the housing crisis.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344762261453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 05:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344762574430-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has created an Government Run Enslaved Society</Title><Username>eat_shit.pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1344745781427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's because it's the only life style that he knows, when he went to college, he was on the tax payers dime, community organizer, tax payers dime, congressman, off the tax payers, senator tax payers, and now prez. tax payers , tax payers have got all kinds of money to blow and now he is going to tax the hell out of us more, (and by out of us I don't mean the so called rich be cause they'll just pass it on to everybody else, I thought you learned that in high school, he went to Harvard and still knows nothing) , for mo money, mo money, mo money . what else does he know.</Msg><Username>montyprython</Username><Timestamp>1344762574430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 05:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344763095944-14</Id><Topic><Title>a record 6 Trillion added to the Debt by Obama and still no hope and change</Title><Username>dr_james391</Username><Timestamp>1344701258064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan, i guess you were talking about all those shovel-ready projects, that didn't happen. wonder were all that money went?</Msg><Username>montyprython</Username><Timestamp>1344763095944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 05:18:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344763696806-15</Id><Topic><Title>I'm Watching Fox News... Ha ha ha!</Title><Username>johnmjay</Username><Timestamp>1344744783735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This country is in much worst shape than Greece, the only difference between us and Greece is that we're printing money everyday and they can't and after four years obama isn't the guy to fix this problem. just doesn't have a clue.</Msg><Username>montyprython</Username><Timestamp>1344763696806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 05:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344772637900-16</Id><Topic><Title>TOP REPUBLICAN...ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION WITH RYAN</Title><Username>dexter.jerusalen</Username><Timestamp>1344769142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 06:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dixter, your lobo is scheduled for 10 am today. Please do not jerk off more than twice before then. Your post counts as one.</Msg><Username>shutter_islandward8</Username><Timestamp>1344772637900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 07:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344772890000-17</Id><Title>What you get when you put a Democrat carpet muncher in a position of authority.</Title><Msg>A longtime special agent in the Department of Homeland Security has filed a salacious discrimination lawsuit, saying he was shoved aside in favor of a woman with ties to DHS Secretary Janet Napolitano -- who the suit claims presided over a female "frat-house"-style department that routinely humiliated male staffers.</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344772890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344774427169-18</Id><Title>Daddy-Mr. Fartaway-Now I know why they call u handsome!</Title><Msg>When three people have sex, it's called a threesome. When two people have sex, it's called a twosome. Now I know why they call u handsome!!!</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344774427169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344774676577-19</Id><Topic><Title>Daddy-Mr. Fartaway-Now I know why they call u handsome!</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344774427169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And when four or more Democrats have sex, it's called a circle jerk.</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344774676577</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344775802871-20</Id><Topic><Title>What you get when you put a Democrat carpet muncher in a position of authority.</Title><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344772890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Golly ned....looks like he can dish it out but he can't take it.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1344775802871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344776047528-21</Id><Topic><Title>What you get when you put a Democrat carpet muncher in a position of authority.</Title><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344772890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like you, I daresay.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1344776047528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344776215293-22</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON GAVE BUSH A SURPLUS... 23 MIL. JOBS. THEN WHAT HAPPENED IN 8 YEARS</Title><Username>dexter.jerusalen</Username><Timestamp>1344769044006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 06:57:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny....about 9/11 EVERYone wanted to go after the perpetrators. I guess you weren't here.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1344776215293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344777565485-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey= show USA your taxes,,what are you hiding???</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344775096877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHY - show you anything - your mind is set on voting Democratic any how - so be it it is futher realized - that if you used your head - if he had not paid any taxes - failed to file proper returns - the IRS - would have nailed him by now - as well as the liberal media .!! he used the tax codes to his benifit - the same as everyone else .! now what is wrong his rich - so is obama - 13 million last year . an he uses the tax codes his benefit .! obama is just jealous - mitt is richer than obama .!!!!!!!!!!!! whoope</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344777565485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344777754541-24</Id><Topic><Title>Lets dismantle USA and have MORE WARS =VOTE GOP</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344775024684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:37:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess when - fellow amecians got killed on 9-11 - you just did not give a dang about them - eh .!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344777754541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344779360905-25</Id><Topic><Title>Liar lib leftist telling lies and denying truths conservatives posted today. Read their posts, reveals ever increasing anxiety and desperation. Now they are saying that swing states are going with Teflon Obam when in fact the swing states are split. Lie all you want, liar libs, it won't change the facts.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344729960745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your 100% right !!! do you realize that most of these fools will never see another dummycrapper in the white house in their live time..8 years for Romney and 8 for Ryan!!! that's 16 years and these lib turds will all be dead!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344779360905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:49:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344779685381-26</Id><Title>MOST of the lying lib turds will never see another dummycrapper in the white house!!!</Title><Msg>8 years for Romney and 8 years for Ryan and it's over for millions of the old crapper party..it's over crappers!!! ILMFAO</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344779685381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 09:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344780220094-27</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON GAVE BUSH A SURPLUS... 23 MIL. JOBS. THEN WHAT HAPPENED IN 8 YEARS</Title><Username>dexter.jerusalen</Username><Timestamp>1344769044006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 06:57:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Donut you seem to forget who the perpetrators were and who we went after. Weren't you here? I know, you don't have TV but Kents summary every week ought to have kept you informed.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344780220094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344780316182-28</Id><Topic><Title>TOP REPUBLICAN...ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION WITH RYAN</Title><Username>dexter.jerusalen</Username><Timestamp>1344769142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 06:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another food stamper that can't read of write...watch fox fool and bet your food stamps..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344780316182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344780630744-29</Id><Topic><Title>What you get when you put a Democrat carpet muncher in a position of authority.</Title><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344772890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what evidence can you provide that she is gay? No one else has found any.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344780630744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344780665283-30</Id><Topic><Title>Daddy-Mr. Fartaway-Now I know why they call u handsome!</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344774427169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You'd thing that fartie was in line to get a beautiful white hoe...oh well he will be dead before another crapper is in the white house..ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344780665283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344780814757-31</Id><Topic><Title>TOP REPUBLICAN...ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION WITH RYAN</Title><Username>dexter.jerusalen</Username><Timestamp>1344769142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 06:59:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was already over for Mitt with his numbers crashing. Now we get the bonus of never having to hear about Paul Ryan seriously again after November.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344780814757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344781534062-32</Id><Topic><Title>a record 6 Trillion added to the Debt by Obama and still no hope and change</Title><Username>dr_james391</Username><Timestamp>1344701258064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First your numbers are off by 20%. I realize anything that won't fit on a bumper sticker is a bit much for you to understand but here are the facts. "The Treasury Department’s “Debt to the Penny” Web site makes it easy to track the growth of the national debt during Obama’s presidency. There are two key figures — for publicly held debt and for gross debt, which includes bonds that the government owes to itself (such as Social Security trust fund bonds.) As of Jan. 20, 2009, the publicly held debt was $6.31 trillion and the gross debt was $10.63 trillion. As of May 14, 2012, the publicly held debt was $10.92 trillion and the gross debt was $15.68 trillion. So, the publicly held debt has grown by $4.61 trillion, and the gross debt has grown by $5.05 trillion. Thus it’s certainly correct that the national debt has grown by about $5 trillion under Obama. Eric Fehrnstrom, a senior adviser to the Romney campaign, said that the $5 trillion figure came from these Treasury Department figures. “We’re using the same standard that Obama used during his campaign in assigning blame to President Bush for the increase in debt that happened under his watch,” he said, pointing to a speech that then-Sen. Obama made during the 2008 presidential campaign. “The problem is that the way Bush has done it over the last eight years is to take out a credit card from the Bank of China in the name of our children, driving up our national debt from $5 trillion for the first 42 presidents,” Obama said in Fargo, N.D. “Number 43 added $4 trillion by his lonesome, so that we now have over $9 trillion of debt that we are going to have to pay back — $30,000 for every man, woman and child. That’s irresponsible. It’s unpatriotic.” Hmm, “unpatriotic” is certainly harsh. But, we’ve often said, two wrongs don’t make a right. Romney also attributed the growth of the debt entirely to Obama’s policies. And, and while the numbers add up, that is a bit more difficult to justify. First of all, Obama has failed to convince Congress to enact some of his proposed policies — such as higher taxes on the wealthy — that likely would have reduced the deficit and thus kept the debt growing more slowly. But more to the point, a major factor in the debt explosion has been the decline in government revenues because of the recession. One could argue — and Romney might — that the laggard recovery is the result of Obama’s policies and thus he should also get all of the blame for the decline in revenues. But the chart below shows that the decline in revenues (the red line) began at start of the recession — a year before Obama took office. The chart also shows an explosion of spending (blue line) began at the start of the recession — that is the result of automatic stabilizers such as unemployment insurance kicking in. The spending kept going up, and a good chunk of that is Obama’s responsibility. Still, as the chart shows, it is not such a simple answer to pin this all on Obama’s “policies.”</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344781534062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344782154090-33</Id><Title>Not quite true Mitt</Title><Msg>"Unlike the current president, who has cut Medicare funding by $700 billion, we will preserve and protect Medicare and Social Security and keep them there for future generations." THE FACTS: You could fill an arena with all the details left out in this statement. Ryan's reputation as a fiscal conservative is built on a budget plan that would overhaul the Medicare program and introduce a voucher-like plan that future retirees could use to buy private health insurance. Whether that results in a better or worse situation for Medicare recipients is a matter of debate. But under Ryan's plan, traditional Medicare would no longer be the health insurance mainstay, just one of many competing options."</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782154090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344782287064-34</Id><Title>Not quite true Paul</Title><Msg>"RYAN on Romney: "As governor of Massachusetts, he worked with Democrats and Republicans to balance budgets with no tax increases, lower unemployment, increase income and improve people's lives." THE FACTS: For a Massachusetts governor, balancing a budget is a requirement of state law. Ryan's claim that Romney didn't raise taxes to comply with Massachusetts' yearly balanced budget requirement is also misleading. While Romney didn't raise state income or sales taxes, he worked with the state's Democratic-controlled legislature to raise hundreds of millions of dollars through new or raised fees on marriage licenses, gun licenses and much more. Romney also closed what he called business tax "loopholes," raising between $350 million and $375 million annually for three years. Many in the Massachusetts business community said they saw the maneuver as a tax increase by a different name. And while Romney himself didn't raise income taxes, he benefited from a huge $1.1 billion tax hike passed by Democrats the year before he took office. It was responsible for roughly half of the deficit Romney helped cut in his first year in office.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782287064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344782515157-35</Id><Title>Not quite true GOP</Title><Msg>: Ryan, like Romney and scores of Republicans in recent weeks, has used comments Obama made at July 13 campaign appearance in Virginia against him. But the rhetorical jab takes Obama out of context. Republicans have seized on only part of Obama's quote — "If you've got a business, you didn't build that" — but the full quote makes clear Obama is talking about the conditions that help businesses and individuals succeed, such as teachers and infrastructure. The more complete quote from Obama: "If you were successful, somebody along the line gave you some help. There was a great teacher somewhere in your life. Somebody helped to create this unbelievable American system that we have that allowed you to thrive. Somebody invested in roads and bridges. If you've got a business — you didn't build that. Somebody else made that happen. The Internet didn't get invented on its own. Government research created the Internet so that all the companies could make money off the Internet."</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782515157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344782578535-36</Id><Title>u.s.a vs. kenya</Title><Msg>on the american team are two succesfull men who believe in the greatness of america,on the kenyan team you have lying worthless pos who`s never accomplished anything on his own and a blowhard retard.</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1344782578535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344782962359-37</Id><Title>The Polls Don't lie!! America tried the crappers way and it didn't work!!!</Title><Msg>now we try mitt and pauls way...you go to work and earn it free loaders!!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344782962359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344783208841-38</Id><Title>OBAMA IS THE FIRST PRESIDENT IN HISTORY TO NEVER SIGN A BUDGET IN 4 YEARS AS PRESIDENT!!!</Title><Msg>I this terrible economy why is he getting a pass on this? be sure to Google the movie "2016 Obama's America" '</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344783208841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:53:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344783327850-39</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344783327850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344783992510-40</Id><Title>Insurance companies can't pass premium increases along to show growth!</Title><Msg>The Wall street ponzi scheme played out over the years in healthcare is finished. Everybody and their mother's 401k and retirement plans were tied to this false growth in healthcare. Now those companies can no longer pass on the premium increases year over year because companies and employees and even the government refuse or can't to pay those premium increases. No growth, because the insurance companies aren't going to work smarter or pay their executives less, they will just lay off the worker bees and answer fewer claims.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1344783992510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344784054642-41</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you want to compare biden to ryan ??? imagine biden becoming pres. if obummer croaked ? -bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1344784054642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344784076993-42</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he can spell potato. I hope. He certainly isn't comparable to any Kennedy.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344784076993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:07:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344784352451-43</Id><Title>Ryan is the Male version of Palin</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney has his Palin got hers and Ryan will get his. These folks are about making money for themselves. The Republicans like Rove, Limbaugh, Santorum and Gingrich are about about sucking the coffers dry any which way they can and making you believe that they are for you and I. Well they ain't and we will be back to where we were before Bush left us with hardly a pot to #$%$ in. Those tea-parties ideologues with their fake ideologies and hypocritical christian beliefs are about foolishness and ranting and raving.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1344784352451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344786023431-44</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey= show USA your taxes,,what are you hiding???</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344775096877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's working on doctoring them right now. It took Obama a few months to doctor his birth certificate, give Mitt some time!</Msg><Username>loriannsouza</Username><Timestamp>1344786023431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344786339601-45</Id><Topic><Title>Not quite true GOP</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782515157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with out the individual taking the bull by the horns - nothing got built - regardless - of teachers an infrastructure - its the individual - an the desire to achieve - that makes it work .! what is next - the government permitted your mommy to give you birth - so their for - we should be thankful that the govenment permitted mommy to have children .! It took the achievement of man an women to succeed - to make this world great .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1344786339601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344786381666-46</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey= show USA your taxes,,what are you hiding???</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344775096877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 08:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you prove either of those statements? Didn't think so.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344786381666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344786935245-47</Id><Topic><Title>a record 6 Trillion added to the Debt by Obama and still no hope and change</Title><Username>dr_james391</Username><Timestamp>1344701258064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:07:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wildly unrealistic assumptions? You mean like Obama promising he would cut the deficit in half and unemployment would be 6% by now? Rofl</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1344786935245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344786999945-48</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wouldn't be the first US president to select a running mate for his life insurance attributes. I know you guys are still trying to forget Dan Quayle, but even the Texas School Board has failed to expunge him from their endorsed history texts. ROTFLMAO at people who either don't understand the game of politics, or complain about the capriciousness of its rules.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344786999945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344787022954-49</Id><Title>Obama Said in 2009 he shouldn't deserve another term if he doesn't cut the deficit in half and Unemployment is 6%</Title><Msg>...............well?</Msg><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1344787022954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344787269320-50</Id><Topic><Title>Not quite true GOP</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782515157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Every successful individual knows that his or her achievement depends on a community of persons working together." Paul Ryan</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344787269320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344787352661-51</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There we have it, Ladies and Germs: the official kiss-of-death from the King! ROTFLMAO at the unintended consequences of some endorsements.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344787352661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344788121913-52</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE FIRST PRESIDENT IN HISTORY TO NEVER SIGN A BUDGET IN 4 YEARS AS PRESIDENT!!!</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344783208841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:53:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's record on the economy is abysmal on every count!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344788121913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344788890599-53</Id><Title>Obama Promised Hope and Change and all I got was a tshirt and a food stamp</Title><Msg>Now he sounds like a typical dirty Chicago Politician.</Msg><Username>pokerface_liar</Username><Timestamp>1344788890599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344789908076-54</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan is the Male version of Palin</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1344784352451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He;s not for gay marriage either! Obama 2012!</Msg><Username>milesed17</Username><Timestamp>1344789908076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344790806335-55</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>potatoe</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344790806335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344790852867-56</Id><Topic><Title>Give a man a fish and feed him for a day, teach a man to fish and feed him for life, take the fisherman’s fish and give it to a bum and buy the vote, of every slacker, for Liberal Democrats.</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344704359886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:59:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344790852867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344792675544-57</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan is the Male version of Palin</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1344784352451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid, stupid posts starting again. "Ryan is the male Palin". What a stupid jerk. How stupid is it to make analogies about Ryan as VP when you got Biden a heartbeat away from being president? Think about that! You are inviting attacks on your stupidity.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344792675544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344792812253-58</Id><Title>Biden is the Male version of Rosanne Barr</Title><Msg>Stupid... comparing Ryan to Palin. A better comparison is dirty old Joe Biden to dirty mouthed Rosanne Barr!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344792812253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344792864525-59</Id><Title>IF YOU ARE POOR OR MIDDLE CLASS AND SUPPORT REPUCANS, UR A CAPITAL #$%$</Title><Msg>I mean completely useless, why in God's name must you work so hard against your own best interest. Repucan's plan is to take on the average $2000 from your pocket and give it to the rich. The assumption is that, the rich will in turn spend that money to make your lives better. GIVE ME A BREAK. You have to be completely brain dead to accept the premise.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344792864525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344794528705-60</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE FIRST PRESIDENT IN HISTORY TO NEVER SIGN A BUDGET IN 4 YEARS AS PRESIDENT!!!</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344783208841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:53:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you even no what a budget is, you freaking FOX news consumer.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344794528705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:02:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344794612168-61</Id><Title>WHAT PARTY LEFT OBAMA THE ECONOMIC MESS HE IS DEALING WITH ?</Title><Msg>hmmm!, let me guess, yes it was the REPUCAN party. Those lying, thieving miserable pile of dog mess.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344794612168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344794714774-62</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN THE NEW JACK KENNEDY</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344710396116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has a Harry Truman quality. He needs to believe he will live as long as his Mother not his Father.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344794714774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344794765738-63</Id><Title>Republicans now favored to win back Senate</Title><Msg>A good thing indeed!</Msg><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1344794765738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344794871473-64</Id><Title>obama (the dumb) leading the dumber (lib trolls)</Title><Msg>Too funny..................</Msg><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1344794871473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795131342-65</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT PARTY LEFT OBAMA THE ECONOMIC MESS HE IS DEALING WITH ?</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344794612168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waaaa, Bush left a mess for me to clean up. Waaaa, my policies failed. Waaaa, it is not as easy as I thought it would be. Grow up, you liberal cry babies. Bush you say was responsible? How about Barney Frank who relentlessy pursued policies to slacken credit so everybody with a heartbeat could buy a house with no money down and no verification of income. Barney, who famously said at the peak of the bubble, "There is absolutely no sign of a housing bubble." In case you missed the high school class that explained how our government works, it has THREE branches. The Legislative Branch makes the laws and regulations... which is what allowed the housing bubble. Liar Libs at it again, twist, deflect, LIE, LIE, LIE!!!!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795131342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344795246060-66</Id><Title>What party left Obama with the economic mess he is dealing with? Let's see, that would be the Barney Frank, "There is absolutely no sign of a housing bubble" party.</Title><Msg>Look in the mirror, liberals, for the source of Obama's problems.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795246060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795306177-67</Id><Topic><Title>Republican vetting process is horribly flawed. How many years of tax records did Ryan submit?</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344715369855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republican choices for Pres. and VP just ensure an Obama re-election. Sit back and watch the repugs self destruct.</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1344795306177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:15:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795383204-68</Id><Topic><Title>Sheriff Joe got his call from Mitt yesterday.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1344716396432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:19:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't Sheriff Joe driving Mitt's clown car?</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1344795383204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:16:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344795419324-69</Id><Title>If you are poor or middle class and support Republicans, you will eventually get a job to pay your bills. If you support Democrats, you'll be standing in unemployment and welfare lines asking for handouts.</Title><Msg>It's the truth, can't deny it... unless you are a liar lib.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795419324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795436036-70</Id><Topic><Title>Biden is the Male version of Rosanne Barr</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344792812253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:33:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come now, Ms. Barr is much brighter and more successful. And a whole lot more fun.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1344795436036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344795587840-71</Id><Title>"Nurse Ratchid, the sedatives in mrstan's enema didn't take. He's in dire need of a stronger dose"</Title><Msg>Dose up, mrstan, before you drown in your own vomit.</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1344795587840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344795603700-72</Id><Topic><Title>Biden is the Male version of Rosanne Barr</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344792812253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 13:33:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right. I apologize to Ms. Barr for insulting her. My bad.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795603700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344795909342-73</Id><Title>mrstan sez, "It is a common risk management tactic for wealthy people to have some money deposited in other countries. It is insurance against a US financial collapse, rampant socialism to sieze assets, etc."</Title><Msg>Paranoid fanatic fringe-right lunatic</Msg><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1344795909342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344796377446-74</Id><Title>cosmo_vitellit recent posts: Sexist, racist, replies to intelligent post with "right wing lunatic" response - VERY INTELLINGENT COSMO! Your an idiot, Einstein. Try more than six word sentences.</Title><Msg>Here is a sample of this jerk's sexits insulting posts. He is truly the tash he accuses others of being. A real potty mouth! Just look for a head in a crotch, that's her And Tapeworm Tirades they are You're on your way bag to the fa9 farm Can't read your lips 'cause they're stuck inside SW's sphincter the klan of trailer trash telezbians is busy tonight</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344796377446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344796837757-75</Id><Title>cosmo_vitelli recent posts: "Just look for a head in a crotch, that's her" "You're on your way bag to the fa9 farm" Now there is a nice guy for you. I doubt even the liberals would want to claim a slob like you as one of their own. Disgraceful</Title><Msg>You're a walking sewer mouth, cosmo.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344796837757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797017832-76</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Promised Hope and Change and all I got was a tshirt and a food stamp</Title><Username>pokerface_liar</Username><Timestamp>1344788890599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:28:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think what we'll get if he has a second term. It involves a finger and a spincter, I'll not say more than that.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344797017832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797121935-77</Id><Topic><Title>obama (the dumb) leading the dumber (lib trolls)</Title><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1344794871473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama the America Destroyer</Msg><Username>wlnfastorlose001</Username><Timestamp>1344797121935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797213884-78</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans now favored to win back Senate</Title><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1344794765738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems hope rest on Phocahontas in Mass. Mass voters are whacked out enough to elect her.</Msg><Username>wlnfastorlose001</Username><Timestamp>1344797213884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797277448-79</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Said in 2009 he shouldn't deserve another term if he doesn't cut the deficit in half and Unemployment is 6%</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1344787022954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, he says anything that is popular at the moment, then does not deliver on any of it. He promised people in the coal country of Virgina that the US would burn more coal, then years later he pushed environmental regulations that closed a lot of mines and he famously said that he would bankrupt anyone who tried to open a new coal mine. Look, if he does not support coal, that is fine. Just be honest about it. Don't lie to people telling them that he will support their industry and their jobs to get them to vote for him, then pull the rug from underneath him. He is the biggest liar in the Whitehouse since, "I did not have sex with that woman" and "I am not a crook." Teflon Obam.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344797277448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797287634-80</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE FIRST PRESIDENT IN HISTORY TO NEVER SIGN A BUDGET IN 4 YEARS AS PRESIDENT!!!</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344783208841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:53:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2016, Obama's America - the truth will scare you to death.</Msg><Username>nwguy_2006</Username><Timestamp>1344797287634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797332384-81</Id><Topic><Title>Give a man a fish and feed him for a day, teach a man to fish and feed him for life, take the fisherman’s fish and give it to a bum and buy the vote, of every slacker, for Liberal Democrats.</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344704359886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:59:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's no denying that!</Msg><Username>wlnfastorlose001</Username><Timestamp>1344797332384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344797509568-82</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Promised Hope and Change and all I got was a tshirt and a food stamp</Title><Username>pokerface_liar</Username><Timestamp>1344788890599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 12:28:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is what he is.</Msg><Username>wlnfastorlose001</Username><Timestamp>1344797509568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798068620-83</Id><Topic><Title>cosmo_vitelli recent posts: "Just look for a head in a crotch, that's her" "You're on your way bag to the fa9 farm" Now there is a nice guy for you. I doubt even the liberals would want to claim a slob like you as one of their own. Disgraceful</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344796837757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan is not Stan Luboff.</Msg><Username>libertydies01</Username><Timestamp>1344798068620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798148174-84</Id><Topic><Title>cosmo_vitellit recent posts: Sexist, racist, replies to intelligent post with "right wing lunatic" response - VERY INTELLINGENT COSMO! Your an idiot, Einstein. Try more than six word sentences.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344796377446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan4089 is not Stan Luboff.</Msg><Username>libertydies01</Username><Timestamp>1344798148174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798170075-85</Id><Topic><Title>mrstan sez, "It is a common risk management tactic for wealthy people to have some money deposited in other countries. It is insurance against a US financial collapse, rampant socialism to sieze assets, etc."</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1344795909342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan4089 is not Stan Luboff.</Msg><Username>libertydies01</Username><Timestamp>1344798170075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:02:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798191182-86</Id><Topic><Title>If you are poor or middle class and support Republicans, you will eventually get a job to pay your bills. If you support Democrats, you'll be standing in unemployment and welfare lines asking for handouts.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795419324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan4089 is not Stan Luboff.</Msg><Username>libertydies01</Username><Timestamp>1344798191182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798226106-87</Id><Topic><Title>What party left Obama with the economic mess he is dealing with? Let's see, that would be the Barney Frank, "There is absolutely no sign of a housing bubble" party.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795246060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:14:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan is not Stan Luboff.</Msg><Username>libertydies01</Username><Timestamp>1344798226106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798422484-88</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah fish2kill, what an intelligent retort! There is no ROTFLMAO with you, it's just pathetic. Typical immature liar lib tactic - personal insults and character assassinations. I am picking on you and the other libs clogging up this board for a reason. This is a BAC board, not a policital commentary board. I sign on Sat morning hoping to find some BAC posts, and all I see is lib political post after lib political post. Endless. Surely there must be a more appropriate place for you to express your views. It has gone from real BAC posts being one in ten to one in a hundred. I am posting conservative themes to give you and the other libs a taste of your own medicine. If the libs stop making political posts here, I will stop posting political posts too. Until the, I will give all the libs the same treatment.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344798422484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:07:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798876352-89</Id><Topic><Title>If you are poor or middle class and support Republicans, you will eventually get a job to pay your bills. If you support Democrats, you'll be standing in unemployment and welfare lines asking for handouts.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344795419324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you forget who destroyed the economy and who saved it ! Bush was losing 3/4 of a million jobs a month at the end,</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344798876352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344798935674-90</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans now favored to win back Senate</Title><Username>drwstring</Username><Timestamp>1344794765738</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:06:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't count on it, only an insane idiot would vote for more Bush #$%$</Msg><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1344798935674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344799629560-91</Id><Topic><Title>Not quite true GOP</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1344782515157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I appreciate how you make your point in an intelligent and respectful manner. I have been stooping to a lower level to make a point with what I think are mostly liberals who resort to personal attacks and lots of "laughing" at other people in demeaning ways. I will treat them the way they treat people. With due respect, I think that it was a very dumb statement for a president to make, and taken in the full contect, not just the one line. He said that government research created the internet - very true. But who paid for the government research? The very taxpayers he says did not build it. How would they have built it without taxpayer funding? Also, what about the construction companies? Yes, they in fact did build that (infrastructure) and a lot of them are small businesses who joint venture to build large projects. Government has a role of course, but time and again it's been shown that the free market fosters more innovation at much lower cost that the government. Take oil cleanup. The government has regulated it and spent billions over the years to improve its efficiency while making little improvement in 20 years. A private group funded a contest in the open market and in months had companies deliver technologies that almost always doubled, and in the winner's case I think it was something like four to eight times the efficiency of existing technology. The problem I have with the theme of the President's statement is it seems that he is saying we all owe it to the government. I disagree strongly. I think the government runs only because of the taxpayers who fund it and the taxpayers have built everything in this country.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344799629560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344799724909-92</Id><Topic><Title>Liar lib leftist telling lies and denying truths conservatives posted today. Read their posts, reveals ever increasing anxiety and desperation. Now they are saying that swing states are going with Teflon Obam when in fact the swing states are split. Lie all you want, liar libs, it won't change the facts.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344729960745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:06:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mrstan is the troll known as TNS</Msg><Username>libertysword30</Username><Timestamp>1344799724909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344799815393-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Said in 2009 he shouldn't deserve another term if he doesn't cut the deficit in half and Unemployment is 6%</Title><Username>tulsaturd</Username><Timestamp>1344787022954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 11:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344799815393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:30:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344800196152-94</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and then count your own. For diversity's sake, also look at the number of non-bac posts I made during that time, and compare it to yours. ROTFLMAO at the math-challenged everywhere, but especially at you.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344800196152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:36:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344800425217-95</Id><Topic><Title>cosmo_vitellit recent posts: Sexist, racist, replies to intelligent post with "right wing lunatic" response - VERY INTELLINGENT COSMO! Your an idiot, Einstein. Try more than six word sentences.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344796377446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nor could it be 'Stan The Man'. ROTFLMAO at the gender anonymity provided by the great and wondrous internet.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344800425217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344800524485-96</Id><Title>Fishing is good. So far, I've bagged surreal_deal, fish4kill, mr.whizzard, f_bird55 (wonder what the f means) and a few others. Not one of their retorts was anything more than a personal insult. Pathetic.</Title><Msg>I gave them a chance to respond with intelligent counter-arguments, but all they could muster was personal insults. What does that tell you about the strength of their arguments (or their ability to even verbalize an intelligent argument)? It means they are nothing more then internet bullies, throwing insults and feeling frustrated with their impotence. Little yellow cowards hiding behind a computer.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800524485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344800743991-97</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why haven't you taken the kingofvietnam to task for his blatantly partisan political comments? That's a rhetorical question, because everyone on this board knows why - even you. ROTFLMAO at anti-regulatory people writing and enforcing their own regulations in an arbitrary and capricious manner everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344800743991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344800747247-98</Id><Title>Lol... this is so much fun. Idiots don't realize that responding to my posts just brings them back to the top of the board.</Title><Msg>These guys are clueless.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344801101747-99</Id><Topic><Title>Lol... this is so much fun. Idiots don't realize that responding to my posts just brings them back to the top of the board.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone here knows how the game is played. Why should we wait for you to bump or respond to your own posts to make them pop to the surface again? Besides, as I've said before, the best way to reveal a neo-con's idiocy is to hand him a microphone, or in this case, a spot above the fold. Congratulations on doing most of the heavy lifting for me. ROTFLMAO at delighted idiots everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344801101747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:51:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344801699430-100</Id><Topic><Title>Fishing is good. So far, I've bagged surreal_deal, fish4kill, mr.whizzard, f_bird55 (wonder what the f means) and a few others. Not one of their retorts was anything more than a personal insult. Pathetic.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800524485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a lawyer reminded me that a lawsuit is just a formalized #$%$ contest, the outcome of which is determined by a single principle: if the opposition #$%$ you off, they win; if you #$%$ THEM off, YOU win. Based on that simple metric, you lost your argument yesterday afternoon, coincident with losing your temper. I accept your out-of-court settlement of this contest. ROTFLMAO at people unclear on a multitude of concepts.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344801699430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344802380020-101</Id><Topic><Title>The Polls Don't lie!! America tried the crappers way and it didn't work!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344782962359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 10:49:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anything is better than four more years of failure. Mitt and Paul couldn't do worse if they tried to f things up.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344802380020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344802522912-102</Id><Topic><Title>Lol... this is so much fun. Idiots don't realize that responding to my posts just brings them back to the top of the board.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO, you just put my post at the top again! You have to be one of the dumbest people I've ever run into. You run off in a dozen different bizzare directions in one post. Amazing. How's the food there at the home?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344802522912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344802525278-103</Id><Title>Mr. Stan is a definder of a cost cause...ilmfao stick the @#$%^ where the sun doesn't shine...Mr Stan!!!</Title><Msg>socialism is not going to happen @#$%$# lover!!!!</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344802525278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:15:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344802775117-104</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Stan is a definder of a cost cause...ilmfao stick the @#$%^ where the sun doesn't shine...Mr Stan!!!</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344802525278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there a thought anywhere in your post? Even a little one? What is a "cost cause?" And the where the sun don't shine thing... not very orginal now is it. It is the signature of a pathetic loser with limited intelligence. My God man, stop embarrasing yourself.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344802775117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344802901215-105</Id><Title>milesed18: "Mr. Stan is a definder of a cost cause" Say what? What the heck does that mean? My God man, stop embarrassing yourself.</Title><Msg>Really, you should stay off message boards. You just make yourself out to be a fool.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344802901215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344803373160-106</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the lighter side, I think Paul Ryan is a very handsome dude, besides being highly intellectual. Not only that he's so religious just like me. Mr. Ryan already earned my vote. Eat your heart out Obama !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344803373160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:29:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344803498128-107</Id><Title>REPUCANS SUPPORTERS HAVE ONE THING COMMON - POOR EDUCATION OR LACK OF IT</Title><Msg>they are mostly hateful, uninformed and uneducated farm boys. It makes it easier for REPUCANS to lie to them. They are gullible baboons.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344803498128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344805166026-108</Id><Title>MOVIE: "2016 OBAMA'S AMERICA" , GREAT MOVIE It is selling out in theaters everywhere</Title><Msg>Google it!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805166026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344805595256-109</Id><Title>THE RYAN PICK JUST WON THE ELECTION FOR ROMNEY</Title><Msg>MARK MY WORDS</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805595256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344805715944-110</Id><Title>Flippers VP made had Major accomplishments in Congress!!!</Title><Msg>He acttualy got a post office renamed!!! Oh ya and a tax on arrows that were mported ................... Yep that all flippers flop accomplished</Msg><Username>drcwls</Username><Timestamp>1344805715944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344805753146-111</Id><Title>$3.5 MILLION Raised online in 24 hrs of @MittRomney's pick of @PaulRyanVP #RomneyRyan2012</Title><Msg>WOW!!!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805753146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344806515201-112</Id><Topic><Title>$3.5 MILLION Raised online in 24 hrs of @MittRomney's pick of @PaulRyanVP #RomneyRyan2012</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805753146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow is right. Adding Ryan to the ticket really energized repubs and scares libs that Ryan will put the Romney ticket past Obama. Look how the libs desperate posts escalated after the announcement, and all of it irrelevant personal attacks and lies without any substance. That is really telling.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344806515201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344807311454-113</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a wise choice. Don't listen to killmyfish, I mean fish4kill, I mean... well whatever his name is, he's not really important enough to remember. He is just angry and feeling impotent that his man Obama is being exposed and Romney's campaign just received a huge adrenalin boost. He's bitter.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344807311454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344807914315-114</Id><Title>Where's Warren's Attempt at a Coherent Synopsis???</Title><Msg>Did Warren once again regale us with yet another feeble and failed attempt at a coherent synopsis of a left leaning, liberal, "ratings-challenged", msm televsion programme tomorrow, just to have it summarily deleted by the Yahoo clean-up crew during the week? Once deleted, do you think Warren will try to repost the drivel again, just to have it summarily deleted a second time? LMAO Later... SW</Msg><Username>sarcasm_och_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1344807914315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344811227091-115</Id><Title>TO BE A GOOD REPUCAN, LEARN HOW TO CHEAT ON YOUR TAXES</Title><Msg>and learn how to hate and lie. Bingo, you are now a REPUCAN</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344811227091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344811341475-116</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being patriotic like me is one thing however being sour losers like Obama and Biden is a different thing. I concured that both Obama and Biden tried their very best to save America from falling further down the abyss however these 2 morons are just not up to the task of the Presidency. In God we Trust America is THE Greatest Don't let lazy &amp; stupid Democrats bogg you down with negative ads !!!! VOTE FOR THE FUTURE VOTE ROMNEY &amp; RYAN Vote for THE Leaders with Substance !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344811341475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344811779283-117</Id><Title>du/m/ba/ma - the writing is on the wall</Title><Msg>the garbage heap of history is ready an waiting ...lmao...hillary might even speak at the GOP convention....lmao</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1344811779283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344813055478-118</Id><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan WILL find you a job !</Title><Msg>Hee hee LOL unless you chose to be unemployed forever !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344813055478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344813392749-119</Id><Topic><Title>du/m/ba/ma - the writing is on the wall</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1344811779283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:49:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, the Cretaceous Era is ending alright....your days are numbered...and Hillary is more likely to be speaking at your convention than the last GOP President. ROTFLMAO at political extinctions and uninvited conventioneers everywhere. Have you and stegosaurus1 crossed paths yet?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344813392749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344813409796-120</Id><Topic><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan WILL find you a job !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344813055478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ABSOLUTELY !!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1344813409796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344813667306-121</Id><Title>***********NOBAMA 2012************* IT'S TIME FOR THE "World JOKE" to go....period!</Title><Msg>RRRRRRRRRROMNEY/RYAN 2012 !!!</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1344813667306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344813866130-122</Id><Topic><Title>Lol... this is so much fun. Idiots don't realize that responding to my posts just brings them back to the top of the board.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll keep you there until you realize you're the laughing stock of this board. That means forever, or at least until Nov. 7th. Nothing I like better than people who think they're scoring points while they're making mine. ROTFLMAO at limelight lovers everywhere. Watch as this tactic neuters Romney and Ryan too.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344813866130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344814184050-123</Id><Topic><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan WILL find you a job !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344813055478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being jobless under Obama for so long sucks !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344814184050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344815003468-124</Id><Topic><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan WILL find you a job !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344813055478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A job in India is better than sitting here collecting welfare feeling worthless !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344815003468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344815226666-125</Id><Title>RYAN DOESN'T NEED A TELEPROMPTER</Title><Msg>THAT'S REFRESHING!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344815226666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344815734186-126</Id><Title>everything is pointing to a blow out come november 6 ...Bo your socialist idea didn't hold up...ilmfao</Title><Msg>now go back to kenya and set and cry over your drunkin daddys grave...ilmfao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344815734186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344816036706-127</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude I just want Obama over with and move on.....</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344816036706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344817105308-128</Id><Title>Larry Sinclair told the truth about Bo...ilmao...</Title><Msg>three gays found shot in the head all from Rev.Wrights church...they say they was Bos lovers that was about to talk...ilmao</Msg><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344817105308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344817646231-129</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN DOESN'T NEED A TELEPROMPTER</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344815226666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take your campaign out of the gutter...best line by Mittens today!</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344817646231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344817728281-130</Id><Topic><Title>TO BE A GOOD REPUCAN, LEARN HOW TO CHEAT ON YOUR TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344811227091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:40:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just like turbo tax cheat tim and charlie rangle, you forget about those tax cheats that are for real tax cheats and not some made up story.</Msg><Username>montyprython</Username><Timestamp>1344817728281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344817872227-131</Id><Title>It is so disgusting that blacks only vote Obama !</Title><Msg>I don't know why they can not escape their sphere of influence and vote for someone who will make this country greater ? I can guarantee you most NBA guys will vote Obama and that really make me sick !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344817872227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344817874365-132</Id><Topic><Title>everything is pointing to a blow out come november 6 ...Bo your socialist idea didn't hold up...ilmfao</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344815734186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:55:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the saul alinsky socialist idea.</Msg><Username>montyprython</Username><Timestamp>1344817874365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344818112376-133</Id><Title>Since the Veep announcement, no Democrat operative has</Title><Msg>missed a chance to characterize Ryan as "the intellectual leader of the Republican party." He has a record of rather specific and radically right wing bills and "plans" that he's backed in the House over the years. Apparently Romney feels this record can be defended. But it goes beyond Romney. The Dem strategy appears to be to 1st get Ryan securely wrapped around, not just Romney's neck, but that of every Republican running for office, then run against Ryan. Republicans running for dogcatcher will have to either defend or scramble away from Ryan's specific plans to turn medicare over to the health insurance guys, turn social security over to the Wall St. guys, eliminate tax breaks which largely benefit the middle class and still run deficits far into the future while reducing taxes on the rich.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1344818112376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344818197035-134</Id><Title>Be a good Democrat. Lie about Romney cheating on his taxes even though the IRS has audited his returns. Essentially.... just lie about it.</Title><Msg>There is no evidence Romney cheated on his taxes. If he paid too little tax for your personal taste, then blame the tax code. If you say the tax code is screwed up, you'll get no argument from me. But to say that Romney cheated is simply more liar lib garbage.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344818197035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344818633840-135</Id><Topic><Title>Be a good Democrat. Lie about Romney cheating on his taxes even though the IRS has audited his returns. Essentially.... just lie about it.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344818197035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:36:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why even talk about this crap....cheat on taxes would have been impossible for romney and bain these kind of people and these kind of companies are always on the irs radar....pure libturd horse chit.....mindless drivel.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1344818633840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344818714921-136</Id><Title>Forbes...Funds selling into rally. Time to get out of stocks or</Title><Msg>buy downside protection. GLTA</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1344818714921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344818747682-137</Id><Title>I am volunteering for Mitt Romney all day today</Title><Msg>I belive in causes and I also belive in reasons. I will shed my last drop of blood posting online day and nite only to make sure Obama wil kiss my butt bye bye this November. DON'T FORGET TO VOTE OBAMA MUST GO !!!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344818747682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344818873093-138</Id><Topic><Title>$3.5 MILLION Raised online in 24 hrs of @MittRomney's pick of @PaulRyanVP #RomneyRyan2012</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805753146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone dumb enough to send them their money deserves to die broke:)</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1344818873093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344819866744-139</Id><Title>Teflon Obam's broken promises...</Title><Msg>"I will fix the economy in 3 years or I will be a one term president." Then you shouldn't run for re-election, should you? "I will run my administration with increased transparency." By invoking exec privilege on Fast and Furious and having your staff meet with lobbyists outside the White House so those lobbyists would not show on public visitor logs? How is that transparent? "I will cut the deficit in half by the end of my first term." Oh, please, give me a break. "I will close Gitmo." Isn't Gitmo still open? "I will televise the healthcare debate." Why did you say that, but then have the debate behind closed doors where the public could not hear what was being said? What are you hiding from us? Liberals, if a Repub pres had made those promises and broken them, you would legitimately be all over them, calling for their resignation... just like Trick #$%$ "I am not a crook." This is why you appear to be hypocrits, and appear to be deflecting the facts about Obama by attacking Romney. Any intelligent responses to what you feel about the promises Obama has broken? Other than name calling and insults? How about some constructive debate?</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344819866744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344820381153-140</Id><Title>Many Americans WILL NOT vote Obama again</Title><Msg>I remember quite vividly that Mr. Obama said to a very enthusiastic crowd in the foot ball field....."This election is not just about me. It's all about you ! We need to pick ourselves up ! Dust ourselves off ! We can ! YES We can ! Hee hee LOL maybe "Yes We Can" was also a lie !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344820381153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344820692510-141</Id><Topic><Title>I can't wait until the Billion $ campaign is waged against Obama</Title><Username>bpr1205</Username><Timestamp>1344738183402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 22:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean that 1 senile, racist billionaire can buy, sorry purchase the election of the USA? and you you Republicans can go back to to screwing Wall Street some more. Also, you can go back to being political ignoramuses.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1344820692510</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344820913266-142</Id><Topic><Title>I am volunteering for Mitt Romney all day today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344818747682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loser boy, wasting your energy and time.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344820913266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344821028660-143</Id><Title>REPUCAN IS WHY WE SHOULD KEEP ABORTION LEGAL</Title><Msg>these bunch are a waste of human space. Brainless, mindless baboons</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344821028660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821110374-144</Id><Topic><Title>TO BE A GOOD REPUCAN, LEARN HOW TO CHEAT ON YOUR TAXES</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344811227091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 18:40:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how can you prove Romney boy is not a tax cheat</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344821110374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:25:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344821126699-145</Id><Title>a vote for the GOP is a vote to support the crooks</Title><Msg>BIG TIME!</Msg><Username>unclenam</Username><Timestamp>1344821126699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821200849-146</Id><Topic><Title>I can't wait until the Billion $ campaign is waged against Obama</Title><Username>bpr1205</Username><Timestamp>1344738183402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 22:23:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There you go again. Can't complete an intelligent thought to respond to his post, so you resort to insults. That is the sign of a pathetic desperate person with nothing of value to say. Liar lib reply to cogent well articulated thought: "you are a caw caw face." Really, you embarrass yourself. It makes you sound so ignorant. It makes you sound so immature. My God man, grow up.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344821200849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821334599-147</Id><Topic><Title>I am volunteering for Mitt Romney all day today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344818747682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I belive you should join me and support Romney-Ryan, otherwise you will NEVER find a job too. Be real !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344821334599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821430186-148</Id><Topic><Title>I am volunteering for Mitt Romney all day today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344818747682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>phacking stupid king living abroad</Msg><Username>unclenam</Username><Timestamp>1344821430186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:30:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821869315-149</Id><Topic><Title>Be a good Democrat. Lie about Romney cheating on his taxes even though the IRS has audited his returns. Essentially.... just lie about it.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344818197035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:36:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344821869315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821918166-150</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Warren's Attempt at a Coherent Synopsis???</Title><Username>sarcasm_och_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1344807914315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344821918166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344821963306-151</Id><Topic><Title>Teflon Obam's broken promises...</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344819866744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:04:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344821963306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822028180-152</Id><Topic><Title>$3.5 MILLION Raised online in 24 hrs of @MittRomney's pick of @PaulRyanVP #RomneyRyan2012</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344805753146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:09:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822028180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822076871-153</Id><Topic><Title>Many Americans WILL NOT vote Obama again</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344820381153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:13:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822076871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822086885-154</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Warren's Attempt at a Coherent Synopsis???</Title><Username>sarcasm_och_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1344807914315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was biased. It sucked. I couldn't allow BAC readers to be assaulted by it. It lasted less than 45 minutes. Too bad you missed it. BAC wasn't a sponsor.</Msg><Username>ebbyonex</Username><Timestamp>1344822086885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822091132-155</Id><Topic><Title>I am volunteering for Mitt Romney all day today</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344818747682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how could you find THE job if you are phacking stupid. What a phacking disgrace to the Vietnamese all over the world</Msg><Username>unclenam</Username><Timestamp>1344822091132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822141059-156</Id><Topic><Title>everything is pointing to a blow out come november 6 ...Bo your socialist idea didn't hold up...ilmfao</Title><Username>milesed18</Username><Timestamp>1344815734186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:55:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822141059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822179749-157</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822179749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344822260066-158</Id><Title>IDIOT REPUBLICANS DID THEMSELVES IN BY CHOOSING RYAN AS VP</Title><Msg>They only have 20% of the Latino vote, and it doesn't take a genius to know they should have chosen Marco Rubio in order to garner many of those votes. Sometimes I think the the whole charade is played out by the money people of both parties, in order to pick the president who will best serve their needs.</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1344822260066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822270383-159</Id><Topic><Title>It is so disgusting that blacks only vote Obama !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344817872227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 20:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822270383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822332905-160</Id><Topic><Title>Lol... this is so much fun. Idiots don't realize that responding to my posts just brings them back to the top of the board.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800747247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822332905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822534624-161</Id><Topic><Title>IDIOT REPUBLICANS DID THEMSELVES IN BY CHOOSING RYAN AS VP</Title><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1344822260066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:44:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you say isn't that far fetched. The whole Washington Establishment is composed of crooks, and cheats.</Msg><Username>bellacooz</Username><Timestamp>1344822534624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:48:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822668116-162</Id><Topic><Title>milesed18: "Mr. Stan is a definder of a cost cause" Say what? What the heck does that mean? My God man, stop embarrassing yourself.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344802901215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 16:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822668116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822777048-163</Id><Topic><Title>What's with all of the dog s*h*i*t* eating fringe right fools on this board?</Title><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1344635539539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:52:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They've got lots to gush about. They can't win and they know it.</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344822777048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822879681-164</Id><Topic><Title>Fishing is good. So far, I've bagged surreal_deal, fish4kill, mr.whizzard, f_bird55 (wonder what the f means) and a few others. Not one of their retorts was anything more than a personal insult. Pathetic.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344800524485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All stan, all the time! Bump!@</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344822879681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344822938888-165</Id><Topic><Title>Picking Paul Ryan was a wise choice</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344751195209</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 01:59:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sarah Palin is a very patriotic American. No one should doubt her love for America.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344822938888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344823013731-166</Id><Title>ROMNEY'S PERSONALITY IS ONE OF A MASOCHIST</Title><Msg>The republicans fire bombs and bullets at him, and he responds by throwing pillows. The guy needs a fire cracker placed in the crack of his #$%$</Msg><Username>bellacooz</Username><Timestamp>1344823013731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344823137447-167</Id><Title>mrstan: Do all of the padded rooms where you live have dial-up?</Title><Msg>Or do you get to share?</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344823137447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823150624-168</Id><Topic><Title>What's with all of the dog s*h*i*t* eating fringe right fools on this board?</Title><Username>surreal.deal</Username><Timestamp>1344635539539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:52:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and we should all help them get it. Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344823150624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823291528-169</Id><Topic><Title>a vote for the GOP is a vote to support the crooks</Title><Username>unclenam</Username><Timestamp>1344821126699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 21:25:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know it too? I think we had enough of greed with Bush Inc. Why would we want to go back to that?</Msg><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1344823291528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344823336362-170</Id><Title>My advice to Mr. Romney &amp; Mr. Ryan</Title><Msg>Just ignore that little chihuahua Obama bites and focus on on how you guys gonna find me a job. You will win all 50 states !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344823336362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823470269-171</Id><Topic><Title>Romney &amp; Ryan WILL find you a job !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344813055478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 19:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344823470269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344823523155-172</Id><Title>dow_wow_wow.... what the heck? dow, wow, wow, what kind of p***y name is that? In the battle of wits, you are UNARMED! LOL... what a fool, jerk, idiot. LOL....</Title><Msg>Another illiterate liar lib that cannot formulate an intelligent thought, so he resorts to personal insults. Running scared that your man Obama will lose like the loser he is? Can't stand the truths I have been posting, so you resort to juvenile insults.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823523155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823581693-173</Id><Topic><Title>My advice to Mr. Romney &amp; Mr. Ryan</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344823336362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude you will need two jobs because you will be paying to take care of your elderly parents or grand parents under ROMNEY/RYAN</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1344823581693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823641120-174</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal talking points: Represent lies as truths, and distortions and reality - it is our only chance to have four more years of mediocrity.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344722848170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 18:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more stan, more often!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344823641120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823757473-175</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to Virginians in 2008 to get votes: "We will burn more coal." Obama 2011 to environmentalists: "I will bankdrupt anybody who tries to open a new coal mine."</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344718359367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:52:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344823757473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823782469-176</Id><Topic><Title>My advice to Mr. Romney &amp; Mr. Ryan</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344823336362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Lord will take care of them dumb ash !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344823782469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344823869838-177</Id><Title>Fishing has been exceptionally good today. I've bagged a mess of liberal fish. Kinda stinky though. Think I will have to use them as fertilizer.</Title><Msg>Ba bye, liar libs. I am signing off for the evening. Sleep well, have a good one. Don't let me ruin your sleep tonight. I know how frustrating it must be for you, being on a losing team and all. I know that I have been a thorn in your side but it is all in good fun. See ya!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823869838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344823881206-178</Id><Topic><Title>dow_wow_wow.... what the heck? dow, wow, wow, what kind of p***y name is that? In the battle of wits, you are UNARMED! LOL... what a fool, jerk, idiot. LOL....</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823523155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344823881206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344824397793-179</Id><Topic><Title>dow_wow_wow.... what the heck? dow, wow, wow, what kind of p***y name is that? In the battle of wits, you are UNARMED! LOL... what a fool, jerk, idiot. LOL....</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823523155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fish why are you bunbing yourself... I think that is illegal in 49 states!!!</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1344824397793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344824468679-180</Id><Title>Paul Ryan will make Joe Biden an idiot !</Title><Msg>Go Ryan ! Yes you can !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344824468679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344824538215-181</Id><Topic><Title>dow_wow_wow.... what the heck? dow, wow, wow, what kind of p***y name is that? In the battle of wits, you are UNARMED! LOL... what a fool, jerk, idiot. LOL....</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823523155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yahoo ghost do you really think MIt has a chance??? It has already been decided... O has followed orders and the ruling party has already granted him another term...</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1344824538215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344824685311-182</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan will make Joe Biden an idiot !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344824468679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buddy... didn't you hear... I guess not casue you are still writing... word has it O already has won... go ahead and check for yourself... it PAYs to stay in the loop</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1344824685311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344824867430-183</Id><Title>mrstan: What's not to get? Dow, wow, wow. You are as stupid as you are rabid. Go froth at the bung somewhere else. Ha, ha, ha!</Title><Msg>Now, don't take it personally, but maybe you should stick your head back up SW's bung for awhile, and cool off. You sound like you're about to pop.</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344824867430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344824983249-184</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan will make Joe Biden an idiot !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344824468679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They - Romney and Ryan - shall, henceforth, be known as the two lying sacks of Mitt.</Msg><Username>hatepolitics101</Username><Timestamp>1344824983249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344825327034-185</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan will make Joe Biden an idiot !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344824468679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dialogue here is that we just can't afford free monies forever and Joe Biden will never believe it !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344825327034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344825340992-186</Id><Title>mrstan: I think Romney's record of using four dererments during the Vietnam War--that he vehemently supported--proves he has no integrity. Especially since four other young men had to take his place. I think the best term for Romney is "Chickehawk Coward Williar." Don't you agree?</Title><Msg>This is a message board, so keep your answer short.</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344825340992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:35:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344825631450-187</Id><Title>mrstan: Have you ever thought about NOT eating dog*s*h*i*t* anymore? It can't be good for you. Let's be honest. Look at yourself. You've become a rabid screaming fringe-right lunatic. All from eating dog*s*h*i*t. What do say? Try to give it up, OK?</Title><Msg>Now, remeber: This is a message board, so keep your responses brief.</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344825631450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344825671360-188</Id><Title>Obama is demonizing the riches in America</Title><Msg>Honestly, sir Mr. President, just what the hell is wrong with being rich ?</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344825671360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:41:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344826791549-189</Id><Title>mrstan: Gee, mrstan, it's been swell chatting with you. I hope you gained some insight from me. I always try to share my wisdom with those of a lesser intellectual status. It makes me feel good to know I was able to help someone in need. If you would really like to get ALL of your mind right, just read ALL of my message history. Buh-bye, now.</Title><Msg>Oh, and, please don't fret. I'll be back later to help keep you on track.</Msg><Username>dow_wow_wow</Username><Timestamp>1344826791549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344827424956-190</Id><Title>The problem with stupid Americans</Title><Msg>There is a tendency out there that Paul Ryan or Mitt Romney will pay off your irreponsible debt but the answer is NO ! You should pay for what you play. Romney &amp; Ryan will make great Presidents !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344827424956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344827506809-191</Id><Topic><Title>Fishing has been exceptionally good today. I've bagged a mess of liberal fish. Kinda stinky though. Think I will have to use them as fertilizer.</Title><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344823869838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 22:11:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpity-bumpity-bump!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344827506809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344827613805-192</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with stupid Americans</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344827424956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You go girl! Bumpity bumpity bump! (As in, 'pity the bums').</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344827613805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344827884385-193</Id><Title>stock market agnostic...</Title><Msg>it couldn't care less whether Romney or Obama is in power. That much is clear from the futures reaction to Romney's pick for VP. If anything it marginally disapproves as they're down slightly tonight.</Msg><Username>gollywogazoo</Username><Timestamp>1344827884385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344827975684-194</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with stupid Americans</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344827424956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:10:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see any reason why America has to keep on tanking like this. Obama is a nightmare don't you think ?</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344827975684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344829523532-195</Id><Title>Good luck finding a job under Obama !!!</Title><Msg>I know how you feel !!!</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344829523532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344829682617-196</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Warren's Attempt at a Coherent Synopsis???</Title><Username>sarcasm_och_witticism</Username><Timestamp>1344807914315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 17:45:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler was big on censorship, too.</Msg><Username>libertysword30</Username><Timestamp>1344829682617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 23:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>