<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348027373563-1</Id><Title>The Spirit of America is Alive and Well</Title><Msg>Many hardworking Americans were dissed by Mitt. So many low wage earners don't earn enough to pay income tax. Does Mitt think those on Social Security never paid taxes? Did Paul Ryan's father pay into Social Security? Of course he did, or son Paul would not have been able to collect it when his father passed.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1348027373563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:02:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348027512498-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only problem is you can't be rich without the poor and middle class, thats where the money comes from ! Everytime you pay your rent or mortgage, fill your tank, eat, buy something it trickles up, and we pay a lower tax on the income.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348027512498</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348027513900-3</Id><Topic><Title>How will dumpobamie and the other rectal drips spin the latest horrific display of arrogance and elitist superiority from Mitt?</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347943906817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will all of these fringe idiot fools do when Obama is re-elected?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1348027513900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348028029772-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It proves OBAMA is a BFKN TERRORIST! GET HIM OUT AMERICA before there i s CIVIL WAR!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028029772</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348028349243-5</Id><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Msg>We Americans will not ALLOW him another term without REBELLING against his LAWLESSNESS! FACT!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348028468502-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We could sell the south to Mexico, most red states are worthless welfare states anyway !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348028468502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348028640413-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who let the SATANIC KENYAN in the door??</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348028640413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348028780432-8</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>starkdirt you are a gay commie #$%$ k.</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348028780432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348029125877-9</Id><Topic><Title>The spirit of America is dead.</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1348026774070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never quit and BUY MORE AMMO!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348029125877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348029188883-10</Id><Topic><Title>The spirit of America is dead.</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1348026774070</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:52:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liar.</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348029188883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:33:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348034208900-11</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how are we? which 50 % are you talking about ? You like Mr. Runaway let him marry your moma as a second wife of course he is allowed to do so in Maxico where his great great grand father went to marry 5 wifes- what is wrong with America is simple so many stupid people don't appreciate their own country. They hate America and hate their fellow Americans. A country with crazy white trash youn men who have no soul. So I am going to give the honor and well come you to dementia family. It is growing every day thanks to the young white trash males . Let me tell you to go and watch FOX making the news and don't forget to make love to yourself to make your fun complete GOD BLESS AMERICA WHERE IDIOTS AND HATERS CAN EXPRESS THEIR FEELING</Msg><Username>dementia500</Username><Timestamp>1348034208900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 01:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348035282636-12</Id><Title>history repeats itself</Title><Msg>1989 Economic Bubble Further information: Japanese asset price bubble In the decades following World War II, Japan implemented stringent tariffs and policies to encourage the people to save their income. With more money in banks, loans and credit became easier to obtain, and with Japan running large trade surpluses, the yen appreciated against foreign currencies. This allowed local companies to invest in capital resources much more easily than their competitors overseas, which reduced the price of Japanese-made goods and widened the trade surplus further. And, with the yen appreciating, financial assets became very lucrative. With so much money readily available for investment, speculation was inevitable, particularly in the Tokyo Stock Exchange and the real estate market. The Nikkei stock index hit its all-time high on December 29, 1989 when it reached an intra-day high of 38,957.44 before closing at 38,915.87. The rates for housing, stocks, and bonds rose so much that at one point the government issued 100-year bonds. Additionally, banks granted increasingly risky loans. At the height of the bubble, real estate values were extremely over-valued. Prices were highest in Tokyo's Ginza district in 1989, with choice properties fetching over US$1.5 million per square meter ($139,000 per square foot). Prices were only slightly less in other areas of Tokyo. By 2004, prime "A" property in Tokyo's financial districts had slumped and Tokyo's residential homes were a fraction of their peak, but still managed to be listed as the most expensive real estate in the world. Trillions were wiped out with the combined collapse of the Tokyo stock and real estate markets. With Japan's economy driven by its high rates of reinvestment, this crash hit particularly hard. Investments were increasingly directed out of the country, and Japanese manufacturing firms lost some degree of their technological edge. As Japanese products became less competitive overseas, some people argue that the low consumption rate began to bear on the economy, causing a deflationary spiral. The easily obtainable credit that had helped create and engorge the real estate bubble continued to be a problem for several years to come, and as late as 1997, banks were still making loans that had a low guarantee of being repaid. Loan Officers and Investment staff had a hard time finding anything to invest in that would return a profit. Meanwhile, the extremely low interest rate offered for deposits, such as 0.1%, meant that ordinary Japanese savers were just as inclined to put their money under their beds as they were to put it in savings accounts. Correcting the credit problem became even more difficult as the government began to subsidize failing banks and businesses, creating many so-called "zombie businesses". Eventually a carry trade developed in which money was borrowed from Japan, invested for returns elsewhere and then the Japanese were paid back, with a nice profit for the trader. The time after the bubble's collapse (崩壊 hōkai?), which occurred gradually rather than catastrophically, is known as the "lost decade or end of the 20th century" (失われた10年 ushinawareta jūnen?) in Japan. The Nikkei 225 stock index eventually bottomed out at 7603.76 in April 2003, moved upward to a new peak of 18,138 in June 2007, before resuming a downward trend. The downward movement in the Nikkei is likely due to global as well as national economic problems.</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1348035282636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 02:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348035429047-13</Id><Topic><Title>history repeats itself</Title><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1348035282636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 02:14:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deflation from the 1990s to present See also: Lost Decade (Japan) Deflation in Japan started in the early 1990s. On March 19, 2001, the Bank of Japan and the Japanese government tried to eliminate deflation in the economy by reducing interest rates (part of their 'quantitative easing' policy). Despite having interest rates down near zero for a long period of time, this strategy did not succeed.[10] Once the near-zero interest rates failed to stop deflation, some economists, such as Paul Krugman, and some Japanese politicians spoke of deliberately causing (or at least creating the fear of) inflation.[11] In July 2006, the zero-rate policy was ended. In 2008, the Japanese Central Bank still has the lowest interest rates in the developed world, deflation has still not been eliminated[12] Systemic reasons for deflation in Japan can be said to include: Fallen asset prices. There was a large price bubble in both equities and real estate in Japan in the 1980s (peaking in late 1989). Insolvent companies: Banks lent to companies and individuals that invested in real estate. When real estate values dropped, many loans went unpaid. The banks could try to collect on the collateral (land), but due to reduced real estate values, this would not pay off the loan. Banks have delayed the decision to collect on the collateral, hoping asset prices would improve. These delays were allowed by national banking regulators. Some banks make even more loans to these companies that are used to service the debt they already have. This continuing process is known as maintaining an "unrealized loss", and until the assets are completely revalued and/or sold off (and the loss realized), it will continue to be a deflationary force in the economy. Insolvent banks: Banks with a large percentage of their loans which are "non-performing" (loans for which payments are not being made), but have not yet written them off. These banks cannot lend more money until they increase their cash reserves to cover the bad loans. Thus the quantity of loans are reduced and less funds are available for economic growth. Fear of insolvent banks: Japanese people are afraid that banks will collapse so they prefer to buy gold or (United States or Japanese) Treasury bonds instead of saving their money in a bank account. People also save by owning real estate. The Economist has suggested that improvements to bankruptcy law, land transfer law, and tax laws will aid Japan's economy. In October 2009 the Japanese government announced plans to increase tobacco and green taxes while reducing rates for small and medium sized companies, according to NHK. In 2011 Japan under Yoshihiko Noda decided to consider joining the Trans-Pacific Strategic Economic Partnership.</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1348035429047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 02:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348036231669-14</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't tell the difference between a Marxist Kenyan and an American ?</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348036231669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 02:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348038816323-15</Id><Topic><Title>Jesus’ Wife Mentioned on Fourth-Century Papyrus Fragment: Now Christian will get mad..like Muslims...lol</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348018867233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:41:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To those who study these things this is nothing new. The wedding feast where he turns water in to wine is his betrothal. How do we know? Mary anoints him with spikenard which was a rare oil only used in ritual where the bride to be anoints the groom to be. Also the washing of his feet was another part of the ritual the bride did to the groom. The evidence has been there before your eyes for those with the "ears to hear".</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348038816323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348039001645-16</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just try it punk.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348039001645</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348039238241-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tax codes have been used for years to redistribute wealth. there is nothing new about that. If you didn't realize it before it was your own ignorance,</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348039238241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348039484621-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Great Redistributor....Did you hear Obama caught on tape in 1998 saying he believed in using the government to redistribute wealth</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1348017450008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 21:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what do you call RR and GWB who established tax rates that redistributed wealth to those at the top of the food chain and placed the larger burden on the middle class? Socialism is a matter of who owns the means to produce income not the way the tax system taxes or distributes the tax money.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348039484621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348039745789-19</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan collected Social Security when his father passed. Is he part of Mitt's 47%?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1348026208097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:43:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He certainly was. So is that disabled Vet down the street,</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348039745789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348040206155-20</Id><Title>Mitt when did you pay taxes?</Title><Msg>You are late this year. How much would you pay under the Ryan plan? Zero? Did you even pay your 10% tithe to the church like a good Mormon is suppose to?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348040206155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 03:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348042146842-21</Id><Topic><Title>ALL of the polls have Obama leading AND gaining. Another term for President Obama.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347941291809</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney will have to take a stand on policy and this is where he'll divide his party. Either he'll #$%$ off the far right or the moderates. Either way he'll lose.</Msg><Username>acerdaprod</Username><Timestamp>1348042146842</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348042224162-22</Id><Topic><Title>you guys will be happy very soon BAC</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1348022721974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure hope so, been falling the past 2 days.....</Msg><Username>acerdaprod</Username><Timestamp>1348042224162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348044204372-23</Id><Title>47%?</Title><Msg>“There are 47 percent who are with him [President Obama], who are dependent upon government, who believe they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you name it,” Mitt Romney May 2012 Is that true? The short answer is, probably not. According to one analysis, only the very broadest definition of Americans "who are dependent upon government" yields a number approaching 47 percent. If Romney is including anyone who receives Social Security and Medicare – both considered an earned entitlement since Americans pay for them – the percentage of Americans receiving money from the government hits 37 percent. That number is from a study of 2010 census data by Robert Greenstein, executive director of the Center on Budget and Policy Priorities. He did a computer search of people receiving unemployment insurance, Supplemental Security Income (for the aged and disabled), workman’s compensation, Medicaid, Medicare, Social Security, the Children’s Health Insurance Program, and food stamps. Including veterans in the list added about 1 percent. Looking at 2007, which was closer to normal unemployment at 4.6 percent to 5 percent through the year, Mr. Greenstein found that 30 percent of the population received some form of entitlement. . Taking away Social Security and Medicare reduces the share of Americans receiving an entitlement to 25 percent. In 2007, the number was 18 percent. Some of the programs have a lot of overlap. For example, many of the 46.4 million people who receive Supplemental Nutrition Assistance (SNAP), or food stamps, also get Medicaid (some 58 million people). There is a similar overlap with Medicare and Social Security. Greenstein wonders if Romney was considering any household which received some sort of entitlement. For example, one member of the household could be on Social Security while another member worked full time. “You can get closer to 47 percent if you consider households,” he says. “But I don’t think most Americans would consider a spouse who works full time should be included as receiving an entitlement.” So how did Romney reach the 47 percent number? Greenstein thinks it was just an error by Romney, who also noted that 47 percent of the population does not pay income tax. “I think he conflated the two figures,” says Greenstein.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348044204372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348049888186-24</Id><Title>How long will the selling last??</Title><Msg>Don't want to see the $8's again</Msg><Username>hubertus88</Username><Timestamp>1348049888186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:18:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348050986255-25</Id><Topic><Title>47%?</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348044204372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone pays taxes of some sort or another from the time they get up in the morning until they go to sleep. Sales tax is the most seductive and choosen by the states. Property tax is especially onerous. Gas, internet, utilities...everything you touch has a tax component attached to it! What Mr. Romney opened up here in front of his friends the other night is what I have said for sometime. The wealthy don't live or think or really care for us "use to be middle classers"! They truely believe we are lazy especially the ones that come from family money. They contempt for us who worked our way through college but can't find a job like they did inside the family business. Steve Forbes is a classic example of what I speak. "I worked my way up from the bottom" why can't the rest of these punks do the same...ha Fighting for tax breaks for the top income earners which is the major platform of the Republican party will not get their candidate elected. Even the Democrat party had to back down on their pet issue of "Gun control" because it only makes you un-electable out here amoung the huddled masses!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348050986255</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348052155998-26</Id><Title>MITT IS CLASSLESS AND ARROGANT BABOON AND RYAN IS A CAPITAL LIAR</Title><Msg>makes them the clown brigade. what a bunch of jokers</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348052155998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348052963744-27</Id><Topic><Title>How long will the selling last??</Title><Username>hubertus88</Username><Timestamp>1348049888186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:18:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you talking about!? Today should be the day BAC breaks through $9.40 and higher.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1348052963744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348054721339-28</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fortunately he's a fangless little snake. He may get underfoot a lot, but no harm, no foul. ROTFLMAO the only things he could lead a rebellion against are sanity and hygiene. "FACT!"</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348054721339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348055116320-29</Id><Topic><Title>How will dumpobamie and the other rectal drips spin the latest horrific display of arrogance and elitist superiority from Mitt?</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347943906817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will spin the latest horrific display of arrogance and elitist superiority from Mitt by posting a non-stop repetitious pile of crap? You mean like this? OBAMA IS THE ENEMY! By obamistan . 7 hours ago . Permalink We Americans will not ALLOW him another term without REBELLING against his LAWLESSNESS! FACT! ROTFLMAO who are you, farragut, The Great Karnak?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348055116320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348055349507-30</Id><Topic><Title>47%?</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348044204372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have yet to meet a person of great inherited wealth who has a clue about how the world works for the rest of us. They’re often attractive in many ways - educated, sophisticated, at ease, even gracious. But when it comes to a gut understanding what it takes to make one’s way in the world without exceptional family influence, without parents with deep pockets, without educational pedigree, and without the benefits of insider savvy that steer so many already affluent youngsters onto elite circles and careers most kids don’t even know exist, the majority of wealthy people simply don’t understand it, because they’ve never had to. As a consequence, Mitt Romney, who may be a nice enough fellow - although the evidence is beginning to suggest otherwise - is simply not presidential timber. Like George W. Bush, he is another vainglorious, uninformed and incurious naif selected to serve as a front man for another Neoconservative coup. Only this time I suspect the coup will not occur.</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348055349507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348055422350-31</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348028349243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:19:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You folks get this wrong everytime...the argument here is over whether the country will house the huddle masses in "Obamavilles or Romneyvilles"! Neither party has an answer so they let the FED keep printing and now they even have the bankrupt Japanese central bank cutting rates and printing! We are so screwed but in Obamavilles I do believe we will get a weekly delivery of government cheese blocks....Romneyvilles will provide you with nothing except slogans about pulling yourselves up by your bootstraps....like Mittens ever worried about money....ha</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348055422350</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348055425560-32</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quit jabbering and learn to do math. You've got yourself all cranked up about a number you don't know how to interpret. ROTFLMAO I'm straining myself trying to avoid the phrase 'the calculus of the situation'.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348055425560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348055682543-33</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His commentary about the 47% is so much rich narcissistic bullsyhte. It's absurd that the party of cutting taxes turns around and blames seniors, students, minimum wage and other working poor and middle class people for not paying enough taxes, especially since a lot of lower income people pay a higher percentage in taxes than Mitt Romney. We do pay federal taxes, state taxes, sales and excise taxes and property taxes so - I guess it's bad if rich people pay taxes but good if poor people pay taxes- right? Give me a frackin' break. These recent revelations simply confirms a suspicion. Romney's a nasty piece of work and by most ANY measure unqualified to lead this nation. Highlow American Net'Zen</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348055682543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348055694702-34</Id><Title>GIVE US A REAL AMERICAN PRESIDENT ! NOT A MUSLIM PRESIDENT WITH MUSLIM TIES !</Title><Msg>..............................USAUSAUSAUSA</Msg><Username>america_help</Username><Timestamp>1348055694702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 07:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348056019995-35</Id><Topic><Title>47%?</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348044204372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said, total agreement. What does get my goat is when Mittens or Mr. Forbe spew in public that it is jealousy, envy or class warfare when we point out the fact that the wealthy have no understanding of lifes struggles! Try having MS, can't work, no family money and no access to treatment.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348056019995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348056021827-36</Id><Title>A CONGRESSIONAL HEARING ON ROMNEY INSULT TO SENIORS THAT DIDN'T PAY TAXES</Title><Msg>TO HAVE HIM APOLOGY</Msg><Username>dexter.bernanke</Username><Timestamp>1348056021827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348056177196-37</Id><Title>CENSSUS BUREAU 72% WHO VOTED IN 2008 WERE SENIORS THAT ROMNEY CALL LEACHES</Title><Msg>SHOULD BE BAN FOR RUNNING</Msg><Username>dexter.bernanke</Username><Timestamp>1348056177196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348056342674-38</Id><Title>Miitt............. really?</Title><Msg>Are you realy as dumb as you seem to be? You have no problem with supporting NO income tax for the very rich or Corp's,You have no problem hideing your Millions off shore to escape paying taxs, you REFUSE to release your tax info.because you know you pay less of a % in taxs than the vast majority of Americans or did you even pay any tax some years, but you express that the working poor , who pay no Federal income tax, are to be disgarded and no doubt is left that who have no interest in being their president if elected. You state that middle class people are those who earn $250,000 per year ....really Mitt, how out of touch with reality are you? You feel Womens rights are a waste of time and are not important ...... is this your Mormon background or are you just a woman hater? Your answer to international problems always lean towards Millitary action ...... Is this because it will make your Defense Contractor buddies who have given Millions to you Billions of $? You seem to have no lasting values and will change [flip] with the wind. You talk about how you are such a success, guess most of us could be if Daddy gave us Millions to get started. Your basic approach to our problems is to ensure the rich get much richer. So are you dumb or just so out of touch with reality..... you have no concept of the reality of the majority of America? EITHER WAY YOU HAVE PROVEN YOU DO NOT DESERVE TO BE THE PRESIDENT.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1348056342674</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348057096025-39</Id><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Msg>Come on, what reality are you living in? The party of deregulation of Wall street banksters and tax breaks for the already wealthy are in the penalty box...maybe forever!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348057364108-40</Id><Title>THANKS REPUCANS, YOU GAVE US A BABOON CALLED MITT</Title><Msg>WHAT A LOSER, LOVING IT.. HEHEHEHEHEHEHHEHEHE</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348057364108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348057668234-41</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS REPUCANS, YOU GAVE US A BABOON CALLED MITT</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348057364108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:22:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you gave us a N*A*Z*I dick-tater for a "president"</Msg><Username>farmkitty</Username><Timestamp>1348057668234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:27:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348058247666-42</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt is not ready for Prime Time</Title><Username>u_should_believe_me</Username><Timestamp>1348005934356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:05:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love how neocons leap to conclusions in the absence of data or facts, and then make sweeping and unsupported generalizations to denigrate anyone opposed to them. The first mistake in your 'reasoning' is that if I don't have more money than Mitt, I'm not qualified to criticize him. I'm never found even a casual association between money and brains, and it's always been a source of pride to me that I've got far more of the latter than the former. As the principal test engineer (for ten years) for a technology company that I helped take from start-up to annual revenues around $500 million, I was a key individual contributor and the most senior technical member of the operations group (a place where the rubber HAS to meet the road 24/7). I do not share your reverence for teams; time and time again I've watched pricey collections of meat come to irrational and destructive conclusions or dead ends, and had to unravel their muddy thinking and logical errors to get them moving again in productive directions. You know nothing of me, and yet have created a fairly lengthy fictitious resume for me. Let me fill in a blank or two before you've used up the whole page with your creative writing. The Meyers-Briggs personality inventory assesses me as an INTJ personality, Type A ++, and Results-Oriented ++. It is one of the rarest of the 16 personality types defined by Meyers-Briggs (approximately 1.8% of test subjects fall into this category) and this type of personality is often referred to as "mastermind" or "schemer". Here is a brief description of that type, and it fits me to a 'T': "INTJ: Have original minds and great drive for implementing their ideas and achieving their goals. Quickly see patterns in external events and develop long-range explanatory perspectives. When committed, organize a job and carry it through. Skeptical and independent, have high standards of competence and performance - for themselves and others." Key words: original and independent. By the way, I LOVE to be alone; lived on a remote mountaintop in northeast Thailand for 2 years, like nothing better than trout fishing by myself on backwoods Berkshire streams....aaaah, you haven't got a clue about me....but I'm sure that won't dissuade you from shoving me into whatever box makes you feel like you've put me in a cage. ROTFLMAO you wouldn't have made it through the first two questions of my typical interview, and neither would Mitt, because I designed them to reveal not technical competence, but intellectual honesty.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348058247666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348058366410-43</Id><Title>Republicans need the un-employment rate down and times to be getting better to get elected!</Title><Msg>That is the only time they can sell their message of low tax rates on the wealthy "job creators"! By extension, if low tax rates on the "job creators" worked, then we would have low un-employment right at this moment in time! Tax rates have never been lower on the "job creators".....ha</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348058366410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348059027455-44</Id><Topic><Title>When is Congress going to IMPEACH HOLDER for his stonewalling on Fast &amp; Furious ????</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348058616223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:43:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect at the same time the Bush administration tells the truth behind why we invaded Iraq and turned a blind eye on the Wall street banksters!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059027455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348059341031-45</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS REPUCANS, YOU GAVE US A BABOON CALLED MITT</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348057364108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:22:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW...Lets me get this right...so are choice now is either a baboon or a chimpanzee .... I still have to go with the baboon !</Msg><Username>buckman2777</Username><Timestamp>1348059341031</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348059399730-46</Id><Title>Gold Can Turn Pennies Into Dollars</Title><Msg>Penny gold mining stocks can return tremendous profits as the price of gold moves higher. Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is one stock to invest in here. The company's new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Gold production is expected to begin soon at the company's Tarantula site. Read the recent Yahoo news. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1348059399730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348059429692-47</Id><Title>Blacks are anti-gay--Obama and the Democratic Party is now the party for carpet munchers, bisexuals, homosexuals, transvestites, transsexuals, pedophiles, and fetishists. Add Socialism to this mix, stir the pot and what you get is something like Faraway!</Title><Msg>African-Americans, Election 2012, president obama..President Obama is at odds with many in the African-American clergy. WASHINGTON (CBS WASHINGTON) – Some black clergy see no good presidential choice between a Mormon candidate and one who supports gay marriage, so they are telling their flocks to stay home on Election Day. That’s a worrisome message for the nation’s first African-American president, who can’t afford to lose any voters from his base in a tight race. The pastors say their congregants are asking how a true Christian could back same-sex marriage, as President Barack Obama did in May. As for Republican Mitt Romney, the first Mormon nominee from a major party, congregants are questioning the theology of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints and its former ban on men of African descent in the priesthood. In 2008, Obama won 95 percent of black voters and is likely to get an overwhelming majority again. But any loss of votes would sting. “When President Obama made the public statement on gay marriage, I think it put a question in our minds as to what direction he’s taking the nation,” said the Rev. A.R. Bernard, founder of the predominantly African-American Christian Cultural Center in New York. Bernard, whose endorsement is much sought-after in New York and beyond, voted for Obama in 2008. He said he’s unsure how he’ll vote this year.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348059429692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348059613416-48</Id><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Msg>I am not a pacifist and really dislike religious lunatics of any religion but can not understand the Bush administrations actions in Iraq? Saddam was a bad guy but then there are so many bad guys in the world, why start there?</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348059752015-49</Id><Title>Are we now down to Johnson Vs. Obama</Title><Msg>Serious answers only, please!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348059752015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348059860517-50</Id><Topic><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the Oil and its good for Huliburton and the Bush clan.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348059860517</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348059928240-51</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He walked it back last night.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348059928240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348060270664-52</Id><Title>Fringe-right fools on a rampage since Mitt's mega gaffe. Do they think non-stop posting of stupidity will negate how stupid Romney is?</Title><Msg>Think again, fools.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060270664</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060274341-53</Id><Topic><Title>How long will the selling last??</Title><Username>hubertus88</Username><Timestamp>1348049888186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:18:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAC was up 20% the last couple of weeks. This is a healthy pullback. Relax.</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1348060274341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348060424207-54</Id><Title>Romney said, "I'd have a better chance of getting elected if my parents were Mexican."</Title><Msg>Should go over well with Hispanic voters. Mitt: what a fool!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060424207</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060508656-55</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the GOV spend to much money for wars and bailouts for the richs(Goldmans Sachs etc). No money has left for a better America.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348060508656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060537525-56</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt is a fool. Ryan is a stooge.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060537525</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060537877-57</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is still trying to walk it back. The rights belief that people who have any type of government assistance from social security to medicaid or food stamps or a disability check want to be in those circumstances and are nothing but deadbeats who view themselves as victims is offensive in the extreme. Your statements reinforce that stilted view.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348060537877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060566390-58</Id><Topic><Title>you guys will be happy very soon BAC</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1348022721974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you guys watching the big buy lots going on right now? I see $10 by options expiration date.</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1348060566390</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:16:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060656528-59</Id><Topic><Title>If Mitt doesn't have s*h*!*t* for brains, then what is that brown mass floating between his ears?</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347960642992</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:30:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else could it be? It certainly isn't brains.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060656528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:17:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060774521-60</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks are anti-gay--Obama and the Democratic Party is now the party for carpet munchers, bisexuals, homosexuals, transvestites, transsexuals, pedophiles, and fetishists. Add Socialism to this mix, stir the pot and what you get is something like Faraway!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348059429692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:57:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a racist POS! GFY!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060774521</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348060781892-61</Id><Title>Government assistance</Title><Msg>Oil companies, farmers, new businesses are they part of the 47%?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348060781892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348060947575-62</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is the muppet of Goldman Sachs. Goldman is the biggest spender for Obamba the Robert Mugabe of America.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348060947575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:22:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348060992477-63</Id><Title>"dumpobamie" is a nazi menace and a s*h*i*t* for brains fascist idiot. He really needs to find a Hitlerite message board.</Title><Msg>Lying #$%$</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060992477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348061054012-64</Id><Title>Soros will make sure Obama stays in</Title><Msg>hes the one who had that camera planted at the 50 k a plate dinner..</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348061054012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348061160993-65</Id><Title>ALL of the new polling indicates Obama lead is gaining, as expected. No one wants an elitist #$%$ for president.</Title><Msg>Only the monied elite who fund Mitt want their puppet in the pulpit.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061160993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348061264389-66</Id><Title>Obama give you money so you must vote him.</Title><Msg>US is the biggest banana country in the world.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348061264389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061384243-67</Id><Topic><Title>ALL of the new polling indicates Obama lead is gaining, as expected. No one wants an elitist #$%$ for president.</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061160993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:26:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK up to the $20Tr debt. Great man Robert Obama Mugabe.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348061384243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:29:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061428634-68</Id><Topic><Title>newvulgarian ....... same old Obamacrap ! ! !</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348061212738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, the Muslim Brotherhood pays you to post all of your Anti-American and Anti-Obama CRAP. Go figure. GFY! Lying POS!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061428634</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061462311-69</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans need the un-employment rate down and times to be getting better to get elected!</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348058366410</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:39:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans,,,Bush Rumsfeld Cheney....Pillage and Plunder Policies...we all know them. Cut Taxes ,,Create Wars for their Friends,,fill up Arlington Cemetery...who leave trillions in debt to be paid by the middle class</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348061462311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061545419-70</Id><Topic><Title>"dumpobamie" is a nazi menace and a s*h*i*t* for brains fascist idiot. He really needs to find a Hitlerite message board.</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348060992477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:23:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dump a lump gets paid to post. Why else would he post hundreds of Anti-American messages every day?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061545419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:32:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061577856-71</Id><Topic><Title>you guys will be happy very soon BAC</Title><Username>stevens1958</Username><Timestamp>1348022721974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would like that, but it seems a stretch. Thats 8% in three days. We'll see</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1348061577856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348061620718-72</Id><Title>Vote a women like Angela Merkel in germany and not a stupid cowboy like Romney or Obama</Title><Msg>America need not another cowboy but a person like Merkel .</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348061620718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:33:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348061639666-73</Id><Title>Republicans need a candidate who is not an idiot</Title><Msg>Not this year.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061639666</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061753714-74</Id><Topic><Title>Is dumpobamie too embarrassed to admit he is one of the 47%? Now we know why he never says anything about Romney.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347942611798</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:30:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dump a lump gets paid to post</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061753714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:35:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348061850262-75</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt sees himself as part of the monied elitist 1% that were born to rule over the plebeian 47%</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347944569768</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 01:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will Mitt diss today?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348061850262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348062040723-76</Id><Title>BAC site woes: 10M+ new mobile apps coming on line. $$$</Title><Msg>eom...</Msg><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1348062040723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062293702-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was stated last evening that they is many who need help - fine ; they also is many who sit on their butts - collect assiantance - an just flat dang well don't care about work - as sit on TV - crying they is - pooooor an then drive away - in their SUV's .! ;when they are living better than those busting their butts to make it point in fact - make them work .! After all - your's an my taxes are paying for that lazy crap .!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348062293702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062304073-78</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was stated last evening that they is many who need help - fine ; they also is many who sit on their butts - collect assiantance - an just flat dang well don't care about work - as sit on TV - crying they is - pooooor an then drive away - in their SUV's .! ;when they are living better than those busting their butts to make it point in fact - make them work .! After all - your's an my taxes are paying for that lazy crap .!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348062304073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062310330-79</Id><Topic><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt and his pals--the 1%-- made billions off of munitions, armaments, and war material sales. Republicans don't fight in wars. They fund them and profit from them.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062310330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348062367405-80</Id><Title>Republicans Pillage and Plunder to be fixed by Romney</Title><Msg>Rumsfeld,,Bush Cheney....widow makers...only care about money.. they exploit you...your mother,,,and anyone else</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348062367405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062513829-81</Id><Topic><Title>How will dumpobamie and the other rectal drips spin the latest horrific display of arrogance and elitist superiority from Mitt?</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347943906817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By continuing to make fools out of themselves with idiotic posts. They don't seem to realize their efforts are futile.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062513829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062519722-82</Id><Topic><Title>How will dumpobamie and the other rectal drips spin the latest horrific display of arrogance and elitist superiority from Mitt?</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347943906817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:51:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By continuing to make fools out of themselves with idiotic posts. They don't seem to realize their efforts are futile.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062519722</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062600530-83</Id><Topic><Title>newvulgarian ....... same old Obamacrap ! ! !</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348061212738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:26:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumpobamia - just put him on ignore - as I have - he is like those -picture on TV - yesterday with the OWS pictures - dumber than dumb .</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348062600530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348062635786-84</Id><Title>48 days to President Obama's re-election to a second term</Title><Msg>Plan to celebrate.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062635786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:50:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062692161-85</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney reminds of a female lawyer I knew , Conservative Republican..we would argue. I would tell her law of cooperation is civilized....she would say its a jungle...survival of the fittest. I would tell her survival of the fittest is for animals..she said,,it was life. She was wealthy had tons of money rolling in . One day Survival of the fittest caught up with her,,,a 15 year old kid shot her dead. She must be so happy dead with survival of the fittest.</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348062692161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062823684-86</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So true</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062823684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062867565-87</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox didn't report that. Go figure.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062867565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:54:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062873695-88</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox didn't report that. Go figure.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062873695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:54:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348062944601-89</Id><Title>Romney lives on Daddys Money</Title><Msg>Send Romney to Afghan lets him fight for 2 years,,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348062944601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062992180-90</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Paul Ryan who collected Social Security after his father died.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348062992180</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:56:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063000261-91</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Paul Ryan who collected Social Security after his father died.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063000261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:56:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063005193-92</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks are anti-gay--Obama and the Democratic Party is now the party for carpet munchers, bisexuals, homosexuals, transvestites, transsexuals, pedophiles, and fetishists. Add Socialism to this mix, stir the pot and what you get is something like Faraway!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348059429692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:57:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is it racist to state the truth? That's what's wrong with you Democrats. You condone lying, cheating and stealing, but anything resembling the truth, you break out your old racist lingo. Those days are coming to an end...a/s/s/h/o/l/e.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348063005193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063066720-93</Id><Topic><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heroin is $1,0000,000 1/2 Barrel..thats why we are in Afghan......Cheney Haliburton is why we went to Iraq,,,Pillage and Plunder</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348063066720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063070947-94</Id><Topic><Title>Romney finally has a plan. He's not going to use Dan Quayle as his debate coach.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347941123200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He finally got one thing right.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063070947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063106916-95</Id><Topic><Title>BAC site woes: 10M+ new mobile apps coming on line. $$$</Title><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1348062040723</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and phluck all these political posts !</Msg><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1348063106916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063119435-96</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>an your crazy riddle - is stupid - to say it was funny that some stupid - punk kid - shot some one dead - is just plain nutty</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348063119435</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:58:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063135418-97</Id><Topic><Title>Blacks are anti-gay--Obama and the Democratic Party is now the party for carpet munchers, bisexuals, homosexuals, transvestites, transsexuals, pedophiles, and fetishists. Add Socialism to this mix, stir the pot and what you get is something like Faraway!</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348059429692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:57:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought that was your MOTHER</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348063135418</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063181244-98</Id><Topic><Title>Romney lives on Daddys Money</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348062944601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:55:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are going on ignore but Romney gave his inheritance to charity idiot.</Msg><Username>winkdog</Username><Timestamp>1348063181244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063248700-99</Id><Title>Democrats-Party of Lawyers</Title><Msg>Two Democrat lawyers had been stranded on a desert island for several months. The only thing on the island was a tall coconut tree that provided them their only food. Each day one of the lawyers would climb to the top to see if he could spot a rescue boat coming...One day the lawyer yelled down from the tree, "WOW, I just can't believe my eyes. There is a woman out there floating in our direction." The lawyer on the ground was most skeptical and said, "You're hallucinating, you've finally lost your mind." But within a few minutes, up on the beach floated a stunningly beautiful woman, face up, totally naked, unconscious, without even so much as a ring or earrings on her person. The two Democrat lawyers went down to the water, dragged her up on the beach and discovered, yes, she was alive, warm and breathing. One said to the other, "You know, we've been on this God forsaken island for months now without a woman. It's been such a long, long time... So... Do you think we should... well... You know... Screw her?" Screw her out of WHAT?!?" asked the other lawyer.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348063248700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063270455-100</Id><Title>Romney sold soul to Satan</Title><Msg>Romney is owned by Satan,,,,all he cares about is Money,,,he has no soul...he is pure Plastic</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348063270455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063316543-101</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan collected Social Security when his father passed. Is he part of Mitt's 47%?</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1348026208097</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:43:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the vetting process for Republican vice-presidential candidates failed again.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063316543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:01:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063438808-102</Id><Title>Romney is done! lets move back to discussing BAC</Title><Msg>Who is with me?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348063438808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063456359-103</Id><Title>The vetting process for Republican vice-presidential candidates failed again. Paul Ryan collected Social Security after his father's death, so he's one of Mitt's despised 47%</Title><Msg>Republicans of late have really dumbed down. Bush jr., Palin, Mitt. What next?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063456359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063511261-104</Id><Title>Keep buying people..she's going HIGHER AND HIGHER..NO STOPPING THE BAC train</Title><Msg>go baby!</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1348063511261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063745373-105</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is done! lets move back to discussing BAC</Title><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348063438808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:03:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not me .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348063745373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063821536-106</Id><Title>Notice how the fringe-right fools NEVER post anything about Romney.</Title><Msg>Why is that, dump o lump? Don't you want to publicly proclaim your support for Romney like you continually condemn America and Obama?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063821536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348063956267-107</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually liberty YOUR comment forwards a stilted view.....I for instance am fiscally to the right, but I do not have the view you note......ie. view everyone as deadbeats...etc.....that would be a very prejudiced view....your comment makes it seem that EVERYONE to the right has no sense of humanity or compassion......it's simple not true.....and frankly It's highly disingenuous that you forward that viewpoint while at the same time accusing me of presenting a stilted view.....can you see that? You're forwarding prejudice........ Obviously there extremes on both the left and the right.....so what....that doesn't mean that ALL people think..... .....so come off your high horse and get real</Msg><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348063956267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348064007630-108</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.......there are obviously all manner of circumstances in which people find themselves....and these can be incredibly unfair.......I think in part what people object to in talking point lamentations from the left.....is we ALL have had unfair things happen to us...we all have obstacles and difficulties.......we've all lost jobs and had idiot bosses.......so for people who have overcome such, they realize everyone has a choice.........give up or push through and make things come out right.......we need more people making things go right and trying....and less giving up if things are going to get better ....</Msg><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348064007630</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348064406848-109</Id><Title>Sales of existing homes surge in August best in4 years. OBAMA DOW JONES UP 7200 SINCE HE TOOK OVER</Title><Msg>Sales of existing homes surge in August Level of activity best since May 2010</Msg><Username>dexter.bernanke</Username><Timestamp>1348064406848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348064529833-110</Id><Title>ITMN under accumulation</Title><Msg>possible buyout--15.00</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348064529833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348064823064-111</Id><Topic><Title>What did the Romney / Ryan Clown Car hit today? Only 47% of the voters.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1348023972830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:06:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheriff Joe at the wheel.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348064823064</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348064823091-112</Id><Topic><Title>What did the Romney / Ryan Clown Car hit today? Only 47% of the voters.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1348023972830</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:06:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sheriff Joe at the wheel.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348064823091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348065074564-113</Id><Title>After the reelection the war USA making in Europe is over(Obamba don t need it anymore)</Title><Msg>The distroying campign of the Euro wil be finished.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348065074564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348065435344-114</Id><Title>BAC would be a nice topic on this board.. Whats going on with BAC</Title><Msg>Lets get some comments about BAC here...</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1348065435344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348065945929-115</Id><Topic><Title>Notice how the fringe-right fools NEVER post anything about Romney.</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063821536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:10:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because we believe that this - IS the BAC message board - not about your beliefs - or silly word games .!!! back to ignore you go .!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348065945929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348066009387-116</Id><Title>HCLP is a short to 17.00</Title><Msg>too much supply--prices are going down--and the lock up will end soon..</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066009387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348066049584-117</Id><Topic><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had to attack Iraq for the same reason we must now attack Iran, to keep Kansas City and Haifa safe Don't you remember?</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1348066049584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348066139690-118</Id><Topic><Title>HCLP is a short to 17.00</Title><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066009387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>17.00 was the ipo --and was over priced to begin with</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066139690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348066207070-119</Id><Title>TraderDick--hop on that HCLP short</Title><Msg>17.00 to cover or less.</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066207070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348066315736-120</Id><Topic><Title>Romney sold soul to Satan</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348063270455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever the price, Satan overpaid.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1348066315736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348066856323-121</Id><Topic><Title>Romney sold soul to Satan</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348063270455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:01:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all the Mo Mos are in Satans hands--they deserve each other</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066856323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348067014819-122</Id><Title>MITT loves those hands on Virgin marriage ceremonies--thats how he got his name</Title><Msg>cant keep his mitts off the brides to be...</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348067014819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348067282205-123</Id><Title>golf &amp; campaigning, campaigning &amp; golf, - repeat. this is obama.</Title><Msg>meanwhile the american people are wondering if they will have a job tomorrow, if they will be able to pay their bills, if they will pass a better life to their children, if they will eat? while oblivious and obnoxious obamam goes on his merry way without a concern in the world. amazing right?</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348067282205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348067404456-124</Id><Title>GASL reversal</Title><Msg>should run back to re test 35.00</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348067404456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348067499989-125</Id><Title>US Ambassador dead, and obambam goes on letterman. but can't make time for netanyahu</Title><Msg>obama - president you say? heh heh, a buster brown shoe would be more qualified</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348067499989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348067613591-126</Id><Topic><Title>US Ambassador dead, and obambam goes on letterman. but can't make time for netanyahu</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348067499989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:11:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called talking to the American people. He is the president of America, remember??</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348067613591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348067631177-127</Id><Title>2 stupid cowboys Obama and Roney</Title><Msg>No choice.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348067631177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348067755639-128</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL</Msg><Username>spock_has_spoke</Username><Timestamp>1348067755639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348067857724-129</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in BAC</Title><Username>francinafag6400</Username><Timestamp>1348060370548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>milliekme13436</Username><Timestamp>1348067857724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348068742769-130</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will be more flexible after my last election" - Obama to Dmitry on negotiating disarming for Russia.</Msg><Username>tomandlynntigard</Username><Timestamp>1348068742769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348068998591-131</Id><Topic><Title>I understand going after al-Qaeda and even taking on the Afgan Taliban but will some Republican tell me why we went to Iraq?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348059613416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:00:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other than Bush junior promissing daddy that he'll get Saddam for him, I don't know of any reason. Saddan was a nice guy, it turns out, compared to the idiots running Irak now. Takes a Bush to f'k things up.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1348068998591</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348069379884-132</Id><Title>Even Sarah Palin thinks Mitt is a Mormon.</Title><Msg>She said : Mitt is just not very smart.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1348069379884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348069824113-133</Id><Title>And Now, A Word From Charles-- Charles Krauthammer on "Special Report with Bret Baier."</Title><Msg>"Look at a featured speaker at Democrat convention, Sandra Fluke. Here's a woman who is from an elite law school, is going to make $160,000 as a starting salary in the private sector. What is her great demand? Why was she the big star? Demanding that ordinary Americans average income $50,000 pay her contraceptives. That is personification of the idea of entitlement, of victimization. That is entire idea of ask not what you can do for your country. Ask what your country can do for you. This is exactly what Romney is talking about."</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348069824113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348070209880-134</Id><Topic><Title>HCLP is a short to 17.00</Title><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066009387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already down 60 cents and going lower..</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348070209880</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348070425809-135</Id><Topic><Title>And Now, A Word From Charles-- Charles Krauthammer on "Special Report with Bret Baier."</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348069824113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he cared, he would know that $50000 is the median NOT average HOUSEHOLD income.</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348070425809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348070434051-136</Id><Topic><Title>HCLP is a short to 17.00</Title><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066009387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:46:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20.18 is 200DMA</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348070434051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348070636537-137</Id><Topic><Title>France went ahead and imposed the tax</Title><Username>derrtuio</Username><Timestamp>1327938599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-01-30 10:49:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The French really believe that the Law of Gravity does not apply to them...Zero Growt, 75pct Wealth Tax, Transaction tax in a country that is now as bureaucratic as Honduras...</Msg><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1348070636537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348071315075-138</Id><Title>Obama Win means more BIG Government and LOW GROWTH for USA INC.,</Title><Msg>IMHO Obama will be re-elected and USA will look more like France in 4 years i.e Gvt will control an increasing share of US economy</Msg><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1348071315075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348071468612-139</Id><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Msg>What do you think?</Msg><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348072426363-140</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama is doing such a great job and has such wide support .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348070891197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>have you any idea how long Romney has been campaigning not stop?? Howz 8 years for ya?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348072426363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:33:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348072532799-141</Id><Topic><Title>FB Facebook is on fire!!!!! $22.43 +0.56</Title><Username>lockkey110</Username><Timestamp>1348072433360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not interested</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1348072532799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348072662784-142</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Win means more BIG Government and LOW GROWTH for USA INC.,</Title><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1348071315075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:15:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Le grand gouvernement est un grand problème</Msg><Username>pondering1959</Username><Timestamp>1348072662784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348072734896-143</Id><Title>Obama is Robert Mugabe from Amerika</Title><Msg>US$ is worthless printed toilet paper.</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348072734896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348072952936-144</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Win means more BIG Government and LOW GROWTH for USA INC.,</Title><Username>greenpoint21</Username><Timestamp>1348071315075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:15:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth is this the first time the goverments gotten smaller under any president ! and thats another reason the unemployment has stayed high.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348072952936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348073061047-145</Id><Title>Obama gives you money via stockmarket and interest.</Title><Msg>Do you vote him because he gives you much money. Is this real or only inflation ?</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348073061047</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348073089620-146</Id><Topic><Title>Is BAC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>sharitadvh69408</Username><Timestamp>1348065765984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:42:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>ladonnajcl718</Username><Timestamp>1348073089620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348073256600-147</Id><Title>The king gives monet to the folk</Title><Msg>Why ?</Msg><Username>hbarackdolf</Username><Timestamp>1348073256600</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348073317684-148</Id><Topic><Title>Even Sarah Palin thinks Mitt is a Mormon.</Title><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1348069379884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:42:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've meet a lot of the super rich they tend to be very good at one that makes money and the ones born rich tend to have super egos without the brains.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348073317684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348073965431-149</Id><Topic><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Disagree...market is up 4/10 of one percent. BAC is up 1.73%. This stock has momentum</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1348073965431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348074118179-150</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in BAC</Title><Username>francinafag6400</Username><Timestamp>1348060370548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally! I found something informative.</Msg><Username>ashliespo43365</Username><Timestamp>1348074118179</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348074566728-151</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, so you like Brown and Mcmahon don"t agree with his statement but many are defending it. You don't have to read far on this board to see the right who believe exactly what he said. Quote "There are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent on government, who believe that, that they are victims, who believe that government has the responsibility to care for them. Who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing.”</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348074566728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348074762063-152</Id><Topic><Title>Take your interest to ...Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) 4 a 5 X's the money</Title><Username>wwzg</Username><Timestamp>1347299409519</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:50:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll agree</Msg><Username>wwzg</Username><Timestamp>1348074762063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348075535549-153</Id><Topic><Title>TraderDick--hop on that HCLP short</Title><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348066207070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:50:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>down 3.25%--and going lower</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348075535549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348075679340-154</Id><Title>Time to short sell BMA as well</Title><Msg>way over done--Argentina pos..</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348075679340</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348075929798-155</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in BAC</Title><Username>francinafag6400</Username><Timestamp>1348060370548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>vivancbr36839</Username><Timestamp>1348075929798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348076027678-156</Id><Title>rigged fraud markets lol look at em churn</Title><Msg>comical...</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348076027678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348076076070-157</Id><Title>~$9.25 to ~$9.45 gap</Title><Msg>looks like the bid is being painstakingly walked back down to fill some percentage of the opening gap. Bid now $9.32. I've opened a swing trading tranche here, and will add on further weakness. It's a trade so I'll be happy with +10 pennies for now.. Let's see how it plays out. Highlow American Net'Zen</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348076076070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348076204495-158</Id><Topic><Title>MITT IS CLASSLESS AND ARROGANT BABOON AND RYAN IS A CAPITAL LIAR</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348052155998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348076204495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:36:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348076454221-159</Id><Title>When Money Dies: The Nightmare of the Weimar Collapse</Title><Msg>by ADAM FERGUSSON A snipet WHEN a nation's money is no longer a source of security, and when inflation has become the concern of an entire people, it is natural to turn for information and guidance to the history of other societies who have already undergone this most tragic and upsetting of human experiences. Yet to survey the great array of literature of all kinds — economic, military, social, historic, political, and biographical — which deals with the fortunes of the defeated Central Powers after the First World War is to discover one particular shortage. Either the economic analyses of the times (for reasons best known to economists who sometimes tend to think that inflations are deliberate acts of fiscal policy) have ignored the human element, to say nothing in the case of the Weimar Republic and of post-revolutionary Austria of the military and political elements; or the historical accounts, though of impressive erudition and insight, have overlooked — or at least much underesti</Msg><Username>rhinoinchgo</Username><Timestamp>1348076454221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348076562688-160</Id><Topic><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like I could be correct. This morning was a Bull trap. I'm betting on $9 by friday. Good luck...</Msg><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348076562688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:42:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348076607332-161</Id><Topic><Title>47%?</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348044204372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 04:43:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Accordingly, Mitten has no chance to win the election. He should give up right now... why waste more than a billion dollars?</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348076607332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348077579833-162</Id><Topic><Title>rigged fraud markets lol look at em churn</Title><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348076027678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HFT's in love and having a feeding frenzy churning and churning and churning it again and again and again. All at a mico-second level for fractions of pennies... So it goes...bid now $9.30 and being set-up to go back into the $9.20's..</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348077579833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348077717404-163</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in BAC</Title><Username>francinafag6400</Username><Timestamp>1348060370548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>preciousrwi317</Username><Timestamp>1348077717404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348077737769-164</Id><Topic><Title>FB Facebook is on fire!!!!! $22.43 +0.56</Title><Username>lockkey110</Username><Timestamp>1348072433360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:33:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a board for BAC, are you that lame?</Msg><Username>cyclefund</Username><Timestamp>1348077737769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348078415588-165</Id><Title>Mitt Romney's father George Romney was on "welfare relief" when he first arrived in the U.S</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's father George Romney was on "welfare relief" when he first arrived in the U.S., according to an interview with Romney's mother Lenore recorded in 1962. George Romney was born in Mexico and moved with his family to El Paso, Texas, during the Mexican Revolution, reports addictinginfo.org. The family received $250, food, clothing, and other supplies from the U.S. government. The family later invested some of their money in the stock market and used that cash to send George Romney to college. This family were illegal, then used welfare money to invest in the stock market. YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME Then you got ryan who’s family had a construction business, filed for social security, and saved it for college (which is illegal). THIS ALMOST TOOOO HARD TO BELIEVE</Msg><Username>dexter.bernanke</Username><Timestamp>1348078415588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348078439379-166</Id><Title>'AA' to takeover lowest PPS stock on DOW from 'BAC'. $0.17 gap and closing</Title><Msg>eom....</Msg><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1348078439379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348078594538-167</Id><Title>Even Trump would be better than Romney</Title><Msg>Trump is dull but not dumb. Romney is dull and dumb.</Msg><Username>hawaiianlogic</Username><Timestamp>1348078594538</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348078668838-168</Id><Topic><Title>rigged fraud markets lol look at em churn</Title><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348076027678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here comes the $9.20's again....bid at $9.30 weakening...with it getting hit with a constant rain of small prints on it...</Msg><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348078668838</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348079041108-169</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt is not ready for Prime Time</Title><Username>u_should_believe_me</Username><Timestamp>1348005934356</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:05:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems aren't nervous...well maybe about which states will count their votes. Despite the polls trying to keep main-stream media alive through the election, GOP has self-destructed again. Even locally it will be hard to not lose the house and senate control. Could be a landslide. The Nazis only control Florida. Ohio is a tough vote to the neocons. Too many poor people are losing family to Arlington Nat Cem and the Bush wars to forget that Mitt does not pay their taxes. They do. 47 percent of America is on entitlement, and only the rich pay for that in trickle-down doesn't pass for truth or even a good imagination. Poll of 100 people in UTAH the source?</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1348079041108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348079222737-170</Id><Topic><Title>rigged fraud markets lol look at em churn</Title><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348076027678</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like it may have stopped. Lets see what happens now. Look what they did to MS</Msg><Username>v.chenzo</Username><Timestamp>1348079222737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348079261027-171</Id><Topic><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MAjor drop coming before close. Will close deep in red.</Msg><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079261027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348079324599-172</Id><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Msg>Major dump job coming this afternoon. This will close deep into the red.</Msg><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348079571492-173</Id><Title>HCLP makes the biggest % loser list--</Title><Msg>next victim--BMA</Msg><Username>shortburner2013</Username><Timestamp>1348079571492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348079642789-174</Id><Topic><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>gwhickle</Username><Timestamp>1348079642789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348081950650-175</Id><Title>Chick-fil-A has agreed to stop funding groups with anti-same-sex marriage stances.</Title><Msg>What a disaster! The gays are taking over the country. Vote for Romney.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1348081950650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348081990280-176</Id><Topic><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to be kidding! BAC is headed in the up direction. I know personally that they are cutting costs, because I own a lot of their debt and they have been collecting their corporate bonds back when ever they're available. I have had 14 called in over the last 2 months of the ones I owned. I believe they have called 44 more that I didn't own. Just one of their corporate bonds, 59022CAB9 they called last month was over $2 billion. At 6.22%, this is a lot of saving and an increase on the bottom line of the balance sheet.</Msg><Username>m.inally</Username><Timestamp>1348081990280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348082002035-177</Id><Title>New High Visa!</Title><Msg>The new high $9.55</Msg><Username>josefernandez892</Username><Timestamp>1348082002035</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348082053039-178</Id><Topic><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing more fun than watching #$%$ predict the market.</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1348082053039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348082184852-179</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney's father George Romney was on "welfare relief" when he first arrived in the U.S</Title><Username>dexter.bernanke</Username><Timestamp>1348078415588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:13:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bunch of crooks. All Mormons are on welfare, with 20 wifes and 50 kids you get like 70 deductions.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1348082184852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348082510995-180</Id><Topic><Title>looking weak. T I M B E R..looks like $9 on friday.</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348071468612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you're correct. This is weak price action, especially since the housing numbers are the only catalyst for the price to go up until earnings in a month. If the price action is good, we should be at over $9.60 this morning.</Msg><Username>wer9man</Username><Timestamp>1348082510995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348082598010-181</Id><Topic><Title>BAC may perhaps wind up the company to see this month.</Title><Username>williamswarner49</Username><Timestamp>1348081392060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumor has it that he or she are pondering switching to a pay as you go subscription system.</Msg><Username>billybarger106</Username><Timestamp>1348082598010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348082934598-182</Id><Topic><Title>BAC may perhaps wind up the company to see this month.</Title><Username>williamswarner49</Username><Timestamp>1348081392060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he is a rich man</Msg><Username>keithkearns33</Username><Timestamp>1348082934598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348083287680-183</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287131735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:25:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$6++ last trade.....huge breakout ahead....look at chart!!</Msg><Username>john.kenell</Username><Timestamp>1348083287680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348083345566-184</Id><Topic><Title>BAC may well become the ticker to view this week.</Title><Username>robertelledge57</Username><Timestamp>1348077958728</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>williampickering924</Username><Timestamp>1348083345566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348083393073-185</Id><Title>NTWK $6....GOING TO $10++....EXPONENTIAL PROFITABLE GROWTH OF CLOUD DICISIONS.....6 PE</Title><Msg>$6++ last trade.....huge breakout ahead....look at chart!!</Msg><Username>john.kenell</Username><Timestamp>1348083393073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348084156116-186</Id><Topic><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great forecast. What else do you expect so I can act accordingly?</Msg><Username>cyclefund</Username><Timestamp>1348084156116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348084977609-187</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama is doing such a great job and has such wide support .....</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348070891197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:08:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It hurts, I know but the people love him, and he is coming back. Whats next for Romney? Something in his Church?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348084977609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348085199322-188</Id><Topic><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You posted this before, didn't you, now?</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348085199322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348085381815-189</Id><Topic><Title>Questions for Options Traders</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1347703704304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 06:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice. Well best of luck to you my friend. I thought about doing Options Trading, even got it enabled on my account. Fortunately it takes 3-5 days to enable it as I recall. I used that time to learn as much as possible and the more I learned the less comfortable I felt with it. Now I'm just starting out with what I have and adding to BAC a month at a time. It's not much but I don't need the money or returns for years to come so I'm not concerned with what happens this or next quarter with BAC. I'm confident in my returns 5 or 7 years down the road.</Msg><Username>samwise547</Username><Timestamp>1348085381815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348085381845-190</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republicans are toast! Watch the Republcian fund raising numbers over the next few weeks! The big dogs aren't going to throw good money down the drain on Mittens campaign. Better spent trying to fix the electoral college computers!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348085381845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348085699393-191</Id><Topic><Title>10% pullback on its way. BAC headed to $8.50</Title><Username>icsammis</Username><Timestamp>1348079324599</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:28:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I know, however when I hear a comment like icsammis made, I try to help so that they don't get caught up in the upcoming squeeze. People can loose everything on this bet and I mean everything. There's no end to the amount a person can loose when shorting. When you own a stock, you loose only the value of the stock. When short the sky is the limit. I don't want to hear of anyone going through that.</Msg><Username>m.inally</Username><Timestamp>1348085699393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348086367852-192</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're heavily depending on short political memory. It has worked before. However, they're oblivious to the fact that now the new info age is upon us and people are much more connected to keep the uninformed amongst them up to date. Times are against such tricksters and liars. The Republican authoritarian obstinate character makes their leaders and followers blinded to the changes of times and of people. Most people are open and accepting of progress... except those who are ideologues and blind followers- Republicans! A landslide win for Obama is in the making!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348086367852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:26:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348086921004-193</Id><Title>hilarious how liberals think people believe what they say. all you need to know about what caused the financial meltdown of ’08. is</Title><Msg>the real history of the deterioration of mortgage underwriting standards, and the reasons for it, which led to the financial collapse of 2008. enter barney frank, for most of his career, congressman frank was one of the leaders of the effort in congress to meet the demands of activists like ACORN for an easing of underwriting standards in order to make home ownership more accessible to more people. It was perhaps a worthwhile goal, but it caused the financial crisis when it was done by lowering mortgage underwriting standards. in the end, it was a colossal policy error by congress and two presidential administrations of carter and clinton along with HUD. barney frank admitted this. to his credit, frank recognized his error by 2007, but by that time it was too late. fannie and freddie were nearing insolvency and the housing market was so engorged with subprime and other low quality mortgages that nothing could save it. Bush sounded the alarms in 2003, but was overruled by the dems. blockade of any investigation into fannie &amp; freddie.</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348086921004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348087193718-194</Id><Title>liberals always laugh at other peoples misfortunes and misery. and are arrogant</Title><Msg>prima donnas. notice that?</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348087193718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348087375608-195</Id><Title>The SEALS REMOVED ONE THREAT TO AMERICA!</Title><Msg>REMOVE THE OTHER in NOvember!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348087375608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348087653212-196</Id><Topic><Title>The SEALS REMOVED ONE THREAT TO AMERICA!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348087375608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:42:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why didn't Bush give the order. Perhaps the Republicans like terrorists more than real Americans.</Msg><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348087653212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348087876972-197</Id><Topic><Title>liberals always laugh at other peoples misfortunes and misery. and are arrogant</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348087193718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lying, sloganeering, hiding behind GOP history will get you and the few millions like will get you nowhere. You are facing here a tsunami. A landslide win for Obama is in the making and the polls are going to make that quite clear... BEFORE the election. Liars, exploiters, and "robber barons"... can no more hide... like it was before... because most people can access the facts speedily to get to the facts as it just happened with the stupid and mindless Romney statements. He has no chance of becoming president and the GOP is a doomed party. Besides... demographic changes are also against the GOP.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348087876972</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348088389826-198</Id><Title>Bank of America discriminates against their disabled employees</Title><Msg>What else is new Bank of America - screw employees, screw customers. Lawsuit filed by former employee - one manager told him bank doesnt follow ADA rules.</Msg><Username>mittromney3400</Username><Timestamp>1348088389826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348088402708-199</Id><Title>Bank of America discriminates against their disabled employees</Title><Msg>What else is new Bank of America - screw employees, screw customers. Lawsuit filed by former employee - one manager told him bank doesnt follow ADA rules.</Msg><Username>mittromney3400</Username><Timestamp>1348088402708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348088631376-200</Id><Topic><Title>The SEALS REMOVED ONE THREAT TO AMERICA!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348087375608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:42:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HOOOONK! YOU LOSE HOMEUS! REMOVE THE OTHER in NOvember!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348088631376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348088895997-201</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America discriminates against their disabled employees</Title><Username>mittromney3400</Username><Timestamp>1348088402708</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:00:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mindless dribble "</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1348088895997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348089641038-202</Id><Topic><Title>liberals always laugh at other peoples misfortunes and misery. and are arrogant</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348087193718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A landslide win for Obama" #$%$ Over our DEAD BODY! OBAMA MUST LEAVE!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348089641038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348089661309-203</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America discriminates against their disabled employees</Title><Username>mittromney3400</Username><Timestamp>1348088389826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:59:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would issue a short on that guys job.</Msg><Username>u_should_believe_me</Username><Timestamp>1348089661309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348089831316-204</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, a landslide win for Obama surely is in the making. They doomed themselves and any voter of ave. intelligence and above has seen the light. The tide of speedy communications and speedy discovery of the facts will destroy the GOP pretenders who have relied of lies and distortions. Besides their 4 years of SABOTAGING the president is fresh in the minds of most voters. The GOP- the materialists - believe in giving tax breaks to the super rich 1%! They will PRETEND and resort to trickery a la Karl Rove (from the Lee Atwater school of GOP tricksters) style. But, they will FAIL!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348089831316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348089890721-205</Id><Title>Old Guys on SS who still like Romney</Title><Msg>He thinks you are a leach on America.</Msg><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348089890721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348090399547-206</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans blow up the financial world and now they expect the un-employed as a consequence of their actions to elect them?</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1348057096025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arguing with a lying communist idiot like you is a waste of time. COMMIES will be CRUSHED!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348090399547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:33:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348090460188-207</Id><Title>EVERYTIME I HEAR A COMMUNIST LIE...</Title><Msg>I buy a little more AMMO!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348090460188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348090697442-208</Id><Topic><Title>Questions for Options Traders</Title><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1347703704304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 06:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sawwise547, Best of luck to all of us, longs! If you are just starting out playing options, I would suggest learning how to Write A Covered Call (Call: Sell to Open) first. Rather than just selling the stocks and risk the chance of making a few more cents too early, you can write a covered call and really maximize your gains, especially when it is only a few days before options expiration date. I often write covered calls a few days before options expiration date when I am really ready to let go those shares (get called away). As for my original post, athought it did not cost me anything, I am so disappointed that BAC did not even reach close to $9.60 today! With that said, BAC helped me master the art of verballly cursing in five different languages today (best way to vent). lol It's time for me to learn about "puts". Can anyone please confirm if "Selling A Put" is the opposite of selling a call? LOL</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1348090697442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348090872555-209</Id><Topic><Title>Old Guys on SS who still like Romney</Title><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348089890721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney and Trump both prove that having a lot of money is not a sign of intelligence.... but even obtuse and warped minds can make money. No matter how much money they have, both show an alarming lack of intelligence, lack of understanding and compassion, and are stuck on generalities. That limited mindset and character makeup is due to early conditioning that money=intelligence whereas there is no such thing. One can't buy intelligence, compassion, and humanity... even though one can get higher degrees in education. It depends on a lot more (like tough life challenges and hardship to develop awareness, understanding, reverence and humanity, etc.) than having grown up in a rich family like these two mental midgets who classify half the U.S. population as being victims and dependents!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348090872555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348091246401-210</Id><Topic><Title>Is BAC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>dellated7611</Username><Timestamp>1348089597905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your post appears to be a spam. Not going to risk opening it because I don't want porn pop-ups to ruine my focus on how to go about trading BAC. LOL</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1348091246401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348091982846-211</Id><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Msg>Think about it. It's almost unbelievable! Their platform includes not only continuing the tax break given to the super rich 1% by the GWB regime that brought us both 911 and Financial Disaster... but now wants to end Medicare by voucherizing it! As to Social Security, the GOP wants to hand control over to the Wall Street Robber BARRONS while removing most rules and regulations! Thanks... but NO thanks, GOP! GO TO HELL!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348092124042-212</Id><Topic><Title>Is BAC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>dellated7611</Username><Timestamp>1348089597905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's prudent and I agree with you! Thumbs up!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348092124042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348092382761-213</Id><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Msg>SS is generated by private-sector are required to pay into with matching funds from their employers. It is not an ENTITLEMENT. It was designed to yield 5% like the PENSION FUNDS till the LIBERALS robbed the SS ......and now if nothing is done it may not last that long. During the BUSH administartion there was 2.7 trillion in the TRUST. He recommended that SS be PRIVATIZED but LIBERALS in CONGRESS OPPOSED it .BUSH knew that it was the only way for the GOV'T to pay for it and to save it for years and years to come. Of course the word BUSH will generate a lot of BASHING but if you listen to his press conference at the WHITE HOUSE he even mentioned that SS was only generating 1%....it should at least generate 5% or more. In retrospect, it should have benn privatized.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348092661812-214</Id><Topic><Title>liberals always laugh at other peoples misfortunes and misery. and are arrogant</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1348087193718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably win by over 100 electoral votes. Nothing you do will change that. Who is "our", that crazy voice in your head?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348092661812</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:11:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348093025400-215</Id><Topic><Title>~$9.25 to ~$9.45 gap</Title><Username>highlowsel</Username><Timestamp>1348076076070</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:34:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Highlowsel, I averaged out at $9.27 on yesterday's quick trade and sold at $9.36 today. For a few seconds, I thought sold them too early. I still have a few shares left and will keep them for long term if the God of Patience can support me. I hope to be wrong on this one, but I think BAC could test $9.09 again this week. It seems as if the market makers are trying to push it below $9 to satisfy their Put Options. $9.14 is our next support level and I hope I don't have to add anything below $9 to my current position. I prefer to buy more at $10 or higher with solid upward trend. Good luck to all longs!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1348093025400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348093137162-216</Id><Topic><Title>Old Guys on SS who still like Romney</Title><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348089890721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ruthlessness is often mistaken for intelligence. The willingness to do things that many would find unconscionable often results in financial reward. For example, taking over a business, robbing the pension funds, selling off the assets and firing the workers or outsourcing a business to a third world country where you can get labor at slave rates while leaving hundreds of your own countrymen unemployed.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348093137162</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348093292396-217</Id><Topic><Title>MITT IS CLASSLESS AND ARROGANT BABOON AND RYAN IS A CAPITAL LIAR</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348052155998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 06:55:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and......you are the board Nitwit.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1348093292396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348093437969-218</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from tea baggin's post ......"Social Security and Medicare ... lousy as those programs are ... are based on taxes paid during one's WORKING years!" It is really not considered as TAX......there is no fixed amount on your contribution which is deducted from your paycheck and matched by your employers. As you can see SS beneficiaries paid with their fare shares from working. If you didn't work and did not contribute to your SS then you have no right to recieve any. Again it is not ENTITLEMENT.....BUT WAS CONSIDERED AS ENTITLEMENT under PELOSI'S CONGRESS..........</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348093437969</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348094065637-219</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would vote for Jesus if he ran as GOP candidate. But then Jesus was not an authoritarian, conniving materialist pig... as most Republicans are!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348094065637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348094343456-220</Id><Title>Disabled Employee Suing Bank of America!</Title><Msg>A former Bank of America employee is suing the bank, saying he faced discrimination because his right hand, arm and leg were disabled in a car accident and he was told accommodation "wouldn't be fair to people with two hands." For three years, Daniel Herrmann, 38, worked in customer service for Merrill Lynch and then Bank of America after BoA acquired Merrill Lynch in January 2010. He said he was fired on Sept. 20, 2010 for being one to two minutes late from his lunch break due to the fact that it took him longer to walk from the lunch room because of a limp. The suit, filed with the U.S. District Court for the Western District of Pennsylvania on Sept. 14, said Herrmann was "severely injured in a car accident in 1992 that left his right hand, arm and leg disabled." His attorney, Emily Town of the law firm Stember Feinstein Doyle Payne &amp; Kravec LLC , said Herrmann is a "hard worker who needed very minor accommodations for his obvious disabilities." "We've filed this lawsuit because Bank of America's conduct was unacceptable and the company should be held accountable when its supervisors and managers violate the law," she said. "Dan was repeatedly told that accommodating him 'wouldn't be fair to people with two hands.' The Americans with Disabilities Act exists to ensure that disabled workers receive reasonable accommodations from their employers and are not retaliated against when they request accommodation."</Msg><Username>big__deal</Username><Timestamp>1348094343456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348094535051-221</Id><Title>Romney victims include 4000 making a million a year</Title><Msg>Nobody's really talking about this slice of the pie, but Mitt Romney's "47%" who pay no federal income tax include several thousand of the highest-income households in the country. The Tax Policy Center estimates that 4,000 households with incomes over $1 million ended up with zero federal income tax liability in 2011. Another 14,000 made between $500,000 and $1 million. Combined, those households represented just 0.025% of the more than 76 million who did not pay. But their presence in the No Tax Club underlines the fact that the tax code is chock full of tax breaks and exceptions benefiting people up and down the income scale. There are various reasons why a household booking more than $1 million in income could owe nothing in federal income tax, experts note. Among them, people who live off their investment income and report large investment losses in a given year may be able to offset the taxes owed on their investment gains. Or they may have gotten a lot of their income from tax-free investments, such as municipal bonds. Another possibility: a wealthy tax filer may report a lot of dividend income from foreign stocks on which he already paid tax to a foreign government. He would get a foreign tax credit on his U.S. return, to avoid double taxation. And if his foreign tax bill tops his U.S. tax bill, he wouldn't owe anything to the IRS on that dividend income.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348094535051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:42:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348094697720-222</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jesus would be called a socialist by the GOP.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348094697720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348095064401-223</Id><Title>What Mitt Romney was doing when he referred to the 47%...</Title><Msg>...as being 'dependents and victims'? He was giving the EXCUSE of HIS DEFEAT... in a LANDSLIDE! It wasn't stupid after-all. He feels and KNOWS what's coming! He was trying to PREPARE his EXCUSE subliminally! Hmm... it will be so... because of the 47% who are 'victims and dependents'... PLUS the independent vote. Result? He may have assumed 52% Obama 48% Romney! I say the chances are good for A LANDSLIDE DEFEAT FOR R-MONEY! THE NON-THINKER-TALKER GOP MATERIALIST!!!!!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348095064401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348095187886-224</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one has ever robbed the social security fund. The money has been used the same way since its inception. Low interest rates are not helping. Had it been privatized most would have lost everything in the last economic downturn and never recovered. No one prohibits anyone from sestablishing their won retirement accounts so what makes you think giving them a few dollars more would change habits. We have social security because workers did not provide for retirement before and became wards of the state.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348095187886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348095494643-225</Id><Title>Return of the poor house, the Romney answer?</Title><Msg>A poorhouse or workhouse was a government-run facility in the past for the support and housing of dependent or needy persons, typically run by a local government entity such as a county or municipality. In England, Wales and Ireland (but not in Scotland[1]) a poorhouse was more commonly known as a workhouse. In early Victorian times (see Poor Law), poverty was seen as a dishonourable state caused by a lack of the moral virtue of industriousness (or industry as it was called). As was depicted by Charles Dickens, a workhouse could resemble a reformatory and house children, either with families or alone, or a penal labour regime to give the poor work at manual labour and subject them to physical punishment. As the 19th century progressed, conditions improved. The term is commonly applied to such a facility that housed the destitute elderly; institutions of this nature were widespread in the United States prior to the adoption of the Social Security program in the 1930s. Facilities housing indigents who are not elderly are typically referred to as homeless shelters, or simply "shelters," in current usage. Often the poorhouse was situated on the grounds of a poor farm on which able-bodied residents were required to work; such farms were common in the United States in the 19th and early 20th centuries; it could even be part of the same economic complex as a prison farm and other penal or charitable public institutions.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348095494643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348095726209-226</Id><Topic><Title>EVERYTIME I HEAR A COMMUNIST LIE...</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348090460188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:34:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ISLAM SUCKS! OINK OINK!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348095726209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348095941128-227</Id><Title>OBAMA'S CAMPAIGN STOPS</Title><Msg>Are just FAREWELL REUNIONS! SEE YA GOAT!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348095941128</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:05:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348095986414-228</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right you are! As an example, I have both SS and a pension and do great having the best of my life! While working I went to excesses and mistakes/learning how to use money- as most people do - but thanks to SS... and my own pension, life is beautiful! The blinded ideologues are all simpletons and think only in idealistic manner. They do not understand that 'to err is human' and there must be another safety net by a strong hand (the STATE) to safe-proof one's survival for those who err. The record shows that almost 95% of those receiving SS (rich or poor in their early lives) indeed need SS monies. But these tiny minded GOP brainwashed followers are incapable to understand complexities... whether in politics or life itself. It's either black or white with no grays in between for them!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348095986414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:06:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348096556523-229</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One should not always think that Privatizing Social Security meant to invest the FUNDS in stocks. It should be invested in conservative investments.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348096556523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348096980277-230</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know. They always use adjectives to label anything that is complex... and then go on hating it FOREVER regardless of any changes that happen and are part of life. Heck, even now when they don't like anything you say... they hurl the label communist at you so that they have a justification to hate you. All such folks are either idiots or too simple to understand anything complex and life has too many complexities to these small minded fellows who find the GOP as their right place! I use them for entertainment and fun!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348096980277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097050795-231</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney hates me...cause I am old</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348097050795</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348097230786-232</Id><Title>6 million uninsured AMERICANS to face TAX PENALTY</Title><Msg>Reality will start to hit the uninsured 6 million AMERICANS .....TOO BAD, YOU WILL NOT HEAR THIS FROM LIBERAL MEDIA AND NETWORKS.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348097230786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348097267705-233</Id><Title>Plastic People Love Romney....</Title><Msg>Romney Hates me....because I am retired,,,I worked 39 years for 1 company,, Now Romney calls me a LOSER....I sent Romney a Noose...I hope he wraps it around his neck and swings,,I was not going to VOTE,,,but Romney motivated me..and my friends.</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348097267705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097391724-234</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>R-money wants your money to give another tax break to HIMSELF and his 1% super rich buddies. That's all. He is not a bad man per se. He just loves money more than people- especially all those who are 'victims and dependents'! What a R-money stooped in depravity!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348097391724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097441827-235</Id><Topic><Title>Plastic People Love Romney....</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348097267705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:27:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>plastic people??? imagine a pres. that actual tells us the truth. now that is refreshing!!!-jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1348097441827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348097531889-236</Id><Title>WENT SHOPPING TODAY BOUGHT TV MADE IN MEXICO BOUGHT CLOTHES MADE IN BANGLADASH BOUGHT VACUME CLEANER MADE IN CHINA</Title><Msg>LOOKS LIKE THIS IS WHY WE DONT HAVE JOBS</Msg><Username>midnight_riderssss</Username><Timestamp>1348097531889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097560759-237</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He hates you because you can't answer the poster's facts.</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348097560759</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097769412-238</Id><Topic><Title>Plastic People Love Romney....</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348097267705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:27:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then I have to thank R-money for motivating you and your friends to vote! They claim this election as the most important election KNOWING the end is near for that BIG PRETENDING party (GOP) to be a friend of the people WHEN it's just the OPPOSITE! Now they are exposed like no time in the past because of the hi-tech info age. They have nowhere to hide. I love it! THEY'RE EXPOSED like never before and lying and trickery are no more working. Ask Karl Rove... he is both Republican and also a rarity who has some intelligence as well! Hey, make sure you vote! We need a landslide to teach'em a lesson for life!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348097769412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348097855244-239</Id><Title>Either the Obama officials are dumb or they are lying or both..</Title><Msg>Intelligence sources tell Fox News that Al Qaeda, including an ex-Guantanamo detainee, is tied to the deadly attack on the US consulate in Libya, as Obama official calls the strike a 'terrorist attack' for first time.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1348097855244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:37:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348097874481-240</Id><Title>I bet OBAMA's UNCLE or OBAMA stole my SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER!</Title><Msg>TWICE! FACT! DESTROY THE KENYAN LIARS TREACHERY AMERICA!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348097874481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348097996471-241</Id><Topic><Title>WENT SHOPPING TODAY BOUGHT TV MADE IN MEXICO BOUGHT CLOTHES MADE IN BANGLADASH BOUGHT VACUME CLEANER MADE IN CHINA</Title><Username>midnight_riderssss</Username><Timestamp>1348097531889</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:32:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just hit the nail man</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348097996471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098051394-242</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A LANDSLIDE IN THE MAKING! This is good news for the U.S. and for that matter... for the planet as a whole!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348098051394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348098065049-243</Id><Title>My next DOG is going to be named CRUSHER</Title><Msg>ISLAMOBAMA and ISLAM will be CRUSHED!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098065049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098100118-244</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama, Obama, Obama!!!!!!!!!!!!!! GBY!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348098100118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098113813-245</Id><Topic><Title>6 million uninsured AMERICANS to face TAX PENALTY</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348097230786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:27:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNN must not have been notified of the liberal media conspiracy. They just reported the story 5 minutes ago, right after reporting that in Michigan, which had the highest unemployment rate in the nation until being displaced by Nevada this month, Romney has fallen behind Obama in the polls by a substantial margin, 52-44. ROTFLMAO what, Romney's message isn't resonating with the unemployed and the poor, what a shocker!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348098113813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098221240-246</Id><Topic><Title>What Mitt Romney was doing when he referred to the 47%...</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348095064401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:51:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ann Romney is a Muslim...George Romney was a Muslim. Romney was born in Mexico and he is Not a Citizen.... Romney es un cullo cagao</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348098221240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098272697-247</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, they'd label him an Occupy anarchist. ROTFLMAO I'd ask everyone to leave Jesus out of this, but even the Democratic Party couldn't do it without an outcry from duh masses.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348098272697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098284018-248</Id><Topic><Title>Disabled Employee Suing Bank of America!</Title><Username>big__deal</Username><Timestamp>1348094343456</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a stupid lawsuite I think it should be thrown out and not only he should be fired he should be put out of this country and somewhere in Libya men!!!!!! What a joke. He walked slow or limped from lunch break back to his desk. Shameful he should know better that if it takes him two minutes more then take lunch accordingly and time himself in such a way that his reporting time he is always there. What was he doing when he had pressure for to unload did he walk slow that time also and unloaded right at his desk what a crap. This are the abuse of a good legitimate system that these kinds of #$%$ do it really send them to Libya or should I say Bengazi and see how fast he starts walking back to USA</Msg><Username>ctsquare</Username><Timestamp>1348098284018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348098354294-249</Id><Title>Our Afghan Troops Pay No Taxes,,they Moochers</Title><Msg>Our Troops are all dependent on the GOVT,,,Romney will ignore them.. they are Moochers</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1348098354294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:45:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098387662-250</Id><Topic><Title>The U.S. Treasury will hit its current "debt ceiling" just after the Novmeber elections.</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348097985607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:39:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You FOOKING GOP SABOTAGERS! Whatever failed... IT WAS ONLY BECAUSE OF SABOTAGING BY THE GOP so that small brained blinded zealots like you act the way you are right now. LOOK IN THE MIRROR and blame your FOOKING LEADERS- Sen. Mitch McConnell, John Bonner, Eric Kantor, etc. etc. for the unemployment and economy's slower recovery. THIS IS WHAT YOU ARE- SABOTAGERS!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348098387662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098513217-251</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>libertydies30. You know you are going to hell don't you?</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348098513217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098553841-252</Id><Topic><Title>My next DOG is going to be named CRUSHER</Title><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098065049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A dog? I'd have thought you'd go for a cat, given what a ......never mind. If you want to wear your political beliefs on a leash, get a pig and name him Mohammed. ROTFLMAO at displaced aggression everywhere. Not cool to take out your impotence and frustration on innocent animals.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348098553841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098600947-253</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libturdydies thinks he was born before The Lord....you have some rough times commin pal!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098600947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098625504-254</Id><Topic><Title>Your SOCIAL SECURITY contributions</Title><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348092382761</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 18:06:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bro...nobody hates you....Romney's video is a wake up to the 47% There are times that somebody will challenge you to wake up. Years ago, my BOSS challenged me to the point that I almost quit my job and yet after 5 years of being an employee and studying at night, my LIFE started to improve and became an employer for 25 years.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1348098625504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:50:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098677038-255</Id><Topic><Title>I bet OBAMA's UNCLE or OBAMA stole my SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348097874481</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet Michelle took your lunch AND your lunch money. ROTFLMAO You must be one of those 'victims' Mitt was talking about.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348098677038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348098680140-256</Id><Topic><Title>Is BAC Ready to Break Out?</Title><Username>dellated7611</Username><Timestamp>1348089597905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move. I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>mariannaltm1657</Username><Timestamp>1348098680140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348098939286-257</Id><Title>When Obama was born HE PARTED HEAVAN AND EARTH....</Title><Msg>So He likes to tell that to the GOATS who take his candy.... When libturdydies was born he pooped like a Palestinian with colon cancer.</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098939286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099037954-258</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But whoever denies Me before men, I will also deny him before My Father who is in heaven.</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099037954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099254546-259</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that one star vote mean you reject what I say or that you reject his word? Every knee shall bow and every tongue confess that Jesus Christ is Lord!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099254546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099460275-260</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO in the language of diplomacy, it means "There, I don't have to even give you the time of day until next year". It's the diplomatic version of the fiscal policy of 'extend and pretend', and where would this POS company be without THAT?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348099460275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099637817-261</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How groovy of you to inflate your own ego! When Jesus died on a cross ...where were you?</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099637817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099700957-262</Id><Topic><Title>My next DOG is going to be named CRUSHER</Title><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098065049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many IDs are you going to use F16 vice, commiehater? Are they just for your multiple personality disorder? One for each voice you hear? Medicaid cut back on your meds again?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348099700957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348099704216-263</Id><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Msg>Unchanged for months.</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099726921-264</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Anthony Salvanto and Doug Rivers (CBS News) The new CBS News/YouGov Electoral Vote Tracker - a computer simulation model of the Presidential race - shows that if President Obama were to win the national popular vote by three points (which is his current edge today in national polls) that would translate into 332 electoral votes for Mr. Obama and 206 for Mitt Romney on election night. The model shows how the votes would most likely be distributed across all fifty states, if Mr. Obama's three-point lead held up on November 6th and that reveals which states would ultimately tilt to Mr. Obama, and which go to Romney. The president would pick up enough swing voters from across the battleground states to take almost all of them. He'd win Pennsylvania, Ohio, Nevada, New Hampshire, Iowa, Colorado, Virginia; he'd win a close race in Florida, and win a squeaker in Wisconsin, while North Carolina would go to Romney. Importantly, it isn't a forecast - it is today's score. We've got six-plus weeks to go, and this can change. We'll re-run the simulation again in the coming weeks. This simulation is based entirely on data collected by CBS News and YouGov, a Silicon Valley research company working with CBS News on this project. The national lead of +3 is based on the findings of the latest CBS News/New York Times national poll. We then use over 36,000 additional interviews fielded by YouGov, matched to voter demographics across the states, and run the simulation. It's designed as a 50-state snapshot meant to show where things stand if we translate a national lead into the only score that really matters - the Electoral College vote.</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099726921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348099838204-265</Id><Topic><Title>My next DOG is going to be named CRUSHER</Title><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348098065049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen STARPORK...I'll be here as long as SATAN is in our WHITEHOUSE and I was born to defy this BTFKN GOAT! GET USED TO IT LOL!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099838204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348099922430-266</Id><Title>OBAMA IS NOT BLACK!</Title><Msg>HE IS A SHAPESHIFTER! OBAMA IS THE ENEMY!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099922430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100084190-267</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA IS NOT BLACK!</Title><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348099922430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:12:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BLIND obamunists can't see it. God said...I will send them a BLINDING DELUSION!</Msg><Username>barackalinski</Username><Timestamp>1348100084190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:14:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348100124307-268</Id><Title>Poor loser fringe-right idiots flood message board with garbage.</Title><Msg>Sour grapes? Poor babies don't know what to do with themselves. LMAO!</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348100124307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100308833-269</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many electoral college votes are needed to make it a LANDSLIDE? I don't like this system. I prefer a direct vote and have the majority vote and not this faked system that can be manipulated with money to give even a chance for a SORDID CHARACTER (R-MONEY or OTHER KNOWN MATERIALISTS) to take power in a land on which not only the U.S. wellbeing, but the WHOLE WORLD depends on!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348100308833</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100324470-270</Id><Topic><Title>The vetting process for Republican vice-presidential candidates failed again. Paul Ryan collected Social Security after his father's death, so he's one of Mitt's despised 47%</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063456359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Palin wasn't one of Mitt's despicable 47%</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348100324470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:18:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100619059-271</Id><Topic><Title>The vetting process for Republican vice-presidential candidates failed again. Paul Ryan collected Social Security after his father's death, so he's one of Mitt's despised 47%</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063456359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ve_etting, idiot</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348100619059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100802802-272</Id><Topic><Title>The vetting process for Republican vice-presidential candidates failed again. Paul Ryan collected Social Security after his father's death, so he's one of Mitt's despised 47%</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1348063456359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:04:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitts father got welfare ! and we still don't know how many years Mitt didn't pay federal taxes !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348100802802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348100916653-273</Id><Title>Mitt will go down as the greatest liberal in history !</Title><Msg>after he gives Obama the senate and congress.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348100916653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348100949894-274</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait anymore. Let's get this thing settled sooner. The end is near for the GOP who would destroy America by sabotaging just to take power! Desperate GOP... A LANDSLIDE IS IN THE MAKING FOR AN OBAMA WIN! Thanks for making it clear to most people in this age of growing enlightenment and knowledge!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348100949894</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348101058528-275</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What different does it make who wins. It is going to be tough 4 years. Unemployment will not dip below 8 it will only climb and the debt will hit 21Tril and above govt will become more FAT, more regulations more welfare we are on same exact path of EUROPE and other socialist country. Repubs will still hold majority in house so even if Obama reelected he will not be able to pass anything. Country has already divided and polarized. I am trying to find ways to become govt. dependent also worked too much now time to slack off like others who are already abusing the system. We have become a society where we do not want to work and that is the reason we have illegal hispanics in this country who are filling up and taking the jobs and we cry for unemployment. Nobody wants to work in farms, cut grass pickup trash nothing. I just interviewed a guy for help in my warehouse was offering him 500 bucks a week he denied said Govt pays him 800/week why to work with you only if you give me 1000 or more as Taxes will be taken from that etc.. etc.. etc... So He with everything I think I can manage with what I have so go broke no salary for myself and go on welfare tooo God Help America</Msg><Username>ctsquare</Username><Timestamp>1348101058528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348101243827-276</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Godless republicans the gates will be the eye of a needle !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348101243827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348101252900-277</Id><Title>Yes, BAraCk is ready for a breakout</Title><Msg>Can't lose on either</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348101252900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348101393528-278</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt will go down as the greatest liberal in history !</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348100916653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greatest liberal in history? That's a joke! I mean he IS! But, picking Paul Ryan showed his desperation and not being a REAL leader. Had he been a bit more intelligent... he woulda known that any good leader has to lead from the center and not from the minority of the wings. HE FAILED THE FIRST TEST by picking from the right wing! The rest will soon be history! That is not to say that had he picked any other person he would succeed now that we do know that he opens his mouth to put his foot in... most of the time. He seems to have with a good looking head... but the problem is that he does not match it with good brains... unfortunately for him... but FORTUNATELY for AMERICA and the WORLD!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348101393528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348101535472-279</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, BAraCk is ready for a breakout</Title><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348101252900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree! I see a 10 in both! Go BAC and BARACK!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348101535472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348102733085-280</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt lacks any kind of conscious moral need to explain himself or apologize to the peasant masses.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1348022405095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney thinks the unemployed see themselves as victims who want the government to take care of them until Romney's plan for 12 million new jobs cranks up. Meanwhile....</Msg><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1348102733085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348103096675-281</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's perception of what he thinks of American voters is so unbelievably skewed, it is mind-boggling to think this blatant elitist is the Republican presidential nominee.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347945613488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 01:20:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's not forget Mitt is the default candidate. He was the last man standing when everyone elses money ran out.</Msg><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1348103096675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348103400413-282</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're all a bunch of breathless panty-wetter #$%$ Nice try, leeches.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1348103400413</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348103673351-283</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt will go down as the greatest liberal in history !</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348100916653</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe this will destroy the right and they can be reborn normal.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348103673351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348103685896-284</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, you're losing your audience. When you call Goebbels to get your "interpretation" of the numbers, be sure and let us all know.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1348103685896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348103914020-285</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excuses, excuses. You just keep telling yourself that, even when Obama's got you standing in line with the others with your back to the ditch.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1348103914020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:18:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348104088414-286</Id><Title>major scandles about to rock the White House the real powers</Title><Msg>that be no longer need him, he has served his purpose for past 4 years..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348104088414</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104113332-287</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was the one that pulled us out of the ditch Bush droves us into !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1348104113332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104294776-288</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt lacks any kind of conscious moral need to explain himself or apologize to the peasant masses.</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1348022405095</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What difference does it make 47% , 30% or any % if people has to depend on govt to take care of them it is the biggest shame for any society. Economy only grows by businesses not by govt funded programs. Even you take entire wealth of 1% individuals that Mitt is going after still 47% can not be fed or taken cared of more than 1 year. It is shame that none of the money for entitlement is budgeted anywhere it is China and Japan and others funding our fed run programs and he only wants to increase that. Lets go for it lets bring Obama back to White house. Mark this post 21Tril of Debt, unemployment at 10% more regulations. Rich using every loopholes available to get their money away from this country this is the same saga happened to Greece, ireland Spain and watch same is going to happen here. Sad part is what are we going to leave behind for our kids only debt. This will crush dollar and one day when you wake up all of a sudden everyone will be 30% poor but what difference does it make that is what we want I guess a socialist country so now everyone looks at each other and feels that we are all in same boat Lets go for it and anyhow even if Mitt wins I do not see much that he can do. None of them have guts to come out and say that they will end all entitlement programs except for Handicapped, really poor, minor kids, and 75 and above. They should increase tax by 3-5% fine go for it too but then make a genuine promise to all Americans that they will ot use that money for anything else other then paying debt but they will not as all of them in DC are nothing but crooks. Want to steal from someone else's pocket to pay someone else God bless our Country</Msg><Username>ctsquare</Username><Timestamp>1348104294776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104332602-289</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unemployment will be around 6% in two years. You offered an employee 12.50 an hour for a 40 hour work week. That is going to leave him with a take home pay of about 11.50. Out of that he has to feed himself, his family, drive to and from work every day, provide insurance and care for any dependents. Perhaps you ought to figure what constitutes a living wage and at least be competitive with unemployment. As illegal workers are driven out of the country at increasing rates of checks by the government like they have over the past 3 years you are no longer going to find 10 dollar an hour labor. Margins between the employer, or management and the employees will have to narrow bringing back some balance between white and blue collar workers. Hire good workers, pay them well and increase your productivity. If you can't do that then maybe you shouldn't be in business.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348104332602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348104390845-290</Id><Title>Those POLL numbers FAVORING the OBANA have to be DOCTORED in OBANA FAVOR.</Title><Msg>No one in their right mind could actuall vote for abana</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348104390845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104532999-291</Id><Topic><Title>Electoral College poll as of Sept.19: Obama: 332. Romney: 206</Title><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1348099704216</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A DIRECT VOTE ????? OBANANA = LOST</Msg><Username>mishaelena</Username><Timestamp>1348104532999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104784783-292</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is correct - someone needs to say it, and more often, I'm glad he didn't walk it back</Title><Username>greekmonster101</Username><Timestamp>1348023001700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:50:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO I don't keep track of 'my audience' or attempt to hold seances with the dead. More of those Mormon idiosyncrasies? What was Goebbel's position on golden tablets?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1348104784783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348105320575-293</Id><Title>MITTEN IS A CAPTAIN OF A SINKING SHIP - ALL ONBOARD</Title><Msg>Romney is the titanic of politics, the dude is going to sink the REPUCAN party and I'm loving it.</Msg><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1348105320575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348105322726-294</Id><Title>Romney: "All right, there are 47 percent... who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you name it. "</Title><Msg>From another forum: Romney: "All right, there are 47 percent... who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you name it. " Romney's mom talking about his grandfather:"...he was a refugee from Mexico, he was on relief, welfare relief, for the first years of his life..." The reason Romney's grandfather went to Mexico is because his father and his father's 4 wives and his father's 30 children fled to avoid the anti-polygamy laws. They fled Mexico because of the violence of the Mexican Revolution. They were destitute and went on welfare. A family moving from Mexico into the United States and going on welfare with 30 children (Romney's grandfather was born in Mexico) is what Rush and GOP are screaming about. A simple search will verify this. Romney's definition of " Redistribution " is take your tax dollars and increase your taxes to line his pockets with cash. Romney said- "Fundamentally, what happens in America that creates jobs is not government. It has its role. But by and large, it gets in the way of creating jobs," he said during a debate Saturday sponsored by ABC News and Yahoo. Bain Capital began looking at investing in the steel start-up in late 1993. At the time, Steel Dynamics was weighing where to locate its first plant, based in part on which region offered the best tax incentives. In June 1994, Bain put $18.2 million into Steel Dynamics, making it the largest domestic equity holder. It sold its stake five years later for $104 million, a return of more than $85 million. As Bain made its investment, the state and county pledged $37 million in subsidies and grants for the $385-million plant project. The county also levied a new income tax to finance infrastructure improvements to benefit the steel mill over the heated objections of some county residents. "I'm very pro-business, but I'm not pro-business-welfare," said DeKalb County resident Suzanne Beaman, 58, who fought the incentives. Steel Dynamics "would have done fine without our tax dollars, I have no doubt."</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105322726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348105592927-295</Id><Title>France had a method of dealing with its 1%.</Title><Msg>Go on, Mitt, tell the 47% to "let theme eat cake."</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105592927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348105717296-296</Id><Title>Romney wants to help the poor and middle class.</Title><Msg>Romney wants to help the poor and the middle class by sending their jobs to China to work in one of his sweat shops.</Msg><Username>billybobseq47</Username><Timestamp>1348105717296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348105728501-297</Id><Title>GS Goldman Sachs Group owns 8.7+ Million shares of FB Facebook bac</Title><Msg>..........</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1348105728501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348105977622-298</Id><Topic><Title>Yes, BAraCk is ready for a breakout</Title><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1348101252900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Breakout NOW! WE WILL DEVOUR YOU! Send Obama packin! He will be bitter but so the the f what! LOL!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348105977622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348106044356-299</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood Says:</Title><Msg>Make My Day...scorch the Middle East</Msg><Username>speedtheirwaytoheaven</Username><Timestamp>1348106044356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106065355-300</Id><Topic><Title>France had a method of dealing with its 1%.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105592927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:46:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumpo-douchebag seems to be confused again. Too much cake making you dizzy?</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348106065355</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348106120335-301</Id><Title>Romney immigration policy</Title><Msg>Speaking to a Hispanic group "Finally, he answered, "We're not going to round up 12 million people, that includes the kids and the parents, and have everyone deported. Our system isn't to deport people. We need to provide a long-term solution." But he did not specify whether he would extend the president's executive order. He also tried to soften rhetoric from the primary, telling the audience that illegal immigrants would have to "make their own choices as to whether they want to go home" when he endorsed a policy of self-deportation." What does that mean? He doesn't have a plan to do anything.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348106120335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106130379-302</Id><Topic><Title>Clint Eastwood Says:</Title><Username>speedtheirwaytoheaven</Username><Timestamp>1348106044356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the empty chair replied,"GFY!"</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348106130379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106256407-303</Id><Topic><Title>Obama -- Send me your huddled masses of ILLEGALS, the wretched refuse of your teeming shore .... and I will give them everything</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348106149612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your fool's cause is lost, dumpo-douchebag. Find something else to do.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348106256407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348106452555-304</Id><Title>Patriots are the TEETH of Liberty!</Title><Msg>Our Forefathers are right! TYRANNY will be SUFFOCATED! Radical Islam is a rathead NAZI! All Islam is , is a sand pounding NAZI !</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348106452555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106465398-305</Id><Topic><Title>Romney immigration policy</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348106120335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:55:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On this issue and all other issues, the Romney plan is no plan.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348106465398</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:01:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106601558-306</Id><Topic><Title>Patriots are the TEETH of Liberty!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348106452555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:00:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have another prozac with that beer, Jethro.</Msg><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348106601558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348107772834-307</Id><Title>They Believe the LIE rather than the Truth!</Title><Msg>liberals.</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348107772834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348108249603-308</Id><Topic><Title>" Rural voters "cling to guns or religion." Barack Obama</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348108132404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and?</Msg><Username>barack4more</Username><Timestamp>1348108249603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348108323374-309</Id><Topic><Title>They Believe the LIE rather than the Truth!</Title><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348107772834</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe in FNH 5.7 like a puppy with a bone to defend American Sovereignty!!</Msg><Username>obamistan</Username><Timestamp>1348108323374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:32:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348108827396-310</Id><Topic><Title>From Mitt's latest remarks we now understand why the fringe right white trash never post anything good about him.</Title><Username>cosmo_vitelli</Username><Timestamp>1347943587574</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:46:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have more in common with Obama than with Romney, but they will never get over Obama being a man of mixed race.</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348108827396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348109073753-311</Id><Topic><Title>France had a method of dealing with its 1%.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105592927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:46:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...too much glue</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348109073753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348109461245-312</Id><Topic><Title>" Rural voters "cling to guns or religion." Barack Obama</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348108132404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt said what he said last May, and you want everyone to remind us of what Obama said over four years ago, as if it is just as bad. You are an idiot.</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348109461245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348109527698-313</Id><Topic><Title>" Rural voters "cling to guns or religion." Barack Obama</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348108132404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think you will find those tax returns right next to obummers columbia college SEALED records.-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1348109527698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348109898194-314</Id><Topic><Title>" Rural voters "cling to guns or religion." Barack Obama</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1348108132404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can cut and paste every gaffe of Obama's all night long. ALL of them combined, PALE in comparison to what Mitt said. You are an IDIOT!</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348109898194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348110512412-315</Id><Topic><Title>Obama -- Send me your huddled masses of ILLEGALS, the wretched refuse of your teeming shore .... and I will give them everything</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1348106149612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Out of touch dumpobamie the fool hasn't kept up with current events.</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348110512412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:08:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348110637896-316</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the typical revealing response of the right wing trash blind follower. Have a nice day/night. PTL!!:)!!</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348110637896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:10:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348110840073-317</Id><Title>Mitt - Since you will never vote for me, I will dismiss you and disrespect you"</Title><Msg>Is this the all time most stupid presidential candidate "gaffe?"</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348110840073</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348110840442-318</Id><Topic><Title>France had a method of dealing with its 1%.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105592927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:46:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>France didn't have the opportunity to deal with them by elections. We do.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348110840442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348110893563-319</Id><Title>Romney hates "dumpobamie"</Title><Msg>Mitt considers a disability check as wasted money given to parasites.</Msg><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348110893563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348110941208-320</Id><Topic><Title>France had a method of dealing with its 1%.</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1348105592927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:46:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I vote, "off with his head."</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348110941208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:15:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348111065937-321</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hates "dumpobamie"</Title><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348110893563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:14:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought it might be about the hate spew.</Msg><Username>willy_the_sage</Username><Timestamp>1348111065937</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348112353776-322</Id><Title>Romney and Ryan can't carry their home states</Title><Msg>Michigan, Wisconsin and Massachusetts all blue. Obama lead expanding.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348112353776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348112656345-323</Id><Title>why is that criminalIrish shill Moynihan always so quiet?</Title><Msg>does Bernankes cat got his tongue? don't get me wrong BOA is in business to make money and the branches seem to bend over backwards to help people and come up with common sense solutions, but their upper mgmt is a bunch of criminals..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348112656345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:44:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348112866436-324</Id><Topic><Title>why is that criminalIrish shill Moynihan always so quiet?</Title><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348112656345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:44:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in other words I think the nice folks who actually run the daily activity of the 1000'sa of branches are decent hard working folks, it's all the upper mgmt who are common criminals...</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1348112866436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:47:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113296968-325</Id><Topic><Title>Romney and Ryan can't carry their home states</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348112353776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:39:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently those states have more informed folks who can evaluate the facts and see the light and what's good for America! That is great news. Thanks.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348113296968</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113465824-326</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know any such thing and neither do you.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348113465824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113579735-327</Id><Topic><Title>Romney hates "dumpobamie"</Title><Username>u_like_teabaggin</Username><Timestamp>1348110893563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:14:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But his choice of Ryan was to please and cater to the base(st part of the GOP) of the party so that he gets their vote. He has no need or use for them after he is elected. He is a business minded materialist businessman. The bottom line dollars and what matters to him... not people.</Msg><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348113579735</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348113596458-328</Id><Topic><Title>Are you voting for the GOP?</Title><Username>giovannijay</Username><Timestamp>1348091982846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>evolving.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1348113596458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>