<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343966577756-1</Id><Title>Harry Reid the Sniveling pos</Title><Msg>great thing to teach our kids idiot. Obama should denounce you low life</Msg><Username>sell_are_you_nuts</Username><Timestamp>1343966577756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343966662027-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gutted the work requirements from the Clinton-era welform reform!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1343959496032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 22:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has no morals. Handouts without work destroys the spirit -FDR's words not mine</Msg><Username>sell_are_you_nuts</Username><Timestamp>1343966662027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343966844155-3</Id><Topic><Title>COME ON REPUCANS, ADMIT YOU MADE A MISTAKE BY PICKING MITT</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1343864515237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:41:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it is a mistake, it will be one that dems, not repubs, will regret. It is not all about the presidential election. It is also about the gains in the House and Senate the repubs will make as a result of Romney's campaign because he has played hardball and will be pitching the balls harder and faster as election day nears. He'll play dirty if necessary, and he will bring out dirt on Obama, and that in turn will galvanize repubs. Read the news... it is all over that even incumbent repubs will be replaced with farther right tea party repubs with more extreme and more deeply entrenched views. As much as the dems complain about the current repubs in Congress, after the elections they will look back and wish that they had compromised with the previous lot because the new lot will be ever more difficult to deal with.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343966844155</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343967478557-4</Id><Topic><Title>The fringe-right idiot rectal drips are in gush mode tonight. They can't handle the FACT that Willard is going down.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1343965671663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 23:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah yes, there it is. The leftist insulting sarcasm when they cannot forumate an intelligent argument. I see it all the time on MSNBC. It has become a liberal signature. "Laughing" has become the ultimate insult when you've got nothing of substance to say. What you apparently fail to realize, or else you would not be "laughing" so much is that win or lose, Romney will hurt Obama. Romney will play dirty, he will fight, he will use that billion dollars to trash Obama. In the meantime, if you read the news, you would know that repubs will gain seats in the Senate. Even worse for dems and repubs, a significant number of moderate repubs will lose to extremist tea party repubs, with more extreme and more deeply entrenched views. How do you think Obama will make out with that? The thing is, Romney with all the money he has at his disposal and more money to come from ultra rich super pac donars, and his willingness to get down and dirty, will hurt Obama so much in public opinion and that coupled with the shift in power to the tea party will make his second term, if he wins, a bigger loser than the first term.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343967478557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343967829617-5</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: -- "Word is out," Romney hasn't paid taxes in 10 years</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343948468318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your dead logic professor won't be voting. And, it doesn't matter what YOU think, either. You are obviously a mindless Fox zombie incapable of realizing how stupid Willard is for continuing to refuse disclosure, AND how stupid the repugs are for not vetting him properly. Talk about the village idiot! Had the repugs known Willard would be this stupid about disclosing his assets, he would have been barred from the selection process. The VOTERS are fed up with Romney's continuing refusal to show what he's got, where it is, and what he's paid taxes on, or not paid taxes on. Who cares about logic? This issue is about Willard hiding what he's got. The issue is not a new one, but Harry Reid just served it up with savvy. The longer this goes on, the more stupid and deceitful Willard looks, got that idiot?</Msg><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343967829617</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343967886532-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are absolutely right! Obama is not electable because of his use of executive privilege to cover up the truth about fast and furious. When he ran for election, he promised to change things. In particular, he promised greatly increased transparency. Yet he has exercised exec privilege more than Clinton and more than Bush... a lot more. That nondisclosure could very well cost him the election, as Romney will have a field day pointing it out. A friend of mine suggests that Romney is sand bagging on his tax returns so that in a public debate with Obama, he can offer to provide the tax returns dems have clamored for... if Obama releases the fast and furious info. We'll see. If I were you, I would not be laughing so hard about something that could turn and bit you right in your #$%$</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343967886532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343968200110-7</Id><Title>*****Romney to Harry Reid: Put Up or Shut Up</Title><Msg>Mitt put that idiot in his place.</Msg><Username>jbstocktalk</Username><Timestamp>1343968200110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343968396198-8</Id><Title>*****Too many jealous people over Mitt's money.</Title><Msg>Remember not to covet someones success. Go out and get a job you lazy liverals.</Msg><Username>jbstocktalk</Username><Timestamp>1343968396198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343968551054-9</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: -- "Word is out," Romney hasn't paid taxes in 10 years</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343948468318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol... it doesn't matter what I think? Lol.. but YOU matter??? You who anal-izes and obsesses with your repeated OCD posts every night? Do you listen to yourself? It's really pathetic. You ASSume that the repubs did not vet. What do you know? NOTHING! He complied with the law, just like McCain and others. Nobody questions McCain's integrity, not even fool dems like you because they knew better than to question the integrity of a war hero. Yet Romney who did the same thing in releasing only the two years is bashed as being crooked. You liberal half wits hate people with wealth and cannot formulate an intelligent argument, so you desperately and pathetically glob on to any issue you, relevant or not. You ask, who cares about logic? THAT IS SO TELLING A STATEMENT!!! Obviously you don't and your emotions get the better of you with your stupid comments. Give it up, man, get some therapy for your anger management before you go postal and end up on the evening news.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343968551054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343968669140-10</Id><Title>Obama's ads on Yahoo are tasteless, dumb, and way out of touch !</Title><Msg>"DINNER WITH BARACK ANYONE" No thanks ! His teeth are white but his breath might stink ! "MICHELLE OMAMA....I AM IN, WILL YOU?" Dumb again, nobody wanna sleep with the pig ! "SIGN OBAMA'S HAPPY BIRTHDAY CARD GUYS" Extremely out of touch with the mainstream. We rather find a job and get off food stamps. The President is an idiot. His campaign staff is a bigger idiot too !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1343968669140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343968685750-11</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: -- "Word is out," Romney hasn't paid taxes in 10 years</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343948468318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot to add... GOT THAT, IDIOT!</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343968685750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343968948055-12</Id><Topic><Title>*****Romney to Harry Reid: Put Up or Shut Up</Title><Username>jbstocktalk</Username><Timestamp>1343968200110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Reid has to either put up or shut up.... then I think he won't have anything to say for a while because he never puts up. Just unsu#$%$tantiated emotional #$%$ rehtoric such as the liberals always resort to when they cannot formulate an intelligent argument. Insults, inuendo, opinions and conjecture twisted into misleading statements stated as facts. That is what they do when they've got nothing su#$%$tantive to work with.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343968948055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343969121321-13</Id><Title>Reid tells Romney AGAIN "... it's his obligation to put up, and release several years' worth of tax returns just like nominees of both parties have done for decades."</Title><Msg>"When it comes to answering the legitimate questions the American people have about whether he avoided paying his fair share in taxes or why he opened a Swiss bank account, Romney has shut up," Reid said. "But as a presiden"tial candidate, it's his obligation to put up, and release several years' worth of tax returns just like nominees of both parties have done for decades."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1343969121321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343969290679-14</Id><Topic><Title>*****Romney to Harry Reid: Put Up or Shut Up</Title><Username>jbstocktalk</Username><Timestamp>1343968200110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:30:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are confused. It was Reid who told Romney AGAIN to "put up." You need to give up your addiction to Fox News. They're only good for lying spin.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1343969290679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343969432380-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama PlSSED away BILLIONS on failed stimulus and solar "investments" !</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1343959209359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 22:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The half billion he wasted on Solindra was a nice photo op for him though! Expensive for the taxpayer but a great photo op for him. What does he care, another half billion of debt for the taxpayers when it buys him a chance to be smug? The cost of his personal glory is getting to be a bit rich for my blood. I don't think he is a bad guy in his intensions, just so grossly naive. A product of goverment aid and handouts. Never struggled on his own in the real world. So what do we expect from a pres who was raised under that culture? I expect exactly what we got.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343969432380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343969565399-16</Id><Title>Layoffs in SEP - part of the NEW_BAC plan</Title><Msg>RUMORS starting to fly: Bank of America preparing for huge layoffs in SEP. Part of the "New BAC" initiative. Numbers close to 15,000 system wide. Already had layoffs in their Philadelphia Customer Support offices. Heads are rolling. Q: will it propel the stock past $ 10+ or just be a sign of worse to come?</Msg><Username>jaxjaguar0</Username><Timestamp>1343969565399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343969712876-17</Id><Topic><Title>*****Too many jealous people over Mitt's money.</Title><Username>jbstocktalk</Username><Timestamp>1343968396198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, but help me understand... why do the liberals hate Romney and his wealth yet they love Zuckerburg and Buffet, each of whom are worth multiples of what Romney is worth? It seems to me that it is not really about Romney's wealth. I wonder if it is because liberals have such difficulty coming up with intelligent arguments that they glob onto anything they can leverage with the poor folks to convince them to vote for Obama.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343969712876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343969855852-18</Id><Topic><Title>Reid tells Romney AGAIN "... it's his obligation to put up, and release several years' worth of tax returns just like nominees of both parties have done for decades."</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1343969121321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are spreading mis-information. It is not true that nominees of both parties have released several years worth of tax returns for decades. Do you listen to the news at all? Try it. If you did, then you would know about the recent nominees who have done exactly what Romney is doing. That is a simple fact.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1343969855852</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343969924506-19</Id><Topic><Title>Layoffs in SEP - part of the NEW_BAC plan</Title><Username>jaxjaguar0</Username><Timestamp>1343969565399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:52:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Follow the plan!</Msg><Username>ppdodv</Username><Timestamp>1343969924506</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 00:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343970410131-20</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: -- "Word is out," Romney hasn't paid taxes in 10 years</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343948468318</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:01:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calm down, boy. I now it's been a rough night for you loser repugs, but don't pop your cork over it. Yes, we know you're upset because Romney is slipping in the polls, and Obama continues to lead in the swing states, and this issue of Willard's refusal to disclose just won't go away, will it? Tough to take, huh, boy? But, then who brought it on? Willard did. And, what does McCain have to do with anything? He gave up disclosure, like ALL of the other candidates EXCEPT WILLARD! Now, how "logical" is that? The point I made is: logic has nothing to do with this issue. Willard is not illogical, or logical for not disclosing his assets; he is deceitful. He is hiding something. Why? Now, here's where logic enters in: the logical thing to do here is: give up disclosure like ALL of the other candidates have done. Savvy, boy?</Msg><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343970410131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 01:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343971121972-21</Id><Topic><Title>The fringe-right idiot rectal drips are in gush mode tonight. They can't handle the FACT that Willard is going down.</Title><Username>doctor_casanova</Username><Timestamp>1343965671663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 23:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a repug plan. Never mind the issues, just spend billions to make Obama look bad, and do as much damage as possible to anything associated with Democrats because you are so angry about losing again. Did you learn that on this message board? That's what the frothing-at-the-bung fringe-right idiots do here all day long. Sorry to be the one to inform, but, that won't work. Buh-bye, loser.</Msg><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343971121972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 01:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343971337240-22</Id><Title>THE TALKING MONKEY IS GOING DOWN THE TOILET</Title><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Thursday shows Mitt Romney attracting 46% of the vote, while President Obama earns support from 44%.</Msg><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1343971337240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 01:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343977224657-23</Id><Title>THIS IS THE BAC BOARD STOP YOUR POLITICAL</Title><Msg>NONSENSE NOW!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>salomonbernstein</Username><Timestamp>1343977224657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 03:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343977706667-24</Id><Title>Romney to Reid: "Put Up or Shut Up"</Title><Msg>Seems the old fart is getting senile.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1343977706667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 03:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343982525497-25</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OJ is happy. He is getting Obama as a new bunk mate. Get out the ky, but he might not need it. He has blow smoke out of his as* for 4 hrs. now.</Msg><Username>garyjohnson34231</Username><Timestamp>1343982525497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 04:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343991203783-26</Id><Title>Face facts traditional Banking model is broken!</Title><Msg>Commercial and residential real estate lending is finished for another 10 years. Proprietary trading is the only source of revenue and it comes with huge risks. Playing the spreads makes them a few bucks but not enough to show growth. Unless we get employment and worker bees back paying taxes and borrowing for houses and cars at a decent interest rate....banks are finished, dead money for a decade!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1343991203783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 06:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343992361980-27</Id><Topic><Title>BAC's dead in the water, QE-ad naseam's foundering, and Mitt's sinking like a stone in the swing-states!....</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1343911150715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:39:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gore Vidal addendum inre BAC. I liked his quote, roughly that 50 percent of Americans don't vote, and 50 percent don't read the newspaper. He hoped they were the same 50. I hope it is these same fifty flocking to "invest" in BAC. Sure appears that way.</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1343992361980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343992852325-28</Id><Topic><Title>TAX CHEATER WILLARD ROMNEY WILL GO TO JAIL</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1343781520734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Steri story (no surprise) has not made its way into national media. Where did you dig it up? Memory, or alternative research. Google, Yahoo, or Facebook?</Msg><Username>f_bird55</Username><Timestamp>1343992852325</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343993078065-29</Id><Title>From a doctor's perspective.</Title><Msg>A doctor from France says: "In France, the medicine is so advanced that we cut off a man's testicles; we put them into another man, and in 6 weeks he is looking for work." The German doctor comments: "That's nothing, in Germany we take part of the brain out of a person; we put it into another person's head, and in 4 weeks he is looking for work." A Russian doctor says: "That's nothing either. In Russia we take out half of the heart from a person; we put it into another person's chest, and in 2 weeks he is looking for work." The U.S. doctor answers immediately: "That's nothing my colleagues, you are way behind us in the USA, about 3 years ago, we grabbed a person from Kenya with no brains, no heart, and no balls. We made him President of the United States, and now....... the whole damn country is looking for work."</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1343993078065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343994473187-30</Id><Title>Shorts are ffried..</Title><Msg>Just curious.. How did you dare ??</Msg><Username>your_ass_is_grass101</Username><Timestamp>1343994473187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343994683551-31</Id><Topic><Title>sell the pump at the beginning</Title><Username>bloomberg_marketwatch</Username><Timestamp>1343992638527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:17:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you come up with that ? Cover your short position ASAP, 8 is the works TODAY!!!</Msg><Username>analysts_are_foolish_idiots</Username><Timestamp>1343994683551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343995474331-32</Id><Topic><Title>TAX CHEATER WILLARD ROMNEY WILL GO TO JAIL</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1343781520734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right, however both Mr. Fartaway and Fish are liars and idiots. We've studied there habits for quite some time now and the results indicate they should be permanently institionalized.</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1343995474331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:04:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343995766643-33</Id><Title>The Hidden Value in Bank of America's Recent Earnings</Title><Msg>"What is clear to me is the company's strategy of rebuilding strong customer and client relationships is now paying off. " See The Street link on BAC page from today.</Msg><Username>cas1999</Username><Timestamp>1343995766643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343996834455-34</Id><Topic><Title>THE TALKING MONKEY IS GOING DOWN THE TOILET</Title><Username>big_triceratops</Username><Timestamp>1343971337240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 01:22:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>should ask someone to explain how the Electoral College System works. That popular vote margin of R-46% - D-44% looks terrific colored in on a map.....and doesn't mean a thing. The only number that matters is 270: the number of electoral votes needed to win. Right now, despite all that Red, it gives Obama 217, Romney 191, and leaves 130 as 'undecided' (the all-important "swing" states that include Wisconsin, Ohio, Michigan, Pennsylvania, Virginia, North Carolina, Florida, and a few smaller outliers). The electoral votes of these states are what will decide the outcome of this election. Most electoral college maps also include for each candidate the probability, expressed as a percentage, that he will achieve the required 270 electoral votes. Right now, the numbers are: Obama: 95%; Romney: 5%; Tie:</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1343996834455</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343997243019-35</Id><Title>Job Report Fraud</Title><Msg>That's what cult member, tax cheat, traitor Romney is saying now.</Msg><Username>tsunamidec2004</Username><Timestamp>1343997243019</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343997772354-36</Id><Topic><Title>Is Harry Reid a Tranny??</Title><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1343956518032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 21:15:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he`s a tranny, so is the kenyan, pig losi is really a man, they all get together at bawney fwanks house and "discuss policy".</Msg><Username>sammywong65</Username><Timestamp>1343997772354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343998677930-37</Id><Title>Analysts are now saying: "BAC is at the bottom, last chance to load up"!! NOW WHAT!!</Title><Msg>This means the shorters get pinched and the longers get rewarded??</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1343998677930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343998985943-38</Id><Topic><Title>From a doctor's perspective.</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1343993078065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 07:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good one</Msg><Username>rbwillmer</Username><Timestamp>1343998985943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343999057533-39</Id><Topic><Title>If Obama Administration Can Control The Numbers</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1343908752113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 07:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most definitely! However, it's most likely I won't have to apologize..this administration is, if nothing else, masters of trickery and deceit. "The nationâ€™s labor market showed some signs of improvement in July as job growth came in above market expectations, U.S. government data showed on Friday. Employment outside the farm sector grew by 163,000 workers in the month, the Labor Department said. This is the fas test pace of job growth since February."</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1343999057533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343999557192-40</Id><Title>163k jobs added, what now Mr Romney????</Title><Msg>losersssss....</Msg><Username>debedus1345</Username><Timestamp>1343999557192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343999828539-41</Id><Title>Space Taxis</Title><Msg>Boeing (BA) is expected to win the majority of up to $1B in federal money for the development of "space taxis" which are spacecraft for space cadets of the Democratic Party. The first two taxiis are named for head cadets Ride-me Reid and Puke-on-me Pelosi.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1343999828539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344000608867-42</Id><Title>Hope, from Perth!</Title><Msg>There is hope in November. The author of hope and d change Mr Obamao to be dethroned!</Msg><Username>bmbmmancini</Username><Timestamp>1344000608867</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344000934171-43</Id><Title>Congress takes a 5 WEEK VACATION!! How nice!!</Title><Msg>AND they will travel on our money!!</Msg><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1344000934171</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344001023868-44</Id><Title>who does CNBC think they are fooling?</Title><Msg>they are a major player in wall streets criminal organization..</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1344001023868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344001914090-45</Id><Topic><Title>Newbies: There are a Few Disgusted Bagholders Here Who Are Investor and Sexually Challenged</Title><Username>brazentrader</Username><Timestamp>1343854732874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:58:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yepper</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344001914090</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344002009747-46</Id><Title>short now</Title><Msg>i just sold my long position yesterday and shorting now</Msg><Username>bengal.tigris</Username><Timestamp>1344002009747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344002049556-47</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a hint</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1343334686851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ID iot</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344002049556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344002064940-48</Id><Topic><Title>Dow Up 200 Points While BAC Sells Off Slowly!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343327535659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 14:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ID iot</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344002064940</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344002077963-49</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday traderx asked fans shorted at $7.11, today hsi fans are crying</Title><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1343317032897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ID iot</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344002077963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344002094150-50</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS LONGS, I 'LL TAKE OVER BAC FROM THIS 7.16 LEVEL!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343315786574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:16:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ID iot</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344002094150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344002181832-51</Id><Title>WHERE IS OLE TURDIEX ANYWAY?</Title><Msg>????? Missing for days now.</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344002181832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344003209564-52</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE IS OLE TURDIEX ANYWAY?</Title><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344002181832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After the FSLR debacle. (He bought before earnings, up 20 percent). He has been in hiding. His aliases Brazentrade and Telez where out in full force but now they are missing as well.</Msg><Username>shareshark1</Username><Timestamp>1344003209564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:13:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344003304689-53</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts are now saying: "BAC is at the bottom, last chance to load up"!! NOW WHAT!!</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1343998677930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:57:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are just talking nonsense BAC is gonna keep going down</Msg><Username>testcdburner</Username><Timestamp>1344003304689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344003320691-54</Id><Topic><Title>TAX CHEATER WILLARD ROMNEY WILL GO TO JAIL</Title><Username>farawaylife</Username><Timestamp>1343781520734</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on dude. It is really hard to put a good crook with massive amounts of money in jail!! Maybe when he is prez he can cheat China out of all the money we owe them. Vote for a smart crook, dude!!!!</Msg><Username>ringomydog</Username><Timestamp>1344003320691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344003340255-55</Id><Topic><Title>Analysts are now saying: "BAC is at the bottom, last chance to load up"!! NOW WHAT!!</Title><Username>gburget2003</Username><Timestamp>1343998677930</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:57:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they just wanna give confidence back into the investors after the KCG disaster gotta find more suckers :)</Msg><Username>testcdburner</Username><Timestamp>1344003340255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344003530469-56</Id><Title>Like I said about the shorts</Title><Msg>We've had very low volume. Today we have low volume. There has been no opportunity for shorts to cover.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344003530469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004026885-57</Id><Topic><Title>Take a Good Look at BAC Up Here, it is its LAST TIME!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343315478623</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:11:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's now lost over 10,000 dollars and is stuck. LOL</Msg><Username>udumfck50</Username><Timestamp>1344004026885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:27:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004169506-58</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a hint</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1343334686851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This was true last week. It's true today. We need to see a 350 million share day before the shorts have any chance of covering.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344004169506</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344004229129-59</Id><Title>going to 8 soon now....</Title><Msg>the word is getting out.</Msg><Username>rocketscienc</Username><Timestamp>1344004229129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004339790-60</Id><Topic><Title>Like I said about the shorts</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344003530469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Traderx is now down over 12,000 on his big 3800 short he bragged about. he went from screaming at the board in anger under various IDs the last couple of days to utter despair.</Msg><Username>udumfck50</Username><Timestamp>1344004339790</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:32:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004400897-61</Id><Topic><Title>Like I said about the shorts</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344003530469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, please stop with it.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344004400897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004703744-62</Id><Topic><Title>going to 8 soon now....</Title><Username>rocketscienc</Username><Timestamp>1344004229129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right now we're just moving with the other financials and the overall market. When "word gets out" it will be $10+. I just don't know exactly when that will happen.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344004703744</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004703855-63</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Telezz!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336768134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 16:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice prediction! You sure is smaaarrrt</Msg><Username>shareshark1</Username><Timestamp>1344004703855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004748107-64</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice prediction</Msg><Username>shareshark1</Username><Timestamp>1344004748107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344004779953-65</Id><Topic><Title>DID I WARN YOU GUBERS YESTERDAY OR NOT????</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336486876000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-05-08 10:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foolish</Msg><Username>shareshark1</Username><Timestamp>1344004779953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:39:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005057392-66</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Sell FSLR Before The Earnings???</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343842249012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad move little dude</Msg><Username>atdabeach48</Username><Timestamp>1344005057392</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005112828-67</Id><Topic><Title>163k jobs added, what now Mr Romney????</Title><Username>debedus1345</Username><Timestamp>1343999557192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need an education. You have to have 140k jobs per month just to keep up with population growth of those entering the job market each month. The Labor participation rate ticked down to 63.7% the lowest in over 30yrs!! The market is up since it looks more likely the fed will do QE3 and what a bad policy that is</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344005112828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005496784-68</Id><Topic><Title>163k jobs added, what now Mr Romney????</Title><Username>debedus1345</Username><Timestamp>1343999557192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>unemployment went up, good job obama.</Msg><Username>bidds000</Username><Timestamp>1344005496784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005597899-69</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Sell FSLR Before The Earnings???</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343842249012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey TRADERZZZ. Got another $98.98 accrued interest today plus a $10.75 payment. The banks are still getting stronger by paying off their debts. Just had Citigroup pay off a debt to me today. Bond was paying 6.15%. That 10 paid off over the last 30 days by the banks mostly by BAC (7).</Msg><Username>m.inally</Username><Timestamp>1344005597899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005838947-70</Id><Topic><Title>163k jobs added, what now Mr Romney????</Title><Username>debedus1345</Username><Timestamp>1343999557192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1984 .... 4 million new jobs created in the last year of President Reagan's term...</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344005838947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005864638-71</Id><Topic><Title>8.3% with a large downward revision to June numbers</Title><Username>kilgares</Username><Timestamp>1343997613370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As in Electoral College Votes. Take a look at any current Electoral College map, and then tell us who's going to fire Obama, and where and how they're going to do it. Forget about the popular vote, and pay some attention to what counts. Right now, most electoral college maps show Obama with 217 firm, Romney with 191 firm, and 130 all-important swing votes still in play. The outcome will hinge on the popular vote in the key industrial swing states like Wisconsin, Ohio, Michigan, Pennsylvania and Virginia, and it is there that Romney's Run For The Roses ends. A week ago, before Mitt's Most Excellent Foreign Adventure, he was enjoying a 47% - 44% lead over Obama in those key states. A week later, following his embarrassing attack of Prancing Pony hoof-in-mouth disease, those numbers have flipped in Obama's favor, and the spread is growing. Romney's cameo appearance at the Wailing Wall in headgear that didn't exactly fit him reminded me of that infamous photo of Dukakis sitting in a tank wearing a helmet that made him look like Mr. Bean in a race car. Besides insulting nearly every country he visited (except Israel, which certainly didn't endear him to his base), undermining US foreign policy, and pulling the covers off his cultural elitist view of the world, his refusal to release his tax returns and Ann's Olympic follies are not playing well with the working class. But the real numbers that should have you reaching for your Dramamine and an airsickness bag are the probabilities those Electoral College Maps are assigning to the three possible outcomes of this election: Obama Wins - 95%; Romney Wins - 5%; and a Tie -</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344005864638</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344005942439-72</Id><Topic><Title>163k jobs added, what now Mr Romney????</Title><Username>debedus1345</Username><Timestamp>1343999557192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U6 also went up to 15%. at the end of the day this is the lowest percent of the eligible American work force who actually has a job in over 30yrs.</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344005942439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344006384255-73</Id><Title>BAC Shorts</Title><Msg>won't let this pig go above $7.42 !!!!</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344006384255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344006457784-74</Id><Title>Short squeezeeeeeeeeeeee</Title><Msg>To $10</Msg><Username>sterminator_734</Username><Timestamp>1344006457784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344006516247-75</Id><Topic><Title>8.3% with a large downward revision to June numbers</Title><Username>kilgares</Username><Timestamp>1343997613370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(continued - Yahoo truncated the above post) As I was saying, a Tie -</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344006516247</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344006744925-76</Id><Title>Let's make one thing clear. Remember the last time DOW was over 14000, BAC was at $54. Well,</Title><Msg>I have news for you, shorts: the volume is low, which means we are heading to $20. And then when the DOW is at 14000 again, we will hit $50. This is not speculation, but math and physics. Firm.</Msg><Username>longtermgull</Username><Timestamp>1344006744925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:12:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344006843826-77</Id><Topic><Title>8.3% with a large downward revision to June numbers</Title><Username>kilgares</Username><Timestamp>1343997613370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or even out of his roomier magic underwear. Kilgares, if you still think he can do it, I'll take the other side of all the even-money action you want (offer expires at 12.01 AM EDT, August 6th, 2012, which is not-so-coincidentally the anniversary of the A-bombing of Hiroshima). ROTFLMAO at exercise in duh-mass distraction and duh-mass destruction everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344006843826</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344006922997-78</Id><Title>Oil and Gasoline Prices Soaring</Title><Msg>Not good for the consumer</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344006922997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344006998105-79</Id><Topic><Title>8.3% with a large downward revision to June numbers</Title><Username>kilgares</Username><Timestamp>1343997613370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just one problem the election is in November</Msg><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344006998105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344007016321-80</Id><Topic><Title>8.3% with a large downward revision to June numbers</Title><Username>kilgares</Username><Timestamp>1343997613370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:40:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for stopping me before I finished cleaning Kilgares' clock. I'll just have to let Obama finish the job. ROTFLMAO at attempts to alter outcomes everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344007016321</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344007150121-81</Id><Title>Yahoo not allowing my non-profane reply to kilgares</Title><Msg>But their efforts, like those of kilgares, will not alter the outcome of this election. ROTFLMAO at small-minded minders everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344007150121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344007563929-82</Id><Title>BAC stock going nowhere...........</Title><Msg>Do you think BAC will go over $7.50 today ?????</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344007563929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344007707272-83</Id><Topic><Title>Oil and Gasoline Prices Soaring</Title><Username>value_investorr</Username><Timestamp>1344006922997</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:15:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Man Mitt Mormon is here now in bankrupt N Las Vegas speaking at a trucking equipment plant...will pickup a big check in Tahoe this evening...mining loves Mitt.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1344007707272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344007743467-84</Id><Topic><Title>Let's make one thing clear. Remember the last time DOW was over 14000, BAC was at $54. Well,</Title><Username>longtermgull</Username><Timestamp>1344006744925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup... 50 is high but 20 - 25 is reasonable.</Msg><Username>rocketscienc</Username><Timestamp>1344007743467</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344007821081-85</Id><Topic><Title>Let's make one thing clear. Remember the last time DOW was over 14000, BAC was at $54. Well,</Title><Username>longtermgull</Username><Timestamp>1344006744925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sucks to be you Telez. Hiding under your rock, I mean alias.</Msg><Username>inowhourviv</Username><Timestamp>1344007821081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344008014670-86</Id><Topic><Title>Let's make one thing clear. Remember the last time DOW was over 14000, BAC was at $54. Well,</Title><Username>longtermgull</Username><Timestamp>1344006744925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not hiding, Mr. Socio(path). As a matter of fact, I freely admitted I was making fun of longtermguy. Luckily, he is not alone, as this board provides plenty of patho-material for entertainment. Enjoy.</Msg><Username>telezz10100</Username><Timestamp>1344008014670</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344008127224-87</Id><Topic><Title>BAC stock going nowhere...........</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344007563929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:26:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't think so and not even next week but I have been wrong several times with this market. IMO</Msg><Username>bmath55</Username><Timestamp>1344008127224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344008190126-88</Id><Topic><Title>Let's make one thing clear. Remember the last time DOW was over 14000, BAC was at $54. Well,</Title><Username>longtermgull</Username><Timestamp>1344006744925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:12:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To many shares outstanding now, vs. when the DOW was 1400 previously. They have to do a reverse stock split of at least 1 for every 4 shares outstanding.!!! t</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344008190126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344008412106-89</Id><Title>THIS IS A BAC MESSAGE BOARD</Title><Msg>BAC MESSAGE, NOT POLITICAL</Msg><Username>ronalddimaio</Username><Timestamp>1344008412106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344008802212-90</Id><Title>If your still short BAC, which is 225mil shares I think you might be in some trouble. House is getting better</Title><Msg>If your still short BAC, which is 225mil shares I think you might be in some trouble. House is getting better</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344008802212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344008949849-91</Id><Topic><Title>If your still short BAC, which is 225mil shares I think you might be in some trouble. House is getting better</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344008802212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Insiders are buying BAC now</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344008949849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344009545730-92</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Shorts</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344006384255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:06:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't look now, but it's $7.45!!!!! I feel sorry for these guys that sell short, because they have no idea what they're doing.</Msg><Username>m.inally</Username><Timestamp>1344009545730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344009824438-93</Id><Title>Way to Go BAC!!!!</Title><Msg>The best way to trade this stock is by swing trading it in my opinion. I still fear credit card pricing will affect all the banks. People will not pay the credit card price and resort to paying cash or using a free checking account. Good luck to all: long, short, and option traders!</Msg><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1344009824438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344009838439-94</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo not allowing my non-profane reply to kilgares</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344007150121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kilgares is just another SW rectal drip alias. The election belongs to Obama. Willard is alienating more and more republicans over his refusal to disclose. Repugs really blew it.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344009838439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344009883441-95</Id><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT IS UP, job is not stabel. next month: MORE LAYOFF THAN NEW JOBS</Title><Msg>THE FED confirmed that U.S is slowing The Euro is in big trouble. ALL BANKS ARE LOSING PROFITS.</Msg><Username>danhong1</Username><Timestamp>1344009883441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:04:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344009971676-96</Id><Title>McCain's VP list included Romney, but he picked Palin because, "She was the best candidate for the job:</Title><Msg>"GOP's 2008 standard-bearer, Sen. John McCain, said on Tuesday that he had picked former Alaska Gov. Sarah Palin as his running mate because she was the best candidate for the job."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344009971676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344010222499-97</Id><Topic><Title>Way to Go BAC!!!!</Title><Username>oh_my_2012</Username><Timestamp>1344009824438</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:03:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes if you have insider information and a crystal ball I agree :) GL</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344010222499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:10:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344011049771-98</Id><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Msg>How does that help America ?</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344011402060-99</Id><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Msg>"When it comes to answering the legitimate questions the American people have about whether he avoided paying his fair share in taxes or why he opened a Swiss bank account, Romney has shut up," Reid said. "But as a presidential candidate, it's his obligation to put up, and release several years' worth of tax returns just like nominees of both parties have done for decades."</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344011561552-100</Id><Topic><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Honestly, I don't think it is necessary since he already released the last 2 years. He has released the last 2 years and that is enough.</Msg><Username>urichey</Username><Timestamp>1344011561552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344012082793-101</Id><Topic><Title>Repugs pick the worst candidate ever. Wayward Wuss Willard is doomed.</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949049124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:10:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want a good laugh? Read the "negative ads" posts of the dozens, and dozens of desperate rectal drips.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344012082793</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344012203251-102</Id><Title>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Title><Msg>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344012203251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344012269490-103</Id><Topic><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oy yeah its one year and a est for 2012 and neither are complete</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344012269490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344012299808-104</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The gap will only continue to widen in Obama's favor. Even Willard's party members are abandoning him.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344012299808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344012652784-105</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard is over. Bye, Willard. What fool will the repugs come up with in 2016?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344012652784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344013083711-106</Id><Topic><Title>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344012203251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Share buy back or dividend coming soon</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344013083711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344013263677-107</Id><Title>Insiders buying now, must be a dividend or share buy back comming soon</Title><Msg>Insiders buying now, must be a dividend or share buy back comming soon</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344013263677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344013378017-108</Id><Title>I hope its a big share buy back and not a dividend</Title><Msg>I hope its a big share buy back and not a dividend</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344013378017</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344013701539-109</Id><Topic><Title>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344012203251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahem, are you referring to listed insider transactions on Yahoo? I don't see any net accumulation there. They are exercising options and immediately disposing of the shares...ie, they are takin' the money and runnin'.</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1344013701539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344014634587-110</Id><Topic><Title>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344012203251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Purchase share are up over 105% and are being held</Msg><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344014634587</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344015273577-111</Id><Topic><Title>BAC insiders are buying BAC shares big time, What times is it BAC buying time</Title><Username>coinmaker77</Username><Timestamp>1344012203251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a link would be nice?</Msg><Username>flumoxed11</Username><Timestamp>1344015273577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344015373736-112</Id><Title>test</Title><Msg>test</Msg><Username>mossbrunson</Username><Timestamp>1344015373736</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344015677355-113</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Behold the awesome power of incumbency! The right had no qualms about using it; are you surprised to discover that in a two-party system, it's a two-way street? ROTFLMAO at the corner The Mittster has painted himself into. Even with their successful disenfranchisement of 750,000 eligible Pennsylvania voters, the GOP finds itself on the bad end of an 11% spread in that state. Even for the crew that stole 2 national elections in a row by twice contesting the results of a single state before a bought-and-paid-for Supreme Court, getting the Roberts gang to reverse a 360 - 208 Electoral College Vote is an exceedingly tough nut to make. Romney's gonna have to pull a huge rabbit out of that tiny yarmulka, or out of his more ample magic panties, and if you still think he can do it, I'll take the other end of all the even-money action you're good for. ROTFLMAO at exercises in duh-mass distraction and duh-mass destruction everywhere.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344015677355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344016069783-114</Id><Title>Obama told us in 2009 Unemployment would be down to 5.6% by now. So what happened?</Title><Msg>Serious replies only</Msg><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344016069783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344016119167-115</Id><Topic><Title>BAC Buy Back, Split &amp; Dividend Raise</Title><Username>grandpanoron</Username><Timestamp>1342984365806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let grandpa "noroM' dream come true. from rug to richest grandpa "noroM'</Msg><Username>grandpanoron</Username><Timestamp>1344016119167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344016307624-116</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo not allowing my non-profane reply to kilgares</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344007150121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I used kinder words than yours, if not a kinder tone, but yeah, that's about the size of it. ROTFLMAO at a dedicated follower of political fashion trends whose sartorial crimes now include wearing yarmulkas and magic underwear with smartly-tailored business suits. I wonder what was on the note he stuck in the Wailing Wall, and if he'd like to change that prayer.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344016307624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344016652054-117</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo not allowing my non-profane reply to kilgares</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344007150121</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 11:19:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know things are bad when the former wannabes who normally, if not reluctantly, fall in line behind the front-runner, like Newtie, Ron Paul, Santorum, and the rest of the clown klan line up to slam Willard for nondisclosure. Willard is toast.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344016652054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:57:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344016808735-118</Id><Topic><Title>Obama told us in 2009 Unemployment would be down to 5.6% by now. So what happened?</Title><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344016069783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What happened was...you started taking more wieners up your chute than usual, Romney is toast, and you only keep posting loser stupidity out of spite.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344016808735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344017136332-119</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the GOP roster of candidate wannabes. All clowns. And Willard was the best of them. GOP is pathetic.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344017136332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344017301000-120</Id><Title>THE UNEMPLOYMENT IS UP; SPAIN IS IN NEED OF $$$</Title><Msg>The job is good only for ONE month. It maybe worse this month and coming months because the UNEMPLOYMENT RATE IS GOING UP. It is now 8.3% Germany may not have extra $$ for Spain to borrow. All problems are still there. BAC should go down to $6/s</Msg><Username>detect_tive</Username><Timestamp>1344017301000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344017494147-121</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would have been so simple to show the world there is nothing to hide. Unless, of course, there IS something to hide.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344017494147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344017507549-122</Id><Title>Oweblama to the Olympic winners "You didn't win that"</Title><Msg>Rumor has it that Oweblama plans to take the spoils from the Olympic winners, since someone else provided everything so they could win. I say "You didn't win the Nobel Peace Prize" after 6 months of presidential do nothing but embrace the wars and backoff the threat to shut Guantanamo.</Msg><Username>pablisimo51</Username><Timestamp>1344017507549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344018171657-123</Id><Topic><Title>Obama told us in 2009 Unemployment would be down to 5.6% by now. So what happened?</Title><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344016069783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great and thoughtful answer. I want to know what polices Obama plans to change since the results of his current policies have been so awful. Americans want pragmatic leaders who will try a different course if the current one is showing no results.</Msg><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344018171657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344018174364-124</Id><Topic><Title>Oweblama to the Olympic winners "You didn't win that"</Title><Username>pablisimo51</Username><Timestamp>1344017507549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:11:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LiKKK DiKKK fool.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344018174364</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:22:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344018225763-125</Id><Title>Time for us to show our slobber</Title><Msg>Mr. Fartaway/Mr. Fish2kill. I know one of you is my daddy. Would either of u go with me today and then retire for a night of bangin? "Gay rights organizations and other advocacy groups promoted a "National Same-Sex Kiss Day" on Friday encouraging people to go to Chick-fil-A restaurants and lock lips with a member of the same sex to protest the fast-food chain owners' opposition to same-sex unions."</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344018225763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344018363186-126</Id><Topic><Title>Time for us to show our slobber</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344018225763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Miles, you and your sick "daddies" are giving the Democrats a bad name. Son, please quit hanging out with these degens.</Msg><Username>milesed17smom</Username><Timestamp>1344018363186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:26:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344018529245-127</Id><Title>Obama told us the Deficit would be cut in half by now what happened?</Title><Msg>Instead the deficit is sky high and economists warn that all this debt will result in lower wages, a lower standard of living and put pressure on the fed to further devalue the currency destroying savings and putting the U.S. in line for further downgrades. I want to know what Obama plans to do about it as if his current tax plan is implemented it would only bring in 80 Billion more each year from the so called "rich" and we are running deficits of 1.3 to 1.6 Trillion. What is his plan?</Msg><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344018529245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344018741887-128</Id><Title>Me &amp; Mike</Title><Msg>"How about that Michael Phelps? But let's remember he didn't win all those medals, someone else did. After all, he and I swam in public pools, built by state employees using tax dollars. He got training from the USOC, and ate food grown by the Department of Agriculture. He should play fair and share his medals with people like me, who can barely keep my head above water, let alone swim."</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344018741887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344018998659-129</Id><Title>Chick-fil-A Has 'Record-Setting' Sales on Appreciation Day</Title><Msg>Chick-fil-A posted "record-setting" sales on Wednesday as thousands of people swarmed the chicken chain for Chick-fil-A Appreciation Day after the chain's chief made anti-gay comments. "While we don't release exact sales numbers, we can confirm reports that it was a record-setting day," Steve Robinson, Chick-fil-A's executive vice president of marketing, said in a statement. At least one location had to close early after nearly selling out of chicken. At others, lines snaked around buildings and patrons waited upwards of two hours to snag their chicken sandwiches and show their support for Chick-fil-A CEO Dan Cathy's comments supporting traditional marriage. "We are very grateful and humbled by the incredible turnout of loyal Chick-fil-A customers on August 1 at Chick-fil-A restaurants around the country," Robinson said. "We congratulate local Chick-fil-A Owner/Operators and their team members for striving to serve each and every customer with genuine hospitality." At the Chick-fil-A in Augusta, Georgia, about 150 miles from the franchise's Atlanta headquarters, the lunch line wait was hours long. And after a day of lines that snaked around the building, the restaurant had to turn away part of the dinner crowd, closing two hours early due to low supplies After an outpouring of support for Cathy and his company during Wednesday's Appreciation Day, gay activists are taking to the streets, or rather the Chick-fil-A parking lots, around the country for National Same Sex Kiss Day at Chick-fil-A on Friday to protest the chicken chain's opposition to the LGBTQ community. Same-sex couples are being urged to take photos and videos of themselves kissing outside of Chick-fil-A restaurants nationwide. About 11,000 have said on Facebook that they will attend the event. The Chick-fil-A Appreciation Day event had about 55 times that many Facebook attendees. Although the restaurant chain has become a rallying cry for people on both sides of the marriage debate, Chick-fil-A has aimed to stay out of the politics and controversy stemming from its CEO's comments. "The Chick-fil-A culture and service tradition in our restaurants is to treat every person with honor, dignity and respect â€“regardless of their belief, race, creed, sexual orientation or gender," Robinson said in a statement. "We understand from news reports that Friday may present yet another opportunity for us to serve with genuine hospitality, superior service and great food."</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344018998659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344019164546-130</Id><Topic><Title>Obama told us the Deficit would be cut in half by now what happened?</Title><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344018529245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:28:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has no solutions. How could he? He is a community organizer who has never had a job or even seen a balance sheet. Might want to plan for more downgrades and a debt crisis if he gets 4 more years</Msg><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344019164546</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:39:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344019234142-131</Id><Title>humblehawk, give it up</Title><Msg>You know Obama has got this election wrapped up.</Msg><Username>kds5862</Username><Timestamp>1344019234142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344019877084-132</Id><Topic><Title>Obama told us in 2009 Unemployment would be down to 5.6% by now. So what happened?</Title><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344016069783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you going to be like one of those werewolf nazis that thought they could keep on with their lost cause after the allies had defeated them? Or, do you howl from the anguish and the pain from losing again? Whatever. Please, don't stop. I find your pain amusing. It makes me laugh.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344019877084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344020013423-133</Id><Topic><Title>humblehawk, give it up</Title><Username>kds5862</Username><Timestamp>1344019234142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:40:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, don't encourage him to stop making a fool out of himself. We all need a good laugh. It's amusing to see losers cry.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020013423</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344020257522-134</Id><Title>163,000 JOBS CAN ANYONE SAY THAT'S GOOD WITH A STRAIGHT FACE!!!??</Title><Msg>No intelligent person</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344020257522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344020361373-135</Id><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Msg>Who will be the first to say, "no thanks, Willard, I have my career to think of?"</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344020452544-136</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid rebukes Willard's "put up, or shut up" and demands Willard "PUT UP!"</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344011402060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean as late as last night, #$%$!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020452544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344020799354-137</Id><Topic><Title>WHERE IS OLE TURDIEX ANYWAY?</Title><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344002181832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 09:56:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My name is Tur die I lost 8 nickels I lost 8 nickels Shiny and new I'm gonna.... lalalalala</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344020799354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344020909251-138</Id><Topic><Title>163,000 JOBS CAN ANYONE SAY THAT'S GOOD WITH A STRAIGHT FACE!!!??</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344020257522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:57:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. The market just did. Duh!</Msg><Username>kkobe36</Username><Timestamp>1344020909251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:08:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344021455094-139</Id><Topic><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree it clearly hasn't helped as unemployment went up again. Vote the offshoring tax cheater Obama out of office before its too late!!!!</Msg><Username>somebody_help654</Username><Timestamp>1344021455094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344021618894-140</Id><Topic><Title>Chick-fil-A Has 'Record-Setting' Sales on Appreciation Day</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344018998659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i hope they hump and kiss at the democrat convention. Obama would like that a lot, I mean he will really really like that</Msg><Username>somebody_help654</Username><Timestamp>1344021618894</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344021731897-141</Id><Topic><Title>Obama told us in 2009 Unemployment would be down to 5.6% by now. So what happened?</Title><Username>humblehawk88</Username><Timestamp>1344016069783</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:47:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is boring and franky I could care less what he says</Msg><Username>somebody_help654</Username><Timestamp>1344021731897</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344022149677-142</Id><Title>Scheduled:</Title><Msg>Shorts covering is scheduled at 12:40 a.m. We are going higher into next week. Market wants to go higher into September. All bad news are factored in at current price level. All aboard! Choo!!! Choo!!!!</Msg><Username>fbi4hire</Username><Timestamp>1344022149677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344022446806-143</Id><Topic><Title>163,000 JOBS CAN ANYONE SAY THAT'S GOOD WITH A STRAIGHT FACE!!!??</Title><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344020257522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:57:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kkobe36, "Yes. The market just did. Duh!" You idiot! THE MARKET IS LOOKING FOR QE3 after that lousy report!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344022446806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344022656705-144</Id><Title>BAC down............</Title><Msg>.........Market off slightly from it/s high for today anfd this (BAC) pig is already starting to work it.s way down.!!!!!</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344022656705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344022729952-145</Id><Topic><Title>BAC down............</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344022656705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did you lose today shortie ????</Msg><Username>kds5862</Username><Timestamp>1344022729952</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344022939481-146</Id><Title>LOOKS LIKE OBAMA WILL INHERIT HIS OWN RECESSION IF REELECTED</Title><Msg>WILL HE CONTINUE TO BLAME BUSH!?</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344022939481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344022980654-147</Id><Topic><Title>BAC down............</Title><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344022656705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:37:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately I bought shares @ $8.95 and still waiting to at least break even !!!</Msg><Username>rloos15</Username><Timestamp>1344022980654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344023293740-148</Id><Title>what a boring stock</Title><Msg>This this has been at 740 to 745 for like 4 hours. Boring!...... Try Facebook</Msg><Username>district.columbia_1968</Username><Timestamp>1344023293740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023482634-149</Id><Topic><Title>traderx... FSLR after hour up 14 percent, earning great $115 soon ..told you</Title><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1343852009426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:13:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023482634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023515375-150</Id><Topic><Title>Time To Come Clean PONZIERS!!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343844095841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:01:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023515375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023526087-151</Id><Topic><Title>Here's a hint</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1343334686851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023526087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023531552-152</Id><Topic><Title>Dow Up 200 Points While BAC Sells Off Slowly!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343327535659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 14:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023531552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023560631-153</Id><Topic><Title>yesterday traderx asked fans shorted at $7.11, today hsi fans are crying</Title><Username>station888canada</Username><Timestamp>1343317032897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023560631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023567410-154</Id><Topic><Title>THANKS LONGS, I 'LL TAKE OVER BAC FROM THIS 7.16 LEVEL!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343315786574</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 11:16:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023567410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023582892-155</Id><Topic><Title>Brazen, Brazen, Brazen.........</Title><Username>open4wild</Username><Timestamp>1343248446715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 16:34:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023582892</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023613789-156</Id><Topic><Title>BREAK UP BANK TALK IS VERY BEARISH, and HERE IS WHY</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343245324291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023613789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023698209-157</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023698209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023734698-158</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Telezz!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336768134000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-11 16:28:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023734698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023775827-159</Id><Topic><Title>40 REASONS TRADERX IS A MORON</Title><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1329328200000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-02-15 12:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023775827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344023799621-160</Id><Title>B OF A RUMOURED TO SETTLE THIS WEEKEND WITH GSE..HERE WE GO</Title><Msg>OFF TO THE RACES</Msg><Username>stocksleuth13</Username><Timestamp>1344023799621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344023907969-161</Id><Topic><Title>CHRIS WHALEN SAYS BAC WILL FAIL BECAUSE OF 100 BILLION LIABILITY!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1342612630512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-18 07:57:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpy dumby</Msg><Username>bumpybumpbump1966</Username><Timestamp>1344023907969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344023942009-162</Id><Title>COVER COVER COVER..GSE'S GOING TO SETTLE</Title><Msg>COVERRRRRRR!</Msg><Username>greatestideaman</Username><Timestamp>1344023942009</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344023962025-163</Id><Title>CNBC just said,market is up..</Title><Msg>..because it was oversold!!!Clowns,we are at 13 000 ! Oversold my a@@</Msg><Username>augispr</Username><Timestamp>1344023962025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344024005942-164</Id><Topic><Title>Time for us to show our slobber</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1344018225763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:23:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Miles, you make such a pathetic case for your situation that I'm ready to help you find your daddy. Have your mom tell you how old you are, and add one year. Now keeping that number in mind, ask her to show you all the hogs on your farm, and have her point out the ones that are at least as old (in human years) as that number you've already forgotten. Either your Daddy is one of them, or he's dead. Good luck! ROTFLMAO at life (and death) on the s_miles farm.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344024005942</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344024373104-165</Id><Topic><Title>How long is Congress going to wait</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344020889758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 15:08:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but I know they've gone home for the month, and you know I'd never jerk you around. ROTFLMAO at people asking all the wrong questions in all the wrong places. No wonder you're having so much trouble finding the right girl, dump. (See, I didn't even accuse you of being light in your loafers. Now who's your buddy?)</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344024373104</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344024475551-166</Id><Title>Low volume today</Title><Msg>Shorts had no chance to cover today. Low volume.</Msg><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344024475551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344024710310-167</Id><Topic><Title>Low volume today</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344024475551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>brazardxelez going to have a looooooooooooooonnnnng weekend.</Msg><Username>udumfck50</Username><Timestamp>1344024710310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344024977781-168</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Sell FSLR Before The Earnings???</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343842249012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now watch me pretend I'm making money and hope that everyone forgets I shorted BAC last week.</Msg><Username>zipzter</Username><Timestamp>1344024977781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025053420-169</Id><Topic><Title>Low volume today</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344024475551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I'm going to lie to the board by starting a new thread and hope you all forget everything I said over the last week. It's like magic. I am always right!</Msg><Username>tarderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344025053420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025151480-170</Id><Topic><Title>Chick-fil-A Has 'Record-Setting' Sales on Appreciation Day</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344018998659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but I wouldn't expect him to have that on the program for the convention, that is unless Larry Craig accepts his invitation. I'll make a few calls, though, and see if Obama would be willing to add it to the dance card for his upcoming Inaugural Ball. I trust you're enough of an adult to wait 6 more months for what you seem to have your, uh, heart, so set on. ROTFLMAO as right-winged ostriches set their sights on China.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344025151480</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025259102-171</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Sell FSLR Before The Earnings???</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343842249012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:30:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's all good because I'm going to lie and say I didn't short. JUst watch!</Msg><Username>tarderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344025259102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:20:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025308971-172</Id><Topic><Title>Chick-fil-A Has 'Record-Setting' Sales on Appreciation Day</Title><Username>calm_reason</Username><Timestamp>1344018998659</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still waiting for you to show us on that mean old Electoral College map where those folks who are going to fire Obama live. ROTFLMAO at people who can't read maps everywhere. Turn off your GPS; you're too lost for it to help you now.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1344025308971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025364416-173</Id><Topic><Title>Low volume today</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344024475551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:07:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good to see you ole turdiex. I see you are still class clown. And here we thought you were cowering in a corner the entire week after making such a big deal about your shorts on BAC and FSLR</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344025364416</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344025370071-174</Id><Title>How much longer is this stock free?</Title><Msg>$7.43 for a world recognized leading banking firm? A pizza costs more. Regardless, the market Cap under $80 billion is too low.</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1344025370071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344025509640-175</Id><Topic><Title>Like I said about the shorts</Title><Username>longtermguy91</Username><Timestamp>1344003530469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 10:18:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No no forget about that. I'm pretending like I'm not short anymore.</Msg><Username>tarderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344025509640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344025987676-176</Id><Title>Obama's Sec working just great!!!! Flash crash, MF global, Perigrine, Knight</Title><Msg>How long before the entire system freezes up?</Msg><Username>dumz_n_dummer</Username><Timestamp>1344025987676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344026078190-177</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Know I Made A lot of $$$ Shorting FSLR Don't You?</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344024818132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? That's the best you could do Turdiex? Pretend your running commentary of holding your short positions didn't happen? You are losing your touch. Pathetic attempt at a coverup buddy. Just admit your losses and move on.</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344026078190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:34:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344026193007-178</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a better chance of getting laid than having this stock go to $4.40. Aint happening.</Msg><Username>squad008</Username><Timestamp>1344026193007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344026919882-179</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Know I Made A lot of $$$ Shorting FSLR Don't You?</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344024818132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one! You almost made me forget you got your #$%$ handed to you shorting by recounting your fake past profits! Nice to see you put in a better effort. LOL 3800 shares...man you do make me laugh turdiex! Next time the stock goes against you like in the case of FSLR and BAC be sure stick around instead of showing up AH on a Friday claiming your millions. It's no fun without you.</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344026919882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:48:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344027225170-180</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, Station, You Know I Made A lot of $$$ Shorting FSLR Don't You?</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1344024818132</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:13:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So much better. I am now so distracted by your fake profits I can barely remember you screaming about your short positions that have done nothing but move against you. Keep up the good work 3800 shares. Next time stick around when stocks like FSLR and BAC violently move against instead of showing up AH on a Friday hoping Monday will be up so you respond to your own thread as if nothing happened. This board sorely lacks humor when you are gone.</Msg><Username>yranidiot78</Username><Timestamp>1344027225170</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344028464366-181</Id><Title>Attn: LiKKK DiKKK dumpobamie: What's the latest finding from Sheriff Joe's Goon Squad Posse on Obama's birth certificate?</Title><Msg>We need an update on your favorite non-issue.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344028464366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344028802714-182</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's the vetting process to consider. All VP candidates must be willing to disclose their tax records for the last 1 1/l2 years, just like Willard.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344028802714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344029133251-183</Id><Topic><Title>McCain's VP list included Romney, but he picked Palin because, "She was the best candidate for the job:</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1344009971676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:06:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!!!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344029133251</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344029136966-184</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you stupid assssssss.</Msg><Username>tung_nguyen121769</Username><Timestamp>1344029136966</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344030470133-185</Id><Title>GOP Rep. Walter Jones (R-N.C.) said Thursday that Mitt Romney's refusal to release more than two years of tax returns will hurt him in the presidential election.</Title><Msg>"I don't think this will go away," said Jones, "And if we're still talking about this in September, he's in deep trouble."</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344030470133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344031628542-186</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yo statement should have been: How many VP candidates will run from Romney like Democrats run from light? whuts wrong wif you boy?</Msg><Username>mike_van_der_slut_irvin19</Username><Timestamp>1344031628542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344032931614-187</Id><Topic><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got that backwards you must be a neotard.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344032931614</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344033649149-188</Id><Title>SPIN IT OBAMA!</Title><Msg>â€œDespite the seemingly good news,â€ reports CNBC (seemingly good news!), â€œthe reportâ€™s household showed that the actual amount of Americans working dropped by 195,000,â€ as labor force participation is at a 30-year low. As Jim Pethokoukis at AEI likes to point out, if the workforce were the same as when George W. Bush left office, the unemployment rate would be 11 percent. Seemingly, indeed.</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344033649149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344034442483-189</Id><Topic><Title>SPIN IT OBAMA!</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344033649149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish we had Bush back!</Msg><Username>gem_shorts</Username><Timestamp>1344034442483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344034836213-190</Id><Title>I had a bad day and then some idiot told me to vote for Obama</Title><Msg>I pushed him down a hill</Msg><Username>dumz_n_dummer</Username><Timestamp>1344034836213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344035868800-191</Id><Topic><Title>BAC is Headed to 4.40 Folks!!!</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1336174719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 19:38:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I see the picture. I see the picture of a blithering idiot with a chip on his shoulder for BAC.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344035868800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:17:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344036405260-192</Id><Topic><Title>How much longer is this stock free?</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1344025370071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know how much longer it will be so low, but when the economy firms and the factors that have investors worried are resolved, then it will make a strong move up and people will be kicking themselves for not buying at these low prices over the past couple months. Shorts who don't get out when the getting is good will lose the money they made trading it. This is a replay of the trust perferreds I bought three and a half years ago for $3 and sold for $21 two years later. That is the kind of move the common can make as well, with an improving economy and improving BAC profits of course.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344036405260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344037048311-193</Id><Topic><Title>BREAK UP BANK TALK IS VERY BEARISH, and HERE IS WHY</Title><Username>traderx1966</Username><Timestamp>1343245324291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are truly clueless. They don't "owe trillions" you fool. There may be trillions of CDCs and MBSs, but the exposure is NOT the full face, it is some small fraction of it. That is how you twist the facts, or maybe you are just too ignorant of how it works to know better and you actually believe the dribble you write. It's gone from amuzing to pathetic. Come on man, stop embarassing yourself.</Msg><Username>mrstan4089</Username><Timestamp>1344037048311</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344037267442-194</Id><Topic><Title>How much longer is this stock free?</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1344025370071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>patience is a vitue....</Msg><Username>george.murphy3</Username><Timestamp>1344037267442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344037292770-195</Id><Topic><Title>How much longer is this stock free?</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1344025370071</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 16:22:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>grossly undervalued...</Msg><Username>george.murphy3</Username><Timestamp>1344037292770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344038302868-196</Id><Title>Trader X is a little disgruntled these days</Title><Msg>since he has been so wrong for so long. You see he is a short and things just don't seem to working out for him, so he has resorted to scare tactics, such as throwing things out here that he has no way of proving, you know...short type of stuff. You will see him post frequently and use very outdated info. also, so be advised, just pity the poor thing, but don't listen to a word he says, unless you want to lose a lot of money. Better yet, just buy BAC and put him on ignore. J.</Msg><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1344038302868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344038500877-197</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA what are you HIDING with your SCHOOL RECORDS???</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344038333187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent question!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344038500877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344038514685-198</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA what are you HIDING with your SCHOOL RECORDS???</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344038333187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent question!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344038514685</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344038515207-199</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA what are you HIDING with your SCHOOL RECORDS???</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344038333187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent question!</Msg><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344038515207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344038655229-200</Id><Topic><Title>SPIN IT OBAMA!</Title><Username>bury_obama</Username><Timestamp>1344033649149</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 18:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't we all!!!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1344038655229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344039296489-201</Id><Title>Just found out my wife is a stupid Democrat</Title><Msg>You ever wonder how I found out ? I found Obama's photo in her wallet. Maybe I will lock her up in the garage with my gay dog. No more sex for her for at least 1 month. Read my lips. I hate Democrat ! !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1344039296489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344041159872-202</Id><Topic><Title>Job offshoring tax cheat for president ?</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344011049771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 12:24:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is unamerican, money first !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1344041159872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:45:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344042864122-203</Id><Topic><Title>Trader X is a little disgruntled these days</Title><Username>jburke2133</Username><Timestamp>1344038302868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That guy is a lunatic as are his many IDs. I remember someone saying he lost over $300,000 and has been on here ever since pretending otherwise. I don't know if it's true, but I do know since the ignore button is gone this board is even worse than before.</Msg><Username>dontovranalys</Username><Timestamp>1344042864122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344043035678-204</Id><Title>GAY MARRIAGE IS THE WAVE OF THE FUTURE</Title><Msg>Hee hee, I'm so glad! Go Obama!</Msg><Username>milesed17</Username><Timestamp>1344043035678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344043442536-205</Id><Title>Why in the F would Obama want to raise taxes on anyone in this God Awful Economy.</Title><Msg>dum #$%$</Msg><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043442536</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:24:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344043702021-206</Id><Title>Obama has to be the dumbest #$%$*k ever</Title><Msg>Most of his policies are at odds with Obama of 2008 #$%$?</Msg><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043702021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046020715-207</Id><Topic><Title>New polling data out from Pew Research Center finds President Obama with a double-digit lead over Mitt Romney nationally:</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343946448481</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Willard was beaten before the race even started</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344046020715</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046176021-208</Id><Topic><Title>How many VP candidates will run from Romney like roaches run from light?</Title><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344020361373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 14:59:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who'll be the first to say, "No, Willard, the thought of spending ANY time with you is repulsive." Portman? Pawlenty? Rubio?</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344046176021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046430585-209</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has to be the dumbest #$%$*k ever</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043702021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh please the dumbest #$%$*K ever, I think not that honor was retired when GW left office; I had a link to prove it but Yahoo in it's wisdom has banned URLs in this format, I guess proof was not necessary in any event.</Msg><Username>imadtchdgr</Username><Timestamp>1344046430585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046616363-210</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has to be the dumbest #$%$*k ever</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043702021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your loser candidate Romney is making it happen!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344046616363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046851720-211</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has to be the dumbest #$%$*k ever</Title><Username>talking.monkeyy</Username><Timestamp>1344043702021</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not nice to talk that way about our president! You ought to be really ashamed!</Msg><Username>gobama2012a</Username><Timestamp>1344046851720</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344046944828-212</Id><Topic><Title>GAY MARRIAGE IS THE WAVE OF THE FUTURE</Title><Username>milesed17</Username><Timestamp>1344043035678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 21:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree milesed! Gays have come along way thanks to Obma!</Msg><Username>gobama2012a</Username><Timestamp>1344046944828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344047002067-213</Id><Title>Senator McCain stated last Tuesday that his VP list included Romney, but he picked Palin because, "She was the best candidate for the job. Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!!</Title><Msg>McCain picked fluff-brained Palin over Wayward Wuss Willard. LMFAAAAAAAAO!!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344047002067</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344047197114-214</Id><Topic><Title>Nondisclosure = Nonelectable</Title><Username>go_choke_charlie</Username><Timestamp>1343949368981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 19:16:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid tells Wayward Willard AGAIN, "PUT UP!!" The more Willard refuses to do what ranking memebers of his own party think he should do, the more deceitful he looks.</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344047197114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344047413264-215</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,what are you HIDING with your TAXES??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344037902151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:51:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney may or may not be hiding anything concerning his taxes, but he is not hiding how arrogant and stupid he is by refusing disclosure. What a fool!</Msg><Username>newvulgarian</Username><Timestamp>1344047413264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344047538755-216</Id><Title>Ralph Nader: "The people want to be paid!" Mr. Obama: "Let them buy stock."</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney: "They should start companies and make 750 million like me. Lazy bums." Mr. Obama: "Make them buy health care."</Msg><Username>longon2007</Username><Timestamp>1344047538755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 22:32:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344051677698-217</Id><Topic><Title>Why doesn't Obama pay his FAIR share of income taxes?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344040576842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why doesn't Mitt pay any taxes?</Msg><Username>h2145h</Username><Timestamp>1344051677698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 23:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344051748112-218</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA what are you HIDING with your SCHOOL RECORDS???</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1344038333187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 19:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt, why are you hiding your tax returns?</Msg><Username>h2145h</Username><Timestamp>1344051748112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 23:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>