<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358571958314-1</Id><Title>Are Republicans are serious about creating jobs for the American people?</Title><Msg>Hell no... they are bullshitters to the highest level, useless politicians and deadbeats.</Msg><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1358571958314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:05:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358588424292-2</Id><Title>call option</Title><Msg>need 2 no the answer if u own a in the money call at the time of expiration does it automatically take affect were their shares will come 2 u or are u stuck with owning the in the money call because of not exersising it before expireation please if u no the answer let me no thanks</Msg><Username>countryjoe95</Username><Timestamp>1358588424292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 04:40:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358593225986-3</Id><Topic><Title>i want to die</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358563565367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:46:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in 59 months bac will be 40.00 pps. That is my belief. Tgat is when i retire. -bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358593225986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358593629486-4</Id><Topic><Title>Are Republicans are serious about creating jobs for the American people?</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1358571958314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:05:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is any congress member willing to make the country their first priority instead of their own personal agenda. Congress is a pathetic bunch. That includes both parties and you can throw the #$%$ pres. In this group too. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358593629486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 06:07:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358600315484-5</Id><Title>BAC 13.75 BY MARCH 8</Title><Msg>IT WILL RALLY BACK</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358600315484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:58:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358600541879-6</Id><Topic><Title>BAC 13.75 BY MARCH 8</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358600315484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 07:58:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LET THE SHEEP RUN FOR THE FENCE</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358600541879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:02:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601781872-7</Id><Topic><Title>Are Republicans are serious about creating jobs for the American people?</Title><Username>reggie.thoma</Username><Timestamp>1358571958314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:05:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reggie, clean up in cell 31.</Msg><Username>shutter_islandward8</Username><Timestamp>1358601781872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:23:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358601814746-8</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With children and Democrats "No" is m=necessary</Msg><Username>barack_crock</Username><Timestamp>1358601814746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602403453-9</Id><Topic><Title>How to control Guns</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358564036223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Half the assault weapons are in ghettos similiar to the one you and Reggie live in, You and your ilk don't pay taxes; you live off the taxes of hard working American citizens. Geez, can't you find a "Women's Daily" site to discuss things like knitting?</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1358602403453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602740587-10</Id><Topic><Title>How to control Guns</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358564036223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's something for example..just search around and you'll find a site more conducive to feminist discussions: In 2008, when Obama announced Moochelle's intention to be “mom-in-chief,” many feminists decried her decision to give up her career and said she had been victimized by her husband’s choices. She was regarded as one of the women feminist Linda Hirshman described as “letting down the team.”</Msg><Username>moronstudyinstitute</Username><Timestamp>1358602740587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:39:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358602831479-11</Id><Topic><Title>How to control Guns</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358564036223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think about it! After reading the following historical facts, read the part about Switzerland twice. A LITTLE GUN HISTORY In 1929, the Soviet Union established gun control.. From 1929 to 1953, about 20 million dissidents, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated. ------------------------------ In 1911, Turkey established gun control. From 1915 to 1917, 1.5 million Armenians, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated. ------------------------------ Germany established gun control in 1938 and from 1939 to 1945 a total of 13 million Jews and others who were unable to defend themselves were rounded up and exterminated. China established gun control in 1935. From 1948 to 1952, 20 million political dissidents, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated ------------------------------ Guatemala established gun control in 1964. From 1964 to 1981, 100,000 Mayan Indians, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated. ------------------------------ Uganda established gun control in 1970. From 1971 to 1979, 300,000 Christians, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated ------------------------------ Cambodia established gun control in 1956. From 1975 to 1977, one million educated people, unable to defend themselves, were rounded up and exterminated. ----------------------------- Defenseless people rounded up and exterminated in the 20th Century because of gun control: 56 million. ------------------------------ It has now been 12 months since gun owners in Australia were forced by new law to surrender 640,381 personal firearms to be destroyed by their own Government, a program costing Australia taxpayers more than $500 million dollars. The first year results are now in: Australia-wide, homicides are up 3..2 percent. Australia-wide, assaults are up 8.6 percent. Australia-wide, armed robberies are up 44 percent (yes, 44 percent)! In the state of Victoria alone, homicides with firearms are now up 300 percent.. Note that while the law-abiding citizens turned them in, the criminals did not, and criminals still possess their guns! While figures over the previous 25 years showed a steady decrease in armed robbery with firearms, this has changed drastically upward in the past 12 months, since criminals now are guaranteed that their prey is unarmed. There has also been a dramatic increase in break-ins and assaults of the ELDERLY. Australian politicians are at a loss to explain how public safety has decreased, after such monumental effort, and expense was expended in successfully ridding Australian society of guns. The Australian experience and the other historical facts above prove it. You won't see this data on the US evening news, or hear politicians disseminating this information. Guns in the hands of honest citizens save lives and property and, yes, gun-control laws adversely affect only the law-abiding citizens Take note my fellow Americans, before it's too late! The next time someone talks in favor of gun control, please remind them of this history lesson. With guns, we are 'citizens'' Without them, we are 'subjects'' During WWII the Japanese decided not to invade America because they knew most Americans were ARMED! The purpose of fighting is to win. There is no possible victory in defense. The sword is more important than the shield, and skill is more important than either. The final weapon is the brain. All else is supplemental SWITZERLAND ISSUES EVERY HOUSEHOLD A GUN! SWITZERLAND 'S GOVERNMENT TRAINS EVERY ADULT THEY ISSUE A RIFLE, and SWITZERLAND HAS THE LOWEST GUN RELATED CRIME RATE OF ANY CIVILIZED COUNTRY IN THE WORLD! IT'S A NO BRAINER! DON'T LET OUR GOVERNMENT WASTE MILLIONS OF OUR TAX DOLLARS IN AN EFFORT TO MAKE ALL LAW ABIDING CITIZENS AN EASY TARGET. Just think how powerful our government is getting! They think these other countries just didn't do it right. Learn from history.</Msg><Username>garyjohnson34231</Username><Timestamp>1358602831479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 08:40:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358604390100-12</Id><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Msg>Golf outings: 113 (Most frequent venue: 52 rounds at Joint Base Andrews) That's 28 times a year for the math challenged like Bucky, a little more than once every two weeks. Of course when he is on vacation He played more frequently. Vacations: 13 (spanning all or part of 83 days)-About 20 days a year, less than three weeks a year including Christmas And of course the really important one to the right wing Fringe Number of speeches, remarks and comments: 1,852, Number of speeches delivered with Teleprompter: 699. So most of the time he was speaking without a teleprompter. Can you imagine that, they posted here that he never spoke without a teleprompter took more vacations and played more golf than anyone. Now we have the truth about all of these important issues presented here repeatedly in error over the past 3 years. Sorry, they didn't have figures for the number of times they ate lobster but they did have that they went out to dinner 57 times in four years, a little more than once a month.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358604406946-13</Id><Title>MOST DANGEROUS PLACE IN THE WORLD</Title><Msg>BETWEEN A WOMANS LEG.You have know idea what's going on down there</Msg><Username>pastel_hero</Username><Timestamp>1358604406946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358604518547-14</Id><Title>VIX and BAC</Title><Msg>VIX is at June 2007 level. Something is going to happen. You know what happened after June 2007. Nobody knows when it comes. But when it comes it will be like a tsunami.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358604518547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:08:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358604709613-15</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's totally incompetent. He was nothing more than a community organizer. What do you expect? He's in way over his head. That's why nothing is going to change with all the problems we have.</Msg><Username>citamar</Username><Timestamp>1358604709613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:11:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605671085-16</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solutions that work like lower taxes by reducing your deductions? Solutions like we can increase military spending by lowering taxes? Solutions like we can have a better health care system by eliminating 30 million Americans from care? Solutions like we can provide more liberty by stopping people on the street and asking them to prove they are citizens? Solutions like we can provide more security if you give us all guns and let us shoot anyone that looks suspicious coming back from a convenience store with Skittle and a drink? Solutions like we can do more for women by making laws about their personal medical choices? Solutions like granting more freedom by controlling sexual preferences? Solutions like we can cut costs by raising our own pay? Solutions like we can raise more money by allowing manufacturing to pollute the environment? Solutions like we can reduce our oil dependency by drilling for more oil?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358605671085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:27:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358605939532-17</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you explain the higher stock market, increase in GDP, reversal of unemployment numbers, record profits for business, fewer troops at war, better relations with allies throughout the world with your assessment?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358605939532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606001696-18</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Socialist governments traditionally create a financial mess. Socialists always run out of other people's money. It's quite a characteristic of them."</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358606001696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:33:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606387644-19</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little Z likes working for them. Thinks they are just grand.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358606387644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:39:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358606789160-20</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libertydies just listed several points that NONE of you imbecile right winger fools could refute. All you fools do is call names and misapply quotes. Looks like Libertydies caught every one of you low IQ repugs in the headlights. Every one of you is just staring back with a blank look. Wipe the drool off your chins and say, "huh?" LMAO!!!</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1358606789160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:46:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607359825-21</Id><Topic><Title>Screw the political messages!!</Title><Username>tmsherrm</Username><Timestamp>1358535970671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:06:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"one sick jerk off fool with hundreds of aliases..." Like you?</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1358607359825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:55:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358607512333-22</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals will never stop me from adding to my arsenal of automatic weapons and ammo.</Title><Username>mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358536255677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is her hair dyed orange, too?</Msg><Username>frankmangus</Username><Timestamp>1358607512333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358607854861-23</Id><Title>USLV EASY 100% OF PROFITS IN FEW WEEKS !!!!!!</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$4</Msg><Username>radardeldinero</Username><Timestamp>1358607854861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358608695889-24</Id><Topic><Title>Low-information liberals are pretty much like this...</Title><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1358479332430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 22:22:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you connected to the internet from another planet, say, fantasyland? Your opinion of a "wise use of resources" is stealing from people who work to give to people who don't. What, exactly, is wise about that? Nothing. Another low information votard who spends too much time on talking points memo, daily kos, msnbc, huffpo, or mother jones. Incredible stupidity, defies common sense. But what can we expect from the demcong? Just more of the same old feel-good, give away other peoples' money guilt assuagement.</Msg><Username>flippant_1</Username><Timestamp>1358608695889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358609407327-25</Id><Title>IF I WERE A DEMOCRAT OR LIBERAL I WOULD DO THE WORLD A FAVOR AND KILL MYSELF</Title><Msg>TAKE A LESSON</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358609407327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:30:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609540080-26</Id><Topic><Title>IF I WERE A DEMOCRAT OR LIBERAL I WOULD DO THE WORLD A FAVOR AND KILL MYSELF</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358609407327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:30:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats and liberals prefer shooting up schools and other public places.</Msg><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358609540080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:32:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358609663365-27</Id><Topic><Title>MOST DANGEROUS PLACE IN THE WORLD</Title><Username>pastel_hero</Username><Timestamp>1358604406946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should know more about who you are with</Msg><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358609663365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:34:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610116868-28</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS LIKE SOLUTIONS THAT WORK OVER EMPTY PROMISES FOR VOTES</Title><Username>purebred_red</Username><Timestamp>1358536223378</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libtards should not talk about lies, and its you nutcases that are bringing down the country, brainwashed #$%$</Msg><Username>hillbillytraders</Username><Timestamp>1358610116868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:41:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358610334260-29</Id><Title>MY ID SAYS IT ALL! I AM A RACIST, INBRED, WHITE TRASH NEO-NAZI PERVERT!!</Title><Msg>And PROUD of it!!!</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610334260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:45:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610509175-30</Id><Topic><Title>MOST DANGEROUS PLACE IN THE WORLD</Title><Username>pastel_hero</Username><Timestamp>1358604406946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've knowd my sister all my life.</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610509175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610601121-31</Id><Topic><Title>IF I WERE A DEMOCRAT OR LIBERAL I WOULD DO THE WORLD A FAVOR AND KILL MYSELF</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358609407327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:30:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You is wrong. They aint got the guts like us orange haired rednecks do.</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610601121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:50:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610791969-32</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals will never stop me from adding to my arsenal of automatic weapons and ammo.</Title><Username>mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358536255677</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 14:10:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aint nobody gonna take my guns lessen they pry them out of my cold dead a*s*s*.</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610791969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:53:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610924609-33</Id><Topic><Title>"The strongest reason for the people to retain the right to keep and bear arms</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358552819368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 18:46:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like the one that says "happiness is a warm gun" That's why I keep one up my a*s*s*.</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610924609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:55:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610965089-34</Id><Topic><Title>How to control Guns</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358564036223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same same for Hitler in 1933, ..an attempt anyway. Too many illegals and other nuts coming here UNCHECKED for filth and sanity, they inbreed and you got more of this #$%$. ALL ALLOWED FOR VOTE BUYING !!! Yesterday a young illegal mess'ican attacked 4 high school ROTC students for raising the American Flag at a Phoenix school. Arrested, he then attacked the Phoenix police screaming they could not arrest him because "Obama said so". Getting worse by the day. Guard your guns and ammo. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1358610965089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:56:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358610980317-35</Id><Topic><Title>My assault rifles, shotguns, grenade launchers, and orange hair are good to go. Let's go see a movie!</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358573658600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:34:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gots my orange hair and my red neck too!</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358610980317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:56:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358611112111-36</Id><Topic><Title>My Ryder truck is ready. Where should I park it this time?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358574020533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:40:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be tellin everybody everthing!! It's supposed to be a surprise!!</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358611112111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 10:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358611223182-37</Id><Topic><Title>How to control Guns</Title><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358564036223</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 21:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever since I made up that story and put it on the KKK website it's been spreadin like your mama's legs.</Msg><Username>whltest_whlte</Username><Timestamp>1358611223182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358611916951-38</Id><Title>Celebrate President Obama's second inauguration. Let the Victory parties begin!!</Title><Msg>The patriotic and intelligent Americans are still celebrating Obama's re-election. Let us all enjoy the Victory celebrations.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1358611916951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:11:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358612644045-39</Id><Title>should i take my 6% loss now</Title><Msg>losing money.</Msg><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358612644045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:24:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358612779206-40</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate President Obama's second inauguration. Let the Victory parties begin!!</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1358611916951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Celebration? 16.4 trillion in debt &amp; climbing? More spending while we mount more debt? 47% pay no taxes &amp; want those who pay all the taxes to pay more &amp; their fair share? You lazy deadbeat Liberals should be celebrating as Herr Obama has your following like in the 30s in Germany! Yes, we will be celebrating the end of the American dream!</Msg><Username>estero655</Username><Timestamp>1358612779206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:26:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613198399-41</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate President Obama's second inauguration. Let the Victory parties begin!!</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1358611916951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>under 4yrs now, day by day we get closer to the end of this nitemare. theres no way the next one in the white house can be this bad, no matter what the #$%$ he does!</Msg><Username>nickshelley396</Username><Timestamp>1358613198399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358613670666-42</Id><Title>Another misanthrope attampting to Post here.</Title><Msg>LOL: We have another certifiable #$%$ole on this Board. Nothing but insults spew from this radical neanderthal, and it is so comical it provides much needed relief. LOL. Its' name is "white (sch!pp) _ white" (trash). This clown purports to have made up a story that was shown on film on FOX News this morning. Story had to do with a mess'ican that attacked 4 ROTC students at a Phoenix high school. Fact. Then the cops had this illegal in a detention room whereupon he attacked 4 cops as he hollered,"you can't arrest me, Obama said so". Very funny. Shown on TV. REALLY would like to read ONLY BAC material, however, a board such as this one provides a forum for such nut jobs, as above and we who have fought for the 1st Amendment are none the less proud we have done same. The rest of us will continue to be objective and informative while ILK such as this misanthrope above continue tohunt for the prettiest sheep in their trailer park. LMAO! BAC will be fine, but very frustrating for a whilel onger. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1358613670666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358613900016-43</Id><Topic><Title>should i take my 6% loss now</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358612644045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definately take your 6% loss before it turns into 12%</Msg><Username>bcboxboy</Username><Timestamp>1358613900016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358614900961-44</Id><Title>Australian message on guns</Title><Msg>From: Ed Chenel, A police officer in Australia Hi Yanks, I thought you all would like to see the real Figures from Down Under. It has now been 12 months since gun owners in Australia were forced by a new Law to surrender 640,381 personal firearms to be destroyed by our own Government, a program costing Australia taxpayers More than $500 million dollars. The first year results are now in: Australia-wide, homicides are up 6.2 percent, Australia-wide, assaults are up 9.6 percent; Australia-wide, armed robberies are up 44 percent (yes, 44 percent)! In the state of Victoria Lone, homicides with firearms are now up 300 percent.(Note that While the law-abiding citizens turned them in, the criminals did not And criminals still possess their guns!) While figures over the previous 25 years showed a steady Decrease in armed robbery with firearms, this has changed drastically Upward in the past 12 months, since the criminals now are guaranteed That their prey is unarmed. There has also been a dramatic increase in break-ins and Assaults of the elderly, while the resident is at home. Australian politicians are at a loss to explain how public Safety has decreased, after such monumental effort and expense was Expended in 'successfully ridding Australian society of guns....' You Won't see this on the American evening news or hear your governor or Members of the State Assembly disseminating this information. The Australian experience speaks for itself. Guns in the Hands of honest citizens save lives and property and, yes, gun-control Laws affect only the law-abiding citizens. Take note Americans, before it's too late! Will you be one of the sheep to turn yours in? WHY? You will need it.</Msg><Username>obamapancake</Username><Timestamp>1358614900961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615419275-45</Id><Title>Susan Rice speaks out on Algeria</Title><Msg>U. S. Ambassador Susan Rice clearly labeled the ongoing hostage crisis in Algeria "an act of terror" today. Speaking from under the luggage compartment of a Greyhound bus, Susan Rice said that now that the election is over, it is quite clear to her that the hostage crisis was not caused by a video. I now have no political motive or directions from the White House to lie about what happened as was the case with the situation in Bengazhi.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358615419275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:10:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358615701054-46</Id><Title>WHITE PURE HIGHLY ADVANCED SUPERIOR TO ALL OTHERS NATURE'S MOST PERFECT CREATION</Title><Msg>SUPREME WHITE THERE IS NO BETTER.</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615701054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:15:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358615937844-47</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE PURE HIGHLY ADVANCED SUPERIOR TO ALL OTHERS NATURE'S MOST PERFECT CREATION</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615701054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:15:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who if given a choice would choose to be black? No one that's who! Look at all these black men wanting to screw white women they know it, too, white is superior in every way.</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615937844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:18:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358616098290-48</Id><Title>Markets is doped and addicted to QE drugs..Like L.Amrstrong, FED initiates DOPING QE program 4 years ago</Title><Msg>QE1..4 Doping program created an artificial strong in this stock market. It gets highly addicted to QE doping program...... Artificial reality... This is not is a free market......</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358616098290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616342013-49</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE PURE HIGHLY ADVANCED SUPERIOR TO ALL OTHERS NATURE'S MOST PERFECT CREATION</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615701054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:15:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just imagine getting out of the shower an looking at that ugly black body with stubbly scrub-brush hair. You would want to take the towel and wipe it all off but it won't go! What a nightmare!</Msg><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358616342013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358616391747-50</Id><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Msg>On the upcoming debt ceiling debate, most voters side with the position of some Republican lawmakers who say Congress should only raise the debt limit after agreeing on major cuts (69 percent). The president says it is Congress’s duty to raise the debt ceiling without demanding spending cuts to do so -- 23 percent agree with that position. Recently White House Press Secretary Jay Carney made news by stating deficit reduction is “not a worthy goal unto itself.” Fully 77 percent of voters disagree. That includes large majorities of Republicans (82 percent), independents (80 percent) and Democrats (71 percent). There is also broad agreement that government spending is out of control. Almost all Republicans (98 percent) and independents (91 percent) say it is, and two-thirds of Democrats (66 percent) agree.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358616506197-51</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE PURE HIGHLY ADVANCED SUPERIOR TO ALL OTHERS NATURE'S MOST PERFECT CREATION</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615701054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:15:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LET'S NO FORGET THE SMELL! UGH!</Msg><Username>vacuous_load</Username><Timestamp>1358616506197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:28:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617657454-52</Id><Topic><Title>Susan Rice speaks out on Algeria</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358615419275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:10:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is it so important to you people whether it was the video or terrorists that have caused American lives? Do you think the people that died care about what event perpetrated their deaths? It seems more important to you people about 'who said what' than those that have died? Idiots!</Msg><Username>votedems</Username><Timestamp>1358617657454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:47:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358617823033-53</Id><Topic><Title>QE 1,2,3,4 ........FED Doping Program</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358548864989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock market is highly addicted and doped by QE1...4 FED doping program</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358617823033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358619832379-54</Id><Topic><Title>Australian message on guns</Title><Username>obamapancake</Username><Timestamp>1358614900961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The biggest problem with your post is that the law was passed in 1996, not 12 months ago, and has been successful in reducing gun violence in Australia. It also implies that the intent in the USA is to ban all guns. Not true again. Only assault weapons need to be banned along with large clips. And we need to close the loopholes in background checks that allow criminals and felons to obtain weapons. So, the question remains why you would want to continue lying to the people on this forum about something that has nothing to do with Bank of America and is completely false? Are you a criminal?</Msg><Username>impossible2no</Username><Timestamp>1358619832379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:23:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621039273-55</Id><Topic><Title>Susan Rice speaks out on Algeria</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358615419275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:10:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So,,,,,you got no interest in preventing such, I take it. In that case, no, I don't suppose it matters.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358621039273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621097592-56</Id><Topic><Title>My Ryder truck is ready. Where should I park it this time?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358574020533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 00:40:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By your Mama's house so there will be no more babies like you!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1358621097592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621138290-57</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE PURE HIGHLY ADVANCED SUPERIOR TO ALL OTHERS NATURE'S MOST PERFECT CREATION</Title><Username>whitest_white</Username><Timestamp>1358615701054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:15:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, some of the crosses are the handsomest of the lot. #$%$zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz..............................HO !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358621138290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:45:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358621860703-58</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama is one of our most dedicated, intelligent presidents we have ever had. Those who oppose him fail in part because they insist on personal attacks on him and his family. They cannot argue the issues without realizing the American public oppose them. So they resort to gerrymandering congressional districts, lies, innuendos, secret money from wealthy donors, and personal attacks. Republicans could have something of value to bring to the table but instead they take the low road of supporting everything that is evil in our society. The Devil is a Republican.</Msg><Username>impossible2no</Username><Timestamp>1358621860703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 13:57:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358622026274-59</Id><Title>sell for loss now</Title><Msg>before it's 9.00 sell now. the order is dump.</Msg><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358622026274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:00:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358622483761-60</Id><Topic><Title>Markets is doped and addicted to QE drugs..Like L.Amrstrong, FED initiates DOPING QE program 4 years ago</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358616098290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doping program gave L. Armstrong artificial strong to hit first place several years, like QE FED doping program has given stock market enough drug to hold and hits green several years. Look at market performance these days and you will realize it walks up like a zombie a highly addicted body.. But at the end, nothing has been fixed at all. This body depends of debt and exponential credit style life like 5 years ago.. Fiscal cliff deal is a probe of it..nothing was fixed, just smoke and mirrors of a body taking another drug breath.. same thing with debt ceiling: this inorganic and addicted body is asking through Washington just the only thing can ask in order to hold its path: more drug..more debt..</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358622483761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358622490405-61</Id><Topic><Title>Markets is doped and addicted to QE drugs..Like L.Amrstrong, FED initiates DOPING QE program 4 years ago</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358616098290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yyyyyyyyyy</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358622490405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:08:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358622798301-62</Id><Topic><Title>Markets is doped and addicted to QE drugs..Like L.Amrstrong, FED initiates DOPING QE program 4 years ago</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358616098290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ttttttttttttttttttt</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358622798301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:13:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358625340639-63</Id><Title>GENERAL STOCK MARKET CORRECTION COMING. CORRECTION COMING.</Title><Msg>General stock market is overbought. combination with demise of bac this will end in horrendous stock price of 7.</Msg><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358625340639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:55:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358628306437-64</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>inflation.... inflation..... many gave up..... inflation..... Bush orchestrated Iraq draw-down,, you said so yourself.... there'd be a big disagreement on that one. :)</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358628306437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 15:45:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358633619991-65</Id><Topic><Title>should i take my 6% loss now</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358612644045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite a few things are against this stock: a junk earning report as called by some analysts, sector rotation away from financial, the phenomenal Bull Run since last June. Everything calls for a correction for bank stocks. Next support level is $10.50, another 6% drop from current PPS. This can happen next week. Oh I forgot to mention the house vote on debt ceiling thing next week.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358633619991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358636096609-66</Id><Topic><Title>QE 1,2,3,4 ........FED Doping Program</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358548864989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 17:41:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doping program gave L. Armstrong artificial strong to hit first place several years, like QE FED doping program has given stock market enough drug to hold and hits green several years. Look at market performance these days and you will realize it walks up like a zombie a highly addicted body.. But at the end, nothing has been fixed at all. This body depends of debt and exponential credit style life like 5 years ago.. Fiscal cliff deal is a probe of it..nothing was fixed, just smoke and mirrors of a body taking another drug breath.. same thing with debt ceiling: this inorganic and addicted body is asking through Washington just the only thing can ask in order to hold its path: more drug..more debt.</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358636096609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:54:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637006593-67</Id><Topic><Title>Susan Rice speaks out on Algeria</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358615419275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:10:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The further a society drifts from truth, the more it will hate those that speak it." George Orwell</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358637006593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:10:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358637215851-68</Id><Topic><Title>sell for loss now</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358622026274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:00:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A*S*S*C*L*O*W*N</Msg><Username>biggusdikkus12</Username><Timestamp>1358637215851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:13:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358637323873-69</Id><Title>Supreme Court or Congress needs to protect Bank of America or it becomes Bank of Alabama.</Title><Msg>Basically, the real earning figure is 0.3 cent EPS x 10.9 bil ( outstanding shares) = 327 mil dollar. That does not cover 3 month lawyers fee. They paid 2-3 times more than their earnings to the lawyers. They sold assets to cover. They are saying that Bank is improving. Closing branches, firing people. Where is that guy with mushy beard, #$%$ Dove. he is quite after earnings see. Unless Supreme Court or Congress shields this company from lawsuits and liabilities, there is no rescue. This company is going to be dissolved into pieces ( already Dallas Fed announced that recently. Why do you think he is saying that right around bank earnings time). Then what, Bank of America becomes Bank of Alabama or Bank of Alaska.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358637323873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358637350462-70</Id><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Msg>Gun nuts will make gun control</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358639700886-71</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great Presidents do more than tactically outmaneuver their opposition in Congress. They lift America's national stature, improve its material well-being, and address the problems that only Presidents can address. He has done none of these. Since he has been in office middle class income has declined, national debt has increased 50%, deficts have exceeded $1 trillion every year and we are a nation deeply divided. Heroically, the private sector has powered through all the unceertainty, populist rhetoric and suffocating regulations to produce higher corporate profits which has drivien the stock market recovery.</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1358639700886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:55:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358640030003-72</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, he's just terrified of me. they all are. :)</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358640030003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:00:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358641463741-73</Id><Topic><Title>GENERAL STOCK MARKET CORRECTION COMING. CORRECTION COMING.</Title><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358625340639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 14:55:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drop to $7 is a stretch. $10.50 support next week. If it get breached, sub $10 will be in reach soon. Brace for the drop.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358641463741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:24:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358641597727-74</Id><Title>Next week test $10.50</Title><Msg>$10.50 support next week. Brace for the drop.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358641597727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 19:26:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358644307198-75</Id><Topic><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Working the Koch sucking late shift !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358644307198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 20:11:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358647534570-76</Id><Title>107 kids and teenagers were murdered in CHICAGO last year, right smack in Obamaland. How much have we heard about this?</Title><Msg>Not a damn peep. Hmmm...Why would that be? Isn't a gun death a gun death? Is it no less tragic for the parents and siblings if their kin die of a bullet from a .38 than the dreaded AR-15? What the hell? How about focusing on disarming the thugs that get their guns ILLEGALLY, rather than disarming citizens that buy them LEGALLY. Apparently gun deaths are OK if the shooter is a criminal or gang banger and they aren't part of a mass shooting and not involving an "assault" weapon. Sure as long as they kill just one or two kids with hand gun or shotgun hey those things happen, right?</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1358647534570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:05:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358648253184-77</Id><Title>Stock Market Correction</Title><Msg>When will this market have a correction? Will it be after Obama raises the debt ceiling?</Msg><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358648253184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:17:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358648682156-78</Id><Title>We should leave Obama alone !</Title><Msg>SOB President is too dumb to even care what we got to say.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358648682156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:24:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358648741358-79</Id><Topic><Title>Libertylies are you going to denyJeep is going to build a plant over here?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1358634143785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 17:22:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Donna Marie Lange is single now in case you are looking to hook up.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1358648741358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358649798703-80</Id><Topic><Title>107 kids and teenagers were murdered in CHICAGO last year, right smack in Obamaland. How much have we heard about this?</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1358647534570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:05:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well it's certainly not going to get you the attention of the congress and the entire country jawing about everyday things like THAT!</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358649798703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:43:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358650636523-81</Id><Topic><Title>should i take my 6% loss now</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358612644045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will i lose 100%? bac will disappear?</Msg><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358650636523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:57:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358652012028-82</Id><Topic><Title>should i take my 6% loss now</Title><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358612644045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, sell some calls once we rebound and get even at least. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358652012028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:20:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358653576323-83</Id><Topic><Title>Stock Market Correction</Title><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358648253184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The House is the party that must raise the debt ceiling. All their baby.</Msg><Username>impossible2no</Username><Timestamp>1358653576323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 22:46:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358654523911-84</Id><Title>Prediction</Title><Msg>Sliding all the way to 9. especially if Dow goes down. Even may test 6 again by mid March. No way up unless earnings improve litigation stops.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654523911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:02:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358654615095-85</Id><Title>By next month it is Bank of Alabama.</Title><Msg>eom.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654615095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:03:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358654712516-86</Id><Title>My advice to CEO</Title><Msg>Instead of earning money doing banking work, they should hire more lawyers to fight against the lawyers they hire. They can make more money than banking. Serious.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:05:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358654784916-87</Id><Topic><Title>My advice to CEO</Title><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way, their deposited money is increasing because all those lawyers are keeping their money at BOA.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654784916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:06:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358657825604-88</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks to your foot dragging party of no Hitch. You did everything you could for 4 years to keep Obama from being reelected and failed. You are also wrong in your evaluation. He has greatly lifted American stature addressed many problems as the president even without congress helping and our well being would have been much worse without his programs. Yes we are divided by a bunch of clowns who think you can cut taxes and have more revenue, want to establish an elite ruling class and a working class and destroy the middle class as opposed to those who want every worker to have a level playing field and opportunity for himself and his family. No organization is more responsible for uncertainty than the tea party who continues to preach that it would be OK to default on US debt which already led to our first ever credit devaluation.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358657825604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:57:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>