<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358658308634-1</Id><Title>Trading the day after Obama sworned in</Title><Msg>At Yellowman Investment Group (YIG) we advised our clients to short the chit out of BAC immediately the second Obama got sworned in again</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358658308634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:05:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658341188-2</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compare in real dollars adjusted for any time period you want and try to justify your answer. Many gave up because they were going to retire anyway and see unemployment as a gift. Yep, Bush negotiated the treaty for withdrawal and Obama carried it out and is still prosecuting the war against terrorism globally with many fewer American deaths and a lot more al qeada dead. As commander in chief he has far outstripped the Bush administration in effectiveness.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358658341188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358658686606-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't mind little z, he is an anti American working for the red Chinese. His allegiance is to the gold Panda.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358658686606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:11:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358659540255-4</Id><Topic><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Full quote: Most importantly because deficit reduction is not a worthy goal unto itself," said Carney, talking about government spending. "This is all about making our economy stronger, making it more productive and allowing it to create even more jobs. That is the most important thing when it comes to economic policy as far as the President is concerned." i.e. you don't just slash and burn, you cut where you can without losing jobs. You don't grow the economy if you cut spending to the point you lose job. More jobs mean more growth which means more revenue and a bigger GDP . Cuts have the same negative impact as tax increases as far as growing the economy is concerned. Just as you have to be careful what taxes you increase you have to be careful where you make spending cuts. I understand that is a little hard for the tea party to comprehend. .</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358659540255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:25:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358673026481-5</Id><Topic><Title>Trading the day after Obama sworned in</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358658308634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 00:05:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" SWORNED IN" REALLY?????? JUST ANOTHER TEAPUBLICAN MENTAL GIANT</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358673026481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 04:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358673173333-6</Id><Topic><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A really great effort, but as always Teapublicans either lie or only tell half truths .............</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358673173333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 04:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358673350337-7</Id><Topic><Title>We should leave Obama alone !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358648682156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:24:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't care what you say since you already have exposed your ignorance many times over</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358673350337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 04:15:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358689642803-8</Id><Topic><Title>We should leave Obama alone !</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358648682156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:24:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What else do you have besides the hatred? Cheer up and enjoy your life!!</Msg><Username>profhope</Username><Timestamp>1358689642803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:47:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358689840318-9</Id><Topic><Title>Prediction</Title><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654523911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:02:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I respect your "prediction" if it is indeed based on something which is beyond your capacity.</Msg><Username>profhope</Username><Timestamp>1358689840318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:50:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358690057948-10</Id><Title>market will smack all these buble stocks</Title><Msg>Just when retail investors thought it's safe to get back in - boom, party over, as always</Msg><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1358690057948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:54:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358690112262-11</Id><Topic><Title>Stock Market Correction</Title><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358648253184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>redneck like you has been yelling "the sky is falling" since WE elected O as our president FOUR years ago. Can you figure out how the market has fared since then? you loser!!</Msg><Username>profhope</Username><Timestamp>1358690112262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 08:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358691804995-12</Id><Topic><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if you're, or he isn't, cutting anything or showing any propensity to do so, it must mean you, or he, think our country is a lean, mean fighting machine. Especially all those jobs the unions force to be kept with the occupants doing nothing.....the masses of duplication throughout the government and anything unions touch....yeah....even YOU don't believe that, so I'd feel safe in saying that some of the things you say are at varience with other things you say, or perhaps it's the timing......or something. huh? :)</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358691804995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:23:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358691957033-13</Id><Topic><Title>Australian message on guns</Title><Username>obamapancake</Username><Timestamp>1358614900961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:01:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yes that has been floating around since 2007. Would you care to give us the statistics today? Check snoopes and Urban legends before you post these fantasies.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358691957033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:25:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358692596353-14</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate President Obama's second inauguration. Let the Victory parties begin!!</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1358611916951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 11:11:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably "she" does.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358692596353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:36:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358693699856-15</Id><Topic><Title>107 kids and teenagers were murdered in CHICAGO last year, right smack in Obamaland. How much have we heard about this?</Title><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1358647534570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:05:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most gun violence has been black on black and Congress pays no attention. Only when white folks start getting shot or if the NAACP raises hell as in Florida does anyone pay attention to gun violence.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358693699856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:54:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358693762560-16</Id><Topic><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Government's twice the size it was 10 years ago. It's 30 percent bigger than it was when Obama became president. Government waste runs rampant...The federal government made at least $125 billion in improper payments last year. It spends $25 billion annually maintaining unused or vacant federal properties. Rife with duplication, Washington runs 342 economic development programs, 130 programs serving the disabled, 130 programs serving at-risk youth, and 90 early childhood development programs. The game’s over for you big spending Socialist “Government knows best” food stampers. Having two or three people doing a job that one person can do looks good for employment numbers, but only causes “gross bloat”. On a scale of one to ten, Government’s gross bloat rating is minus 2. “Useful idiot” democrats are now backed into a corner… talking a good game is over.</Msg><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358693762560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 09:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358694639645-17</Id><Title>Michelle Meyer</Title><Msg>Does anyone remember her saying home prices will reverse in the 4th qtr of 2012 on CNBC? Funny!!!</Msg><Username>tymisup</Username><Timestamp>1358694639645</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:10:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358695546084-18</Id><Title>BANK OF AMERICA CORRECTION</Title><Msg>This stock missed on revenues. It also has a few new lawsuits to workout. The revenues may even decline this year. That in combination with the lawsuits makes this a broken stock still for years to come. I do not anticipate and stock price appreciation in BAC for this year, maybe back to 12 if we are lucky. It may still be 5 years off before this stock sees 20. In those five years there are so many other stocks that will do a double. If you hold you will be missing out on other opportunities. I am moving on. Good luck to all of you.</Msg><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358695546084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:25:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696200787-19</Id><Topic><Title>Supreme Court or Congress needs to protect Bank of America or it becomes Bank of Alabama.</Title><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358637323873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holy cow, a rationalist! ROTFLMAO what the heck are YOU doing here?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1358696200787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358696622081-20</Id><Topic><Title>Stock Market Correction</Title><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358648253184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 21:17:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock market is already up big this year. Trees do not grow to the sky.</Msg><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358696622081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358696961505-21</Id><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Msg>Debt is big.</Msg><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358699186255-22</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope your right so I can buy another 2,000 shares. Back up the truck, my friend.</Msg><Username>bcboxboy</Username><Timestamp>1358699186255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:26:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358699386503-23</Id><Title>Cry somewhere else the stock is going back to $12</Title><Msg>The bank had poor earnings primarily due to TWO HUGE LAWSUIT SETTLEMENTS - those were one time events. Those two lawsuits cost us 22 cents eps for the quarter but they are now done. Yes there may be a few more lawsuits to settle but all of them will be for a LOT LESS. In essence, it is just two lawsuits left, the MBIA Lawsuit, and one other one. what will happen - the small investor will be scared by the headlines and sell. Then the big boys will scoop up the shares and make a large profit very fast (by next quarter in just three months).</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358699386503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:29:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358699862432-24</Id><Topic><Title>BANK OF AMERICA CORRECTION</Title><Username>captainjack_s</Username><Timestamp>1358695546084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:25:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should move on since you do not know how to invest. If you cannot discern ONE time charges, two lawsuits settled that cost us 22 cents this quarter, then you should go lose your money someplace else. Without the two major lawsuits we would have had 25 cents. The lawsuits are only temporary and the bank is quickly, very quickly healing. All the negative stories are just the big boys feeding the media outlets drivel to allow them to buy in at a cheap price. Investing is long term GREATER than just one earnings report.</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358699862432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:37:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358700223898-25</Id><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Msg>The media analysts who do not know how to invest are pouncing on this earnings report as a huge failure. Let's look at the facts: 2 who major lawsuits were settled that cost us 22 cents this quarter, we would have had earnings of 25 cents. All though these are not the last of the lawsuits they probably were the largest and they have been settled and in essence paid for with this quarter's earnings. Now we move on to 25 cents next quarter and much higher after that as the billions of dollars in extra personel who do the paperwork for bad mortgages are let go. THREE years from now the bank will earn $2 - $3 eps. I am not going to miss the drive up.</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358700301326-26</Id><Title>this week 20 jan 13</Title><Msg>This week, Jan 20, introduced as “at the inauguration”. And David Plouffe, presidential adviser, highlighted three issues—the debt, immigration, and guns, but stressed that “Washington views” are not same as the larger American population. He confessed that “some democrats”—six senators mentioned—are from Romney voting states, thus vulnerable to GOP thrusts, especially re the gun issue… Not all Obama proposals, he admitted, are likely to get thru Congress. Switching to budget/debt matters, he stressed “balance” is needed re cuts and new income, noting recent GOP House mention of “closing loopholes” as a way of raising that new income. Another matter, :”immigration”: Plouffe feels “the stars are aligned for action”. GOP senator Rubio from Fla has spoken re the matter, albeit not “negotiating (etc)” with the president. Eva Longoria, Texan, Hispanic, and eloquent, calls the matter one of “economic and humanitarian importance”. No longer Penna Sen “Rick” Santorum considers “paths” a puzzling concept, as there are “many” such “paths” (to citizenship) and thus agreement is difficult. At the roundtable, Santorum stressed that people feel “safe” owning guns. M C Roberts noted that concept, but also added that “mental health” matters are relevant, but there is little agreement on parameters of “mental health” matters. Once senator Santorum noted “guns could be bought easily 50 years ago”, there were few examples of gun massacres, though he did not mention the one from a Texas’ college tower.. With his usual harrumph, g f will proclaimed “one thing is for sure in Washington—there will be a large and growing welfare state and it will not be ‘paid for’” Past Mich governor Jennifer Granholm considers “compromisings” unlikely because the House is not interested…period. Lance Armstrong’s cheating: “terrible”. Actress Longoria, with a leadership role in inauguration planning, feels the president will “recommit” his administration to the people. No “In memor</Msg><Username>cent_0425</Username><Timestamp>1358700301326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:45:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358700816861-27</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sell for loss now and buy at 8.</Msg><Username>choutony</Username><Timestamp>1358700816861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:53:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701164908-28</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting how the Price Target has increased to $12 on Yahoo. It probablyl will drop, although how low I do not know, as the no nothing media scares investors. However, we both know the stock is moving MUCH higher after they report earnings in 3 more months.</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358701164908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:59:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701452493-29</Id><Topic><Title>My advice to CEO</Title><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358654712516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 23:05:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. Understand your feelings,however, we are necessary in this corrupt environment. So if you don't like lawyers, next time you have a legal issue of importance, call a "hippie".!! GL with BAC. Most of the negatives are behind now. Good earnings forthcoming.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1358701452493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:04:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358701821759-30</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. Considering they still had a profit of 0.3 AFTER a 6.8 Billion dollar charge off it is astounding! Now do a visual on a balance sheet wherein the outstanding shares are lessened by a buyback, to say 10 billion shares. Enter a revenue stream of 20 Billion. Yup, $2.00 a share. It's coming, just a matter of time. We must get all this government B/S behind us. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1358701821759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:10:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702095747-31</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The CEO said a year ago, and other analysts agree, that BAC should earn $30 - $40 billion before taxes after all the housing mess is done. Therefore, I would use $30 billion and not $20 billion for after taxes and that would = $3 eps. $3 eps X 12 p/e = $36 and that is what I am waiting for along with dividend increases and share buybacks all along the way.</Msg><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358702095747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358702256417-32</Id><Title>Mr. Fartaway-Daddy!!!</Title><Msg>While dancing at the Inaug Ball, Michelle Obama farted! Twice and loud. That's cool aint it Dad?</Msg><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1358702256417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:17:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358702376325-33</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Lib,, the conservatives did try to win the electiion. They saw the danger in excessive debt accumulation, failed fiscal stimuli (billions lost on bk green companies, and cash for clunkers programs spring to mind), a foreign policy of withdrawing from the world scene, and an ever intrusive government. Actually, the party of no resides in one man, slinky Pinky Reid: no budget - no compromise. And as far as tax revenues and tax rates you might read the IRS data.. The Reagan and the Bush II years demonstrated this. After the cuts were enacted tax receipts to the gov't icreased 66% and 41%. respectively. Rates and revenues tend to de-link. Returning earnings to the private sector promotes growth and with that higher taxes. As simple fact that liberals fail to grasp.</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1358702376325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:19:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358704076296-34</Id><Title>Wouldn't it be the KNOW nothing media instead of NO nothing media</Title><Msg>Who KNOWS nothing hmmmmmmm?</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1358704076296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:47:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358704212174-35</Id><Title>More lawsuits and LIBOR scandel and Price fixing etc are still gonna hit BAC ..... Look for re-trace to $10.50's</Title><Msg>If that falls $9</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1358704212174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:50:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704337557-36</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$10.50 is the next support. If it gets breached, BAC is in trouble. For now, it is quite a stretch for $9 or $12. $10.50 to $11.50 is a more reasonable expectation.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358704337557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:52:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704458310-37</Id><Topic><Title>this week 20 jan 13</Title><Username>cent_0425</Username><Timestamp>1358700301326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:45:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Plouffe????? Plouffe mud. OTT.... "the stars are aligned" does not presage anything that might resemble "action". Too bad they haven't the commitment they put into pulling off the inauguration, for running the country.</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358704458310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:54:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358704864182-38</Id><Topic><Title>this week 20 jan 13</Title><Username>cent_0425</Username><Timestamp>1358700301326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:45:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They do. The Congress can't interfere with the inauguration, there's your difference.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358704864182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:01:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358705213588-39</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bs, hitch. Reid has funded the government on a shoestring. The republicans with filibusters and a my way or the hiway approach haven't left much room for a real budget negotiation. I'll grant you tax rates were too high at the top level when Reagan came in to office but that is about as far as I will go. You keep neglecting that both pof those presidents you mention seeded the numbers with massive debt. both doubled the existing US debt. reagan was the first big debt builder in the nation and GWB was right behind him with the same senseless policies. Now they have the country in such bad shape the only solution is piling up more debt to get growth back again the same way they did. Only this time when it gets better lets pay off some debt instead of starting another war without funding it.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358705213588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:06:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358706003821-40</Id><Topic><Title>Cry somewhere else the stock is going back to $12</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358699386503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:29:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were two huge distributions on the chart, one on downgrade by Credit Suisse, the next one right after the earnings. Huge volume down. These are not games played by you and me. The big boys you are referring to iareshaking all of us. 10.7 billion shares. They cant sell it in one day. More shares will be dumped. Bad news reaction you are talking about is nonsense. In fact small guys bought the stock.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358706003821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:20:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358706078669-41</Id><Topic><Title>Cry somewhere else the stock is going back to $12</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358699386503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:29:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the way I am not crying. I bought puts. I am in laughing mode. Not crying. fyi.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358706078669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:21:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358707170140-42</Id><Title>European Parliament President Martin Schulz views the European Union as headed for a depression</Title><Msg>European Parliament President Martin Schulz views the European Union as headed for a depression Jan. 19, 2013, 1:37 p.m. EST Schulz says EU on path to depression: report By MarketWatch European Parliament President Martin Schulz views the European Union as headed for a depression, according to an interview with Saturday's edition of the Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung. "[The E.U.] is on a path to a depression, apathy, a mood of not caring. That's dangerous, as that mood superimposes the great successes of the E.U., for which it recently won the Nobel Peace Prize," Mr. Schulz is quoted as saying.</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1358707170140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:39:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358707199464-43</Id><Title>Harvard Prof Niall Ferguson S&amp;P 500 Index goto 418 Harvard Business Review</Title><Msg>Harvard Prof Niall Ferguson S&amp;P 500 Index goto 418 ... Harvard Business Review : Harvard Professor Niall Ferguson S&amp;P 500 Index go to 418 --- Scenario: Top Income-Tax Rate of 45%--- The Standard &amp; Poor's 500 Index at 418 where it was in December 1982... Harvard Business Review Harvard Business Review Harvard Business Review</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1358707199464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:39:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358707228975-44</Id><Title>Goldman Sachs Charles Nenner Dow eventually hitting 5000 in 2013</Title><Msg>Goldman Sachs Charles Nenner Dow eventually hitting 5000 in 2013 Goldman Sachs Dow eventually hitting 5000 in 2013 Charles Nenner Goldman Sachs Dow eventually hitting 5000 2013 Charles Nenner Goldman Sachs confirm a multiyear bear market with the Dow eventually hitting 5000 Goldman Sachs Charles Nenner Dow eventually hitting 5000 in 2013</Msg><Username>fairvalue23</Username><Timestamp>1358707228975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:40:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358707966922-45</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Fartaway-Daddy!!!</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1358702256417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, you need to save your efforts to blow up your next date , the rubber doll</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358707966922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:52:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358708190677-46</Id><Title>TEAPUBLICANS pROVE THE POINT!!!!</Title><Msg>That we have too many freaks and not enough freak shows</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358708190677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 13:56:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358709883980-47</Id><Topic><Title>Markets is doped and addicted to QE drugs..Like L.Amrstrong, FED initiates DOPING QE program 4 years ago</Title><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358616098290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:21:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No free market... It is THE FED STOCK MARKET</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358709883980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:24:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358710638876-48</Id><Title>voter id vs gun id, vs obamacare id, vs America. Libs just don't get it</Title><Msg>And Democraps do not want vote ID. "Fathom the Hypocrisy of a Government that requires every citizen to prove they are insured... but not everyone must prove they are a citizen." Add to this: many of those who refuse or are unable to prove they are citizens will receive free insurance paid for by those who are citizens</Msg><Username>valley_cookie</Username><Timestamp>1358710638876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:37:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358710784662-49</Id><Title>Ravens and Atlanta will prevail.</Title><Msg>That is my hopes. Obama hopes you won't notice his hand in your wallet.</Msg><Username>valley_cookie</Username><Timestamp>1358710784662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358710786675-50</Id><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Msg>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Msg><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711053705-51</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some day our children will celebrate a new holiday called "Obama Day". This will happen.</Msg><Username>robininfl29</Username><Timestamp>1358711053705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:44:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711055027-52</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOu can get some at $10.50 we know that...... IF that holds there ya go but that is cocktail napkin support as BAC ran up fast to $12. Consolidation around $10 is more likely. The one time charges etc. may not just be one time. Remember interest rates are so low banks are having trouble with margins compared to when rates where higher. The stringent lending laws are also a hindrance. JMHO being a chartist, $10.56 or so is the next stop. Good luck my friend.</Msg><Username>csaintswin</Username><Timestamp>1358711055027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:44:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358711463610-53</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michelle is so beautiful with her new hair style. She is the most beautiful first lady in history, easily.</Msg><Username>ysidfso</Username><Timestamp>1358711463610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:51:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712458479-54</Id><Topic><Title>Ravens and Atlanta will prevail.</Title><Username>valley_cookie</Username><Timestamp>1358710784662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Betting against brady /belechick at home? Bad move. Jmho-bucko Ps i think falcons get to tge rookie qb today. Atlanta by 7. pats by 14</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358712458479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:07:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358712776856-55</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. Fartaway-Daddy!!!</Title><Username>shlltehead_miles</Username><Timestamp>1358702256417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:17:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shu weee, smelt that all the way back here at the pig farm in Illinois. Yep, Obama and his thugs from Chicago financially destroy Illinois. Now he is finishing his job on USA.</Msg><Username>cfljmljfl</Username><Timestamp>1358712776856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713265160-56</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A drop back to 10.00 would be welcomed by me. I have enough cash for 6k more at that price. Might even buy another 4k on margin at that price. 20k of bac with 59 months till retirement. I would be set as imo 40.00 pps in 59 months is very doable and actually conservative. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358713265160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:21:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713483922-57</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAC requires patience. Check back in a few years, it will be much higher. I went through something similar with a company called Philip Morris in the late 90s. Those who turned off the stock market chatter and held on did quite well. So turn off the whole market, go play golf or read a good book and get out of the house and live a little. Come back next January and let's touch base then.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358713483922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:24:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713827282-58</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not looking for a political debate but i do have a question for dems and liberals. If given a choice,who would you prefer as president for the next 4 yrs? Bill clinton or obama? i am serious. Who would you choose?-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358713827282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:30:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358713976507-59</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe bac pps would rise much faster uf romney would have been elected. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358713976507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:32:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358714261373-60</Id><Topic><Title>Biden: 'Proud to Be President'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358713444353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe could single handily eleminate the national debt. All he would have to do is redeem his empty beer cans. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358714261373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:37:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358714651671-61</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lincoln hasn't been alive for more than 150 years - no way he was inaugurated today.....</Msg><Username>cycleogical1488</Username><Timestamp>1358714651671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:44:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358714905315-62</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She is so elegant and stylish. I love her new hair. Her figure is incredible. Yes, she's model material and a wonderful first lady.</Msg><Username>bertmanwithplan</Username><Timestamp>1358714905315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:48:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358715444316-63</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>michele reminds me of esther from the tv show sanford and son. Jmho-bucko</Msg><Username>muench.john</Username><Timestamp>1358715444316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358718649778-64</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Litigation will subside, earnings will normalize. All in since 5-7</Msg><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1358718649778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 16:50:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358720160145-65</Id><Title>news for the banks</Title><Msg>the banks are going down,BAC back to 10 in 10 days..The market fixing to take a hit..The market totally pump to where it is,,there is no reason for the market to be 13,600..No stock is worth keeping for a long term..America is living on worthless paper..</Msg><Username>jackmebit56</Username><Timestamp>1358720160145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:16:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358720177775-66</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the umpteenth time, Lib, it is Congress that creates debt not the President. Actually, Reagan's crusade against deficit spending and the Dem Congress's manta to spend, spnd and spend led to 4 o 5 gov't shutdownns in the Reagan era. Now, the continuing resolution process started under that feckless Carter is Pinky Red's best friend. No budgetary responsibilities. Just borrow from the Chinese, dole out the pork, and screw the generations to come. Finis</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1358720177775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:16:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722216984-67</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffffbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbttttttttttttttttttttttttt!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1</Msg><Username>amazing.donut</Username><Timestamp>1358722216984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:50:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358722303506-68</Id><Topic><Title>Ravens and Atlanta will prevail.</Title><Username>valley_cookie</Username><Timestamp>1358710784662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you continue to have a fifty-fifty chance, bucko John!</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358722303506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 17:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723098653-69</Id><Topic><Title>Something to think about..Democrats, get someone to read this to you..</Title><Username>oh_mama_say_it_aint_so</Username><Timestamp>1358616391747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 12:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bigger means more corruption, inefficiency, and waste.</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358723098653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:04:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358723585517-70</Id><Topic><Title>Ravens and Atlanta will prevail.</Title><Username>valley_cookie</Username><Timestamp>1358710784662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe back to brother-brother? Wow, talk about your family feud!</Msg><Username>ngaibruce</Username><Timestamp>1358723585517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:13:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358724370442-71</Id><Topic><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History and facts drive the right wingers nuts, love that free market BS when almost everything is fixed, except labor.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358724370442</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358725017933-72</Id><Topic><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flush the meth put the moonshine down get off your sister and get a job !!</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358725017933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:36:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358727792404-73</Id><Topic><Title>Watch for the drop back to $9.</Title><Username>alvin555</Username><Timestamp>1358696961505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:49:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The one time charges etc may not just be one time." Good point. Institutions are dumping BAC. Look at the distribution Friday. Not retailer for sure.</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358727792404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358728170526-74</Id><Title>Bank of America and Citi reports are junk</Title><Msg>Jan. 17, 2013, 11:27 a.m. EST By MarketWatch SAN FRANCISCO (MarketWatch) — Sugarcoat it all you want. Let the analysts try to make sense of it. Buy the story you’re being fed. The reality is, Bank of America Corp. and Citigroup Inc. turned in garbage reports parading as fourth-quarter earnings Thursday. Special and one-time charges, unforeseen costs, settlements, legacy costs, foreclosure legal fees — it was a junkfest. But that’s not even the worst of it. These types of quarters happen with such regularity for banks these days that to suggest they’re year-end, “kitchen sink” quarters is an insult to sinks, kitchens, quarters and, mostly, investors. At Charlotte, N.C.-based Bank of America /quotes/zigman/190927/quotes/nls/bac BAC -1.24% , Chief Executive Brian Moynihan said the bank would take $2.7 billion in one kind of mortgage-related charge and another $2.5 billion tied to a separate charge. Still, he wrote with a straight face, the bank is “strong and well positioned for further growth.” See full story on B. of A. profits . Meanwhile, up in New York, Citigroup /quotes/zigman/5065548/quotes/nls/c C +1.02% posted a 25% increase in quarterly profit. But lo and behold — there was a $1.3 billion surprise in the form of legal costs, another $305 million charge, more losses at Citi Holdings, and a charge for an increase in the value of its own debt (a confusing and questionable rule that’s on the accountants, not the bank). Read report on Citigroup’s results . More alarming, Michael Corbat, Citi’s new CEO, had the audacity to blame regulatory costs for the bank’s performance — as if it were operating under some especially onerous rules that others weren’t. Even with these “special” and “one-time” circumstances stripped out, these banks continue to be black boxes. Investors’ only choice is whether to trust the junk they spew forth. The bottom line is that, quarter after quarter, these banks turn in financial reports that are impenetrable and full of what analysts politely call “moving pa</Msg><Username>markedtofuture</Username><Timestamp>1358728170526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:29:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358728171314-75</Id><Title>Stock market walks up like a zombie a highly addicted body to FED´s QE doping program</Title><Msg>........asking for more QE drug to be able to step up</Msg><Username>arcanos70</Username><Timestamp>1358728171314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:29:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358730291863-76</Id><Title>Fox News to be renamed</Title><Msg>The FCC has ruled that Fox news must change their name so to reflect the mission statement of the organization. Fox News will , effective Aug. 2nd, 2013 be named L.I.B. Lies for Idiots and Bigiots.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358730291863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358730644763-77</Id><Title>Gun Rights supporters gather</Title><Msg>In many States gun rights supporters gathered to protest the plans to ban assult weapons, eliminate the insane from obtaining weapons, eliminate high capacity Mag's, and required regeristration at Gun shows. Two shootings were reported.</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358730644763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:10:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358730687072-78</Id><Title>What Wingers can't understand</Title><Msg>They LOST, American has spoken</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358730687072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:11:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358731726827-79</Id><Title>What defines a Teapublican</Title><Msg>1. Their house has wheels 2. The 7th grade was the best 3 years of their life 3. Their Father is also their Uncle 4. They either have are can't wait to get a free Hover Round from SS 5. Their retirement plan is the lotto 6. Turning in their empty Beer Cans for a deposit return is what they call their savings account 7. They failed to pay the Electric bill in order to get a new tat 8. They own guns to protect their treasures [ Elvis painting on velvet, a lava lamp and two NASCAR ashtrays] 9. They own at least one Police Scanner 10. The rent a large screen TV in order to watch the WWF</Msg><Username>carolyne47</Username><Timestamp>1358731726827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:28:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358733130326-80</Id><Title>Hurray!!!</Title><Msg>Obma is RE_ELECTED!!!</Msg><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358733130326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:52:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733273190-81</Id><Topic><Title>It's a GREAT DAY FOR REAL AMERICANS! Our GREAT PRESIDENT who SAVED THE UNION is inaugurated!</Title><Username>kfdogdo</Username><Timestamp>1358710786675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:39:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes He did save the Union I agree.</Msg><Username>marthaweicker32</Username><Timestamp>1358733273190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:54:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358733417063-82</Id><Topic><Title>Bank of America and Citi reports are junk</Title><Username>markedtofuture</Username><Timestamp>1358728170526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:29:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's very true</Msg><Username>observer777</Username><Timestamp>1358733417063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:56:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358734525440-83</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite a downward price adjustment in only 5 days! ROTFLMAO do you even remember half of the #$%$ you dispense? nasa_rss • Jan 13, 2013 12:26 PM Yahoo has raised the Price Target from $10 a couple of months ago to now $12. Get ready, the stock is headed t $18 - $20 by Dec/2013. BAC does not need earnings it already has it earnings are just being wiped out from housing and eg a costs,, those costs are dropping every month. That means earnings will Pop and fast.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1358734525440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:15:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358734892998-84</Id><Topic><Title>Should be $15 by the end of the year</Title><Username>nasa_rss</Username><Timestamp>1358700223898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patience pays in many circumstances. Not in stock market controlled by wall street. This bank will be fragmented into state zonalities, not going to be nationwide bank. Not needed. Its functions dont support its current structure. In fact the only salvation is to anounce bankruptcy and get rid of the lawsuits. Many experts said the same thing. Bankruptcy was the original solution recommended. That is why I rename this bank as "Bank of Alabama". or Bank of Alaska. Bank of Charlotte. etc.....</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358734892998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:21:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358735523730-85</Id><Title>I got so many rotten eggs ready for Obama's inauguration !</Title><Msg>Hee hee LOL can't wait to buy a new plasma !</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1358735523730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736261093-86</Id><Topic><Title>Bad companys made unions, bad health insurers made Obamacare</Title><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358637350462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 18:15:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you pay no taxes then whats your problem ? Sounds like a taker to me wants to use everything and not pay for it !</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1358736261093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:44:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358737317461-87</Id><Topic><Title>Biden: 'Proud to Be President'</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358713444353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 15:24:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden can't get elected ever. Vice President is a worthless job, a do nothing job. He's bored to death.</Msg><Username>mgiuseff</Username><Timestamp>1358737317461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358739309822-88</Id><Topic><Title>Did you know I am just one of the hundreds of SW's rectal drip aliases?</Title><Username>dumpobamie</Username><Timestamp>1358738786419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:26:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go take your pills and #$%$ !!!</Msg><Username>venny_320</Username><Timestamp>1358739309822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 22:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358740963469-89</Id><Title>"ONE TIME CHARGES" Those famous words uttered in all earnings report</Title><Msg>BOA has multi-layered litigation problems. Affected groups lining up with identical case. That means one settlement opens a gate for another lawsuit. A lot of institutions waiting for these settlements to finish so that they can open their cases better and spending less on legal preparation. Any settled case always reduces the preparation price of the identical cases. 2.7 billion dollars in that announced earnings is tax credit by US citizens. That is also " one time" . Don't forget. A branch of roseless rose stacked with thorns was presented at the earnings report. Better to hold it by both ends.</Msg><Username>naydin2005</Username><Timestamp>1358740963469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:02:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358742183912-90</Id><Topic><Title>The presidential numbers important to the right blown away</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358604390100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-19 09:06:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have had your lower tax rates for the past 12 years. Where are the revenues?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358742183912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:23:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358743697746-91</Id><Title>The truth about Reaganomics and the laffer curve</Title><Msg>Reagan got his tax cut in 1981 but Laffer's promised voodoo never really worked. Government tax revenues remained stagnant from 1981 through 1984. Revenues did increase later in the 1980s, but this occurred only after Reagan realized that Laffer's program wasn't working and agreed to a series of small tax hikes in an attempt to address soaring budget deficits. These increases offset many of the gains individual taxpayers reaped from Reagan's initial 1981 tax cut. Individual tax savings were further eroded by Reagan's 1982 Social Security reform package, which increased payroll taxes to fund the national retirement system. And yet another hit to taxpayers' savings came from widespread increases in state and municipal taxes across the country, levied as local governments sought to make up for funds lost when Reagan's budgets slashed federal payments to the states. When all was said and done, the total tax burden imposed on the American people from all sources—state and local taxes, federal income and capital gains taxes, and payroll taxes—remained basically unchanged throughout the 1980s. In the end, Reagan's reputation as a tax-cutter far outran his actual performance. Reagan's tax policies did, however, redistribute the tax burden significantly, even if they failed to reduce it overall. By cutting income taxes, which are paid at a higher rate by the wealthy, while increasing payroll taxes, which are paid at a higher rate by the working poor and middle class, Reagan shifted the tax burden down the income scale. During the 1980s, the total effective federal taxation rate for the poorest one-fifth of American families actually increased by more than 16%. By contrast, the effective taxation rate for the wealthiest one-fifth of families fell by 5.5%, and the richest one percent of Americans saved even more: their tax rate fell by 14.4%.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1358743697746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 23:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>