<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-11-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383453410631-1</Id><Title>Et tu, Brutes?</Title><Msg>The greatest pain of all is betrayal by a close friend or lover...except that is for betrayal by both having an affair behind your back. 'vieweroutrage' and 'shutupstellas' and 'ekonprophet' and spocklovesyou'? One lonely ballsmuggler and testicular pirate. "Amos.ignore' and 'ghostwriter' and 'doggiedoggie'? One more of the same. 'Roccofelardi'? The jury is still out on rocco; I could hope, but why expect any better treatment or support from him than from my other so-called 'friends'? The veil of denial has been ripped from my eyes. Stay away from the 'Bundy-Dube' Symposium on Circular Logic and Dismal Scientists, because it ain't ever gonna happen....it's a scam. Don't worry about the Igloo....I've always got back-up plans for my back-up plans....he'll reach his destination, even if anonymous supporters are going to have to carry him on the last leg of the journey. I'm sure they'll try to beat me down on the terms of our contract, but I've got a little dope on them too, and I long ago took Sun Tzu's message to heart: "Always offer your enemy a face-saving way out. ROTFLMAO he was quite a gentleman, because they'll easily accept a loss of face as long as they can preserve their hindquarters." Besides, Mrs. Fish has received and distributed enough copies of Fast Eddie's and my own Hoover bags that I'm not worried about my personal safety....in fact, the way I've scripted and executed the Staggerwing Saga, they're more likely to be fighting with each other over who gets to surround me with vicious bodyguards and Gulfstream transportation. Keep the light on, baby.....I'll be home in time for Thanksgiving. ROTFLMA ('allies') O. Yours in admiration and respect lost, -Franklin Thadwaller Kilbyrne III.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383453410631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 00:36:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383462057112-2</Id><Title>Greetings From Omaha! Obamacare Rollout a Travesty</Title><Msg>There really needs to be investigations. Make people talk. Follow the money, stop at nothing till answers are obtained and people are put in prison, otherwise people's faith in government and the presidency will collapse</Msg><Username>nancy_pelosi.idiot</Username><Timestamp>1383462057112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 02:00:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383469384780-3</Id><Topic><Title>6 people signed up on day one for $1 billion spent on Obamacare website</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1383421257188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor people like me need that subsidized healthcare.</Msg><Username>david_kupidlowski</Username><Timestamp>1383469384780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 04:03:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383479691492-4</Id><Topic><Title>6 people signed up on day one for $1 billion spent on Obamacare website</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1383421257188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and that would be because of a bipartisan agreement to pay government workers for doing nothing; the populace never even saw that happening, and they well know we're paying too many of the government workers for doing nothing on a regular basis.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1383479691492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 06:54:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383479922373-5</Id><Topic><Title>Is bung crack lapping required for Teabag membership? Or, is s*h*!*t* eating all it takes?</Title><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1383181382697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-30 21:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you live in a fart-filled bubble, boy? Pop that bubble, and breathe, boy. Now, look around you, boy. Look at the MAJORITY of voters that re-elected Obama AFTER the ACA was enacted. They outnumber all of you wing ding morons by HUGE numbers.</Msg><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383479922373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 06:58:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383480111992-6</Id><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Msg>Oh, it's the new dawn of a new day, and in my home port of Boston I understand the sun rose in a partial eclipse. How fitting! Nay, how prophetic! Here in the eastern atlantic a strange and distorted sun rose a few hours ago, and under a strange light I convened a kangaroo court, brought myself up on charges and convicted myself of the following crimes against humanity and self: 1) group-think 2) mutual flattery 3) unenlightened ego inflation and self-puffery 4) ball-smuggling Satellite news reports of the throngs mobbing downtown Boston yesterday have reached me at sea, and I am seasick. As I read the accounts of hundreds of thousands of patriots defying bombers, sporting fake beards, and reveling in the achievements of our hometown boyz of summer, a ragged band of free agents and Irish Travelers and overpaid illiterates and musclebound lobbyists for the Boston Strong Movement, I am overcome by guilt and self-doubt. Even at a great distance, I too have fallen under the spell of this rabid flock of sheep. How many of my ersatz brothers, fans and patriots would have showed up for a rally to support getting the money out of our political system, or making free health care the right of every citizen, or demanding that our courts apply the same system of justice to State Cops and political bit-players as they do to lovers, muggers and thieves, or getting the weapons that kill 8 of our children in this country every day? Down by the banks of the river Charles, duh masses are a-chugging that dirty water. Thanks, but I'd rather drink seawater, and I think I might. No matter how many of the infinite series of antipodes one visits, it's still hard to discern the great truth that lies within their perimeter: that we all reside within the arc they describe, and none but a handful of us deserve to stroll on what should be hallowed ground. My compass and GPS are spinning.....re-calculating, recalculating.....ROT deck and barfing over the rail...self-loathing....</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383480132618-7</Id><Title>Mandatory intelligence test now required for anyone registering as GOP</Title><Msg>It's about time !</Msg><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480132618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:02:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383480428007-8</Id><Title>ACA will end up all pluses for the Democrat party. The people will not forget which party stood</Title><Msg>with them on affordable healthcare coverage. History is replete with what I speak! Feckless Republican party will rue the day they did not support the plan and continued their plutocrat butt kissing obstructionist politics. A healthy work force that doesn't have to stay at dead end jobs just to have healthcare coverage is going to open up new levels of creativity and believe me HR departments understand the ramifications of losing this leverage over employees!</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1383480428007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:07:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383480843303-9</Id><Topic><Title>"Ask not . . . . Ask what you can do to destroy your country." -- House Republicans</Title><Username>sammysedwat</Username><Timestamp>1381348055143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-09 15:47:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>24 billlion dollar waste House Republican caused shut down is over, but the polls indicate House Republicans are now regarded as completely incompetent, wholly partisan, bigoted and racist, over the top extremists, blatantly untruthful, and given over to unspeakable perversions.</Msg><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480843303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383480895292-10</Id><Topic><Title>Bring on 2014 and rid the world of Tea Bag SKUM!</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1368436506133</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 05:15:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more year, and it will be here!</Msg><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480895292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:14:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383480965506-11</Id><Topic><Title>ACA will end up all pluses for the Democrat party. The people will not forget which party stood</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1383480428007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPOT ON ! !</Msg><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480965506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:16:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383484379935-12</Id><Topic><Title>N.R.A STRIKES AGAING NOW AT LA AIRPORT. THOSE REPUBLICANS ASSASSIN</Title><Username>dexter.westsideny</Username><Timestamp>1383343468037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-11-01 18:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Flawed logic"? "Overconfident" "Ban Guns"? "Ban cars....trucks....alcohol"? ROTFLMAO where exactly did I say "ban guns"? Since you brought up all those other killers and extrapolated from my non-existent call to ban guns, lets look at your own flawed logic on display. Working from a false premise, you extended it to banning all kinds of other potentially lethal products which in fact are not banned.....they're REGULATED, genius! Sensible, well-crafted and genuinely monitored and enforced regulations are not bans - they're RESTRICTIONS! "Clown"? Hey bozo, look in the mirror before you start accusing others of having red noses and orange hair.... ROTFLMAO and dropping my loaded Glock .40. Here's a sobering thought for you: I can buy guns, and with my psych profile, do you think that's a good thing?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383484379935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 08:12:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383484970343-13</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm starting my new novel, "The Sun Sort of Rises" a modern adaptation of Hummingway's classic work. The running of the humans tragedy is munged into the same narrative as a botched sun rise and love story. Then it takes a strange twist and starts explaining how the handicapper general and mind control and the sexy leader of north chorea will make a utopia here on urth by taking away all the capabilities, including the ability to read which is the source of a lot of disagreements. ROFLMFO. yabba dabba doo. I'm sure under different circumstance the cardaasians could have out played the socks but we have what we have. All praise the humans.</Msg><Username>spocklovesyou</Username><Timestamp>1383484970343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 08:22:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383485415280-14</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also if you look at USGS earthquake map it is quite decorated, I'm sure someone could look at longer term stats but at least in theory small gravity changes can be a big deal for systems on the edge of relaxing. A total eclipse of the heart....</Msg><Username>spocklovesyou</Username><Timestamp>1383485415280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 08:30:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383487039853-15</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does this mean you'll be getting a new and equally cryptic ID? We like, wait with baited breath.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1383487039853</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 08:57:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383487337503-16</Id><Title>Ask not what you can do for your country ....</Title><Msg>ask what you can GET from your country -- Obamabots</Msg><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383487337503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:02:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383487731946-17</Id><Topic><Title>Mandatory intelligence test now required for anyone registering as GOP</Title><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480132618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama allows equal protection under the law and requires an intelligence test for ALL voter registrations ..... the Democratic Party will be completely decimated !</Msg><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383487731946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383487798025-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are making about as much sense as spocklovesyou. The only thing consistent with your prior posts is your fascination with "ball-smuggling", whatever that is. Anything like Boca Ball?</Msg><Username>whyduyouask</Username><Timestamp>1383487798025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:09:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383488182769-19</Id><Title>Contratulations Obama ..... not every politician can manage to #$%$ off BOTH sides in a foreign conflict !</Title><Msg>With U.S. aid to Egypt being cut in the wake of the military crackdown on the Muslim Brotherhood, word on the street in Egypt, along with tweets and Facebook posts, seems to indicate anti-U.S. sentiments are at an all-time high. Washington has lost friends on both sides of the Egyptian political battle, including both supporters and critics of ousted Egyptian President Mohammad Morsi.</Msg><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383488182769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:16:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383488274737-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you ask? ROTD eating can after can of Chicken Of The Sea packed in brine and chasing them down with bilge water.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383488274737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:17:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383488665676-21</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fish, check the disclaimer on Boston Strong ... naming rights at Harvard can be subject to change ... based on large donation from Malaysian casino ... culinary union sushi chef to replace white lunch lady</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1383488665676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:24:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383493990741-22</Id><Title>Why does Obama lie?</Title><Msg>Does he think that shows leadership?</Msg><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383493990741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383494203308-23</Id><Topic><Title>ACA will end up all pluses for the Democrat party. The people will not forget which party stood</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1383480428007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes my son loves the $600.00 a month more insurance his family will pay .This money will be given to welfare insurance to buy votes. What color is the sky in your world?</Msg><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383494203308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383495227390-24</Id><Topic><Title>Got My Cancel Letter. I will NEVER vote Democrat again!!!</Title><Username>tony_dungeee</Username><Timestamp>1383425795531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any non complying policy will end at the first of the year. Now you will have to get a policy that complies with the standards. You may find similar coverage for a lower rate or a higher rate depending on what state you are in or what your income is. Yes you will have maternity care covered even if you are a man. This is typical of the minor problems that should have been dealt with by now instead of voting 40 times just to try to get rid of the program.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383495227390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:13:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383495654662-25</Id><Topic><Title>Rand Paul caught plagiarizing from Wiki. Literary theft, copy and paste: The way of the Teabagger</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1383423547581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 16:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His speech writers seem to be pretty lazy and copy word for word from several outside sources which he then reads off without attribution. I think it is more revealing that he quotes movie plots as sources of factual commentary than that he derives his comments word for word from other sources.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383495654662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:20:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383496422962-26</Id><Topic><Title>ACA will end up all pluses for the Democrat party. The people will not forget which party stood</Title><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1383480428007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:07:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I make it a policy not to respond to anecdotal data promoting either side of the aisle. Years of Republican healthcare with it's associated horror stories of families being kicked to the curb when one came down with a serious illness, pre-existing condition exclusions and at the same time huge bonus payments to the top CEO's in the healthcare markets never get any play on Fox news.</Msg><Username>andym_30054</Username><Timestamp>1383496422962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:33:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383496740153-27</Id><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Msg>Bank of America acquired Countrywide Financial and Merrill Lynch in the depths of the financial crisis for roughly $25 billion. With acquisitions of that magnitude, there will almost undoubtedly be operational overlap and duplication. It's been five years since these deals were announced, and Bank of America is continuing to integrate these acquisitions and work toward making them more efficient -- a process that will benefit both clients and shareholders. To recap, Bank of America's diverse revenue streams are continuing to deliver results even as the company puts its mortgage-related issues behind it. The bank is becoming more transparent and open to customer feedback, and as it works toward becoming a more efficient operation, profits should drop to the bottom line. Obviously, it hasn't been all blue skies and sunny days for Bank of America or Moynihan since the passing of the Dodd-Frank act in June 2010. But as the legal woes have abated and the performance has improved since passing the Federal Reserve-run stress tests earlier this year, the perspective of the employees has improved a bit as well. Although it's hard to narrow Bank of America's culture down to a few words on a page (or screen), the data suggests that Bank of America is seeing improvement there as well.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383497827344-28</Id><Topic><Title>6 people signed up on day one for $1 billion spent on Obamacare website</Title><Username>nasa_rs</Username><Timestamp>1383421257188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 15:40:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just can't believe we have yet another entitlement when both Medicare and Social Security are going bankrupt. Instead of this Obama should have made his main focus to pass Simpson-Bowles. I knew when he dropped his own commission it was just a smoke screen anyways and he never had any intention of taking their advice. Nothing like wasting taxpayer money on a web of lies</Msg><Username>nancy_pelosi.idiot</Username><Timestamp>1383497827344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:57:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383498210998-29</Id><Topic><Title>Contratulations Obama ..... not every politician can manage to #$%$ off BOTH sides in a foreign conflict !</Title><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383488182769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 09:16:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's only enemy is American Conservatism. He uses the IRS quite strategically don't you think?</Msg><Username>nancy_pelosi.idiot</Username><Timestamp>1383498210998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 12:03:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383498436550-30</Id><Topic><Title>Got My Cancel Letter. I will NEVER vote Democrat again!!!</Title><Username>tony_dungeee</Username><Timestamp>1383425795531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 16:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry you are caught up in wealth redistribution known as obamacare. The balance sheet of the US government is broken and nobody seems to care what we are doing to our children</Msg><Username>nancy_pelosi.idiot</Username><Timestamp>1383498436550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 12:07:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383498954999-31</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was an excellent study done on the cost/benefits of the WAMU/Bear Stearns take overs by JPM. It basically compared the cost of the acquisitions and all legal settlements - past and expected future - to the present value of cash flows from these two companies growing at 3% and discounted at 8%. The difference was a positive in the $billions for JPM. Maybe similar for BAC, depending on the legal issues. Motley Fool, if they were worth anything, would have performed the same sort of exercise instead of reguritating the obvious. Their pieces seem to come from pseudo-analyst bloggers. Not worth a helluva lot. And when will they ever learn the word "data" is plural?</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1383498954999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 12:15:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383501806759-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Obama lie?</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383493990741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His whole life is a LIE!</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1383501806759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:03:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383502418110-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Obama lie?</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383493990741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because that's all he knows! He certainly doesn't know anything about leadership!</Msg><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383502418110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:13:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383502575099-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Obama lie?</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383493990741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His trade was community organizing and a politician in Chicago. I would actually be more shocked if he didn't Lie</Msg><Username>nancy_pelosi.idiot</Username><Timestamp>1383502575099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:16:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383503404828-35</Id><Topic><Title>Why does Obama lie?</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383493990741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 10:53:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just to prove white people's dumbility is way beyond comprehension</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1383503404828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383503470774-36</Id><Title>Obama is Unaware of Everything</Title><Msg>Either that or a diabolical liar. I would choose the latter</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383503470774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:31:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383504291521-37</Id><Title>GOP infested with toxic menace Teabagger plague of hate-mongering imbeciles</Title><Msg>Voters will turn out in record numbers for a mid-term election just to rid the country of this plague.</Msg><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1383504291521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:44:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383504556514-38</Id><Title>Seditious futility. Loser Teabaggers think trashing a MB will promote their anti-American agenda</Title><Msg>Like all things Teabag, it ends in futility.</Msg><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1383504556514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:49:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383505592836-39</Id><Topic><Title>GOP infested with toxic menace Teabagger plague of hate-mongering imbeciles</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1383504291521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:44:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU are infested with Racism and Denial about Obama. Thanks for showing everyone what an idiot you are!!</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383505592836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:06:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383505721160-40</Id><Title>next week's headlines today, obama shocked Iran has a nuke weapon</Title><Msg>The gopping idiot will probaly use thyat event to blame bush</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383505721160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:08:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383507325860-41</Id><Title>libertylies pulled the gerbil out of masons obama, and suggests the public eat it sautee'd</Title><Msg>What a starnge group the libs naybobs are, so self rightoues, so stupid, so wrong, such a waste</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383507325860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:35:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383507835359-42</Id><Title>tomorrow's headlines today, obama's arrogance costs America dearly</Title><Msg>Yup old jugears just is not ready for prime time, and his arrogance will cost America very dearly. He is laughed at everywhere on the world stage, while being seen here in the states as a total failure. He needs to resign, and go into exoile, along with plugs biden</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383507835359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:43:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383508370135-43</Id><Title>Obama's new memorial planned to be on top of the abandoned Book Tower in Detroit.</Title><Msg>In the spirit of King Ozymandias, Obama's head will adorn the top of the Book Tower with two soaring teleprompters on either side. He will be captured in a pose familiar to all of us, looking down his nose, mouth agape.</Msg><Username>the_power_inyou</Username><Timestamp>1383508370135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:52:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383509643254-44</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Data" has a plural Latin derivation but only pedants would insist it is not OK to use it as singular. You, likewise, have a plural derivation from your two parents but we would be cursed if there were more than one of you.</Msg><Username>whyduyouask</Username><Timestamp>1383509643254</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 15:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383510610493-45</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When they start addressing audiences with a higher IQ than whyduyouask's...who would rather attack than learn. In fairness, unlike the British, it's mostly used wrong in America and the Motleys would be in the majority.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1383510610493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 15:30:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383512466808-46</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mason you reckon you have anyone fooled?</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383512466808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 16:01:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383513521403-47</Id><Topic><Title>next week's headlines today, obama shocked Iran has a nuke weapon</Title><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383505721160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:08:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They acquired several a few years back from Iraq. These along with the dirty bombs they already have should give them an extra seat at the next G7 meeting.</Msg><Username>pkm92101</Username><Timestamp>1383513521403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 16:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383514622101-48</Id><Topic><Title>next week's headlines today, obama shocked Iran has a nuke weapon</Title><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383505721160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 14:08:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About time Iran protects itself from the US criminal activities. Iran like the US, should not hesitate to use nukes to strike those seeking to harm her. But history is clear, and Iran like most countries that possess nukes, will not use them. Only nation in the history of mankind that have used them is the US. I am all for Iran to protect itself.</Msg><Username>ayimakirei</Username><Timestamp>1383514622101</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 16:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383516853346-49</Id><Topic><Title>How come fevoter does not have a sphincter czar? Teabaggers lined up at his back door want to know.</Title><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1382504774611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-23 01:06:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kum one, kum all! [tee, hee, hee !]</Msg><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1383516853346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383516978348-50</Id><Topic><Title>I am so embarrassed and ashamed that I was ever associated with the Tea Party jackasses</Title><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1381921336134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My sister is also my ma. Does that count?</Msg><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1383516978348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383517086661-51</Id><Topic><Title>What's all this foul talk about me having a gerbil stuck up my heinie?</Title><Username>zevoter02</Username><Timestamp>1381551354967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-12 00:15:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mason, do you think you are fooling anyone</Msg><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1383517086661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383517166945-52</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberty, due to circumstances beyond my control (a Bundy-Dube organizing committee more committed to having congress with themselves than to doing any work at all or planning for a successful convention or even collecting a mountain of easy ka-ching), I regret to inform you that the War of Dismal Scientists and Sushi-Sucking Festival has been cancelled. However, MY reputation and word of honor are beyond reproach or question. Although I am presently quite indisposed, I promise you I'll make it jake with you. You won the emcee contest fair and square, and I'll be back home in Boston before Thanksgiving, so put on your Schuey hat and start thinking about what sort of trump-worthy Christmas offering I should send you as a contest consolation prize and offering of atonement. And if it wouldn't be too much trouble, please see that the following message reaches Mrs. Fish in Beantown: Keep that candle in the window, 'cause it's time for me to move. Though I been gone, gone, I'll be coming home soon, 'Long as I can see the light. My bag is packed and I now I'm movin', you always knew I'd drift a while. But I know, while I was gone, gone, you didn't worry no, You always knew I'd see the light. I've always had that old trav'lin' bone, It's a feelin' won't leave me alone. But I won't, won't be losin' my way, no, no 'Long as I can see the light. Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Oh, Yeah! Start making pies and stuffing for your old bird....see ya for Thanksgiving Sugar Babe. - Frankie</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383517166945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:19:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383517315998-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mandatory intelligence test now required for anyone registering as GOP</Title><Username>sachaklamur</Username><Timestamp>1383480132618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:02:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You did'nt pass the Intelligence Test, did you? Don't feel bad. fevoter flunked it to.</Msg><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1383517315998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:21:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383518675118-54</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. President: Don’t Free Jonathan Pollard</Title><Username>pat_buchanan_42</Username><Timestamp>1383445359931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 22:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ Israel!</Msg><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383518675118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:44:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383518718232-55</Id><Topic><Title>Anne Pollard Statement</Title><Username>pat_buchanan_42</Username><Timestamp>1383445697925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 22:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ all K_kes!</Msg><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383518718232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:45:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383519148779-56</Id><Topic><Title>Say what you will but everytime mason uses my ID I am scoring</Title><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1377685368589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 06:22:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mason, do you really think anyone gives a %&amp;#*?</Msg><Username>zevoter02</Username><Timestamp>1383519148779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383519599416-57</Id><Topic><Title>GOP infested with toxic menace Teabagger plague of hate-mongering imbeciles</Title><Username>take_out_the_white_trash</Username><Timestamp>1383504291521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 13:44:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Teabagger plague of hate-mongering imbeciles" That pretty much sums them up.</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383519599416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:59:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383519627486-58</Id><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Msg>What was I thinking?</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383519793335-59</Id><Title>Why are all the Companies Obama has in Charge of Obamacare so Corrupt?</Title><Msg>Many of them are being sued and already had lawsuits going when Obama awarded them No bid contracts. In a word Corruption</Msg><Username>frankster1955a</Username><Timestamp>1383519793335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:03:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383520493020-60</Id><Topic><Title>Mr. President: Don’t Free Jonathan Pollard</Title><Username>pat_buchanan_42</Username><Timestamp>1383445359931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 22:22:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Execute J*ew filth.</Msg><Username>mel_gibson_8</Username><Timestamp>1383520493020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:14:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383520536809-61</Id><Topic><Title>Anne Pollard Statement</Title><Username>pat_buchanan_42</Username><Timestamp>1383445697925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 22:28:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Execute this #$%$.</Msg><Username>mel_gibson_8</Username><Timestamp>1383520536809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:15:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383520542594-62</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You probably smoked too much cheap pot before you go into the voting booth</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1383520542594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:15:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383520614237-63</Id><Title>Los Angeles Airport Shooting Appears To Be Another Psyop Hoax</Title><Msg>November 2, 2013 Source: Lee Rogers, Blacklisted News In recent times we’ve had a number of highly publicized mass shooting rampages in which the official story was full of outright lies and deception. The so-called Sandy Hook and Washington Navy Yard shootings are just two good examples of this. This past Friday’s alleged Los Angeles airport shooting at a TSA security checkpoint is no exception as there are already a number of questions surrounding the official story. In fact the official story has already changed a couple of times which has further ruined its credibility. At first the shooter was identified as a disgruntled TSA worker by law enforcment sources. That story has since been revised with the shooter now identified as an angry patriot who wanted to kill as many TSA agents and cops as possible. Conveniently the official story is being presented in such a way where the corporate media stooges can further criticize the Second Amendment and people who have problems with the government. It is also very likely that we will see this event used as justification to arm TSA agents. Here’s a few of the main reasons why this story seems to be a complete and total fabrication. The alleged shooter has been identified as someone with the name of Paul Anthony Ciancia. Look at the two CIA references in his last name. What are the odds of the shooter having a name like that? This appears to be an inside joke by the clowns who put together this operation. Ciancia if that is even his real name to begin with has been described by friends and family as a bit of a loner but not someone who they thought would ever be capable of doing something like this. He has also been described as not having any prior criminal background. Undoubtedly this is a convenient profile for the government to continue fear mongering about lone wolf and domestic terrorists. Again what are the odds that the shooter would fit this exact profile? This type of profile gives more ammunition to the promoters of fear in both the government and the corporate media. During a press conference Los Angeles airport police chief Patrick Gannon said that they recently had an exercise practicing the exact same scenario just three weeks earlier. Gannon would even slip up and say that they played the same thing out the day of the shooting indicating that the event was staged in some fashion. In the press conference video carefully look at the body language of the people behind Gannon when he talks about the exercise. FBI agent David Bowdich who is located behind and to the left of Gannon looks particularly concerned when Gannon makes that remark because he realizes that Gannon messed up and revealed too much. Let’s face it though, if this wasn’t staged the odds of their training exercise and a similar real world event happening within just three weeks of each other is extremely low. Amazingly, the shooter is said to have had notes in his bag talking about how the TSA is a fascist organization, references to the New World Order and other messages which have been described as anti-American ramblings from a conspiracy theorist. Looks as if they thought this part of the story would give them more bang for their buck since so-called conspiracy theorists are the only people doing any sort of real investigative journalism. The odds of this being part of a real life non-scripted event is ridiculously low. The shooter was even said to have used an AR-15 rifle which the gun control lobby has been foaming at the mouth to ban. Here we have yet another convenient angle to the official story which will likely be used to justify more anti-gun legislation from clowns like Dianne Feinstein and others of her ilk. In both a CBS and ABC news report (1:50 in) covering the shooting a helicopter camera shows a couple of cops quickly pushing a wheelchair down the road with a dummy in it. An Associated Press report also shows similar footage. The dummy has what appears to be a TSA uniform on and is actually identified in the CBS report as a wounded TSA agent. This is despite the fact that the video conclusively shows that they are pushing a dummy around. Not only that, but for someone who was supposedly shot you certainly don't see a whole lot of blood on the uniform. The dummy looks like it has some sort of water stain on its chest but that's about it. It is completely and utterly insane. Media idiocy and scripting aside, why would cops or any first responders in a real world situation be wasting their time running down the road with a dummy in a wheelchair unless this was part of a drill or a more elaborate hoax? Watch the video and you will see how plainly ridiculous it is. It is absolutely comical that CBS or any other news organization would even try to claim that it was anything but a dummy. This is a major fail on their part. Maybe next time they’ll get their lies straight. So far no video footage from security cameras of the actual incident have been released to the press. Only a couple of still photos showing the supposed crime scene have surfaced. If this happened at any TSA checkpoint at any airport in the United States there would have been multiple video cameras recording everything that happened. If the events unfolded exactly as we are being told than why haven’t they released the video footage yet? It seems as if this would be a simple thing to do unless of course the story is entirely fabricated. It is also worth noting that the shooter is in critical condition after allegedly being shot by law enforcement. Considering how ridiculous the official story is, it is very likely that we will be told of his death very soon. They obviously can't have him telling his side of the story. It is possible with what we know so far that he might have been setup and thought that he was participating in some sort of TSA sanctioned drill. There are probably other inconsistencies and questions surrounding this event but the ones described here prove conclusively that the official story is not believable. Every aspect to the official story indicates that this was a scripted psychological warfare operation of some kind. Even if you don’t believe that this was a hoax, there is no question that this incident will be used to push for more gun control and to arm TSA agents. That’s right, more guns for government security enforcers and fewer guns for average Americans. Apparently the Obama regime doesn’t have enough armed goons to control the public so this is certainly a great excuse for them to increase the number of armed thugs at their disposal.</Msg><Username>mel_gibson_8</Username><Timestamp>1383520614237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:16:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383520734018-64</Id><Topic><Title>Los Angeles Airport Shooting Appears To Be Another Psyop Hoax</Title><Username>mel_gibson_8</Username><Timestamp>1383520614237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:16:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seek help. You are severely ill.</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383520734018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:18:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383521184864-65</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Youre certainly the expert on that.</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383521184864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:26:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383522037628-66</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad but true. I supect whyduwhatever doesn't know the singular form of 'data'. I hope he doesn't open his mouth in educated circles, he'll only enbarrass himself.</Msg><Username>jhitcher2011</Username><Timestamp>1383522037628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:40:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383522152507-67</Id><Title>I Burned all my hope and Change Posters</Title><Msg>The others I lined my cat liter box with. I love seeing my cat #$%$ all over Obama's Face</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383522152507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383523778545-68</Id><Topic><Title>Hard-pressed American Taxpayers to “Donate” Another Half-Billion Dollars to Israel</Title><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383519200974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why not just drop $500MM worth of nukes and be done with this krap?</Msg><Username>usedtobehomeiess</Username><Timestamp>1383523778545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:09:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383523974954-69</Id><Topic><Title>Say what you will but everytime mason uses my ID I am scoring</Title><Username>zevoter33</Username><Timestamp>1377685368589</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 06:22:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahh again you provide excellent evidence, or are you going to blame your position on that gerbil stuck up your obama?</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383523974954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:12:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383524079024-70</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May I add that those "educated" circles would exclude those folks like libertylies, mason and of course WARREN EDDY.</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383524079024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:14:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383525307581-71</Id><Title>Gee why isn't the msm'ers telling us obama is the smartest thing ever anymore</Title><Msg>Theory is when you know everything and can not explain why things are not running co9rrectly, practise is when things are running rigtht, but you can't explain why. What we have in jugears obama is the united form of both, where nothing works and he does not know why</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383525307581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:35:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383526323929-72</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try not to be too hard on yourself. There is not much of a choice when you go to the polls and you could have been frustrated and marked the wrong box. It is also very possible your vote was not counted, no one sends a confirmation that your vote was counted, only the receipt that you voted. Cheer up!</Msg><Username>pkm92101</Username><Timestamp>1383526323929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:52:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383526836609-73</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one needs to fool YOU, little z. You commandeered that position at birth.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383526836609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:00:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383528271283-74</Id><Topic><Title>Hard-pressed American Taxpayers to “Donate” Another Half-Billion Dollars to Israel</Title><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383519200974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or you could just blow it out your anti-semitic butt.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1383528271283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383528283774-75</Id><Topic><Title>Hard-pressed American Taxpayers to “Donate” Another Half-Billion Dollars to Israel</Title><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383519200974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 17:53:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or you could just blow it out your anti-semitic butt.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1383528283774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:24:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383528312336-76</Id><Title>The difference between Obama and Kim Kardashian</Title><Msg>One guy got a pair of teleprompters and one girl got a pair of nice boobs. Both will rather die if they can't find a TV spot every day.</Msg><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1383528312336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:25:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383528600944-77</Id><Topic><Title>The difference between Obama and Kim Kardashian</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1383528312336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:25:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What on earth are you babbling about you freakin twit?</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383528600944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:30:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383528796894-78</Id><Topic><Title>Gee why isn't the msm'ers telling us obama is the smartest thing ever anymore</Title><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383525307581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:35:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that even English? What is that insane little rant supposed to mean little z? Feel free to decode your babble for us.</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383528796894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:33:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383528963600-79</Id><Title>Obama ask new hires to name 57 states.</Title><Msg>But some can not name them all ,Obama is so smart.</Msg><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383528963600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383529302727-80</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who?</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383529302727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383529411587-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ask new hires to name 57 states.</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383528963600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:36:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? THAT is your Obama insult? Lame.</Msg><Username>erazor111</Username><Timestamp>1383529411587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:43:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383530781391-82</Id><Topic><Title>I Burned all my hope and Change Posters</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383522152507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will the people do with the Bust of himself he leaves in the White House?</Msg><Username>pkm92101</Username><Timestamp>1383530781391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:06:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383531003999-83</Id><Topic><Title>Los Angeles Airport Shooting Appears To Be Another Psyop Hoax</Title><Username>mel_gibson_8</Username><Timestamp>1383520614237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:16:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets hope someone reveals the truth on this, It is very disturbing to see these events become everyday in this country. And it is all staged by our government. very sad.</Msg><Username>pkm92101</Username><Timestamp>1383531003999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383531860474-84</Id><Title>Yahoo's sponsors aren't going to like the lack of traffic here due to wing ding stupidity.</Title><Msg>Excrement eating fools like fevoter and donkey dumbama_sucks keep posting under 50 different IDs and it drove the BAC investors away. The BAC forum has become a litter box for the deluded and demented winger bung-jumpers, tea bagger trash, and neo-n@zi goons. Time to clean house, Yahoo, and flush the right-turds OUT !</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1383531860474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:24:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383532089802-85</Id><Topic><Title>The difference between Obama and Kim Kardashian</Title><Username>kingofvietnam</Username><Timestamp>1383528312336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:25:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please don't insult the king or tarnish the page with this stuff. The king speaks to all of us. Can't we just enjoy the victory of the socks over the less interesting kardassassians? ROFLMFO.</Msg><Username>spocklovesyou</Username><Timestamp>1383532089802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:28:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383532127079-86</Id><Topic><Title>Right wing Tea Party trash squeal like rats trapped on a sinking ship</Title><Username>lv.246er</Username><Timestamp>1381633130348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-12 22:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because they are rats trapped on a sinking ship.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1383532127079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:28:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383532274728-87</Id><Topic><Title>Mass hysteria and the socks nation of ballsmugglers</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1383480111992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 07:01:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>recent post I read from him something about chicken of the sea, out looking for mermaids near their HQ probably. ROFLMFO. How else to celebrate socks over cardassassians?</Msg><Username>spocklovesyou</Username><Timestamp>1383532274728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383532490650-88</Id><Title>Moronic right-wing efforts to sabotage Obama administration have failed.</Title><Msg>The right-winger jackasses strategy of slinging lies is a laughable failure. The Obama administrations' policies will continue on regardless of the failed efforts by the incompetent winger fools to undermine them.</Msg><Username>dawg_earl</Username><Timestamp>1383532490650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:34:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383532509604-89</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sorry to hear of the cancelation and I have relayed the warning to Mrs Fish. It seems she got it as the red light is no longer on in the window or it may be more than one whom is indisposed at present. A suitable consolation prize of course would be the autographed flight plan and clearance consultation information of the great Staggerwing flight in oblivion accompanied by a copy of the Go Pro videos.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383532509604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:35:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383532736823-90</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I always thought the big argument was whether the "a" was long or short.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383532736823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:38:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383533546229-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama ask new hires to name 57 states.</Title><Username>nathan71943726</Username><Timestamp>1383528963600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 20:36:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hysteria, depression, confusion, agitation, disrepair, suspense and grace are the seven other states Obama had to visit to woo republican voters in the first election. Many of them still remain in the first five after leaving the other two.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383533546229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 21:52:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383534136287-92</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party is Over. Time for all of you lying goon right-wingers to go flush yourselves.</Title><Username>chas.rankin</Username><Timestamp>1377734351565</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 19:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They self-destructed. With "leaders" (Ha, ha!) like Rand Paul, Michelle Bachmann, and Ted Cruz heading down rabbit holes with no agenda other than non-stop lying, it was inevitable.</Msg><Username>lv.246er</Username><Timestamp>1383534136287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:02:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383534155675-93</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>racial discrimination against BAC = 2.2mil racial discrimination against BACs Merrill Lynch = 160mil discrimination against women at BACs Merrill Lynch = 39 mil debt collection settlement for BAC = 32mil There is your BAC culture</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1383534155675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:02:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383534383985-94</Id><Topic><Title>BUSH and GOP, DOW, 14000 TO 6500 IN 8 YEARS. OBAMA, DOW 6500 to 15500 in 5 years. Any questions?</Title><Username>georgew_dunce</Username><Timestamp>1377700504847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-08-28 10:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton left a massive surplus. Bush created a massive deficit. Obama has done well considering all the damage done by Bush including Bush starting and waging two wars on credit.</Msg><Username>lv.246er</Username><Timestamp>1383534383985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:06:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383534587500-95</Id><Title>Racist pigs will never get over Obama in the White House. Deal with it, trailer trash.</Title><Msg>Your destiny is life in a single-wide with all the squaller in the holler. Get off meth, learn to read, turn off Fox News, and stop humping sis.</Msg><Username>lv.246er</Username><Timestamp>1383534587500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:09:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383534615485-96</Id><Topic><Title>I Burned all my hope and Change Posters</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383522152507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can only imagine maybe the same thing they did to the other Hussein</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383534615485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:10:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383534882821-97</Id><Topic><Title>Racist pigs will never get over Obama in the White House. Deal with it, trailer trash.</Title><Username>lv.246er</Username><Timestamp>1383534587500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:09:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who are you talking to weirdo? Better not be talking to me I voted for that Liar Obama. He duped me and a lot of people</Msg><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383534882821</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:14:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383535496123-98</Id><Topic><Title>I Burned all my hope and Change Posters</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383522152507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:42:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold mine in Times Square to some tourists from Tanzania. They said they'd display them in some museum. Make cash off Obama when you can. The tshirts were also sold out, and with the winnings I made more dough in stocks. Now that's hope and change you can believe in.</Msg><Username>bigwariscoming</Username><Timestamp>1383535496123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383536635255-99</Id><Topic><Title>Gee why isn't the msm'ers telling us obama is the smartest thing ever anymore</Title><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383525307581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 19:35:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To repeat Theory is when you know everything and can not explain why things are not running correctly, practise is when things are running rigtht, but you can't explain why. What we have in jugears obama is the united form of both, where nothing works and he does not know why</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383536635255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:43:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383537094193-100</Id><Topic><Title>War Crimes Committed Against U.S. Military Personnel, June 8, 1967</Title><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383444236036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-11-02 22:03:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump....</Msg><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383537094193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383537260452-101</Id><Title>Hard-pressed American Taxpayers to “Donate” Another Half-Billion Dollars to Israel</Title><Msg>Even though America is struggling to pay its own bills and is heading for a record deficit which recently caused a 17-day government shutdown, the US House of Representatives Armed Services Committee has proposed a nearly half a billion dollar increase in military aid to Israel. This is over and above the $11 million a day which American taxpayers already give to Israel every day, and a total US$3.1 billion in military assistance that Washington provides to the Zionist regime. The committee approved $488 million last week to fund Israel’s development of two missile systems and to finance the purchase of extra batteries for 2014. The proposal must now be approved by the House Appropriations Committee and then submitted to the Senate. US Secretary of Defense Chuck Hagel has previously promised that the current aid would not be reduced even while significant cuts are being made to the US defense budget. At the same time, the Israeli government has just announced an (Israeli Shekel) NIS 2.75 billion (US$780 million) budget increase for its own armed forces, drawn from a “government surplus.” According to a report in the Times of Israel, the increase in the Jewish state’s defense budget is in addition to the Israeli Defense Force’s budget set earlier this year at NIS 51 billion ($14.5 billion). Significantly, when the Israeli cabinet approved the budget increases, they also called for the establishment of committee to “focus on pushing along the dismantlement of army bases in prime real estate areas so that the land could be used for construction projects.” A large number of the “bases” to which they are referring are in the Judea and Samaria Area, the official Israeli term for the occupied Palestinian West Bank, and the “dismantlement” for “construction purposes” means an increase in Jewish settlements in Palestinian territory. Just this week, the Israeli government announced that its Housing Ministry would be “offering land for the construction of 1,700 homes in Jerusalem, Judea and Samaria.” According to a report in the Israeli National News service, Housing Minister Uri Ariel said that his office “continues to market lands for construction of homes around Israel. Thanks to our efforts there has been a noticeable rise in housing starts. Today we are building an average of 43,000 new homes a year. With that, in order to bring about a major change in the housing market, we need to increase our efforts to build new homes.” In other words, the American taxpayer is directly funding the Zionist state’s war machine, and the dispossession of the Palestinian people. This situation will carry on for as long as the Jewish Supremacists control the US government, politics and media. Americans need to understand that the reason why they are disliked throughout the world is exclusively to do with the way their government is controlled by the Jewish Supremacists—and that if this situation is ever to change, they have to overthrow the Zio-deathgrip over their organs of government.</Msg><Username>sal_bando_oakland</Username><Timestamp>1383537260452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 22:54:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383537998095-102</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You weren't thinking</Msg><Username>frankster1955a</Username><Timestamp>1383537998095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:06:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383538153117-103</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no thinking rational human could have voted for the fraud/failure called obama</Msg><Username>fevoter</Username><Timestamp>1383538153117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:09:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383538745721-104</Id><Title>ObamaCare debacle reveals rot at core of Barack Obama's administration</Title><Msg>Thanks to the ObamaCare debacle, Americans are getting a close-up of the rot at the core of the Obama administration. “The majority of people calling for me to resign I would say are people who I don’t work for,” health czar Kathleen Sebelius says. Press secretary Jay Carney dismisses all those complaining about the screw-ups as “willfully ignorant” and “partisan.” The refusal to see any criticism as legitimate helps explain why Obama is a failed president. He rammed ObamaCare through Congress without GOP votes, so it is bizarre to claim now that Republicans permanently forfeited all right to complain. His us-against-them mentality restricts input to those who agree with him. The same dynamic is playing out in foreign policy. Israel, Saudi Arabia, France and Germany have lost confidence in our policies on Syria, Iran and surveillance. They, too, have been shut out because his way is the only way. Meanwhile, our enemies have his ear. Their complaints alone are taken seriously. That’s who he is. -- Michael Goodwin | October 28, 2013 | New York Post</Msg><Username>dumbama.sucks</Username><Timestamp>1383538745721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383538777232-105</Id><Topic><Title>I am so Ashamed I ever Voted for that Lying #$%$ Obama</Title><Username>stokmktstudstock</Username><Timestamp>1383519627486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 18:00:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me too. Getting rid of him, and pledging my vote to Hillary in 2016. Can't stand that #$%$ Christy, a thousand times will vote for Sarah Paulin, she's entertaining beyond idiocy.</Msg><Username>bigwariscoming</Username><Timestamp>1383538777232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:19:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1383538888630-106</Id><Topic><Title>Motley fool on BAC</Title><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1383496740153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 11:39:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the thumbs up probably from Justice Barbara Kapnick</Msg><Username>gamblin09</Username><Timestamp>1383538888630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:21:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1383540458391-107</Id><Title>Barock Hussein Obama Must Go</Title><Msg>Impeachment a Good Option Now</Msg><Username>peter.buttsore</Username><Timestamp>1383540458391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-11-03 23:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>