<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366430632568-1</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lost a thousand bucks because you probably bought when those criminal carnival barkers Whitney and bartrona were pumping it heavy on the cnbc boiler room glta</Msg><Username>tom.foolery2</Username><Timestamp>1366430632568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366431012201-2</Id><Topic><Title>What do you call 20 inbreeding rednecks living in a lot rent doublewide?</Title><Username>sofreakinghot</Username><Timestamp>1366376596374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The oshame-a family</Msg><Username>tradewindsiv</Username><Timestamp>1366431012201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366431427129-3</Id><Title>homeland securties new name is Hometown Buffet</Title><Msg>and that sausage throat napolitano, that disgusting man disguised as a woman should be fired and locked up for aiding and sustaining terrorists.</Msg><Username>tradewindsiv</Username><Timestamp>1366431427129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366431537325-4</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no not them i was studying it i didnt even know who whiteny #$%$ was till after</Msg><Username>wandasshop</Username><Timestamp>1366431537325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366432914919-5</Id><Title>Syrian's sending support to Boston</Title><Msg>Boston bombings represent a sorrowful scene of what happens every day in Syria Do accept our condolences The Syrian Revolution KNRC KAFRANBEL 19-4-13 I'm speechless</Msg><Username>deficitcut</Username><Timestamp>1366432914919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366433459397-6</Id><Topic><Title>Taxpayors will pay millions Boston bomber</Title><Username>kramerclyde</Username><Timestamp>1366426438146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, the inbred family members might want to leave Boston. They are already running their smelly, thick mouths about setups and conspiracy, to which their bloated, criminally connected attorneys will act upon, and totally confuse the moron jury pool.</Msg><Username>tradewindsiv</Username><Timestamp>1366433459397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366433560084-7</Id><Title>....................................FBI interviewed Boston bombing suspect in 2011: source</Title><Msg>.........................FBI interviewed Boston bombing suspect in 2011: source nice to know????</Msg><Username>deficitcut</Username><Timestamp>1366433560084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366433613777-8</Id><Topic><Title>Taxpayors will pay millions Boston bomber</Title><Username>kramerclyde</Username><Timestamp>1366426438146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well we pay trillions in Tarp to banksters???</Msg><Username>deficitcut</Username><Timestamp>1366433613777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366433709617-9</Id><Topic><Title>....................................FBI interviewed Boston bombing suspect in 2011: source</Title><Username>deficitcut</Username><Timestamp>1366433560084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FBI should reassess all the database....lol</Msg><Username>deficitcut</Username><Timestamp>1366433709617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366443462536-10</Id><Topic><Title>Banning underground bunkers should be banned.</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1359594996220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 20:16:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An undergdround bunker in Boston instead of a boat woulda bought us more boom for our buck.</Msg><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366443462536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366444665447-11</Id><Topic><Title>Orange haired fanatic right-winger lunatics at it again.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387411372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mason and Warren, who do you think you are fooling?</Msg><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366444665447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 03:57:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366456057240-12</Id><Title>Happy Trails To You, Amerika! Part I of a 4-part history of patriots and shoot-outs.</Title><Msg>Welcome to the best little police action since 'Open Range'! C'mon, buck up there, buckaroos, you didn't think karma wouldn't eventually track us down, didja? Karma's a #$%$, boys and girls, and she's got a few scores to settle. How long did you think our gunslinger ethic would be able to hold the fort? Did you think we could export murder and atrocities forever without karma giving some of the victims our address? Did you think our sheriffs and their posses could ride out of town onto the open range every day for 50 years randomly shooting dirty cowboys and stampeding their herds without a couple of crazies deciding to bring the fight into town? Remember, we all knew our sheriffs were evil; we all knew they were in the pocket of the wealthy ranchers; we all knew what our posses were doing out there, and aside from either mumbling under our breath or cheering them on, we did nothing but hand them badges and pistols and pay their wages. Sure, whatever the wealthy cattlemen want, that's OK with us, go get 'em, men! Well, yippy-ti-yi-ay, the bullets are flying in our streets now, not just out there on the prairies, and the cowboys are picking us off one at a time. Now you seem to think that handing out guns to every man, woman and child is gonna make the town a safer place to live? ROTFLMAO the most they'll do is brandish them or blow their own feet off, which is probably a blessing. Most of them don't have brains to even pick up the right targets, never mind the skill to hit what they're aiming at without killing innocent bystanders and shooting out the windows in the saloon and barbershop. Ah, the 19th century frontier mentality......so productive and seductive, we can't put it down. In the next installment we'll look at how well it continued to serve us in the 20th century. Stay tuned for part II: Some Splendid Little Wars. ROTFLMAO.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366456057240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366456635691-13</Id><Topic><Title>Taxpayors will pay millions Boston bomber</Title><Username>kramerclyde</Username><Timestamp>1366426438146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:53:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Will" pay? ROTFLMAO! Whaddaya think this drama has cost taxpayers already? Hey, being on the heavy (wrong) end of an asymmetric war is expensive, no matter whether you wage it on foreign soil or play it as a home game here in God's Country. ROTFLMAO and our solution seems to be a bad spin on the old Jewish tailor joke..... lower the cost by doing a volume business. ROTFLMAO "Idjits, I'm workin' with idjits....." (spits a juicy wad)</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366456635691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366457483167-14</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they would have beat earnings estimates the crooks would have SOLD ON THE NEWS earnings no longer determine any out come. If investors would just hold eventually they are the winners.</Msg><Username>vinscoot2000</Username><Timestamp>1366457483167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 07:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366459563462-15</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he was on hard drugs. During the year I spent in Thailand (same era; '72-'73) as an Air Force sergeant, my buddies and I were randomly and frequently tapped for drug testing, but the technology at that time could not detect marijuana use. We used to see how stoned we could get, and then showed up for our urine tests with red eyes and feces-eating grins, staggering and laughing so much it was hard to hit the container. Heck, the Air Force had a sign posted at the main gate of Udorn RTAFB with a big caricature of Free-Wheelin' Franklin (Thank you, R. Crumb!) waving a big j-bar, and this caption: "Most local DOPE is laced with heroin or opium. For information and a free test kit, contact the base Drug Information Office." As long as we kept their birds up and running, all the Air Force was concerned with was the hard stuff. Besides the abundant and cheap heroin and opium, Thailand also had no pharmaceutical laws. If you could name it you could buy it, and cheap. British "White Horse" speed? 5 cents a hit. Valium? 10 cents. More guys got in trouble from uppers and downers than got hooked on heroin or opium. Look, it's no secret that Little Georgie was a cokehead and a juicer, and it wasn't until he got political ambitions that he found Jesus and went straight. ROTFLMAO Chuck Colsen Light.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366459563462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366460890743-16</Id><Title>Prophecies are like stocks</Title><Msg>There are plenty to choose from, and the ugly ones often turn out to be the big winners. ROTFLMAO so which one did you pick? The Beatles: All You Need Is Love or The Doors: The End? This is the end Beautiful friend This is the end My only friend, the end Of our elaborate plans, the end Of everything that stands, the end No safety or surprise, the end I'll never look into your eyes...again Can you picture what will be So limitless and free Desperately in need...of some...stranger's hand In a...desperate land Lost in a Roman...wilderness of pain And all the children are insane All the children are insane Waiting for the summer rain, yeah There's danger on the edge of town Ride the King's highway, baby Weird scenes inside the gold mine ROTFLMAO have a nice day, you BAC gold miners!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366460890743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462084303-17</Id><Title>BAC</Title><Msg>Why Bank of America Crashed and Burned This Week By John Grgurich | More Articles | Save For Later April 19, 2013 | Comments (4) As of Friday morning, Bank of America (NYSE: BAC ) has lost 4.24% on the week. This epic drop came squarely on the heels of fairly solid first-quarter earnings. I'm a B of A bear, but even I can't figure out why investors reacted like they did. The power of negative thinking As B of A crashed and burned this week, it also took the rest of the big banks and the markets down with it: •Citigroup lost 0.90% so far. •JPMorgan Chase (NYSE: JPM ) lost 2.75%. •Finally, Wells Fargo (NYSE: WFC ) is down 0.68% The markets all took it on the chin this week, as well, with the broader S&amp;P 500 down 1.63%, the narrower Dow Jones Industrial Average down 1.82%, and the Nasdaq Composite down 2.15%. Swing and a miss For the first quarter, net income at B of A was up, revenue was up, and total deposits were up: that last one always being key at consumer-focused bank like B of A. And these aren't small accomplishments given the current economy and the current state of the banking sector. JPMorgan Chase just reported a nearly 4% year-over-year drop in total revenue for the first quarter. At Wells Fargo, total revenue dropped 1.4%. For B of A to see rise in revenue of 5.5% year over year is impressive. So why did B of A investors run for the hills after earnings like this were announced on Wednesday morning? The only explanation is that B of A missed Wall Street expectations. Analysts had predicted earnings per share of $0.22, and B of A's came in at $0.20. For two measly cents then, investors abandoned ship at B of A and took the rest of the big banks along with them. For good measure, the markets went down with the ship, too. This is an absurd outcome of, all things considered, a good quarter for B of A. Analyst expectations are just that, expectations. Educated guesses at best. Random opinions at worst. The good news is, the market seems to have gotten hold of itself: B of A stock is up 1.49% on the day. Maybe by the end of today, B of A investors will have gotten back some reasonable amount of the money they lost in this week's market panic. As always, Fools, remember that you're in this for the long term. Although the share prices in your favorite companies may gyrate up and down on a short-term basis, your eye is on the far horizon. So long as the companies you're invested have solid fundamentals, and you still believe in their mission, have faith that your money is in the right place. Looking for in-depth analysis on Bank of America? Check out this Motley Fool premium report -- expertly researched and written by top Foolish banking analysts Anand Chokkavelu and Matt Koppenheffer. They'll help you lift the veil on the bank's operations, and give you three reasons to buy and three reasons to sell along the way. For immediate access to this eye-opening report, simply click here now. The Death of the PC The days of paying for costly software upgrades are numbered. The PC will soon be obsolete. And BusinessWeek reports 70% of Americans are already using the technology that will replace it. Merrill Lynch calls it "a $160 billion opportunity." Computing giants including IBM, Yahoo!, and Amazon are racing to be the first to cash in on this PC-killing revolution. Yet a small group of little-known companies have a huge head start. Get the full details on these companies, and the technology that is about to destroy the PC, in a free video report from The Motley Fool. Simply enter your email address below to watch this stunning video. .Privacy / Legal Information. . Fool contributor John Grgurich owns shares of Citigroup and JPMorgan Chase. Follow John's dispatches from the bleeding heart of capitalism on Twitter @TMFGrgurich. The Motley Fool recommends Wells Fargo. The Motley Fool owns shares of Bank of America, Citigroup, JPMorgan Chase, and Wells Fargo. Try any of our Foolish newsletter services free for 30 days. We Fools may not all hold the same opinions, but we all believe that considering a diverse range of insights makes us better investors. The Motley Fool has a simply cracking disclosure policy. Read/Post Comments (4) | Recommend This Article (3) EmailPrintFeedback6. Obama Has a Trick up His Sleeve Imagine a fuel that's 27% cleaner than gasoline and costs just $1.50 a gallon. Developing it is one of the President's top priorities for his second term. But it's already out there on the highways, in millions of vehicles. And it's already making savvy investors rich... A new video report reveals the surging company that controls the only green energy solution that actually works. Ford, Volvo, and Shell are jumping on board — you can too, if you act now. Click here to watch this game-changing video! Comments from our Foolish Readers Help us keep this a respectfully Foolish area! This is a place for our readers to discuss, debate, and learn more about the Foolish investing topic you read about above. Help us keep it clean and safe. If you believe a comment is abusive or otherwise violates our Fool's Rules, please report it via the Report this Comment icon found on every comment. Report this Comment On April 19, 2013, at 3:51 PM, ChristianRiley wrote: Nice perspective in this article. It is a reflection of the reflex sell on anything bad behavior that is often quite common. Report this Comment On April 19, 2013, at 9:51 PM, Burstedbladder wrote: Let them crumble to the ground. No love lost if you ask me. The BofA are nothing but a bunch of corrupt banks robbing the people left and right. Let them fall, and let them fall hard. Chase and Wells Fargo can go to. Report this Comment On April 20, 2013, at 12:14 AM, angiedecay wrote: I have no pity for this bank at all. Nothing but a bunch of corrupt thieves if you ask me. Report this Comment On April 20, 2013, at 7:25 AM, gb3tay wrote: To those of you who have made comments regarding letting B of A fall, this article was not about that. The article actually identified that B of A is doing well. The ones who suffered last week are the people who hold the company stock, people like you who invest. So, thank you for wishing us so much ill will. Should it return to being a $50 stock one day, I will be happy to have had a purchase price of $16 and will be happy to have held it. Add your comment. Your Fool username will be displayed with your comment. Please be respectful with your comments. Review our Fool's Rules. Your comment may be delayed up to 15 minutes Compare Brokers E*TRADE Trade Free for 60 Days &amp; Get up to $500. Open an Account TD Ameritrade. Open Account Fidelity Investments more info Fool Disclosure Today's Market updated 11 hours agoSponsored by: DOW 14,547.51 10.37 0.07% S&amp;P 500 1,555.25 13.64 0.88% NASD 3,206.06 39.70 1.25% . Create My Watchlist Go to My Watchlist You don't seem to be following any stocks yet! Better investing starts with a watchlist. Now you can create a personalized watchlist and get immediate access to the personalized information you need to make successful investing decisions. . Data delayed up to 5 minutes You Might Like... 1.BAC - Will Bank of America Abandon Its Promises? 2.CAT - The 1 Thing You Need to Watch When Caterpillar Reports Earnings 3.^DJI - Are Bonds Announcing a Stock Market Correction? 4.^DJI - IBM Almost Singlehandedly Sabotages the Dow 5.^DJI - IBM and GE Mask the Dow's Strength . Related Tickers 4/19/2013 4:01 PM BAC $11.66 +0.22 +1.92% Bank of America Co… CAPS Rating: JPM $47.23 +0.59 +1.27% JPMorgan Chase &amp; C… CAPS Rating: WFC $36.69 +0.42 +1.16% Wells Fargo CAPS Rating: . . .</Msg><Username>haideh00</Username><Timestamp>1366462084303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366462104762-18</Id><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Msg>Money and profits are being manufactured out of thin air in quantities that would even impress Howard Roarke (Ms. Rand short-suited that hero by giving him such a harsh surname; I've taken the liberty of adding the 'e' to give him the Schuey-like continental flair he deserves, no, EARNED). Now heroes are being manufactured so quickly and cheaply that soon we will all be heroes, and pigs and dogs and goats and sheep will be wearing laurels too. ROTFLMAO</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366462615679-19</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well liberty Obama - did not serve Clinton did not serve Biden - did not serve Pelosi - did not serve all those listed - did not do nothing - in defense of this country - either Clinton got free sex in the oval office - opps wait - he didn't sex with that woman - he just had something else .!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1366462615679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366463091058-20</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Feds give out of date error filled information ... Reddit gets government contract to run FBI...fat Jan wins blue ribbon for pie recipe.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1366463091058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463195718-21</Id><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Msg>It took President Obama to kill Bin ladin and bringing justice to the American people which George Bush failed. George Bush's personal aganda was to kill Sudan Hussein no matter at what cost, over 5000 soliders died, because he was only focused on revenge to his fathers failed attampt to kill Hussein in the golf war....</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463542054-22</Id><Title>Congress: "Happy Birthday, Columbine!"</Title><Msg>We know what you really wanted, so we wrapped that hysterical gun control bill in a Hefty and mailed it early to be sure it would arrive ahead of the party. You won't need a knife to cut the cake, either; just use the enclosed AR-15 with 30-round clip and blow it to pieces (hope you didn't invite more than 30 kids!). Sorry we couldn't attend, but we'll be celebrating with you in spirit! ROTFLMAO we're reconvening so we can give ourselves a raise to cover the shipping and handling. Special thanks to Wayne Lapierre for his generous donation of 101 rifles to the Senate; we sent you the extra one.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366463542054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366463673292-23</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama did not kill nothing - the military - did . .!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>da23533</Username><Timestamp>1366463673292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463694111-24</Id><Title>Gresham's Law as applied to message boards -</Title><Msg>Inane posts drive out thoughtful posts.</Msg><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1366463694111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366464062154-25</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know the Middle East is a confusing place, but 'Sudan' Hussein? Wasn't he the leader of Labia? Or was that Murmur Getoffme? I'm gonna give Coffee Ann-Ann a call. ROTFLMAO Maybe he and his pal Bunkie Moon can sort this out.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366464062154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:21:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366464482673-26</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boston's finest conduct most expensive house-to-house search in history, come up 40 yards short of a win, give the 'all-clear' signal, and a few hours later another average homeowner is promoted to hero. I heard a rumor that shutupstellas was in line for the Medal of Honor until his HOA killed it by telling Congress about the sketchy characters coming and going from his end-unit condo at all hours. ROTFLMAO they gave some pretty gripping testimony about the odor, too.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366464482673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366464713373-27</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am long on BAC, however I didn't lose a thing. Here's the secret. You lose nothing until you sell. You hold until the price goes above the purchase price and than sell if you like. I'm waiting for the big bucks. I bought at $6.28 and waiting fo $38. I have years to wait however long it takes.</Msg><Username>bondholder44</Username><Timestamp>1366464713373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366464731878-28</Id><Title>learn the art of BASHING. BARRIESNIGHTMARE6 on BCCI board (REAL PRO)</Title><Msg>TAKE A LOOK</Msg><Username>candscam6</Username><Timestamp>1366464731878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366464827769-29</Id><Topic><Title>Gresham's Law as applied to message boards -</Title><Username>jefatkinson</Username><Timestamp>1366463694111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:14:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO "You talking to ME? Are you talking to ME?" Go Fibonacci book value cash reserve margin dollar average yourself!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366464827769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366465081236-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The subject is George Bush. Try to stay focused.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1366465081236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366465298008-31</Id><Title>MF Global up 57% yesterday on news</Title><Msg>and why not? ROTFLMAO if you can shoot an entire city full of holes and it comes back even stronger, winner, why wouldn't a Ponzi shot full of holes be seen as The Comeback Kid? ROTFLMAO speaking of which, anybody seen my old friend Jon?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366465298008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366466593500-32</Id><Title>Ex DuPont CEO Heads Up SECOND WORST COMPANY IN AMERICA!</Title><Msg>Chad Holliday Sits On Top the Pyramid of the Second Worst Company in America. The WEAK IN REVIEW Good Morning, Bonjour, Guten Tag, Readers. No surprise. Consumers in America have voted Bilk of America the second worst company in the country in an annual survey Hmmmm...The top guy in the organisation is the Chairman of the Board of Directors of Bank of America Corporation. Now who happened to become a Director in 2009 and then Chairman in 2010? Why, none other than the erstwhile Chairman &amp; CEO of the most unethical, corrupt chemical conglomerate in the world...Chad O. Hollliday, Jr. Given the DuPont backdrop of environmental crimes, cover-ups involving toxic, cancer-causing Teflon chemicals, fraud in litigation, fraud in consumer products (Imprelis, Tell Us!), criminal price-fixing, we are sure Mr. Holliday has made some fine contributions to the reputation of Bilk of America. For long suffering shareholders of BAC, the question is: When are they really going to get serious about cleaning up this foul, fraud-infested financial institution? Merely THE WEAK IN REVIEW digitally penned by one individual investor and long-time student of the disreputable DuPont...funfun..</Msg><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1366466593500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:03:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366466771626-33</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's amazing that there's this level of research on Bush, and nothing on Obama, except for his friendship with, and sponsorship by, known domestic terrorist bombers, his marxist parents and mentors, and his cabal of useful idiots writing things about Bush to deflect attention from Obama's troubled, heavily concealed and protected past.</Msg><Username>obamalipsync</Username><Timestamp>1366466771626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:06:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366466983817-34</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They started the repurchase plan, fewer shares on the market, supply and demand, simple economics, it only goes up from here.</Msg><Username>want2besailing</Username><Timestamp>1366466983817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467081186-35</Id><Topic><Title>MF Global up 57% yesterday on news</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366465298008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:41:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO he freeh-ed a lotta people, but it seems the good, they die young. I just turned around, and he was gone.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366467081186</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467941108-36</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bottom line is that at least He served as did many of us. Fact remains that most in this joke of an (alleged)"administration" did not, would not, and they are nothing more than paper-hanging parasites themselves. BAC is doing very well considering the dilemma created by that POS named Ken Lewis. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366467941108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366468007661-37</Id><Title>Boston bombers 4 killed 180 plus injured</Title><Msg>Boston police/FBI 1killed 1 in custody..........#$%$ is everyone in Boston so happy about..........shouldnt of happened in the first place.........the authorities and gov let their guard down.........the cost of capture is great in death/injured</Msg><Username>kramerclyde</Username><Timestamp>1366468007661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468143794-38</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but thanks to brilliant research by GOP scientists like Donald Trump and Joe Arpaio, the massive cover-up was exposed, and Obama was impeached. Gosh, but history is fun when you get to write it yourself!</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366468143794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468241791-39</Id><Topic><Title>BAC HAD A BREAKOUT TODAY</Title><Username>stockineer</Username><Timestamp>1363740659980</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 20:50:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The report today is not that positive...The major support of the 10-month trendline had broken after earnings. The next level of defense is $11, which is quite strong but if it breaks a head and shoulders top will be confirmed which predicts a move to $9. Certainly $10 is in the mix and should offer good support. Good luck guys, updated charts and discussion is on Stockineer.</Msg><Username>stockineer</Username><Timestamp>1366468241791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469018155-40</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Feds super computer gets stuck in the online Orvis catalog fly fishing section while trying to match hat worn by bomber...delays capture. This morning MIT professor tells Fox News blames social media for ruining the lives of people who are identified as the bomber while Psychologist tells Fox party after #2 capture and twitter will help relieve PTSD...lol</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1366469018155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469267958-41</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"....searching social media for people who may wear baseball caps and hikinmg gear like shoes and backbacks"? You're looking for my daughter....she's probably not answering up because REI is running a special on climbing gear. She's an anti-social climber and you won't get far with the old pina colada gambit, but she'll fall for a Sierra Torpedo every time, especially if Elmo's buying.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366469267958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469547386-42</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROTFLMAO ouch! Look, I could never match your terse genius, so I have to use lots of words and can't seem to string them together in ways that please all the numbnuts all the time. Sorry.....but not very.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366469547386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366470083399-43</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greg Maddux strikes out in real estate...loses 20% on a Spanish Trails home he purchased in 1996.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1366470083399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366470554848-44</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George Bush is no longer the president.</Msg><Username>day.old_donut</Username><Timestamp>1366470554848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:09:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366470733922-45</Id><Topic><Title>The desperation of the left to deny yet another Obama failure is most telling</Title><Username>kerrywaffle</Username><Timestamp>1366467942615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:25:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spot on! "Allowed" is the key work. Exactly correct. Allowing his muuuuzzzzlim friends is just what is happening. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366470733922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471207287-46</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama gave the final order from the situation room in the white house to kill Bin Ladin...That is what history will remember him by.....Also, Obama will be known as one of the greatest commander and chief of the military....George Bush will be rememebered as a commander and chief who failed to catch Bin Ladin because his priority was to fight his personel vengeance to get Sudan Hussein and in process got over 5000 american killed..... He refused to go after Bin Ladin in Afganistan because Bin Ladin was a family friend.....</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366471207287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471247515-47</Id><Topic><Title>Your thoughts on why is BAC up today?</Title><Username>davidelliotnyc</Username><Timestamp>1366406061439</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:14:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Wanda": It is not the Stock,..it is the stock manipulators that are doing this. Hedge funds are ALLOWED to do this by a apathetic, job seeking group at SEC, however, they are controlled by politicians who have their own money with the same hedge funds that do this. It IS a huge casino, and one cannot figure the outcome in such situations. You might want to look at ETF's. BAC will be fine in time. Doing very well, but long term is a requirement. As the PPS gets higher, the hedgies control less number of shares. Share buyback now in progress, means less shares for the hedgies also. Future Stock price looks very promising. Rated a strong buy at all analysts locations. GL.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366471247515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472027986-48</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quite correct. And they got the "INTEL" from the agencies who were ordered to get it by "W". Obama simply took the grandstand, used the INTEL gathered BY "W", then as always claimed the credit. He is a joke of a CIC.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366472027986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366472159424-49</Id><Title>Mark Twain</Title><Msg>A banker is a fellow who lends you his umbrella when the sun is shining, but wants it back the minute it begins to rain.</Msg><Username>fivestarsam</Username><Timestamp>1366472159424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472577202-50</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RTFLMFAO!! What a deluded Fox gorging fool!! The joke is you, fool!</Msg><Username>zdz.dedd</Username><Timestamp>1366472577202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472588819-51</Id><Topic><Title>One of the terrorists traveled to parts unknown last year, what was obama doing in pakistan in 1984?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366417144120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is a "closet muuuzzz'lim" socialist. As a so called "community organizer", his trip was paid for by others/taxpayers of course. Issue is, he traveled on a Indonesian and/ or British passport. Hmmm, how do you get that if you are an American. MSM hides facts. FACT!</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366472588819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472750692-52</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was it the same INTEL that Bush used to attack Iraq because he was looking for Wapon Of Mass Destruction...The INTEL that helped Obama find Bin Ladin had President Obama"s administration corrdinating the operation and not George Bush's people</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366472750692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366472867338-53</Id><Topic><Title>One of the terrorists traveled to parts unknown last year, what was obama doing in pakistan in 1984?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366417144120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"FACT" RTFLMFAO!! A fact to you is what you just heard on Fox!! Lying Tea Bag Jackass!!</Msg><Username>zdz.dedd</Username><Timestamp>1366472867338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473106521-54</Id><Topic><Title>One of the terrorists traveled to parts unknown last year, what was obama doing in pakistan in 1984?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366417144120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIBTURD! Get your facts straight. Take your meds before you attempt to Post here. To remain in denial is a symptom of your obvious disorder. Which liquor store do you go to to cash yo' wef'air check. LMAO!</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366473106521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473307258-55</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Part of the judicial INTEL. Weapons of mass destruction were seen being sent to Syria.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366473307258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473370230-56</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your name calling is clearly demonstrative of what a misanthropic libturd you are. No doubt a minority on we'fair. Go away little turd.</Msg><Username>dfaduke</Username><Timestamp>1366473370230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366473415862-57</Id><Topic><Title>Orange haired fanatic right-winger lunatics at it again.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387411372</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:03:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Russian boys are done. zevoter and dfaduke are next.</Msg><Username>zdz.dedd</Username><Timestamp>1366473415862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366475461537-58</Id><Title>The desperation of right-wing liars to continue slandering Obama's successes is most telling</Title><Msg>The mindless right-wing fools continue on with their incessant stupidity by telling the same pathetic lies that they told before Obama's re-election. The educated and informed voters knew not to believe the right-wing liars then, so what -- other than desperation -- would drive the liar right-wing fools to keep telling the same pathetic lies now?</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475461537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:31:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366475593661-59</Id><Title>Do unto the Tea Baggers before they do unto you</Title><Msg>It's time to put an end to the lies and stupidity.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475593661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366475899366-60</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did the truth hurt you, boy? What you say has been said a thousand times before you in the exact same words. You are a mindless parrot stooge. Blather on, boy.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475899366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366475995008-61</Id><Topic><Title>George Bush went to Iraq after Bin Ladin who was responsible for the bombing of the world trade center from Afganistan...</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366463195718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lying idiot fool.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475995008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476490861-62</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IDIOT</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366476490861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366476593260-63</Id><Topic><Title>One of the terrorists traveled to parts unknown last year, what was obama doing in pakistan in 1984?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366417144120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been busted, fool. Accept it. Now, move on. Go back to the John Birch board.</Msg><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366476593260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:49:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366476844873-64</Id><Title>Robin Williams on Boston</Title><Msg>ROBIN WILLLIANS MADE THIS SPEECH IN NEW YORK . The Plan! Robin Williams, wearing a shirt that says 'I love New York ' in Arabic. Robin Williams' plan...(Hard to argue with this logic!) "I see a lot of people yelling for peace but I have not heard of a plan for peace. So, here's one plan": 1) 'The US, UK , CANADA and AUSTRALIA will apologize to the world for our 'interference' in their affairs, past &amp; present. You know, Hitler, Mussolini, Stalin, Tojo, Noriega, Milosevic, Hussein, and the rest of those 'good 'ole' boys', we will never 'interfere' again. 2) We will withdraw our troops from all over the world, starting withGermany , South Korea , the Middle East, and the Philippines . They don't want us there. We would station troops at our borders. No one allowed sneaking through holes in the fence. 3) All illegal aliens have 90 days to get their affairs together and leave. We'll give them a free trip home. After 90 days the remainder will be gathered up and deported immediately, regardless of whom or where they are from. They're illegal!!! France will welcome them. 4) All future visitors will be thoroughly checked and limited to 90 days unless given a special permit!!!! No one from a terrorist nation will be allowed in. If you don't like it there, change it yourself and don't hide here. Asylum would never be available to anyone. We don't need any more cab drivers or 7-11 cashiers. 5) No foreign 'students' over age 21. The older ones are the bombers. If they don't att end classes, they get a 'D' and it's back home baby. 6) The US, UK , CANADA and AUSTRALIA will make a strong effort to become self-sufficient energy wise. This will include developing non-polluting sources of energy but will require a temporary drilling of oil in the Alaskan wilderness. The caribou will have to cope for a while. 7) Offer Saudi Arabia and other oil producing countries $10 a barrel for their oil. If they don't like it, we go someplace else. They can go somewhere else to sell their production. (About a week of the wells filling up the storage sites would be enough.) 8) If there is a famine or other natural catastrophe in the world, we will not 'interfere..' They can pray to Allah or whomever, for seeds, rain, cement or whatever they need. Besides most of what we give them is stolen or given to the army.. The people who need it most get very little, if anything. 9) Ship the UN Headquarters to an isolated island someplace. We don't need the spies and fair weather friends here. Besides, the building would make a good homeless shelter or lockup for illegal aliens. 10) All Americans must go to charm and beauty school. That way, no one can call us 'Ugly Americans' any longer. The Language we speak is ENGLISH...learn it...or LEAVE. Now, isn't that a winner of a plan? The Statue of Liberty is no longer saying 'Give me your tired, your poor, your huddled masses.' She's got a baseball bat and she's yelling, 'you want a piece of me?' '</Msg><Username>carburetorkid</Username><Timestamp>1366476844873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366478278226-65</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please use proper military terminology: in the Great War That Wasn't A War (ever read the actual text of the so-call Paris Peace Accords?) we referred to them as Johnny TearAss costumes. ROTFLMAO I recall busting the chops of one of America's aces by asking him whether he planned to wear it downtown in the hopes of scoring a free shot of leg, or if he was just going Trick-Or-Treating (late October of '72). Officers are certainly gentlemen, but sometimes they forget, and it becomes the duty of a lowly airman to bring such oversights to their attention in a diplomatic way.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366478278226</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366478663324-66</Id><Topic><Title>The desperation of right-wing liars to continue slandering Obama's successes is most telling</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475461537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:31:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hatred drives right-wingers. Hatred and stupidity. They live to hate, and to spew fanatic stupidity.</Msg><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1366478663324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366479321310-67</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey sailor! I was wondering where you'd gone! Ironbar_2 still hasn't been able to bring himself to thank me for my service or share the details of his. Maybe he's just awed by my combat experience, or maybe our fearless, I mean ferrous, swabbe is just shy, but I'm eager to hear more from him. Granted, I may have given more than some (like George) but it was still a lot less than others (like the 50,000 wounded or the 600,000 injured or the hundreds of POWS). Yep, service is service alright. If you're wondering why I'm addressing him using nautical honorifics, that's easy. ROTFLMAO I can tell he was in the Navy by the cut of his jibberish and the way he handles his dinghy.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366479321310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366479760272-68</Id><Topic><Title>Mark Twain</Title><Username>fivestarsam</Username><Timestamp>1366472159424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five stars and two thumbs up! He's been my main man since I encountered him in grade school (like, at least 5 years ago) but I haven't thought of this particular barb in ages. Thanks.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366479760272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366480038138-69</Id><Title>PHONY BOSTONIANS SING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM LIKE THEY ARE GREAT AMERICANS</Title><Msg>Boston has the highest rate of Segregated Schools in the country, and has among the highest rate of Alcoholism. Because they have Harvard University, (where most students are out of state), the myth persists these are a smart and noble people. Yeah! Right!</Msg><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1366480038138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366480129042-70</Id><Topic><Title>Facts before right wingers = pearls before swine</Title><Username>ebonics4gfy</Username><Timestamp>1365387309689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:15:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The brainwashed wing-nut morons qualify for maggot feed. Nothing else.</Msg><Username>hd.callahan</Username><Timestamp>1366480129042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366480290552-71</Id><Topic><Title>Ex DuPont CEO Heads Up SECOND WORST COMPANY IN AMERICA!</Title><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1366466593500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As an off and on again shareholder and trader in BAC shares, we are more than mildly curious: How did Chad Holliday become Chairman of this bank? As for as we know Holliday who harks from Nashville, Tennessee had no prior banking or financial experience. In his official biography posted before his departure from the DuPont Company on DuPont's Webbed-Site, Holliday is recorded as possessing only an undergraduate degree in "industrial engineering" from the U. of Tenn. He has no earned advanced degrees or further formal education. When Holliday grabbed power at DuPont in 1998, E. I. du Pont de Nemours and Company was the largest, most powerful chemical enterprise in the world. By 2008, a much shrunken and mismanaged DuPont had dropped dramatically to a number 10 rank in revenues amongst global chemical concerns. Shares of this beleaguered chemical Company hit a peak of 83 and change in May of 1998. By the time Hollliday departed from DuPont, DD had fallen off the cliff, closing @ 33.67 at the end of December, 2009. DD trades in the forties currently. How are the interests of BAC shareholders being served today by Chad Holliday qua Chairman of the Board? Merely the query of one individual retail investor...funfun..</Msg><Username>funfundvierzig</Username><Timestamp>1366480290552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366481185673-72</Id><Title>Radicalized Repugnant Republicans, i.e., RRR is the new KKK</Title><Msg>A turd by any other name . . . .</Msg><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1366481185673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366481558086-73</Id><Topic><Title>The desperation of right-wing liars to continue slandering Obama's successes is most telling</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475461537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:31:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their deep rooted bigotry that has passes from generation to gerneration....they will have to explain to their gods their hatered toward their fellow humen race....</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366481558086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366481713742-74</Id><Topic><Title>PHONY BOSTONIANS SING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM LIKE THEY ARE GREAT AMERICANS</Title><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1366480038138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Relax! I'm in the neighborhood.....I'll keep them in line! ROTFLMAO Harvard never COULD compete with UMass in anything but quiche-and-brie pie throwing; even the 'good' brother could only get a scholarship on the outlying Dartmouth campus.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366481713742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366482076515-75</Id><Title>I quit my job...</Title><Msg>Insurance billing 14 years for a gastro Dr. He comes in last week ranting and raving about the salaries he pays the staff, how tough things are, etc. etc. Mind you I know exactly what the numbers are. Lets also put out there he's on his third marriage with alimony and child support. Lets also throw out there I've been to his 8,000 sf home complete with rock waterslide, Jacuzzi, etc. Now I don't mind anyone making their way in this world and buying what you want but when you throw my 9 hour workdays in my face like I'm some sort of welfare case for you..that's it. So he comes in and announces in his #$%$ off manner that if people don't like the idea of salary cuts, the door is right there. So I pack my things and go. 2 days later I'm getting messages from him about insurance billing issues. Wow.</Msg><Username>medtechins</Username><Timestamp>1366482076515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366482196388-76</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't need to advertise; I figured THAT out after reading two or three of your posts about a year ago, right before I stuck you in my iggy box. I don't know who gave you a thumbs-down, but I swear it wasn't me. Thumbs up and thanks for making my day, and for making me ROTFLMAO. Glad I took you out today, but back in you go now.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366482196388</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366484194564-77</Id><Title>all i have the say it would better in the eyes of world to see bac the bigest and the best!15 christmas time!2013!!!</Title><Msg>ok</Msg><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1366484194564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366484574994-78</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geo. Bush served the interests of his father's business partners. That's all. PERIOD! He was (is) a gutless chickenhawk like thousands of other Republican sons with deep-pocketed daddies of influence who bought their way out of REAL military service. No doubt about it. The 1% do not permit their progeny to be put in harm's way. The cannon fodder middle and working class patriots' sons and daughters do the fighting and dying in this country. Always have. Always will.</Msg><Username>mr.whizzard</Username><Timestamp>1366484574994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485975338-79</Id><Topic><Title>PHONY BOSTONIANS SING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM LIKE THEY ARE GREAT AMERICANS</Title><Username>bejupete</Username><Timestamp>1366480038138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:47:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your right, I didn't see any American Indians....</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366485975338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:26:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366487302289-80</Id><Topic><Title>I quit my job...</Title><Username>medtechins</Username><Timestamp>1366482076515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:21:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll say, wow! ROTFLMAO Schuey never told us he was a doctor, and he's not known for his modesty.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366487302289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366488589789-81</Id><Title>I now have a 3rd Timex glow-in-the-dark wrist watch...</Title><Msg>I can see that the trailer park residents are not amused as I drive by in my AMC Pacer.</Msg><Username>jedbs2</Username><Timestamp>1366488589789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366489352876-82</Id><Topic><Title>all i have the say it would better in the eyes of world to see bac the bigest and the best!15 christmas time!2013!!!</Title><Username>ron.wallach</Username><Timestamp>1366484194564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was wondering what happen if they made a decision to bankrupt the countrywide in2011. The downside is perhaps around 40 billion dollars of damage, and then you can get your hand clean. Unlike now, you already spend 40 billion on litigation claims, and you still don't know how further it will go. Monihan was a lawyer before he get into high rank executive??? , and I don't think his vision of indefinite settlement is correct for this one.</Msg><Username>wyuli007</Username><Timestamp>1366489352876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366490340953-83</Id><Topic><Title>Robin Williams on Boston</Title><Username>carburetorkid</Username><Timestamp>1366476844873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:54:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a fake Williams is not this smart. check snopes</Msg><Username>barack_crock</Username><Timestamp>1366490340953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366492557219-84</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spanish Trails? Is that anywhere near Air Stream?</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366492557219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366492586731-85</Id><Topic><Title>Radicalized Repugnant Republicans, i.e., RRR is the new KKK</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1366481185673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry, but you've been placed on my IGNORE LIST!! No sence responding, because you IGNORED!</Msg><Username>bondholder44</Username><Timestamp>1366492586731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366492868576-86</Id><Topic><Title>Mark Twain</Title><Username>fivestarsam</Username><Timestamp>1366472159424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:35:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry, you don't even qualified for "ONE" star. But you have qualified for my IGNORED LIST!!</Msg><Username>bondholder44</Username><Timestamp>1366492868576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493026189-87</Id><Topic><Title>One of the terrorists traveled to parts unknown last year, what was obama doing in pakistan in 1984?</Title><Username>zevoter22</Username><Timestamp>1366417144120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:19:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry, but this is the BAC message board and because of that you have been laced on my IGNORE LIST!</Msg><Username>bondholder44</Username><Timestamp>1366493026189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493788200-88</Id><Topic><Title>Bush Jr. served as mascot in Alabama Air National Guard. Monkey suit provided.</Title><Username>sebedeciste</Username><Timestamp>1366387037876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could you see Bush flying a plane !! But he couldn't have done as much damage as he did as President.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1366493788200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366494923783-89</Id><Title>Democrats Terrified Of Terrorism Election Impact</Title><Msg>Realize that country knows they don't protect Americans from Islamic radicals.</Msg><Username>libblibb</Username><Timestamp>1366494923783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496204736-90</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Terrified Of Terrorism Election Impact</Title><Username>libblibb</Username><Timestamp>1366494923783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It took a democrats President to kill Bin ladin, and help kill Kadafi.....The American public rewarded President Obama by reelecedt him for the second term......LOL..Repulicans are all talk and nothing but talk...LOL</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366496204736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366496461877-91</Id><Title>I'M BACK IN @ $11.29 , AND I WANT TO BUY MORE SCALE - UP IF YOU SHAREHOLDERS CAN HELP ME....</Title><Msg>I love to buy strength , so lets get this stock moving up again over 412.00 n its way to $15.00 this year for openers......</Msg><Username>flashywildwest</Username><Timestamp>1366496461877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366496651747-92</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Terrified Of Terrorism Election Impact</Title><Username>libblibb</Username><Timestamp>1366494923783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dream on, #$%$. GOP racists have already lost the next election and the one after that.</Msg><Username>smithjoel5</Username><Timestamp>1366496651747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366497617664-93</Id><Title>The best thing the American public had done was to elect Clinton over George Bush senior who served only one term in office.</Title><Msg>The worst thing the American public did was elect George Bush junior who not only destroyed the American Economy but the worlds Economy....His stronge arm tactics caused the oil price rise to triple degits.... His lack of leadership caused the economy to collapes...</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366497617664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366498163351-94</Id><Topic><Title>The best thing the American public had done was to elect Clinton over George Bush senior who served only one term in office.</Title><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366497617664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:40:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the record Gore had 600,000 more votes but the republican supreme court still gave it to Bush, then you had the Ohio 04 voting problem.</Msg><Username>sirifuture</Username><Timestamp>1366498163351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366498264905-95</Id><Title>Thanks to George Bush, certain middle east countries used their new found wealth to found their terrorist operation all over the world</Title><Msg>Bush accomplished his Presidency aganda as planned...without any consideration to the Americam people, he helped his billionaire friends enjoy their profits from triple degit oil price gains, while American died in the battle field..</Msg><Username>delljohn70</Username><Timestamp>1366498264905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366501782253-96</Id><Topic><Title>why they robbed 7-11 store? - that was idiotic</Title><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1366392827772</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:33:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They" weren't the imported terrorists, just some homegrown yummies (Young Urban Maggots). Like the fire at the JFK Library, totally coincidental timing, that's all.</Msg><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366501782253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366506789918-97</Id><Topic><Title>Bush served in the military, he served in the National Guard, Serving in the military is the opposite of being a draft dodger, seems like I am stating the obvious, but you have to stay the obvious with some of the people on this board.</Title><Username>ironbar_2</Username><Timestamp>1366386370105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:46:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thankfully. I didn't start the topic, I just corrected it. The topic is george Bush military service, which is a farce. He did no service. He received training and never served the country with it at all. Comparisons to other presidents or people too young to have ever been in a draft have little to do with the reality of the situation during Vietnam when there was a draft in effect.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1366506789918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366507496267-98</Id><Topic><Title>Bac back over $12 next week 10 billion buyback on the cheap great buy at $11.25</Title><Username>mistermotox74</Username><Timestamp>1366402851123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:20:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5 billion common &amp; 5billion preferred</Msg><Username>mistermotox74</Username><Timestamp>1366507496267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366514365901-99</Id><Topic><Title>shutupstellas' did predict a manufacturing recovery</Title><Username>fish2kill</Username><Timestamp>1366462104762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 08:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Several ballers have made Spanish Trails home...Tiger Woods, Latoya Jackson...the country club filed bankruptcy in 2011...lol. WOW is being carried international now,,,you would think with the Women of Wrestling we would have less violence.</Msg><Username>vieweroutrage</Username><Timestamp>1366514365901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366514705748-100</Id><Topic><Title>I'M BACK IN @ $11.29 , AND I WANT TO BUY MORE SCALE - UP IF YOU SHAREHOLDERS CAN HELP ME....</Title><Username>flashywildwest</Username><Timestamp>1366496461877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 18:21:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bad time to buy. head and shoulders pattern developed in BAC and JPM. I think there is a bit more downside here and besides p/e is outrageous. PNC and HBAN are better buys right now IMO. GLTU.</Msg><Username>jrpowell01</Username><Timestamp>1366514705748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515025400-101</Id><Topic><Title>The desperation of right-wing liars to continue slandering Obama's successes is most telling</Title><Username>f.dollarhyde</Username><Timestamp>1366475461537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:31:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What successes??????? Obama SUXXXXXXXXS!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>pfswsucks</Username><Timestamp>1366515025400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515156709-102</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats Terrified Of Terrorism Election Impact</Title><Username>libblibb</Username><Timestamp>1366494923783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will never be safe with a commie muzzie in the WH!!!</Msg><Username>pfswsucks</Username><Timestamp>1366515156709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515578401-103</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's masterful handling of the Boston situation</Title><Username>im_a_proud_american_citizen</Username><Timestamp>1366404896370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:54:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You DUMB SMUCK .... best thing Obongo did was get out of the way!!!</Msg><Username>pfswsucks</Username><Timestamp>1366515578401</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515669352-104</Id><Topic><Title>Radicalized Repugnant Republicans, i.e., RRR is the new KKK</Title><Username>j.farragut</Username><Timestamp>1366481185673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:06:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you #$%$!</Msg><Username>pfswsucks</Username><Timestamp>1366515669352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515899879-105</Id><Topic><Title>What do you call 20 inbreeding rednecks living in a lot rent doublewide?</Title><Username>sofreakinghot</Username><Timestamp>1366376596374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>freakingSNOT</Msg><Username>pfswsucks</Username><Timestamp>1366515899879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>