<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352600977633-1</Id><Topic><Title>Since Yahoo's new design looks so much like MSFT's can MSFT be in talks with Yahoo for a takeover?</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352577140778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 14:52:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think that Yahoo is going to take over Microsoft.</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1352600977633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 21:29:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352602843769-2</Id><Title>Anyone have an idea how Yahoo will liquidate its Yahoo Japan shares without tanking the stock?</Title><Msg>It would take years to get out of that position without affecting the pps.</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352602843769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 22:00:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352603653052-3</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons Marrissa</Title><Username>naples2627</Username><Timestamp>1352595468946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 19:57:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With the cash on hand and their stake in Alibaba worth over 7 to 8 billion and its holdings in Yahoo Japan about 7+ billion Yahoo is trading at its post tax cash value if these were both liquidated. This is a put in the stock price at $17. That is why Yahoo is such a huge interest to anyone looking to take it over. The value of Alibaba once it goes public is between $50 and $150 billion. If people just knew how big this company was and that they have a corner on the Chinese e-business. To put it in perspective it would be like combining Ebay, Amazon, and the top b2b site all into one company. China has turned the corner as stated by the new Premier introduced on Friday. It has changed from a manufacturing to a consumer country. This is huge for Alibaba as most Chinese will use that site for years to come because they have all the infrastructure in place to make their purchases care free. Yahoo is a $30+ stock, imo and if Alibaba announces its ipo and it is bid up as most people think look out because yahoo's stake could be worth $20 billion in just that holding. Again, all jmho</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352603653052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 22:14:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>