<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347076918014-1</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey cungsuongban..."Please share your honest vision," eh?!? Great question. As you can read from the responses from our "short resident posters," the term "honesty" ... does ... not ... compute. Mr.Market has a tendency to price these events ahead of schedule. On the other hand, if the "retail dentists/doctors" come around late to the party, opening price on 9/12...could be the same as if opening up a bottle of warm champagne. POP !! Your question is an honest one ... Longs welcome you to the 9/12 Apple party. GOOOOOOO HIGHER APPLE !!!!</Msg><Username>commander_response</Username><Timestamp>1347076918014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077039735-2</Id><Topic><Title>From the GM message board</Title><Username>rldcis</Username><Timestamp>1347066241301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:04:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are too stupid to use bell curve analogy, especially when 50% pay no taxes you idiot. Your lame reference to mathematical statics belies your scholastic ignorance and your belief in Obamanure!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347077039735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347077089111-3</Id><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Msg>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE) Per the Fiscal Q3 (Period Ending 6-30-12) Conf. Call, APPLE INC. closed their books with a TOTAL CASH of $117.2 BILLION - including CASH, Short-term Marketable Securities &amp; Long-term Marketable Securities. The TOTAL CASH BALANCE increased by $7 BILLION from the prior Quarter. APPLE INC. holds more TOTAL CASH than any corporation ever in the history of the world. A few tidbits of information from the last Conf. Call.... * iPhone usage "doubled" in Fortune 500 companies; * iPad usage "tripled" in Fortune 500 companies; * One order for the iPad was for 11,000 iPads -- enough for every student in the Mansfield, Texas School District; * Smart Homes are now using iPads in Japan; * iTunes added 12 more countries; 20 Million songs; * iTunes University has 750 New Courses; * 650,000+ Apps in App Store; * iCloud has 150+ Million users....acquired in only a few months. LOAD UP.... Ahead of the Herd -- and Ahead of the iPhone 5 LAUNCH -and- iPad Mini LAUNCH !!!!!!!!!!! INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077433938-4</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's alone with his pooch and jr of ky lube. Isn't beastialty illegal in your state musichead?</Msg><Username>mablehardestofknockers</Username><Timestamp>1347077433938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077494736-5</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long term started 2005.......doing very well.....thx Apple!!!</Msg><Username>billsjk</Username><Timestamp>1347077494736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077540522-6</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About 665 but it will definitely start drifting starting Monday. Watch n learn. LoL</Msg><Username>risc6k</Username><Timestamp>1347077540522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077616796-7</Id><Topic><Title>excellent day</Title><Username>tendulrocks</Username><Timestamp>1347075762861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:42:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next week should be lot fun for bullish people..........GL</Msg><Username>tendulrocks</Username><Timestamp>1347077616796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347077617757-8</Id><Topic><Title>I have not seen my peenus in 6 years</Title><Username>aapl20l6</Username><Timestamp>1347067221539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone else has?</Msg><Username>risc6k</Username><Timestamp>1347077617757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347078002224-9</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone 5 new LTE technology brings the fastest data services to huge customer base and carriers to sell</Title><Username>tvc7205</Username><Timestamp>1347071572869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:32:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And get sued by Samsung for the technology patents on 4g lte technology which was already stated lol this will be a massive sell off during product launch i5 = failure nothing new to market and not much change to apple</Msg><Username>gcaravousanos</Username><Timestamp>1347078002224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347078428966-10</Id><Topic><Title>FunnieBucket next 6-18-Month Market Outlook...</Title><Username>funniebucket</Username><Timestamp>1347033610211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 12:00:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could of saved a lot of time by saying that the market could go up or could go down. Lol. What a genius.</Msg><Username>applrun</Username><Timestamp>1347078428966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347078821550-11</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A week or so ago, Bob Pi$ani wrote a blog piece which I agree 100% with. It refuted the "Law of Large Numbers" myth with regards to APPLE INC. - which had been portrayed earlier in the day on the $hill-Network that he works for. On a side note, investors looking for a good LONG-TERM stock pick can note that EXXON MOBIL (XOM) never suffered the dramatic pullback that the other companies did....after rising to the $500 to $600 Billion Market Cap. Together, XOM and AAPL = Fortress Portfolio for the LONG-TERM. Like EXXON MOBIL, APPLE is very well-managed with strong fundamentals. I firmly believe that APPLE will continue innovating for DECADES to come. Furthermore, the APPLE ECOSYSTEM adds a "stealth value" to an investment in AAPL that is certainly not factored into the low TTM PE ratio. Here's Pi$ani's Blog essay about APPLE versus the "Law of Large Numbers" Myth.... Why Apple Isn't Finished Yet Published: Tuesday, 21 Aug 2012 | 2:38 PM ET I have been listening to debates on our air about Apple all morning, particularly about the fact that it is now has the largest market cap ever. The debate has been: is Apple [AAPL 680.44 4.17 (+0.62%) ] worth it? Can it keep up the innovation? On the surface, the stock is having a tough day — a rare downgrade has caused a reversal, and the stock has given up almost all of its gains from yesterday on very heavy volume. I rarely editorialize on individual stocks, but since I have been a rabid Apple user for a decade I do have a strong opinion, and the answer is, yes, they can keep going. First, one argument against AAPL is its sheer size. Very few companies have ever had market caps over $500 billion, let alone $600 billion: Exxon Mobil [XOM 89.92 0.93 (+1.05%) ], General Electric [GE 21.59 0.28 (+1.31%) ], Intel [INTC 24.19 -0.905 (-3.61%) ], Microsoft [MSFT 30.95 -0.395 (-1.26%) ] and Cisco [CSCO 19.56 -0.165 (-0.84%) ]. The argument is that these companies (with the exception of XOM) eventually fell dramatically, why shouldn't it happen to AAPL? There are several reasons: 1) Apple is not overpriced. Apple is trading at about 11 times forward earnings, at a time when the S&amp;P 500 is trading at almost 14 times forward earnings. According to Topeka Capital Markets, the three tech companies (INTC, MSFT and CSCO) were trading at an average P/E of over 80 times earnings when they passed the $500 billion level. 2) Apple has plenty of room to increase its share of the products it sells. Here's the stats: Apple share of the market for: PCs 4.7% Mobile phones 6.4% Source: IDC/Topeka Capital Yes, it has 68 percent of the tablet market, but it invented that category and it is now facing stiff competition. Compare that to the share of the market that the other $500 billion market cap tech companies had at their height: Microsoft share of PC operating systems 90% Intel share of PC processor market 80% Cisco share of networking market 70% Get it? These other guys already had thoroughly penetrated their markets when they hit those big market caps. They had nowhere to go but down. That is not the case with AAPL. 3) Apple continuously reinvents its products and is growing into new categories. The iPhone 5 is the gift that keeps on giving; millions of Apple users like myself will reflexively go out and buy it. They are working on an iPad "mini." And they may be on the verge of cracking the TV conundrum. They have tried for years to get a foothold in TV, and have fallen short. But word that they are now working on a set-top box that can deliver a cable feed, rather than a full-scale TV, may be just the right approach. Forget the hardware, create software that is linked to iTunes. The problem: it's not clear they can get buy-in from cable companies. But just wait until the numbers get worse, and cable companies realize they are losing subscribers faster than they thought. This would integrate the iPad, the iPhone and Macs with iTunes...and cable TV content. Watching anything you want on your iPhone? Heaven!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347078821550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347078851801-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why everybody hating on funnie today? Getting brutal out there.</Title><Username>riznob408</Username><Timestamp>1346964961584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:56:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is hilarious</Msg><Username>applrun</Username><Timestamp>1347078851801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347079070379-13</Id><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Msg>For you AAPL lovers/diehard, (by the way, me predicted the success of iPads, although not to this scale) you have to watch the development of AMZN products very carefully.. Hardware eventually will be cheap. (less profitable, DO I HAVE TO EXPLAIN THIS AGAIN, gawd) So it is the services,,, OK. you get the idea.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079292404-14</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most Wall Street Analysts are "behind the curve", but Brian White &amp; Gene Munster are definitely "ahead of the curve". AAPL P&amp;F CHART TARGET = $875.00 The P&amp;F Chart Price Target and my personal Technical Analysis line up almost perfectly. LOAD UP in AAPL – and Enjoy the ride higher… The AAPL pattern is a VERY BULLISH Ascending Triangle (Bull Flag). Here are the details: High = $644.00 Low = $363.32 Length of Move = $280.68 Breakout Level = $580.50 (Own AAPL ahead of NEW LAUNCHES of BOTH the iPhone5 and iPad Mini !!!!!!!! PRICE TARGET = $861.18 (Trememdous Upside -- with still a Very Low PE Valuation!!! INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347079292404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:41:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079500514-15</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like apps that solve real world problems vs the ability to hold many books in a small container.</Msg><Username>big_boy_invests</Username><Timestamp>1347079500514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079680544-16</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason market makers price the stock at over $100 is to discourage retail investor interest in buying and holding apple. stupid niave retail investors think a $100 stock is more expensive than a $5 stock or too expensive, they want to own at least 1000 shares. as stupid as it sounds that is how stupid retail investors are. a stock split is actually bullish for longs. but market makers don't want retail participation because the float is very thin. for stocks over $100 dollars mostly institutional investors like mutual funds very few retail individual particiption.</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347079680544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079738187-17</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>apple requires too much capital to trade. for 100 shares..and has low return on capital from a traders perspective.</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347079738187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:48:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079811451-18</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>capital will go where it can get the maximum return that is capitalism...and money is not in short term interests or lending to gov't at even 4% 10 year bonds. and corporations are having difficult time obtaining capital.</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347079811451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:50:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079857345-19</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>most of the traders trade the apple options. it's more volatile than the stock</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347079857345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347079956852-20</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most likely an Ignoramus that believes in Obamanure! Has no clue what is happening in the the Apple market.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347079956852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080044311-21</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the amount of trading activity on friday is so low and too much capital stuck in apple to make it worthwhile to trade the stock. you might as well have a 3 hour 4 day trading week and not waste everyone time. the market is closed on weekends because there is no business.</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347080044311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080081043-22</Id><Topic><Title>Only trader idiots believe in a stock split!</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1347073669453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>today's trading was flat all day. you might as well close the market after 12 pm EST on fridays.</Msg><Username>splittheatomf</Username><Timestamp>1347080081043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080501094-23</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HUGE DIFFERENCE -- You get what you pay for. With the cheap Kindle, you can read a book. With the iPad, you benefit from over 225,000 Apps for iPad with almost limitless uses. Wonder if Amazon ever got the ON / OFF BUTTON fixed ??? ....Geez, what an embarrassment for the Kindle debut. Meantime, the APPLE iPad is now being used and TRUSTED in many applications -- including AIRLINE COCKPITS for bad-weather, all-instrument landings. The iPad has the landing strips in detail. FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE) Per the Fiscal Q3 (Period Ending 6-30-12) Conf. Call, APPLE INC. closed their books with a TOTAL CASH of $117.2 BILLION - including CASH, Short-term Marketable Securities &amp; Long-term Marketable Securities. The TOTAL CASH BALANCE increased by $7 BILLION from the prior Quarter. APPLE INC. holds more TOTAL CASH than any corporation ever in the history of the world. A few tidbits of information from the last Conf. Call.... * iPhone usage "doubled" in Fortune 500 companies; * iPad usage "tripled" in Fortune 500 companies; * One order for the iPad was for 11,000 iPads -- enough for every student in the Mansfield, Texas School District; * Smart Homes are now using iPads in Japan; * iTunes added 12 more countries; 20 Million songs; * iTunes University has 750 New Courses; * 650,000+ Apps in App Store; * iCloud has 150+ Million users....acquired in only a few months. LOAD UP.... Ahead of the Herd -- and Ahead of the iPhone 5 LAUNCH -and- iPad Mini LAUNCH !!!!!!!!!!! INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347080501094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080661952-24</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will surely meltdown day of iphone5 fer sure</Title><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347073371920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you think SamDung got their (stole) technology from? They're not the innovators you might think they are. They just know how to copy and refine well and have the ability to produce a product quicker.</Msg><Username>trycomsen35</Username><Timestamp>1347080661952</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080662826-25</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple thank you for my new pool deck and driveway, thank you for my new roof,thank you for a ton of cash in the bank, and thank you for a 300% return this year. You changed my life.............</Msg><Username>santacruzmogul</Username><Timestamp>1347080662826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347080750133-26</Id><Topic><Title>Iphone 5 announcement on sept12</Title><Username>samman14</Username><Timestamp>1347064456925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No iphone 5 will be available this year. Apple has pulled off many unexpected tricks in the past. I can pretty much guarantee that u will not see the newest iphone on the store shelves this year. It doest make a difference in the long term with apple, but for the short term u very well may see a large dip until Q1. I am not bashing with all do respect, but I have seen this many times before. This is extremely overhyped for the time being, and I understand the excitement and anticipation for this new device. Whether the phone comes out next month or next year, the stock will blow thru 700, but not now. Watch and see.</Msg><Username>samman14</Username><Timestamp>1347080750133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347081443430-27</Id><Topic><Title>Iphone 5 announcement on sept12</Title><Username>samman14</Username><Timestamp>1347064456925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...Apple has pulled off many unexpected tricks in the past." Can you give a couple of examples?</Msg><Username>plzplzplayfaster</Username><Timestamp>1347081443430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347082644416-28</Id><Topic><Title>I have not seen my peenus in 6 years</Title><Username>aapl20l6</Username><Timestamp>1347067221539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:20:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its been in musicheads mouth that long? Come up for air buddy.</Msg><Username>mablehardestofknockers</Username><Timestamp>1347082644416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:37:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347082677997-29</Id><Topic><Title>Iphone 5 announcement on sept12</Title><Username>samman14</Username><Timestamp>1347064456925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No new iphone till october. And as always, stick with kraymer!</Msg><Username>gymkraymer</Username><Timestamp>1347082677997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347082882389-30</Id><Topic><Title>How did Iran which was progressive, liberal, democratic free country in the 1950's 1960's</Title><Username>unleashthefinalsolution</Username><Timestamp>1347068619961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iran was not progressive, liberal, democratic or free they had a Shah the Shah had SAVAK think tea party with badges. The people thought anything other than the Shah would be better they now know they were wrong.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347082882389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347083580676-31</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$600 is about right. No Youtube and Google Maps app is not good.</Msg><Username>bhtt</Username><Timestamp>1347083580676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 01:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347084541316-32</Id><Title>AH close is 680$ pin how can the SEC sit on their hand and do nothing</Title><Msg>It is clear maipulation criminal activity and the SEC could car less about this. Last week the same pin 665$ pin AH this is criminal and WS option criminal</Msg><Username>israelmichel</Username><Timestamp>1347084541316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347085167945-33</Id><Topic><Title>How did Iran which was progressive, liberal, democratic free country in the 1950's 1960's</Title><Username>unleashthefinalsolution</Username><Timestamp>1347068619961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now, their educational level is very high. 66% of undergrads are women. Shariff university is equivalent to Stanford/MIT. Their ex-VP was a woman, Ph.D. What do we have, a bullshitter like Peloser who gain from insider trading or Meddling Al-not-bright who thinks it's ok to starve Iraqi kids.</Msg><Username>argtam</Username><Timestamp>1347085167945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347085477472-34</Id><Topic><Title>Apple will surely meltdown day of iphone5 fer sure</Title><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347073371920</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've seen people who don't know how to use commas, but not knowing how to use a period is way pathetic!</Msg><Username>mrgizmo1</Username><Timestamp>1347085477472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347085595428-35</Id><Topic><Title>Where did $75B of AAPL cash go? divy? bought something? Only $25B on books</Title><Username>housedoctor66</Username><Timestamp>1347068485608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:41:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't o good bit of it overseas, due to U.S. tax constraints?</Msg><Username>mrgizmo1</Username><Timestamp>1347085595428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347086290992-36</Id><Topic><Title>AH close is 680$ pin how can the SEC sit on their hand and do nothing</Title><Username>israelmichel</Username><Timestamp>1347084541316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the big boys love taunting you.</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347086290992</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347090160967-37</Id><Topic><Title>How did Iran which was progressive, liberal, democratic free country in the 1950's 1960's</Title><Username>unleashthefinalsolution</Username><Timestamp>1347068619961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mass amounts oil was not discovered in the middle east unti the 1950's. Should be pre-1953 UK and US overthrown a an elected civilian free gov't. there is a saying what goes around comes around. In 1951, after the assassination of prime minister Ali Razmara, Dr. Mohammad Mosaddegh was elected prime minister by a parliamentary vote which was then ratified by the Shah. As prime minister, Mosaddegh became enormously popular in Iran after he nationalized Iran's petroleum industry and oil reserves. In response, the British government, headed by Winston Churchill, embargoed Iranian oil and successfully enlisted the United States to join in a plot to depose the democratically elected government of Mosaddegh. In 1953 US President Dwight D. Eisenhower authorized Operation Ajax. The operation was successful, and Mosaddegh was arrested on 19 August 1953. The coup was the first time the US had openly overthrown an elected, civilian government.[82]</Msg><Username>warforprofitsandoil</Username><Timestamp>1347090160967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347090466453-38</Id><Topic><Title>How did Iran which was progressive, liberal, democratic free country in the 1950's 1960's</Title><Username>unleashthefinalsolution</Username><Timestamp>1347068619961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:43:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iran was one of the first constitutional gov't early in the century...constitutional gov't was first by american 1776....the key is 'constitutional' gov't. Iran current doesn't have constitutional gov't and has sharia laws etc. so individual freedoms after 1979 revolution..although the shah was authoritarian it was still modern and capialist system of govt' or free enterprise..from an economic system much like the US today...except the president or shah was king. and not elected.</Msg><Username>warforprofitsandoil</Username><Timestamp>1347090466453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 03:47:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347093173765-39</Id><Topic><Title>Fundamental research method</Title><Username>bakert82</Username><Timestamp>1340465556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-06-23 11:32:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next Wednesday, September 12, 2012 is the day when the big (iPhone 5) announcement from Apple is expected. It will be interesting to see how the new bells and whistles will be viewed by the market. There seems to be universal agreement that many millions of the new phone will be sold. It is just a question of how many millions that might be. Of equal (or maybe even greater) importance will be whether a deal with China Mobile is also announced. If it is, great things could be in store for the stock. Forbes Magazine published an article speculating that a China Mobile-Apple agreement would result in an $800 price for AAPL, for example.</Msg><Username>bentuviaten</Username><Timestamp>1347093173765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 04:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347095002319-40</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stock is coming off a 25% run on bad earnings. Some pull back is expected.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347095002319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347095393474-41</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worry wart</Msg><Username>freewillybird</Username><Timestamp>1347095393474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347095631606-42</Id><Title>With no Apple TV coming, how much growth is left here?</Title><Msg>I guess everything depends on iPhone 5 and iPad sales, but can iPads maintain market share when so many low-cost tablets are coming out? iPad is still the best product, but these aggressive price wars will take their toll. As for iPhones - how many can Apple sell in one quarter? 50M? How much innovation can you put into a product that comes out every year?</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347095631606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347095696260-43</Id><Topic><Title>With no Apple TV coming, how much growth is left here?</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347095631606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>enough</Msg><Username>freewillybird</Username><Timestamp>1347095696260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347095922672-44</Id><Title>ASSDUMB BASHERS, THE SPHINCTER .....</Title><Msg>.... Cannot take the kind of reaming out you are getting. But we like reaming you out, so please keep that diarrhea assmouth running on the board! Lol!</Msg><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347095922672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:18:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347096467918-45</Id><Topic><Title>Longs set for sleepless weekend</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347067571932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:26:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot that SIRI wil upgrade from beta version to full version, and she even speaks cantonese. Oh and I think iOS6 will interface very nicely with the iCloud. And...did you know about the new CPU speed?? Burpy, your post is not very complete !! Maybe we should find out next week and not succumb to the pessimism of your short position. Get outa here!!!</Msg><Username>freewillybird</Username><Timestamp>1347096467918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347097448918-46</Id><Title>ENDED THE WEEK AT ALL TIME HIGH. EVERY SINGLE ASSBASHER AND ASSSHORT TOOK IT RIGHT UP THE ANAIL SPHINCTER STINK HOLE. LOL!</Title><Msg>GGGGGGGG</Msg><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347097448918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347098965139-47</Id><Title>Let compare iphone 5 vs Lumia 920 specification</Title><Msg>Iphone 5 dont even stand a chance</Msg><Username>zinrc</Username><Timestamp>1347098965139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347100188881-48</Id><Topic><Title>AH close is 680$ pin how can the SEC sit on their hand and do nothing</Title><Username>israelmichel</Username><Timestamp>1347084541316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, what do you think the price should be?</Msg><Username>packt25</Username><Timestamp>1347100188881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347100809926-49</Id><Topic><Title>With no Apple TV coming, how much growth is left here?</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347095631606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if and when that would ever happen then you split the stock and we double.,,we're a long ways away,,,,imo</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347100809926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347101171978-50</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Third best record qt in Apple's history and it was bad earnings? Think again as WS did and this is why Apple's stock is up.</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347101171978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347101451928-51</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell early = loss. Remember. We will be over $800 before Christmas.. Stay long and get rich..</Msg><Username>packt25</Username><Timestamp>1347101451928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347103605064-52</Id><Title>In AAPL we trust</Title><Msg>Shorts and bashers will go bust.</Msg><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1347103605064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 07:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347103962137-53</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes this happens every time and it is a small window for get into apple or to add.Apple will go back up after that.How much of a drop did you see?</Msg><Username>samsueshef3</Username><Timestamp>1347103962137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 07:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347104355869-54</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL PPS went up on 1st Iphone unveil, the remainder went down, then rebounded in the next 4-6 weeks. The 12th has more in store than "just" the I5. Don't underestimate AAPL. It won't be just another smart phone. In fact, I believe AAPL will unveil some other surprises the 12th. Last qtr AAPL did beat, but not at the level "analysts" demanded. Use your own judgement and IGNORE the analysts. Consider their perspectives, but ALWAYS revert to your own opinion. This #$%$ has been going on with AAPL for 8 years. NEVER listen to Goldman Sachs. Evil incarnate. GLTY</Msg><Username>askmeformypicture</Username><Timestamp>1347104355869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 07:39:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347104701425-55</Id><Topic><Title>With no Apple TV coming, how much growth is left here?</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347095631606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 05:13:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh let's see.... China Mobile (655 MILLION subscibers) that the new I5 with a world wide chip and 4G LTE. Oct earnings, holiday sales, Jan earnings New music service New products AAPL only has 20% share of smart phone market Do you see competition taking that away? Smart phone market penetration is about 3-4 years away. 8 years from now IF AAPL only stayed in their "rut" maybe the stock might be topped. But AAPL is too diverse and expanding to become stale. Question is....do AAPL engineers have "vision" Jobs did and be able to "wow" 3 years from now?</Msg><Username>askmeformypicture</Username><Timestamp>1347104701425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 07:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347105977287-56</Id><Topic><Title>Let compare iphone 5 vs Lumia 920 specification</Title><Username>zinrc</Username><Timestamp>1347098965139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:09:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you find iPhone 5 spec?</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347105977287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347106062937-57</Id><Topic><Title>Fundamental research method</Title><Username>bakert82</Username><Timestamp>1340465556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-06-23 11:32:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The announcement on AAPL &amp; China Mobile deal, the largest (by far) mobile device company in the world, should really give AAPL stock a big boost, as if just the idea of the iPhone 5 has not boosted it hugely already</Msg><Username>lindontomson</Username><Timestamp>1347106062937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347106684914-58</Id><Title>Dems say wars are over???</Title><Msg>Wow just heard that another bombing in Afghanistan took many lives again today. Aren't the democrats out in mass acclaiming Obama ended both wars (i.e. Iraq and Afghanistan??) Did not Obama say yesterday that by ending the wars he will have money to pass along (redistribute to us?) Of course when he says us he means them (the welfare non working illegal alien group.) But just last week Obama while in Afghanistan stated we are winning but we need to gear up for what undoubtedly will be a long fight. It seems to me they just say whatever they feel will best help them. I work for a defense contrator and know for a fact the US State Dept will have 16,000 employees in Iraq and all those employees will have protection provided by private/ex military personnel (many ex Special Ops that can make more money outside military but do the same job.) Obama never tells folks that only the spin that he has ended the wars. burnpit legion org/2011/10/private-military-firms-and-post-2011-iraq (PUT PERIOD WHERE SPACES ARE FOR LINK 2 periods one after burnpit and one after legion) The only reason Iraq is appearing to wind down is because private firms are replacing military with ex military to give said appearance.</Msg><Username>rldcis</Username><Timestamp>1347106684914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347106894086-59</Id><Topic><Title>Let compare iphone 5 vs Lumia 920 specification</Title><Username>zinrc</Username><Timestamp>1347098965139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 06:09:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drawing conclusions without facts. Congratulations!! You are not employable for compensation higher than minimum wage. Ignored...Poof!!</Msg><Username>todd0888</Username><Timestamp>1347106894086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347107687907-60</Id><Topic><Title>vote obama and get nuked by iran, vote Romney and thrive</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347106940997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:22:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another kid gets on my ignore list.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347107687907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347108469664-61</Id><Topic><Title>Dems say wars are over???</Title><Username>rldcis</Username><Timestamp>1347106684914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:18:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>War is over but fighting isn't. Even in the US there are fighting and shooting on the street from time to time but it doesn't mean there is a war going on here. 16,000 in Iraq is less than 10% of troops that we used to have over there just a couple of years ago and the cost of supporting 16,000 is far less than supporting 200,000. So please don't look at everything with a black-and-white extreme view like what our congress is doing. It isn't helpful.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347108469664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 08:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347109761455-62</Id><Title>apple stock crash burn on iphone day</Title><Msg>big money like me is moving out of this overhyped pig as you small time retail investors with your huge 100 share lots hahahhahahahahhaha get reamed iphone 5 is nothing special samsung has had all the same features for months only difference is one phone has an apple on it and is much much more expensive see ya 10% lower by friday idiots turn the machines back on mortimer has heart problems because of his orange juice futures</Msg><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347109761455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347109838296-63</Id><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Msg>looking at 692 then a decline through event as IV gets crushed on options</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110049429-64</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right pact remember analysts will get estimates wrong for jan earnings and apple has a histoic qtr</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347110049429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110119839-65</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the jan qtr will be of epic proportion mith misqiided anal;ysts apple will make you a fortune</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347110119839</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:15:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347110137381-66</Id><Title>Anyone on here ever been in Prison?</Title><Msg>Because I feel like that is where I'll be in due time. My life is not good.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347110137381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:15:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347110422773-67</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you need a&amp;&amp;wipe...to be placated for you insestuous gambling addiction..remember what happened after the bid 4S announcement....or is this your first time here limp dieck? Up big then instant 40 point drop when he takes stage you stupid mother sucker.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347110422773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347110772694-68</Id><Title>recent pole of 1000 black americans on who their voting for</Title><Msg>not one vote for Romney.I am not sure what to say.But i would like to say thats sound like a bias towards ones own race.</Msg><Username>paulvaliant2</Username><Timestamp>1347110772694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111049495-69</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just want to remind you that AMZN and GOOG are global companies too. They have cloud services too. While AAPL has been strong in school, (just like apple II computers) it is the majority (global and regular folks) that counts. I am not saying AAPL is dead right away. I am just saying you have to WATCH the trend.. Suddenly, Samsung has 70% of EU shares... It is just an example..</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347111049495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111281199-70</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL makes most of money from HW sales.. It will be facing pricing pressure. Watch the pricing on the new iPhone too. (and iPad mini for that matter.)</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347111281199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111771224-71</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you looking to get out Tuesday, Wednesday am, or Thursday am?</Msg><Username>basshead554</Username><Timestamp>1347111771224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111814545-72</Id><Topic><Title>I just looked at historical prices for the past three iPhone announcements and I think ALL of them went down on the day of the announcement (compared to 2-3 previous days beforehand) - Now I am worried!</Title><Username>alexq12789</Username><Timestamp>1347061380396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:43:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are worried when it goes down a little , but you are not worried when it is going up???</Msg><Username>samsonn25</Username><Timestamp>1347111814545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111817522-73</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>keep up the intelligent responses. you make me laugh. Can you utter a serious answer or are you still in middle school</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347111817522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112043737-74</Id><Topic><Title>AH close is 680$ pin how can the SEC sit on their hand and do nothing</Title><Username>israelmichel</Username><Timestamp>1347084541316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 02:09:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The price moved up more than 2% in a week. Which is more than bank savings account pays you in 10 years.</Msg><Username>samsonn25</Username><Timestamp>1347112043737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112126265-75</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wednesday morning</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347112126265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112132255-76</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good AM Opt...yes, I do believe you are right. Brian White is firmly grounded on the Apple story, and his own expectation could very well be conservative. I agree...epic !!! Glad you replied...I wanted your opinion on some Calls for this week. Looking to sell some Calls in the 695 to 705 range...what is your take on that...ie: is 700 realistic for this week ? Thanks in advance !!!</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347112132255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112248700-77</Id><Topic><Title>Longs set for sleepless weekend</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347067571932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:26:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just the bigger screen is a HUGE difference, they haven't changed it since 2007. 4G LTE would be good too, because it current. No ipad mini till October.</Msg><Username>samsonn25</Username><Timestamp>1347112248700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112314588-78</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just watched the interview-great stuff!!!!</Msg><Username>centerdir</Username><Timestamp>1347112314588</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:51:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112406296-79</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same here. Hopefully itll have a nice 6-7 pop premarket. I look to reenter the aapl Sept 26 long some April 2013. Plan A, sell out on earnings day into the pop and high IV. Plan B, if I missed, hold the Aprils through Ipad launch and count my blessings.</Msg><Username>basshead554</Username><Timestamp>1347112406296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:53:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112444962-80</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy and stay long for real gains!!</Msg><Username>centerdir</Username><Timestamp>1347112444962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112483309-81</Id><Topic><Title>Many of the key patents in the suit are in EVERY android touch screen phone</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1345939146260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:59:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have that little box that appears in bottom right of screen with + and - to zoom in and out</Msg><Username>samsonn25</Username><Timestamp>1347112483309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112510240-82</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>centerdir traders have to earn a living too....</Msg><Username>basshead554</Username><Timestamp>1347112510240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112529981-83</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i will reneter on friday before launch date of iphone and be up huge when they report 10 million sold over weekend long 10 jan 500 10 octber 665 40 weekly 680 at 9.00 bucks</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347112529981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112570141-84</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHICKENHAWK!</Msg><Username>rockpir</Username><Timestamp>1347112570141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112618837-85</Id><Topic><Title>What happens to all the people that using Android phones...</Title><Username>billsjk</Username><Timestamp>1345912748877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:39:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOg has moved up 46 points the last 9 trading sessions since the news.</Msg><Username>samsonn25</Username><Timestamp>1347112618837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347112832677-86</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I considered coming back Friday, but didn't feel like gambling (I bet football big as well haha). Feel like we'll get a strong consolidation after launch if aapl have a strong p/e of 17 or so, especially with iPad mini being announced into earnings. The biggest play I think will be post earnings of a significant drop from late Oct to Late Nov or early Dec. Markets should be a wreck.</Msg><Username>basshead554</Username><Timestamp>1347112832677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347113377461-87</Id><Topic><Title>21 company over 150 000 engineer ready to take one Apple g man EOY, 2013 are Samsung, Google, Microsoft, Amazon, Motorola, NOK, HTC, RIM, Asus, Dell, HP, Sony, Acer, Lenovo, ZTE, Huawei, Baidu, Xiaomi, Gionee, Meizu</Title><Username>davidnexkeck</Username><Timestamp>1347111406286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Apple's percentage of all mobile profits will probably jump above 80% once the new Iphone and Ipad Mini are released. You silly bashers act like Apple has been in a protected environment with no competition the last 5 years!!!!!!! LOL!</Msg><Username>miguelsicluna</Username><Timestamp>1347113377461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347113402456-88</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this level, don't make option trades that depend on share price going up but instead, sell the elevated IV going into the event. Since you are experienced option trader, you know what to do, don't you? But if you need any pointer, just ask.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347113402456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114353005-89</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i dont think i need any advice but thanks for your point</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347114353005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347114376579-90</Id><Title>If AAPL were afforded the same P/E as AMZN it would be trading</Title><Msg>over $14,000 a share. Even GOOG's P/E would put AAPL above $950. AAPL constantly bashed by the haters and CNBC is getting old. Funny that they have been wrong all the way up the chart to new highs now above $680.00</Msg><Username>onwardthroughthefog2003</Username><Timestamp>1347114376579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114462348-91</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you shoud understand one thing before you posted message, apple make big money then amzn!</Msg><Username>jwang1688</Username><Timestamp>1347114462348</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:27:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114567704-92</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appreciate your input. I have been looking at selling Calls between 695 thru 705. Would you have a strategy or idea to recommend ? I suppose my question here is just how far do you think the share price will run ? Thanks in advance, Pure.</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347114567704</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114588590-93</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>white is nothing but a paid apple shill if you are too stupid to see that obvious fact i pity you</Msg><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347114588590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114643963-94</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dan nathan has been wrong side of trade on apple so many times he is no longer credible get your facts straight before you post he was burned like toast wen is did his bear put spread and hasnt recovered since</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347114643963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:30:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347114730185-95</Id><Title>Brian White Apple $ 1111 nothing more than a paid apple shill</Title><Msg>have you ever watched this dope on tv no matter what facts are thrown at him he just keeps hyping the apple fruit which is about to be rotten see ya 10% lower after icrap5 launch so easy to see it coming idiots are you longs holding</Msg><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347114730185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347114810964-96</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good morning Shortinguy...wow, I feel so much better now...one of my favorite contrarian indicators you are ... lol !!! 800 here we come. Lmao</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347114810964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347115144430-97</Id><Title>Apple 750 by Friday</Title><Msg>Baby pumped for 60 point rise after iPhone 5 release..yep.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347115144430</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347116815558-98</Id><Title>P&amp;G has an 18.7 PE</Title><Msg>Will the market ever value this stellar tech innovative growth company(Apple) as highly as this stodgy slow to no growth toothpaste maker?</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347116815558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347116978951-99</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High school loser without a position..</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347116978951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117588623-100</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I needed to reply to this. Remember the drop came because people were expecting an iphone5 not the 4s. People Thought the 4s would be a disappointment because of perception. I think the feeling in the market place was there were not a enough new features and it was just a slight upgrade.</Msg><Username>ezjc79</Username><Timestamp>1347117588623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117642916-101</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets see.. What is the best selling smart phone so far? Iphone4s Was it a game changer? No! Iphone 5 will be much more of a change than 4s was! There has not been a game changer since the release of original iphone in the industry.</Msg><Username>aragre</Username><Timestamp>1347117642916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:20:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347118612941-102</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pureinvestor, how does one check for elevated or diminished IV in an option such as a call position. Thanks!</Msg><Username>toeachandall</Username><Timestamp>1347118612941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347118650893-103</Id><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Msg>Iphone 5 will be talked down as not having whatever feature. It will still sell record number in last week of September juicing this quarter's earnings. Holiday sales will also eclipse last year. iPad mini will launch in October. ChinaMobile will finally come on with the iPhone 5 working on their network. TMobile may finally come on. iPods will get refresh with the intro of the iPad mini. October earnings will be around 9.50 but Apple will guide $14 for holiday quarter. Judge will award treble damages against Samsung. Europe is no longer an issue and world economies and businesses can now start to move forward putting tailwind behind stock market. Last, the new Yahoo Message Board is awful.</Msg><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347118689029-104</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know how high it will run but the 14 day RSI is developing a bearish divergence since it peaked on 8/20 (i.e. RSI goes down while stock price goes up). It usually signals that we are near a short term top. MACD is also leveling off. That is why I said don't make option trade based on upward stock movement because the odds aren't good at this level. If you have already owned shares, selling calls is a good idea. I would sell Sept 685 to capture the maximum IV effect but if you feel more comfortable with 705, it will work too.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347118689029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119088081-105</Id><Topic><Title>P&amp;G has an 18.7 PE</Title><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347116815558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:06:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P&amp;G existed for about 150 years, sells about 200 different products used daily around the globe, pays good dividend. AAPL produces 2 products that are hot now, but that will become commoditized in due time (I'd give it 2 years). $500BIL of AAPL's market cap depends on margins of Iphone and Ipad. Even $100 decrease in margin on Iphone kills $15 of AAPL's annual profit. Can it happen, very likely when saturation hits the market. With all of the smartphone sloshing in the market, I believe we'll reach the point of saturation faster. Eating the stake first time gives you so much satisfaction. Now let's say the restaurant tries to sell you 2 more for the same dinner. Will you be satisfied more with the second and the 3rd?</Msg><Username>moneymeyka</Username><Timestamp>1347119088081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119186107-106</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can use a volatility calculator. Try google ivolatility. I can't post link here since yahoo doesn't allow link anymore.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347119186107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119497876-107</Id><Topic><Title>recent pole of 1000 black americans on who their voting for</Title><Username>paulvaliant2</Username><Timestamp>1347110772694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:26:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Recent poll of bigots revealed average IQ around room temperature. Learn to spell before you broadcast your views.</Msg><Username>ray_crucet</Username><Timestamp>1347119497876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119661411-108</Id><Topic><Title>Apple already price in $110 for ihone5 after big miss last qts earning, The verdict next week ???</Title><Username>aea_k2</Username><Timestamp>1347119291945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey aea_k2...Saturday morning...a post from you...PROVES you have no life beyond writing... ggggggggggg's !! You are SHORT / Silly postings have ZERO effect on the Market. Get Lost !!!</Msg><Username>commander_response</Username><Timestamp>1347119661411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:54:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119747658-109</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent, Pure. Now I understand why you say not to follow upward trend of stock price. Will need to look at MACD and 14 day RSI also. Yes, my plan is to sell Calls on owned shares. So your viewpoint here is with the Monthly as opposed to to next week ? Just want to make sure I follow you correctly, thanks.</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347119747658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119767823-110</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with your entire post except the treble damages. I have no faith in this judge or for that matter the entire legal system when it comes to patents. The whole verdict has already been watered down by Judge Koh's delay. I am wondering what good Apples patents are to them. The etire far east disregards them and the west lets them be infringed for years before a jury can judge then the Judge delays even more. You tell me.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347119767823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119889734-111</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, just having some fun with ya !!! I slept in this AM...was still waking up...should be lots of fun here this week...lol !!!</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347119889734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120069352-112</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to look at the IV. Sometimes the weekly IV will elevated to almost the same as monthly or even higher than monthly (an IV skew), than there is no reason to sell monthly, isn't it?</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347120069352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120685339-113</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, patents are pretty much useless based on how long it has taken to get it to trial, the likelihood of appeals delays, and the fact that but the time a verdict is rendered it's already on last year's model. Would be nice if the judge used this decision to find equal infringements on S3 and ban them now also. Now that would have some meaning. It's sad that a company can decide to steal Apple's ip and then undercut their products by flooding the market to gain market share. The WTO ought to review Samsung's practices in this case. Steal a competitor's property and then sell it as your own and as many as you can in the hopes that they can drive the original inventor out of business.</Msg><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347120685339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120685947-114</Id><Topic><Title>If AAPL were afforded the same P/E as AMZN it would be trading</Title><Username>onwardthroughthefog2003</Username><Timestamp>1347114376579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True, and at $14,000, Apple market cap will be almost $13 trillions, just $2 trillions less than the entire U.S. GDP in 2011. It will never happen. No point to keep dreaming about it.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347120685947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120795945-115</Id><Topic><Title>Apple already price in $110 for ihone5 after big miss last qts earning, The verdict next week ???</Title><Username>aea_k2</Username><Timestamp>1347119291945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:48:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how many times will you post the same Garbage? One Time Is to Many</Msg><Username>ottoman272000</Username><Timestamp>1347120795945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347120896030-116</Id><Title>Iphone 5 is amazing - first look at the phone tells me it will be a game changer</Title><Msg>the phone is sleek with larger screen and resembles Samsung Galaxy III. Clearly a revolutionary technology. You will be able to go to web, talk on the phone in the elevator (before you couldn't) and ask questions to some chick about some totally trivial stuff. For this you get to sign an agreement to shell out $80 per month at the local Verizon or ATT store for 2 year contract and $300 up front, for a total of only $2,220 over that period.</Msg><Username>moneymeyka</Username><Timestamp>1347120896030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347121073657-117</Id><Title>"Dreamers" need jobs too in this recession</Title><Msg>How can the govt help those young undocumented get jobs in this economy? Can we have them building roads and bridges for us?</Msg><Username>sirola1</Username><Timestamp>1347121073657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121148274-118</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thomas you hit exactly. We are counting on China for future growth so I am hoping there are enough upperclass chinese that want the real thing because the clones will be everywhere. I spent 2 weeks in Beijing in 2006 and you could buy a copy of anything from a Rolex to a Gucci. They had whole warehouses full of copycat goods and the Government couldn't care less.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347121148274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121204676-119</Id><Topic><Title>If AAPL were afforded the same P/E as AMZN it would be trading</Title><Username>onwardthroughthefog2003</Username><Timestamp>1347114376579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not think he is dreaming about it......just clearly stating what we know......Amazon's PE over 315 is a Joke ....Google should not be given a higher PE Then Apple.... When it comes down to it.......Apple is not being treated the way Amazon or Google are......these are just the facts</Msg><Username>ottoman272000</Username><Timestamp>1347121204676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:20:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121236170-120</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're making a great point here. iPhone 4s had zero innovation, but was still the best Apple seller ever. The question is how much juice is left? How many people are going to throw away their 4s to upgrade to 5 after one year? 4s still had the Jobs hype, but with all the smartphone phone launches, I feel like iPhone 5 is not as hyped. I'm going to get an iPhone 5 for myself, but that's because I have a 4 year old 3G that barely works. There is no way I'm buying a new phone every year. It makes no sense.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347121236170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347121437057-121</Id><Title>split stock not like BK.A</Title><Msg>apppl wil never be a berkshire hathaway so not split</Msg><Username>tommystudley</Username><Timestamp>1347121437057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121672264-122</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Software patents should be banned. There is absolutely no sense in these patents. The LAST thing we need is for Apple to have a monopoly in the smartphone market. It's bad for everybody. Apple, Samsung and everybody else need to stop this legal #$%$ complete and #$%$ Smartphones are currently way overpriced and part of it is because of these #$%$ patents.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347121672264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121883347-123</Id><Topic><Title>If AAPL were afforded the same P/E as AMZN it would be trading</Title><Username>onwardthroughthefog2003</Username><Timestamp>1347114376579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are not facts, they are fantasies. Stock prices are decided by the supply and demand of shares and not by some magical formula.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347121883347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122004456-124</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From two weeks ago my "optimistic" target for announce day was 710--with the intention of selling just below 710 and looking for a 35 to 65 point pullback over the subsequent weeks. Not sure we will make it that high now, but... To me, the chart now says: Low Bull: Monday 685 close Tuesday 691 close Wednesday 694 open, pop 699, close 688 Normal Bull: Monday 688-9 close Tuesday 695-7 close Wednesday open 701, pop 707, close 695 Extreme Bull: Monday 693 close Tuesday 702 close Wednesday open 707, pop 712, close 701 of course these are guesses and I also see sideways and down scenarios, but I`m not counting on them happening. if you are interested in what happened for the last two launches, you can read what I wrote in my journal early last Monday. I`m not sure how much relevance they have for this launch as many factors are different this time, but if you care to read it have at it. If nothing else you can check the dates out on your own chart. GLTA and give yourself a boost iPhone4 launch June 7 2010 This launch took place: 1 beginning of Summer 2 first day of developer`s conference 3 about 6 weeks before July earnings In a nut shell: 1 started a run up about 2 weeks before announcement 2 hit run up high 2 trading days before announcement 30pts/12.9% 3 2 trading days down directly before announce day 5pts/1.9% 4 gapped up slightly announcement day but then dropped 7pts/2.8% from open to close 5 bottomed 2 days later June 9 at 243 or 6.2% below the June 7 open. 6 ran up from there for a little over a week—29pts/11.8% 7 then back down to 243 in 10 trading days 8 up again, down, up, and bottomed again at 240 (from swing high June 21 at 279—or 16% tip to tip) on the last day of August (so about two months from top to bottom) where it started a longer term run up to over 400—67% 4S launch October 4 2011 1 almost middle of fall 2 2 weeks before earnings (an earnings that missed) in a nut shell: 1 AAPL took a dive starting 2 weeks before announcement—47pts/12.6% 2 Oct 4 -- opened about where it had close the day before and then extreme volatility with 27 point swing, but at the end of the day it was less than 2 pts down. 3 Oct 5—gap down 5 to the open, 5 more to low before finishing green up more than 5 4 Oct 5-18 ran up 54pts/14.7% into earnings 5 missed earnings and bottomed to 363 (-16% from Oct 18) on Nov 25 where the beginning of its now infamous run to 644 began. 4S Launch pattern Sept 21-Oct 4 dropped 420-373 (47pts/12.6%) Oct 4—this day alone-- HLOC 381.80 354.24 374.89 372.58 (from tip to tip 27pts/7.8% one day`s volatility!) Oct 5 gap down but closed well green Oct5-Oct 18 (earnings) run up 368-422 (54pts/14.7%) Oct18 missed earnings Oct18-Nov25 slid 422-364 (58pts/15.9%) Interestingly Sept 21 and Oct 18 formed a double top And Oct 4 and Nov 25 a double bottom Nov 25 marked the beginning of AAPL`s now famous run—which went into over-drive Jan 24-25 (earnings) iPhone 4 launch June 7, which was also day one of the developers conference. May 21-June 3 run up 233-263 (30pts/12.9%) AAPL slid 5pts. the next day and through the weekend (1.9%) June 7 O 258 C 251 down 2.8% June 9 bottomed at 243 or 6.2% lower than the open on June 7 June 10 -18 245-274 (29pts/11.8%) Then down and up and down to 240 again before taking off in the end of the end of August</Msg><Username>aaplboost</Username><Timestamp>1347122004456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122056441-125</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the verdict would be tuned over in an appeal. iPhone 5 will sell well - the question is how well? iPad mini will be meaningless for Apple, as it would have thin margins which will contribute very little to the bottom line. Apple still gets way too much of its profits from the iPhone and it looks like competitors have closed that huge lead the iPhone had. $199 phones from Google/Amazon could force Apple's hand like they did in the tablet market.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347122056441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122075901-126</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've been sayin it all along that the sleeper will be the new ipad and they'll sell a shht load. But the new iphone a bust no way,,, As LC said 800 here we come.</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347122075901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122095775-127</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the carrier buys it for you.</Msg><Username>derek_k_man</Username><Timestamp>1347122095775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122172569-128</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forget how many millions PASSED on the iphone 4s because it was not the 5. You will see it sell out in 24 hours. BOOK IT!</Msg><Username>peashooter14</Username><Timestamp>1347122172569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122189827-129</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man I can't wait for wed already!!!! if Amzn went up about 10% on their new tablet imagine Apple with 2 new prods,,,, LC we rock for the next 3 months! imo</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347122189827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122260033-130</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you still believe that this a battle of who has the biggest screen and fastest processor you are missing the point completely. I can't say your alone but that is the mistake that has cost investors dearly.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347122260033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122396605-131</Id><Topic><Title>Any thoughts on price action before event wednesday on apple</Title><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347109838296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:10:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should mention that I am not an experienced trader, though I do trade. This is all part of my self-imposed charting torture. Just starting on a self-imposed fundamentals torture.</Msg><Username>aaplboost</Username><Timestamp>1347122396605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122481656-132</Id><Topic><Title>Accessing the situation</Title><Username>gcaravousanos</Username><Timestamp>1345947936586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 22:25:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it means get short this week</Msg><Username>gcaravousanos</Username><Timestamp>1347122481656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122555790-133</Id><Topic><Title>If AAPL were afforded the same P/E as AMZN it would be trading</Title><Username>onwardthroughthefog2003</Username><Timestamp>1347114376579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon is a joke. No sense comparing anything to it. As for Google - they deserve a far higher P/E than Apple since the risks are much lower. Making cellphones is one or the riskiest businesses in the world. Look at Nokia/Rimm. Consumer tastes change way to quickly in this market and the iPhone's margins are simply unsustainable. The P/E is low, but it's low for a reason and it's not going higher.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347122555790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122827782-134</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course it isn't about the biggest screen of fastest processor. It's about the user-interface and user experience. I have an iPhone and I love it, but I'm not stupid enough to deny Android/Samsung's success. Android is not going away - it would be stupid to assume so.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347122827782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123069294-135</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iPad mini will have no margins, so they can sell 20M per quarter and it would still be meaningless. What are they going to make on it? $40 gross per device? That's what? $500M per quarter net? Meaningless.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123069294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123156188-136</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Rob...yup it is all Good. The 'level' of Posts should be a real gag too...hahaha !!! Heck, I have to remember that we have Football this weekend. I'll be rooting for you over Buffalo. I don't even know the spreads for this week...gotta get with it here...lol</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347123156188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347123203013-137</Id><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Msg>They are going to sell it for $199. Gross margins are probably going to be around 20% - that's $40 per device. It's a meaningless joke, even if they sell 20M minis per quarter. Stop talking about the iPad mini as if it means something - it's completely meaningless.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123245049-138</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ahh so when it comes to margins Apple's name always come into play right? But when it comes to Amazon they can lose 20 bucks a Kindle and the stock doubles? lol</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347123245049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123468863-139</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LC the spread in the Jet- Buff is 3,,,,,I hate to say it but i think the Jets are in trouble!!!</Msg><Username>robpic5</Username><Timestamp>1347123468863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123685230-140</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The carrier only buys it for me after two years and I still have to pay $200 for it and a new two year contract.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123685230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123980324-141</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no doubt, but it's the numbers that matter. How many will it sell? 30m? 40M? 50M? 60M? I think that anything under 50M iPhones sold in Q4 would be a disappointment. That's a very high bar for Apple and unless they can get major sales in China going, it would be very difficult to meet.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123980324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124126882-142</Id><Topic><Title>Catalysts for rest of year</Title><Username>thomasthecat69</Username><Timestamp>1347118650893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:37:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen the poll of smartphone users that say 90%of Iphone users will upgrade to the next Iphone version Vs. about 48% of Android users that will stay with Android. Now who is more likely to increase there market share as we go forward?</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347124126882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124197205-143</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you have inside info on price point....perhaps it will be $249.....and if a product was so meaningless then why bother making it? what is not smart is thinking one knows what is meaningless.....What is truly meaningless is some small fry pretending and guessing to know what possible gross margins will be..... It is like saying you probably would be better staying indoors all day cause it might rain....That is the true sign of one needing more education ....... The fact that you have no shares of Apple..is the only sure thing</Msg><Username>ottoman272000</Username><Timestamp>1347124197205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124456978-144</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I assume that you are in the military and are ready to storm the beaches to take Tehran.</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347124456978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347125078924-145</Id><Title>look for $640 leading to iPhone 5 event, and $590 afterwards. Trade accordingly.</Title><Msg>almost TOO easy</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347125078924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347125485828-146</Id><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Msg>But I may wait for $1,200 pps</Msg><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347125836220-147</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it's that little pesky thing called math. Whether the price point is $199 or $249, doesn't matter that much. Apple is making it to maintain marketshare and try to fight off Android tablets. It is not going to make any meaningful profits from it. You're basically saying NOTHING here and contributing NOTHING. Please - show me any set of realistic assumptions, where iPad mini makes a significant contribution to EPS and then we can talk. I'm guessing you can't because you understand nothing about GMs or profits or any type of real analysis. And yes - I sold Apple. I loved it in the $400 range, I love it at $500. At $700, I think expectations are too high and only $60M iPhone sales in Q4 can drive it to $1000.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347125836220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:37:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347126001885-148</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you have to "take" Tehran? Why can't you just bomb it back to the stone age? why not destroy every single power plant in the country? People without power don't build nukes. The US should NEVER EVER send group troops and occupy any country.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347126001885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347126245622-149</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For Apple to get to $1000 and beyond, it will have to sell around $60M iPhones. The only way I can see this happening is with massive China growth, but Q2 showed China contraction. The road to $1000 is not as easy as some may think. Apple maybe reaching the ceiling in terms of iPhones sales sans China.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347126245622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347126254722-150</Id><Title>Just pleasured myself 14 times today before you loser even got out of bed</Title><Msg>Bunch of loser on this board.</Msg><Username>aapl20l6</Username><Timestamp>1347126254722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347126405714-151</Id><Title>IPAD MINI</Title><Msg>IT WILL BE NUMBER 1 CHRISTMAS PRESENT THIS YEAR.</Msg><Username>jimbomcguinness</Username><Timestamp>1347126405714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347126455117-152</Id><Topic><Title>IPAD MINI</Title><Username>jimbomcguinness</Username><Timestamp>1347126405714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yup - an Apple device for the masses</Msg><Username>kokohead1</Username><Timestamp>1347126455117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:47:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347126602928-153</Id><Topic><Title>look for $640 leading to iPhone 5 event, and $590 afterwards. Trade accordingly.</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347125078924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dam_n...thought I had put you on ignore</Msg><Username>kokohead1</Username><Timestamp>1347126602928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347126617568-154</Id><Title>SPLIT COMING</Title><Msg>APPLE WILL ENTER DOW JONES 30. 7 for 1 split, for correct weighted averaging.</Msg><Username>jimbomcguinness</Username><Timestamp>1347126617568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347126844864-155</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The BOM will probably be around $130. They'll sell for $249 and add another $2B profit per quarter.</Msg><Username>x0thellox</Username><Timestamp>1347126844864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127018957-156</Id><Topic><Title>look for $640 leading to iPhone 5 event, and $590 afterwards. Trade accordingly.</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347125078924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are hilarious. im gonna look at my acct to laugh harder .people like you help me get rich</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347127018957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127055523-157</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gene Munster thinks Apple cans sell 200 million Iphones in 2013. They may not but even if he is off 10-20% THAT IS ALOT OF iPHONES.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347127055523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127376593-158</Id><Topic><Title>SPLIT COMING</Title><Username>jimbomcguinness</Username><Timestamp>1347126617568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Tim Cook tell you this or someone else? Jim Cramer maybe??</Msg><Username>centerdir</Username><Timestamp>1347127376593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127902317-159</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Apple can sell 200M iPhones in 2013 then the stock is guaranteed to hit $1200 next year, but I see this as an INCREDIBLY optimistic. For this prediction to come true, Apple will need to sell at least 50M iPhones in China, while recent trends have been showing that they are losing, rather than gaining market share in China. The problem is that there is no more RIMM/Nokia to squeeze market share from. It's a dog fight with Samsung right now and there are no guarantees Apple is coming in top.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347127902317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127904623-160</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you loved it at 400 and 500 but didn`t mention 600 did you sell around 550 just curious</Msg><Username>aaplboost</Username><Timestamp>1347127904623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127948715-161</Id><Topic><Title>look for $640 leading to iPhone 5 event, and $590 afterwards. Trade accordingly.</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347125078924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:24:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pothead</Msg><Username>lrcourtney56</Username><Timestamp>1347127948715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127993217-162</Id><Topic><Title>Iphone 5 is amazing - first look at the phone tells me it will be a game changer</Title><Username>moneymeyka</Username><Timestamp>1347120896030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:14:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>game changer my a same phone as is already out there samsung and others no big deal look for a bust idiot</Msg><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347127993217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:13:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128162713-163</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sellapplenow - My multiple LONG-TERM INVESTMENTS in AAPL are enough reward for me. How many years now has it been.....since you have been going in the WRONG DIRECTION with AAPL ??? INVEST in AAPL for THE LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347128162713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128315696-164</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NYK, Yeah let's have tens of thousands of powerless people die because a few dictatorial leaders are pursuing enrichment (which btw complies w/ NPT). I'm sure that'll make the world a lot safer, and boost America's image in the world. Gosh I'm so tired of people who don't use their brains...</Msg><Username>kvhrad</Username><Timestamp>1347128315696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347128371563-165</Id><Title>No wonder all you altruistic bloggers are dead broke</Title><Msg>You make money by doing what others are not..all this "good luck to all" and the asinine recommendations...you all are nothing but white trash losers.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347128371563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128372715-166</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see China Mobile selling Iphone 5 within 3 months of Iphone 5 launch. If so, Apple hits $1000 by Jun next year. All jmho. GL tf</Msg><Username>tfberynell</Username><Timestamp>1347128372715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128422713-167</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not realistic. However, even if they do make $120 in Gross Revenue as you claim (which is a pipe dream), that's a next profit of around $80 at most per device. Assuming 100M of these sell in 2014, you're looking at $8B in Earnings. That's worth around $100B in market cap or around $100 per share (assuming some dilution). The iPad mini, even under the most optimistic (unrealistic) assumptions will not be a significant factor in Apple EPS. There are major risks that it will cut into the (large) iPad sales and worse - it would push Google/Amazon to lower prices further (they both could care less about losing money) and put more pressure on Apple's marketshare. IMO, the iPad mini is a grave mistake. Apple should not be focusing on marketshare - it should continue to focus on selling high-end products for a premium.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347128422713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128429259-168</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUMP UP....for the WEEKEND VIEWERS.</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347128429259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128788520-169</Id><Topic><Title>No wonder all you altruistic bloggers are dead broke</Title><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347128371563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kinda sound like your loser a&amp;&amp;. Youre nothing but a pathetic troll that obviously has zero money in the market except for your virtual account that you trade like it is real money. LMAO!!!!! So sad! Have fun trolling this board and watching internet porn today you pathetic sad loser. I bet you forget what the outdoors even look like. LMFAO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>burpy68</Username><Timestamp>1347128788520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128825221-170</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's what's not mentioned - most of the earnings come from iPhone sales. The question is how long can Apple sell iPhones for 80% gross profits, when Android phones have closed the technology gap and Galaxy III is already running ahead of the iPhone. Eventually, margins are going to come down back to earth and that's something any long-term investor needs to consider. The only real driver for massive stock gains is going to be Apple TV. If they can deliver that, the sky is the limit, but with iPhone/iPads, they are coming close to the ceiling.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347128825221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347129085422-171</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If iPhone sales in China pickup, Apple is guaranteed to hit $1000 and much more. I don't see it as a lock, particularly with Huwei and ZTE selling their iPhone versions at a fraction of the price.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347129085422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347129244250-172</Id><Title>AFTER MULTIPLE TIMES BEING WRONG ON AAPL, DAN NATHAN CONTINUES GETTING WIPED-OUT !!!!</Title><Msg>Who does Dan Nathan work for? CNBC-COMCAST -- A network that has been perma-bashing AAPL -- all the way up the chart. This network TREMBLES IN FEAR at APPLE INC. entering the TV Industry. Like his coworker, Meli$$a Lee, both of these "shills" are simply trying to secure their position on Television -- by towing the Anti-AAPL line of krap. Dan Nathan is definitely not playing with REAL MONEY.... because he has been WRONG on trades of AAPL at least 4 times that I can recall in the past 6 months. I do not remember Dan Nathan EVER BEING RIGHT on AAPL. I would take his call very seriously -- he is a FANTASTIC CONTRARIAN INDICATOR !!!! --- THEREFORE --- AAPL is about to make another big move higher !!!!!!! Like Meli$$a, Dan will probably take a week of vacation....to let the EMBARASSMENT wear off. AAPL P&amp;F CHART TARGET = $875.00 The P&amp;F Chart Price Target and my personal Technical Analysis line up almost perfectly. LOAD UP in AAPL – and Enjoy the ride higher… The AAPL pattern is a VERY BULLISH Ascending Triangle (Bull Flag). Here are the details: High = $644.00 Low = $363.32 Length of Move = $280.68 Breakout Level = $580.50 (Own AAPL ahead of NEW LAUNCHES of BOTH the iPhone5 and iPad Mini !!!!!!!! PRICE TARGET = $861.18 (Trememdous Upside -- with still a Very Low PE Valuation!!! INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347129244250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347129601915-173</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean $100B market cap is insignificant? So what is a significant number in your mind? BTW, I don't think iPad Mini will add $100B market cap. But if it just adds $20B it is still a significant number. There aren't that many companies in the world worth $20B for selling one product.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347129601915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347129760245-174</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"it would push Google/Amazon to lower prices further...and put more pressure on Apple's marketshare." Two sentences later... "Apple should not be focusing on marketshare" Apple's currently ceding the market for one-hand tablet devices to the Nexus 7 and Kindle Fire. While there are many good uses for the smaller form factor, it does not compare to the experience of using a full-size iPad. Apple's risking very little by creating an entry in that category and there's a huge upside. They won't be losing as many iPad sales as they will be heading off Nexus/Fire sales. A $300 or $250 iPad Mini would sell like hotcakes, further cement Apple's dominance in the tablet space (with both consumers, businesses, and developers) before the only real competition shows up (Windows 8 tablets), and add significant revenue to the balance sheet. People said the iPhone was going to kill the iPod, too. What they didn't realize was that was the whole point. Apple made their own product obsolete before someone else could do it first.</Msg><Username>x0thellox</Username><Timestamp>1347129760245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347129891286-175</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$100B in market cap is 15% in terms of the current price. We're talking about 2014 and this is the most optimistic scenario possible. IPad mini will not and cannot be a significant driver of stock price appreciation for Apple. IMO, it will be a net negative and it is the wrong direction for Apple to take.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347129891286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131090114-176</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER MULTIPLE TIMES BEING WRONG ON AAPL, DAN NATHAN CONTINUES GETTING WIPED-OUT !!!!</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347129244250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He already took that vacation a few months back when he told everybody to get out at $540.00!!</Msg><Username>wildcarrot50</Username><Timestamp>1347131090114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131492086-177</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER MULTIPLE TIMES BEING WRONG ON AAPL, DAN NATHAN CONTINUES GETTING WIPED-OUT !!!!</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347129244250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait until banginshorty gets a hold of him.</Msg><Username>short_reaper_will_get_ya</Username><Timestamp>1347131492086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131631137-178</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they will sell at least 50 million iphone 5s in the coming holiday quarter. Analysts projections are for 200-250 million iphone 5s in total.</Msg><Username>derek_k_man</Username><Timestamp>1347131631137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131648220-179</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank God you are not running Apple.</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347131648220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131667216-180</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with At&amp;T and verizon having 30 million current iPhone users that are eligible for upgrades....should not be a problem....Once Apple inks China Mobile....that is 650 million subs to sell to....if Apple sells to a third...of them......or anywhere near 200 million.....again....Iphone sales could be off the chart....again all just possible thoughts</Msg><Username>ottoman272000</Username><Timestamp>1347131667216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131704017-181</Id><Topic><Title>Brian White Apple $ 1111 nothing more than a paid apple shill</Title><Username>sellapplenow</Username><Timestamp>1347114730185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:32:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are..... a credible analyst for what firm. Keep dreamin of a white christmas. i might send lord chatttely or bangin shorty to give you a suprise watch and learn monday my poor lemming</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347131704017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:15:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347132110384-182</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER MULTIPLE TIMES BEING WRONG ON AAPL, DAN NATHAN CONTINUES GETTING WIPED-OUT !!!!</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347129244250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dan nathan was only right twice on apple and the trades were weak only captilizing on selling premium no guts going long and strong like me and you and the rest of the romney supporters Go apple and go paul ryan. In america under obama is a criminal act to be prosperous as a republican. Keep up the great post white you are a schola and a gentleman</Msg><Username>opt_trdr</Username><Timestamp>1347132110384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347132319261-183</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>30M US will not cut it. There is NO WAY China mobile can sell 200M. Anything is possible, but these 200M numbers are stratospheric and would be very difficult to meet.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347132319261</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347132361772-184</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50M is about what the market expects for Q4. I'm not sure it's a slam dunk though.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347132361772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347132431389-185</Id><Topic><Title>AFTER MULTIPLE TIMES BEING WRONG ON AAPL, DAN NATHAN CONTINUES GETTING WIPED-OUT !!!!</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347129244250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:34:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw that too. This is truley embarasseing to see that guy trash AAPL like that again.For how many times this AAPL hater was wrong yet he continue to show is face again and again,he continue to have the nerve to show up his face again after being so wrong for so many times.I dont expect ML to take up with this guy.Shows how much hate there is there for AAPL sucsses .They just cant stand seeing AAPL going up despite their bashfull calls making them look like very unprofessionals.</Msg><Username>israelmichel</Username><Timestamp>1347132431389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347132483521-186</Id><Title>shorts are freaking out!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>love it!!!!!!!!!!! LOL</Msg><Username>pedroso74</Username><Timestamp>1347132483521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133032915-187</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it's pretty obvious that the iPad mini would sell like hotcakes. Saying that it would not cannibalize on the 10" iPad is a little naive IMO. The only question is how much? If the iPad mini is enough to push Google/Amazon out of the market, then it would be a brilliant move. However, I see that as an unlikely outcome. IMO, Google/Amazon will respond by lowering prices. I see Amazon selling the Kindle for $99 and Google selling the Nexus for $149. The fear is that Apple is eventually forced to cut prices and that is just about the worst thing that could happen since the process is irreversible.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347133032915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133399816-188</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Canclled Dan Nathen's option service. HE IS AN IDIOT.</Msg><Username>tradermkx</Username><Timestamp>1347133399816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347133659621-189</Id><Title>iPhone Insurance allows for upgradet to new Windows phone!</Title><Msg>Here's the deal. Many iPhone users buy insurance for loss or stolen iPhones. But, those are private insurers and they will allow free upgrades to the new super exciting Windows phones! So, I suggest you pick a spot in the back yard where you bury that out of date iPhone and prepare to start life anew with a Wonderful Windows Phone! Windows. Wonderful. SuperWin</Msg><Username>superwinpad_8</Username><Timestamp>1347133659621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133863575-190</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you actually think Dan Nathen is smart? Your post may be this months winner.</Msg><Username>tradermkx</Username><Timestamp>1347133863575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:51:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133922975-191</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does Cramer think? lol</Msg><Username>tradermkx</Username><Timestamp>1347133922975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133935288-192</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone Insurance allows for upgradet to new Windows phone!</Title><Username>superwinpad_8</Username><Timestamp>1347133659621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:47:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft has NEVER been able to compete in a non-monopolistic environment. Windows is crap and Windows phone will fail, just like every Microsoft product from Zune to Bing failed..</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347133935288</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347134036402-193</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big time sleeper...everyone is forgetting how much more that can be connected to the Apple ecosystem, and added Revs as such. The margin argument of the device itself could be extremely moot. Let's not lose sight of how much more the Mini could add here.</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347134036402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347134551147-194</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL vs AMZN</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347079070379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:37:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per the APPLE INC. Conference Call, the ENTERPRISE &amp; EDUCATION GROWTH-TRENDS are incredible! Here's a couple facts mentioned: (1) iPhone use has "doubled" at *Fortune 500 companies!!! (THIS IS HUGE). Did anyone else hear that? PepsiCo is now making use of the iPhone; (2) iPad use has "tripled" at *Fortune 500 companies!!! (THIS IS HUGE). Did anyone else hear that? British Airways is now making use of the iPad; Smart Homes are using the iPad in Japan; (3) iPad use in the Education Market is showing amazing growth!!! 11,000 iPads were bought by the Mansfield School District in Texas - enough for every student. With the iPad, the kids can learn at their own pace! * If you were in charge of IT Hardware purchases at your corporation, then you would ONLY buy the BEST hardware - and that is APPLE INC. iPhones, iPads and Macs - to improve productivity and keep up with the competition. You would not even consider an unproven knock-off copycat product....because your job is on the line -- and why risk it by buying an inferior product? ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Looking forward, the iPad "Mini" will be the LOW-COST product that will capture market share in the 7 inch tablet space (low-end price market). And, the iPhone "5" will be a HUGE HIT with a totally new hardware refresh. APPLE Management repeatedly reminded listeners of an exciting NEW PRODUCT PIPELINE. APPLE is the Top Brand in the World... and when the Holiday Buying Season rolls around, you will only buy the "best" for you and your family....not the second rate knock-off copy-cats. There is ONLY one orginal innovator - and that is APPLE INC...and that is the FACT of the MATTER....Only the Best will do. INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347134551147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347134754709-195</Id><Topic><Title>Only idiots talk about the iPad mini</Title><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347123203013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:53:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't say they wouldn't cannibalize some iPad sales, I said they would sell far more at that price point to offset the difference, for a net gain. Anything under $300 is getting into stocking stuffer territory and Apple saw how lucrative that could be with the iPod. Price pressure was never really an issue with the iPod because of the perceived hardware/software integration superiority Apple enjoyed. There were cheaper alternatives offered, even by such heavyweights as Microsoft, Sony, and Dell, but consumers ignored them. The advantage Apple enjoys when it comes to tablets is exponentially higher. A $149 Nexus with very few apps written expressly for it simply doesn't compare favorably to a $249 iPad Mini and its incredible wealth of available software. Not to mention, the iPad Mini would enjoy tremendous retail exposure that the others won't. If simply lowering prices were the answer, why haven't the Kindle Fire or Nexus 7 already taken market share from Apple? Their share of the tablet market has gone UP since they were introduced.</Msg><Username>x0thellox</Username><Timestamp>1347134754709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347134942320-196</Id><Title>Apple collects 71% of the world’s smartphone profits, analysts reckon.</Title><Msg>GGGGGGG</Msg><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347134942320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347135081558-197</Id><Topic><Title>BRIAN WHITE OF TOPEKA CAPITAL - REITERATES APPLE PRICE TARGET OF $1,111 (SEE BLOOMBERG VIDEO)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347069394338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a previous interview, when a reporter questioned Topeka Capital's Brian White's $1,111 AAPL PRICE TARGET, he said the following: "At $1,111/share, AAPL will be trading at a LOW PE VALUATION of only 19 times his forward estimates." INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347135081558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347135139713-198</Id><Title>TODAY, SUNDAY AND EVERY DAY NEXT WEEK AND BEYOND, APPLE BRINGS IN $142,857,142 IN NET PROFIT (AND NET DIVIDENDS). E-V-E-R-Y S-I-N-G-L-E D-A-Y!</Title><Msg>GGGGGGGGGG</Msg><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347135139713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347135469311-199</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no need to send troops anywhere. iran has the same number of nuks as switzerland ZERO !</Msg><Username>cincinatikid99</Username><Timestamp>1347135469311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347136741858-200</Id><Topic><Title>Apple collects 71% of the world’s smartphone profits, analysts reckon.</Title><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347134942320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sustainable.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347136741858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347136830931-201</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is huge room for upward growth in market share for APPLE. Apple has plenty of room to increase its share of the products it sells. Here's the stats: Apple share of the market for: PCs = 4.7% Mobile phones = 6.4% Source: IDC/Topeka Capital When you hear about the iPhone use "doubling" in Fortune 500 companies and the iPad use "tripling" in Fortune 500 companies, THEN YOU KNOW the growth momentum is strong....and APPLE INC. is capturing MARKET SHARE !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Maybe you prefer to buy stolen property from a copycat competitor -- but picky people who prefer "high-quality"...well, they purchase APPLE products...because they are trusted -- Top Brand in the World -- and enjoy the multiple benefits of the APPLE ECOSYSTEM. iTunes - 28 Million Songs; iPod - 70% of market; iPhones - CHINA MOBILE, with over 1 Billion subscribers, is expected to be announced as a New Carrier in early 2013; iPhones - 230 Carriers now; iPads - Strong demand... Air Force, Bechtel, Roche, Amgen, Bayer, British Airways, Smart Homes in Japan...to name a few APPLE clients added recently; App Store - Over 650,000 Apps (Up from 600,000 Apps the previous Qtr.) iPad Apps - Over 225,000 iPad Apps; iCloud - 150 Million Users (IN JUST A FEW SHORT MONTHS -- AMAZING !!!!) AND.... COMING SOON... iPhone 5 &amp; iPad Mini. LOAD UP on AAPL -- Ahead of the Herd !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347136830931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:40:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347137081059-202</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We dump the kenyan moslem mandingo assgroid in 60 days.</Msg><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347137081059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:44:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347137872473-203</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Countries exist to provide protection to their citizens. If Iran gets a nuke, it will blowup in NYC (where I live) within the next few years. This is not as complicated as you think - simple us or them decision. Either the Iranian people will suffer some discomfort of the US as you know it will seize to exist. People who think a nuclear Iran can be "contained" are clueless. PS - The world will be a very safe place once you take out Iran's ability to fund terrorists.</Msg><Username>nyk20h</Username><Timestamp>1347137872473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347138207691-204</Id><Topic><Title>Apple collects 71% of the world’s smartphone profits, analysts reckon.</Title><Username>adiosgroidcare</Username><Timestamp>1347134942320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>APPLE = TOP BRAND in the WORLD... With a 1,000+ Employee Product Design Team led by Sir Jony Ive, APPLE's INNOVATIONS will be SUSTAINED for DECADES TO COME !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! APPLE pumps profits right back into the company to research &amp; develop NEW iPhones, iPads, Macs, iPods, etc. etc. On Next Wednesday (September 12th), APPLE will LAUNCH the NEW iPhone 5 !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347138207691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347138280297-205</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>white knight. thanks for the very informative posts! you are one of a very few on this board who anything valuable to say!!! keep it coming!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>gideonfriend</Username><Timestamp>1347138280297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:04:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347138623798-206</Id><Title>Apple= Big Gains!!!!</Title><Msg>Apple has made many people much money!!! For traders and investors alike!!! Apple is such a money machine that it even makes money (for savy traders) when the stock price drops!!!!!</Msg><Username>gideonfriend</Username><Timestamp>1347138623798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347139820093-207</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gideonfriend, APPLE INC. (AAPL) is best described as a "BUY &amp; HOLD" -or- LONG-TERM INVESTMENT. Very few companies are as well-managed and offer such a strong Balance Sheet &amp; Income Statement. The APPLE Supply-Chain is a well-oiled machine (VERY EFFICIENT) -- and it was architected by the CEO - Tim Cook. The APPLE "Brand" is enjoying strong momentum in multiple sectors. And - For DECADES into the future, I am confident (With a Over-Weighted Investment in AAPL) that the industry-disrupting, AMAZING innovations will continue to be brought to market. INVEST in AAPL for the LONG-TERM !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! P.S. -- EXXON MOBIL (XOM) has made a clear break-out (just started) of the Long-term Ascending Triangle - Long-term Target = $120ish. Just above $100, I expect another 2 for 1 Split...as XOM manages their share price very well -- with XOM management splitting it 2 for 1 multiple times over the long-term.</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347139820093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347140928374-208</Id><Title>1200 Shares= Infiniti QX56</Title><Msg>Thank you AAPL- let's keep climbing....life does not suck! Just bought a new QX56. Ride on to $1000...for sure!</Msg><Username>kevinpop</Username><Timestamp>1347140928374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347142648713-209</Id><Title>Anyone hear about the legal judgements against apple?</Title><Msg>Latest is NY . Suckers.</Msg><Username>formerinfocure</Username><Timestamp>1347142648713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347142653177-210</Id><Title>Don't ever smoke that weed oil wax here in california</Title><Msg>I still can't see I drove into 3 mailboxs and a small kid or I think it was a kid.Maybe it was a stuffed animal. I slept like a baby but my eyes are still glued shut.. Stinky like skunk smell. It's all over here in san diego and head shop.It should be illigal</Msg><Username>northofhell200333333</Username><Timestamp>1347142653177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347142751002-211</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone hear about the legal judgements against apple?</Title><Username>formerinfocure</Username><Timestamp>1347142648713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOSER!!!!! Crawl back under your rock.</Msg><Username>bone412000</Username><Timestamp>1347142751002</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347143311881-212</Id><Title>Man's Country and Barack</Title><Msg>the story the media will not tell you. do an internet search and see what your president is really about.</Msg><Username>sirmidnight</Username><Timestamp>1347143311881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347144142829-213</Id><Topic><Title>I might sell @ $1000 pps</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347125485828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We won't know for sure until after Chinese new year AND Apple has a China Mobile deal. I wouldn't put much stock in Apple losing market share over the last 3-4 months. There are alot of folks waiting for this new Phone which has been talked about for 8 MONTHS. Nothing is certain but I think the key is the China mobile deal before Chinese new year. If that happens I like Apples chances to sell 160 million or more Iphones next year.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347144142829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347144373035-214</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone Insurance allows for upgradet to new Windows phone!</Title><Username>superwinpad_8</Username><Timestamp>1347133659621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:47:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lee - you are backing a loser still. You and Ballmer are joined at the...</Msg><Username>wistful_vista_pcs</Username><Timestamp>1347144373035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347144405213-215</Id><Title>Dan Nathon os a JOO on CNBC manipulating you cads left and right - he hasn't lost a dime</Title><Msg>Wake up...with as much money those Joos have cost people over the last three years, if CNBC was honest, those dogs would have been fired long ago...especially Cramer with all of Ho's Bear Sterns #$%$ and Lenny Dykstra scheming. And dumb fucs like you keep watching them and letting them steal ypu blind. Typical greedy Low life American who has to build up their self esteem in cyberspace but will die broke and alone.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347144405213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347145171719-216</Id><Title>Google RieseJones - Article on Apple - Prediction breaks $700 by November</Title><Msg>Interesting...</Msg><Username>kenrp713</Username><Timestamp>1347145171719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347145175345-217</Id><Title>Google RieseJones - Article on Apple - Prediction breaks $700 by November</Title><Msg>Interesting...</Msg><Username>kenrp713</Username><Timestamp>1347145175345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347145446854-218</Id><Title>iphone 5 nothing new only catch up here we GGGGGGAAAAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Tthhhaaarrr ssshheeee bbblllloooooowwwwsssssss!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347145446854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347145479368-219</Id><Topic><Title>Google RieseJones - Article on Apple - Prediction breaks $700 by November</Title><Username>kenrp713</Username><Timestamp>1347145175345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aapl 700 by Friday.</Msg><Username>lolux22</Username><Timestamp>1347145479368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347145677168-220</Id><Topic><Title>iphone 5 nothing new only catch up here we GGGGGGAAAAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347145446854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:04:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey MusicHaid...I thought you took weekends off...lol</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347145677168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347145768034-221</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eat your yellowcake and go to bed.</Msg><Username>anncisback</Username><Timestamp>1347145768034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347145897308-222</Id><Title>Is there a limit on ignore?</Title><Msg>I try to ignore someone but I keep getting ignore fail message. Anyone know if there is a limit on the number of ignore?</Msg><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347145897308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347146214963-223</Id><Topic><Title>Is there a limit on ignore?</Title><Username>pureinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347145897308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When that happens just try again. The second time usually works for me. If there is a limit I am surley getting close to it as I ignore 10-15 posters a day on avg. It is slowing down a little.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347146214963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347146359234-224</Id><Topic><Title>Multiple sources have confirmed that on Monday 09/10/2012 Apple will bid $ 10.00 PPS for SiriusXM</Title><Username>ryan_for_president</Username><Timestamp>1347134755754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:05:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First Kenneth does not know the frequency and if it is a Labrador retriever named Harvey take my word for it he is a liar</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347146359234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347146392829-225</Id><Topic><Title>Is is true that on Monday 09/10/2012 Apple will bid $ 10.00 PPS for SiriusXM</Title><Username>ryan_for_president</Username><Timestamp>1347134665121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no no it is not</Msg><Username>notahchort</Username><Timestamp>1347146392829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347146640671-226</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney know Nothing about foreign policy zero! And that's putting it mildly. He would be a joke as President a disgrace... Our current President is the best and the focus should be in the House because those non patriotic Republicans focused on only getting Obama out have failed the American people! What about the jobs bill they fail to past? They are criminals!</Msg><Username>rberry5828</Username><Timestamp>1347146640671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347146947668-227</Id><Title>A LAWYER WITH A BRIEFCASE CAN STEAL MORE THAN A THOUSAND MEN WITH GUNS.</Title><Msg>The Lawyers' Party, By Bruce Walker The Democratic Party has become the Lawyers Party. Barack Obama is a lawyer. Michelle Obama is a lawyer. Hillary Clinton is a lawyer. Bill Clinton is a lawyer. John Edwards is a lawyer. Elizabeth Edwards was a lawyer. Every Democrat nominee since 1984 went to law school (although Gore did not graduate). Every Democrat vice presidential nominee since 1976, except for Lloyd Bentsen, went to law school. Look at leaders of the Democrat Party in Congress: Harry Reid is a lawyer. Nancy Pelosi is a lawyer. The Republican Party is different. President Bush is a businessman. Vice President Cheney is a businessman. The leaders of the Republican Revolution: Newt Gingrich was a history professor. Tom Delay was an exterminator. Dick Armey was an economist. House Minority Leader Boehner was a plastic manufacturer. The former Senate Majority Leader Bill First is a heart surgeon. Who was the last Republican president who was a lawyer? Gerald Ford, who left office 31 years ago and who barely won the Republican nomination as a sitting president, running against Ronald Reagan in 1976. The Republican Party is made up of real people doing real work, who are often the targets of lawyers. The Democrat Party is made up of lawyers. Democrats mock and scorn men who create wealth, like Bush and Cheney, or who heal the sick, like First, or who immerse themselves in history, like Gingrich. The Lawyers Party sees these sorts of people, who provide goods and services that people want, as the enemies of America .. And, so we have seen the procession of official enemies, in the eyes of the Lawyers Party, grow. Against whom do Hillary and Obama rail?....Pharmaceutical companies, oil companies, hospitals, manufacturers, fast food restaurant chains, large retail businesses, bankers, and anyone producing anything of value in our nation. This is the natural consequence of viewing everything through the eyes of lawyers. Lawyers solve problems by successfully representing their clients, in this case the American people. Lawyers seek to have new laws passed, they seek to win lawsuits, they press appellate courts to overturn precedent, and lawyers always parse language to favor their side. Confined to the narrow practice of law, that is fine. But it is an awful way to govern a great nation. When politicians as lawyers begin to view some Americans as clients and other Americans as opposing parties, then the role of the legal system in our life becomes all-consuming. Some Americans become adverse parties of our very government. We are not all litigants in some vast social class-action suit. We are citizens of a republic that promises us a great deal of freedom from laws, from courts, and from lawyers. Today, we are drowning in laws; we are contorted by judicial decisions; we are driven to distraction by omnipresent lawyers in all parts of our once private lives. America has a place for laws and lawyers, but that place is modest and reasonable, not vast and unchecked. When the most important decision for our next president is whom he will appoint to the Supreme Court, the role of lawyers and the law in America is too big. When House Democrats sue America in order to hamstring our efforts to learn what our enemies are planning to do to us, then the role of litigation in America has become crushing. Perhaps Americans will understand that change cannot be brought to our nation by those lawyers who already largely dictate American society and business. Perhaps Americans will see that hope does not come from the mouths of lawyers but from personal dreams nourished by hard work. Perhaps Americans will embrace the truth that more lawyers with more power will only make our problems worse. The United States has 5% of the world’s population and 66% of the world’s lawyers! Tort (Legal) reform legislation has been introduced in congress several times in the last several years to limit punitive damages in ridiculous lawsuits such as spilling hot coffee on yourself and suing the establishment that sold it to you and also to limit punitive damages in huge medical malpractice lawsuits. This legislation has continually been blocked from even being voted on by the Democrat Party. When you see that 97% of the political contributions from the American Trial Lawyers Association go to the Democrat Party, then you realize who is responsible for our medical and product costs being so high!</Msg><Username>faribachicagomed</Username><Timestamp>1347146947668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347146989572-228</Id><Topic><Title>iphone 5 nothing new only catch up here we GGGGGGAAAAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347145446854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:04:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7 days a week all day everyday i run this board</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347146989572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347147622691-229</Id><Title>David Axlerod called the Gallop polling agency in on the carpet about there methodolgy and guess what..</Title><Msg>Obama has a 52 % approval rating and 5 point lead in the head to head polls. If you believe that I've got some wonderful pasture land in downtown Chicago to sell ya. BUY AND HOLD APPLE AND OH YEAH VOTE ROMNEY . THAT IS THE RECIPE FOR SUCCESS.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347147622691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347147761259-230</Id><Topic><Title>David Axlerod called the Gallop polling agency in on the carpet about there methodolgy and guess what..</Title><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347147622691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea baby. Agree.</Msg><Username>tradermkx</Username><Timestamp>1347147761259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347147978936-231</Id><Topic><Title>David Axlerod called the Gallop polling agency in on the carpet about there methodolgy and guess what..</Title><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347147622691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bye-bye O</Msg><Username>pjcl123</Username><Timestamp>1347147978936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347148380503-232</Id><Topic><Title>A LAWYER WITH A BRIEFCASE CAN STEAL MORE THAN A THOUSAND MEN WITH GUNS.</Title><Username>faribachicagomed</Username><Timestamp>1347146947668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said fariba !!!! If anyone has ever had their business attacked with a frivolous lawsuit, RIGHT THEN.... they learn quick that many lawyers are dirty scoundrels. The Free Enterprise System (and every citizen) are the losers. Vote for TORT REFORM -- and the ONLY way you get it is from Republicans --- because the American Trial Lawyers Assoc. is "owns" the Democrat Party. Texas has passed Tort Reforms on the State level. Lawyers just argue -- as they have been taught to do -- and it is hard to get anything done. A lawyer should NEVER be elected to hold political office. OWE-bama is a perfect example as a person who is very smart, but lacks any sense about economic matters. And - the Federal Government MUST be run more like a business -- especially when it comes to BALANCING THE BUDGET -- and PAYING DOWN THE $16 TRILLION IN DEBT. Romney has IMMENSE business experience. The company he co-founded would hire the elite Business School Grads. (4.0 GPA types). I don't care what OWE-bama says during a speech.... He will NEVER address the DEBT-PROBLEM. Business people make split-second decisions - EVERY DAY. Back to real-time... ROMNEY's 5-POINT ECONOMIC PLAN does indeed address the DEBT-DEATH-SPIRAL- PROBLEM in the USA-- in writing (SEE BELOW). Mitt Romney’s Plan for a Stronger Middle Class A Plan For More Jobs And More Take-Home Pay Energy Independence • Increase access to domestic energy resources • Streamline permitting for exploration and development • Eliminate regulations destroying the coal industry • Approve the Keystone XL pipeline The Skills To Succeed • Give every family access to a great school and quality teachers • Provide access to affordable and effective higher education options • Focus job training programs on building valuable skills that align with opportunities • Attract and retain the best and the brightest from around the world Trade That Works For America • Curtail the unfair trade practices of countries like China • Open new markets for American goods and services • Build stronger economic ties in Latin America • Create a Reagan Economic Zone to strengthen free enterprise around the world Cut The Deficit • Immediately reduce non-security discretionary spending by five percent • Cap federal spending below twenty percent of the economy • Give states responsibility for programs that they can implement more effectively • Consolidate agencies and align compensation of federal workers with their private-sector counterparts Champion Small Business • Reduce taxes on job creation through individual and corporate tax reform • Stop the increases in regulation that are tangling job creators in red tape • Protect workers and businesses from strong-arm labor union tactics • Replace Obamacare with real health care reform that controls cost and improves care</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347148380503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149023339-233</Id><Topic><Title>David Axlerod called the Gallop polling agency in on the carpet about there methodolgy and guess what..</Title><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347147622691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:40:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OWE-bama was never qualified to be President. He was a GREAT CAMPAIGNER....feeding the masses EVERYTHING they wanted to hear in the past....and at the convention....and he's now asking for more time. Time to do WHAT ??? --- Put us further in DEBT past $16 TRILLION ??? ..... I just hope ROMNEY can pull us out of this mess. ROMNEY's background is just stellar -- and he is so highly qualified to be President (See his background below - taken directly from his website).... Building Businesses, Creating Jobs Governor Romney's time at Bain Capital was spent fixing struggling businesses and giving new businesses a shot at success. From 1984, when Romney co-founded the firm, to February 1999 when he left to lead the Olympics, Romney helped save thousands of jobs at companies that were in trouble. And the businesses Romney helped start while at Bain Capital employ more than 100,000 people today. Since Bain Capital's founding, the company has had a remarkable record of success, especially considering that it largely invests with struggling or startup enterprises. Eighty percent of Bain Capital's portfolio companies have increased revenues, and only five percent of the companies under its control have filed for bankruptcy. Romney's work not only helped to save and create jobs, it also provided returns to investors, the majority of which were pension funds for retirees, university endowments helping with financial aid, and charities serving their local communities. This experience helped Romney fix a scandal-plagued and debt-ridden Olympics in 2002 and to fix a budget shortfall in Massachusetts. He knows how to provide strong leadership in challenging times, and he will bring that experience with him to the White House to fix America's broken economy and to create jobs for the millions of Americans who are out of work. The Obama campaign's attacks on business and free enterprise aren't just false; they explain why we aren't creating jobs. They reveal what this President really thinks about free enterprise. This is the most anti-business President in memory, and the results are clear: 23 million Americans are struggling for work, and unemployment has been above eight percent for 42-straight months. It's time to make a change to someone who understands the private sector and can get America working again.</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347149023339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149053649-234</Id><Title>Your opinion - Has anyone reads this article and is apple going to make all the way thru the year.</Title><Msg>What is your opinion on this article? : Wall Street Week Ahead: A nice rally while it lasted. My opinion is that the FEDS or market analysis are going to drive the market down sometime.</Msg><Username>mr.megawatt</Username><Timestamp>1347149053649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149182495-235</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Knight for the Pisane piece. I have a little more respect for the guy.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347149182495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149183506-236</Id><Title>Apple is taking over the world....</Title><Msg>Cook is the Man!</Msg><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347149183506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149272832-237</Id><Topic><Title>Is is true that on Monday 09/10/2012 Apple will bid $ 10.00 PPS for SiriusXM</Title><Username>ryan_for_president</Username><Timestamp>1347134665121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is true :-)</Msg><Username>bagholder_15</Username><Timestamp>1347149272832</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149300270-238</Id><Title>Obama, What a useless arogant lying P.O.S. Go back to Chicago and take Biden with you!</Title><Msg>Obama must be voted out in November</Msg><Username>db4759</Username><Timestamp>1347149300270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149316751-239</Id><Title>NBA</Title><Msg>When I go out, I observe what ppl are using as far as phones and computers and such. Just went to a new Starbucks I've never been to before. It was NOTHING but AAPL. Also on my trip to Vegas, NBA. NOTHING BUT AAPL. FORGET the talk of Samsung taking over. It's only a dream of theirs or a rumor started by AAPL haters but entirely inaccurate. iPhone 5 will absolutely blow the doors off! Probably close the year at $750.</Msg><Username>escapegrl1</Username><Timestamp>1347149316751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149322498-240</Id><Title>IF THEY ANNOUNCE CHINA MOBILE DEAL-ITS $800 QUICK</Title><Msg>If they announce the china deal, its off to the races</Msg><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1347149322498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149352723-241</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ewhh Haa! Get in the pickup trucks! Don't forget the shotguns and spitting tobacco! War! More War! Ewhh Haa! Trailer Trash!</Msg><Username>sillysam86</Username><Timestamp>1347149352723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149481601-242</Id><Topic><Title>IF THEY ANNOUNCE CHINA MOBILE DEAL-ITS $800 QUICK</Title><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1347149322498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow they could potentially announce Wednesday. That could be the 'surprise' no one is really expecting.</Msg><Username>escapegrl1</Username><Timestamp>1347149481601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347149549632-243</Id><Title>THE IRS IS JUST ANOTHER BRANCH OF OUR DYSFUNCTIONAL GOVERNMENT</Title><Msg>The entire system is riged :-(</Msg><Username>bagholder_15</Username><Timestamp>1347149549632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149589306-244</Id><Topic><Title>IF THEY ANNOUNCE CHINA MOBILE DEAL-ITS $800 QUICK</Title><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1347149322498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Jeff. To me it is the key to getting to 1K.</Msg><Username>docproc1_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347149589306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347149665642-245</Id><Topic><Title>FACT-- APPLE TOTAL CASH = $117.2 BILLION -- AS OF JUNE 30, 2012 (THIS IS FINANCIAL MUSCLE)</Title><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347077089111</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>docpro.... He is a loyal APPLE product user !!! Before this blog-essay, I filtered much of what he would say...because of his close alignment with traders on the floor. I "think" he is looking to the future..... knowing that Cable TV will evaporate in a "wireless" society as people CUT the cable TV wires. And...hehe...Just maybe he wants to head up APPLE's future Business TV Channel ??? (LOL)</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347149665642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:14:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347150396764-246</Id><Title>Riese Jones</Title><Msg>This guy is trying to make a name for himself at Apple's expense. Many people will sell off anyway at certain profit levels - no matter what the company does. Riese Jones is trying to act like the iPad and iPhone has been made obsolete because Steve Jobs is gone. Innovation is gone. WRONG! The transformation in business is just beginnning. At my working place EVERYTHING is done by email. 7yrs ago it was just starting out. Now people are using their PERSONAL iPad and smartphone for work - nobody thinks anything of this change. Businesses see this and are just now seeing the application. Schools and universities will have to get iPads for the kids because it is cheaper than buying the newest revision of books. homework will be done this way eliminating paper iPads and iPhones have not reached saturation. Apple has not run out of ideas yet. Microsoft and Intel became like the washing machine or oven - an appliance. Steve Jobs and Apple took the PC a step further and made it mobile and easy to use, not to mention the WOW or cool factor. Look at any airport there are young and old alike using iPads, iPods, and smartphones. This is just starting. smartphone videos are our news. smartphone videos are being shown in court and to police and for businesses. Look at the political impact social media has had on the world and its ruling governments. This is just getting started - China just got the iPad this summer and NOBODY has an iPhone5 and Jones is writing about his friend who won't buy an iPhone6!!??!!?? I think Jones better go home and talk to his kids because they are going to want an iPad mini and his wife will want the iPhone5. Riese Jones talks like the hype is over, innovation is over and Apple is done. This is gonna cost him a lot of money whether he is right or wrong. I think he is wrong.</Msg><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347150396764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347150422971-247</Id><Title>Positive catalysts to take it to low 700's</Title><Msg>1. Technical: Ready to move up to low 700's. 2. New product announcements: iPhone 5 (next Wed) and iPad Mini 3. New areas: Streaning music, iTV 4. 3Q12 and 4Q12 will reflect sales of new products, so margins will stay healthy. 5. Analyst estimates for EPS already started moving up; more upgrades after next Wed. 6. Possible dividend increase and stock split (last split was in 2005). 7. A deal with China Mobile, the largest mobile company in China.</Msg><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347150422971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347150580640-248</Id><Title>Ego is good for business</Title><Msg>How do you think jobs took AAPL to moon? His ego was larger than planet earth. Tim is clearly not a leader, which is why he is following what AMZN does/did. The moment he releases a mini iPad, it's over! Jobs created UNIQUE PRODUCTS. Once you enter into a competition, you are basically commoditizing your product and hence cant claim big premiums. I am long AAPL but I don't have good vibes about iPhone 5. I seriously hope that they announce a china deal or come up with extra ordinary product, else we will go down fast. There is a lot of expectations built into $680 pps.</Msg><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1347150580640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:29:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347150658980-249</Id><Topic><Title>iphone 5 nothing new only catch up here we GGGGGGAAAAAAOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347145446854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:04:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our latest Cult Contrarian !!! Take us to 800 ... lmao</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347150658980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347150711215-250</Id><Topic><Title>NBA</Title><Username>escapegrl1</Username><Timestamp>1347149316751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well said escapegirl !!!!!!!!!! When AAPL makes a breakout run higher (currently-in-motion), then the dirty funds begin spreading their blatant lie$, rumor$ and mi$leading information to try and hold the price down -- and collect Call Premiums -- and hold onto their shares. EVERY TIME a big move on AAPL is started and moves higher up the chart, I see the same modus operandi -- as the $hill-Media begin writing their lie$ &amp; rumor$. On this same note, when CNBC-COMCAST linked up with Yahoo, I thought --- oh noooo.... there will be more hit-pieces. Now - they link them right up at the top of the news feed -- and call them Yahoo Exclusives (LOL...Business Insider is "code" for $hill Insider in my view). For the LONG-TERM INVESTOR, just ignore all this.... and LOAD UP on any weakness. This company is very well-managed -- and continuing innovating -- and enjoying the power of the most valuable "brand" in the entire world !!! OWN AAPL -- Ahead of the iPhone 5 &amp; iPad Mini LAUNCHES !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347150711215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347150937981-251</Id><Title>Listen to all you idiots talking like ypu actually know something and have any REAL money invested.</Title><Msg>The reason you're so complacient with the thriving Joos is obviously because you're role playing in cyberspace and will never have enough to have your own real position. Anyone with actual money is disgusted bu the way the Joos operate. Learn hostory jack a&amp;&amp;...read about Lehmon, Bear Sterns, Merryl Lynch...all Joos collapsing the financial system.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347150937981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347150946751-252</Id><Title>Making call now. Sirius XM is bought out by Apple</Title><Msg>Apple will buy Sirius XM satellite.</Msg><Username>mytek38088</Username><Timestamp>1347150946751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347151023286-253</Id><Title>What will apples short term pull back be after 9/12/2012.</Title><Msg>I have about 75 shares of apple I would like to add share.After most of apples show and tell for investors apple always pull back.But how much.Please give this some thought and no short only longs please.</Msg><Username>samsueshef3</Username><Timestamp>1347151023286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347151120545-254</Id><Topic><Title>Making call now. Sirius XM is bought out by Apple</Title><Username>mytek38088</Username><Timestamp>1347150946751</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:35:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why jerk off? Because you say so? Does anyone in the real world ever give you the time of day? Obviously not or else you wouldn't be posting your obtuse opinions on Saturday night...hoping some other loser will respond so you can have someone ro talk to...go f yourself loser.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347151120545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347151237696-255</Id><Title>appl2016</Title><Msg>You will be glad to know that all your emails have been forwarded to the Israeli Consulate in Washington DC. They were very glad to hear your thoughts. I don't think you should worry though. All that stuff about finding somebody through emails and blogs is just a bunch of baloney, right? lol</Msg><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347151237696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347151384300-256</Id><Topic><Title>Positive catalysts to take it to low 700's</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347150422971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:27:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too much is being made of AMZN offerings - they are just hardware - where are the applications? iPad's strength is in applications that are so far advanced that AMZN or anyone else will never be able to catch up. Too much hype about AMZN - they price it low but they will not make any money, so revenue growth without profit! Buy AAPL and sell AMZN. Valuation of AAPL is incredibly low trailing PE of 15 vs AMZN's 306. Forward PE of AAPL 12 vs AMZN 106 !!!</Msg><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347151384300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347151532893-257</Id><Title>Just Kidding aapl2016 I didnt send it</Title><Msg>I always enjoy your posts!</Msg><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347151532893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347151701997-258</Id><Topic><Title>A LAWYER WITH A BRIEFCASE CAN STEAL MORE THAN A THOUSAND MEN WITH GUNS.</Title><Username>faribachicagomed</Username><Timestamp>1347146947668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumpity bump</Msg><Username>faribachicagomed</Username><Timestamp>1347151701997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:48:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347152082222-259</Id><Topic><Title>appl2016</Title><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347151237696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More idle threats from some anonymous dead beat living in cynerspace....I am shaking in my boots deick wad and have been waiting anxiously for those fucs for about two years...when the first dead beat recluse said he was sending them....hahaha. Ask them though why they need 21 billion from us every year to do nothing but steal land from their neighbors and steal blindly from Wall Street and Medicaid every year. You obviously don't pay taxes Hawaii high schooler, so keep your mouth back and go back to surfing your porn faggboy.</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347152082222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347152119624-260</Id><Topic><Title>Here. We. Goooooo!!!</Title><Username>whettphartts</Username><Timestamp>1347151154380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lead us to 800 ok ? LoL</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347152119624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347152172559-261</Id><Topic><Title>Riese Jones</Title><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347150396764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting article and interesting opinions.</Msg><Username>riese832</Username><Timestamp>1347152172559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347152330114-262</Id><Topic><Title>Here. We. Goooooo!!!</Title><Username>whettphartts</Username><Timestamp>1347151154380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, sure, whatever...duh..</Msg><Username>appl2016</Username><Timestamp>1347152330114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347152385845-263</Id><Topic><Title>Riese Jones</Title><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347150396764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are your thoughts on this?</Msg><Username>riese832</Username><Timestamp>1347152385845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347153321395-264</Id><Topic><Title>Just Kidding aapl2016 I didnt send it</Title><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347151532893</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol</Msg><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347153321395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347154364351-265</Id><Topic><Title>appl2016</Title><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347151237696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:40:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol I like this guy! I think if you stick with it, you can make swearing an art form lol</Msg><Username>hawaiianmm</Username><Timestamp>1347154364351</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347154722079-266</Id><Title>A MAN WITH A LAPTOP!!!!</Title><Msg>Can make money in one week than 1000 men without one!!!</Msg><Username>gideonfriend</Username><Timestamp>1347154722079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347154807923-267</Id><Topic><Title>Apple is taking over the world....</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1347149183506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:06:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not really. just most of it!!</Msg><Username>gideonfriend</Username><Timestamp>1347154807923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347155820242-268</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's some food for thought, but it's kind of hard to chew though.... WND EXCLUSIVE Iran threatens to bring war to U.S. shores Reports: Terror cells preparing to strike from South America Published: 2 hours ago by Reza Kahlili Email | Archive Reza Kahlili served in CIA Directorate of Operations, as a spy in the Iranian Revolutionary Guard, counterterrorism expert; currently serves on the Task Force on National and Homeland Security, an advisory The deputy chief commander of Iran’s Revolutionary Guards warned this past week that any aggression against Iran will expand warfare onto the turf of its enemies. “Our nation is ready to rub the enemies’ snout into dust and send thousands of coffins to their cities,” Gen. Hossein Salami told Fars News Agency. “Any aggression against Iran will expand the war into the borders of the enemies,” he warned. “They know our power, and we won’t allow any aggression against our land.” The general cited two reasons for what he called the greatness of the Islamic regime: “One is that the supreme leader, who is the deputy of the Hidden Imam [the Shiites' 12th Imam], rules with power, knowledge, penetrating the hearts; the other is the martyrs who shed their blood for the greatness of the country.” In praising those martyrs, he said, “God states in the Quran that martyrs are alive and not to consider them as dead, as they had the art to exchange death to life and reach eternal life.” Salami likened the supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, to a sun shining on the Islamic world, and that despite all the international sanctions and threats, Iran is progressing on all fronts. Fars News Agency also reported a stern warning by Gen. Hassan Firoozabadi, head of the Army’s Joint Chiefs of Staff. Although he accused the U.S. and European nations of supporting al-Qaida and “terrorists” in Syria, he warned that America and the European countries should expect major attacks by al-Qaida and other terrorist groups in their homelands. As reported earlier this year, terror cells have been placed on high alert to attack targets in the U.S. and Europe should Iran be attacked. Hundreds of terror cells have infiltrated America and, in collaboration with Hezbollah, are awaiting orders to strike American targets. Thousands of cells have also been placed in Latin America. “The Quds Force has established a command and control center in both Bolivia and Venezuela,” a former Iranian official with knowledge of the regime’s terror network recently revealed. “Though it has presence in Europe and other parts of the world, it has focused on Latin America. Thousands of such cells have been placed in Bolivia, Brazil, Ecuador, Guatemala, Nicaragua and Venezuela.” A recent report from within Nicaragua indicated that Iran has established a training base in the northern part of that country, where operatives, including Hezbollah terrorists, are being readied for an attack on U.S. and Israeli interests should a war break out with Iran. Hassan Abassi, a former Guard commander and a current strategist, has stated that many of the cells are of Latin American origin, including from Mexico, and that several hundred targets have been identified in the U.S. for a possible attack. “If America dares to destabilize the Islamic Republic of Iran, it should have no doubt that we will destabilize America,” Abassi said. Another senior commander of the Islamic regime, Gen. Masoud Jazayeri, recently warned America, “In the face of any attack, we will have a crushing response. In that case, we will not only act in the boundaries of the Middle East and the Persian Gulf; no place in America will be safe from our attacks.” Khamenei has also warned America that any conflict will expand beyond the region. That same warning was issued days ago by Hassan Nasrallah, the general secretary of the terrorist group Hezbollah. The response by Iran in case of an attack on its nuclear facilities will be “very great,” Nazrallah said. Thousands of Revolutionary Guards and paramilitary forces of the Basij are set to conduct exercises in the coming weeks within Iranian cities on the occasion of the week of holy defense, an annual event commemorating the Iran-Iraq war. According to a source within the Guards intelligence division who has defected to Europe, the exercise is a practice to use force against the Iranian population and to militarize and take control of major cities because the regime expects another uprising over deteriorating economic conditions and major resentment by the majority of Iranians against the Islamic regime. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Reza Kahlili is a pseudonym for a former CIA operative in Iran’s Revolutionary Guards and author of the award-winning book “A Time to Betray” (Simon &amp; Schuster, 2010). He serves on the Task Force on National and Homeland Security and the advisory board of the Foundation for Democracy in Iran (FDI).</Msg><Username>white_knight_in_texas</Username><Timestamp>1347155820242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 21:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156012549-269</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$</Msg><Username>mablehardestofknockers</Username><Timestamp>1347156012549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156567533-270</Id><Topic><Title>Get rid of iran nukes vote Romney ROMNEY ROMNEY ROMNEY!</Title><Username>forza_usa</Username><Timestamp>1347110976496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ mouth</Msg><Username>mablehardestofknockers</Username><Timestamp>1347156567533</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347157285262-271</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If AAPL is around 700 before 9/12 then it will be 720-730 on 9/12.</Msg><Username>thienban</Username><Timestamp>1347157285262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347157537120-272</Id><Title>750$ NEXT WEEK ?</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$</Msg><Username>barronsfanatic</Username><Timestamp>1347157537120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347158601242-273</Id><Title>September 12 open $670 close $635 here we GGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>bigger screen + samsungs patented 4G tech = old news</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347158601242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347158821969-274</Id><Topic><Title>September 12 open $670 close $635 here we GGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347158601242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is your real name McMurphy from one flew over the cookoo's nest.</Msg><Username>lrcourtney56</Username><Timestamp>1347158821969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347159024629-275</Id><Topic><Title>CNBC Dan Nathan Say's iPhone 5 Will Be a Bust!!</Title><Username>shortinguy</Username><Timestamp>1347114359440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? A bust? I dont't think Mr. Nathan has his finger on the pulse of consumers. He is probably over 50 yrs old.</Msg><Username>lrcourtney56</Username><Timestamp>1347159024629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347159860860-276</Id><Topic><Title>Positive catalysts to take it to low 700's</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347150422971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:27:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you serious about the PE valuation of AAPL vs AMZN? That is hard to believe</Msg><Username>ceinternational1</Username><Timestamp>1347159860860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160016862-277</Id><Topic><Title>Is is true that on Monday 09/10/2012 Apple will bid $ 10.00 PPS for SiriusXM</Title><Username>ryan_for_president</Username><Timestamp>1347134665121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:04:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, go buy you a boat load and wait.</Msg><Username>z0mbia</Username><Timestamp>1347160016862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347160374166-278</Id><Title>I am short aapl. Next stop 400.</Title><Msg>WAAAAAAAAAY OVERVALUED.</Msg><Username>wallstreetkoolaid</Username><Timestamp>1347160374166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:12:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160635852-279</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, What a useless arogant lying P.O.S. Go back to Chicago and take Biden with you!</Title><Username>db4759</Username><Timestamp>1347149300270</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:08:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O's progression: 2008 "HOPE" --------- 2010 "DOPE"-------------- 2012 "NOPE"</Msg><Username>bigbizluvr</Username><Timestamp>1347160635852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347160738087-280</Id><Title>$680 finally here!</Title><Msg>If you sold the Jan $600 calls for $80....? Rule of thumb is don;t chase it...once the money is in your pocket; leave it there</Msg><Username>biglefthook_00</Username><Timestamp>1347160738087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:18:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160758092-281</Id><Topic><Title>Positive catalysts to take it to low 700's</Title><Username>sm081969</Username><Timestamp>1347150422971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:27:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But very true. I like AMZN but not that much. I'll stick cheap ole safe AAPL.</Msg><Username>escapegrl1</Username><Timestamp>1347160758092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160777037-282</Id><Topic><Title>I am short aapl. Next stop 400.</Title><Username>wallstreetkoolaid</Username><Timestamp>1347160374166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:12:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you are is "short on brains", next stop for you is "the short bus".</Msg><Username>bigbizluvr</Username><Timestamp>1347160777037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:19:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160832437-283</Id><Topic><Title>$680 finally here!</Title><Username>biglefthook_00</Username><Timestamp>1347160738087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you realize IF you bought AAPl under $600 and sold these JAn $600 calls for $80..your break even is now $$520..you have a $160 hedge...</Msg><Username>biglefthook_00</Username><Timestamp>1347160832437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160920731-284</Id><Topic><Title>iPhone Insurance allows for upgradet to new Windows phone!</Title><Username>superwinpad_8</Username><Timestamp>1347133659621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:47:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey szhythead Lee, are you still alive? I thought you died of self-disgust.</Msg><Username>bigbizluvr</Username><Timestamp>1347160920731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347160969341-285</Id><Topic><Title>I am short aapl. Next stop 400.</Title><Username>wallstreetkoolaid</Username><Timestamp>1347160374166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:12:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just put your money in an envelope and donate it to charity cause with that investment philosophy you surely won't keep it.</Msg><Username>lrcourtney56</Username><Timestamp>1347160969341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347161334123-286</Id><Topic><Title>September 12 open $670 close $635 here we GGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347158601242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I am that character from that movie.</Msg><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347161334123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347161645471-287</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm about there too, Ten.</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347161645471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347161690616-288</Id><Topic><Title>What price AAPL will be at open on 9/12?</Title><Username>cungsuongban</Username><Timestamp>1347073833429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:10:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>695</Msg><Username>lord_chatterly</Username><Timestamp>1347161690616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347162551584-289</Id><Title>All apple longs listen up good</Title><Msg>we is goin to 700 so lits git er done</Msg><Username>lord_chaterly</Username><Timestamp>1347162551584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347162697317-290</Id><Title>I like pleasuring myself to madonna</Title><Msg>gggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggggg</Msg><Username>lord_chaterly</Username><Timestamp>1347162697317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347162771004-291</Id><Topic><Title>September 12 open $670 close $635 here we GGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347158601242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Music--you are a lovable nut.</Msg><Username>samsam43229</Username><Timestamp>1347162771004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347162851220-292</Id><Topic><Title>Ego is good for business</Title><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1347150580640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:29:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jobs would have never chased AMZN with mini tablets. THE WORLD FOLLOWED HIM, HE NEVER FOLLOWED THE WORLD.</Msg><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1347162851220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347163115217-293</Id><Title>Can I get my mom pregnant if she is post menopausal?</Title><Msg>I sure hope not?!!!!!! Im not ready to be a dad</Msg><Username>aapl20l6</Username><Timestamp>1347163115217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:58:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347163178650-294</Id><Topic><Title>September 12 open $670 close $635 here we GGGGGGGOOOOOOOOOOOOAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!!!!!</Title><Username>musichead2005</Username><Timestamp>1347158601242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Longs, don't be blind folded. This guy is a pest but he could be true if AAPL doesn't come out with extraordinary product. Markets let-go AAPL for crappy 4s, a mere upgrade, but if iPhone is just another 4s with bigger screen then we are in trouble. AAPL will go back to $500 in no time.</Msg><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1347163178650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 23:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>