<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352880650131-1</Id><Title>Obama admin threatens to punch out reporter - not covered by yahoo?</Title><Msg>Interior Secretary Ken Salazar threatened to punch a reporter with the Colorado Springs Gazette after the reporter asked him about the Bureau of Land Management's wild horses program at an Election Day get-out-the-vote event. After the interview, Kathrens said she tried to shake Salazar's hand. He brushed past her, she said, and approached Philipps. Salazar then reportedly was caught on tape saying, "Don't you ever ... You know what, you do that again, ... I'll punch you out."</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1352880650131</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 03:10:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352881169566-2</Id><Title>Petraeus crossed Obama</Title><Msg>Obama and his communist minions do "purges" just like Stalin did. They get rid of their enemies and anyone who might challenge them...by bribes, threats, punishments... or worse. This is also likely the reason why Justice Roberts flipped. Our country is no longer what it was and Yahoo "news" seems to be very pleased. The senate has not passed a budget like they're supposed to in close to 4 years, this is why the deficits are so high. Obama and the democrats gave us $6 triilion more debt in just 4 years.</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1352881169566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 03:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352886527500-3</Id><Title>Going through ..</Title><Msg>..18 today and than it will explode. I still mean that something big is cooking here. Look at the chart, do your TA!!!</Msg><Username>zissi022000</Username><Timestamp>1352886527500</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 04:48:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352894387257-4</Id><Topic><Title>Petraeus crossed Obama</Title><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1352881169566</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 03:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didnt just realize that Yahoo has bgeen up Obama's a(ss) since 2008 have you ? Yahyoo employees would PAY Obama to bend them over</Msg><Username>garybirch55</Username><Timestamp>1352894387257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 06:59:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352895871944-5</Id><Title>I can assure you...Yahoo management does not care for Obama....at all</Title><Msg>They wanted Mitt big time in the White house just like we all did. Only the meek and the weak wanted Obama. Us Georgia boys don't care for him as well as my old friends Greg A. and Butch Trucks. Also my old compadre Duane... a die hard Republican... may God rest his soul.</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1352895871944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 07:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352896765504-6</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Bought Back $200 Million in Stock Last Month. Wait Until They Really Start Buying!</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1352487967365</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:06:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strong Buy $21 by 11/26</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1352896765504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 07:39:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352899057824-7</Id><Title>nervously inhaling some week before the open. I bought 1000 November 18's yesterday at 7</Title><Msg>Need this baby to run to 18.25. There I will sell 500 for $12500. Then when it hits 19 Friday I will unload the rest for $50,000. I do not want to be greedy or else I would be planning on holding them all til 19 Friday to claim my $93,000 profit.</Msg><Username>jurgensmuscle</Username><Timestamp>1352899057824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 08:17:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352899742437-8</Id><Title>Well Over 18 in premarket. Nice</Title><Msg>Today could really spike up big.</Msg><Username>jurgensmuscle</Username><Timestamp>1352899742437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 08:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352900965181-9</Id><Topic><Title>To whom it may concern.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1276031248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-06-08 17:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sell your blood and a kidney, buy Yahoo. Sell a lung and half your liver, buy Yahoo. You are a proud Yahoo long, your brain is in mint condition ready to be started up for the first time and tested in some lab, sell it , buy Yahoo. Just keep saying to yourselves; special dividend, buyback, cash rich split, IPO, special dividend, buyback, cash rich split, IPO, special dividend, buyback, cash rich split, IPO..... AND BUY BUY BUY</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352900965181</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 08:49:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352901121997-10</Id><Topic><Title>$17, the magic number.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352831390157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:29:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No $28 Yahoo long buying, just telling others to buy. Makes you think. $28 longs still waiting for a penny profit.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352901121997</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 08:52:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352901351061-11</Id><Title>NTWK $6.4 Reports Record Fiscal 1Q 2013....$11.1 M Revenues vs. $6.2 M a Year Ago....12c/share Net Income vs. 30c/share Loss in 1Q 2012. Reiterates $49 M 2013 Revenue Guidance for 2013 or 45% Revenue Growth Over 2012....Projects 80c/share - $1/share Net Income For 2013.....Exponential Growth of Cloud Divisions fueling Profitable Growth.....No.1 Worldwide in Leasing/Financing Software......Only $6 PE .......4 M Share FLOAT.</Title><Msg>TARGET $15+ BY YEAR END.........AVERAGE ANALYST TARGET PRICE: $16/SHARE TODAY's EARNINGS RELEASE: Record First-Quarter Revenue Reaches $11.1 Million vs $6.2 Million Fiscal 1Q 2012 Net Income $929,000, or $0.12 per Diluted Share vs 30c/share loss in 1Q 2013 EBITDA Advances to $2.5 Million, or EBITDA per Diluted Share of $0.33 Reiterates Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Guidance of $46 million to $49 million; Earnings per Diluted Share of $0.80 to $1.00 CALABASAS, Calif., Nov. 14, 2012 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- NetSol Technologies, Inc. (NTWK), a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions, today reported financial results for its fiscal 2013 first quarter ended September 30, 2012. Fiscal 2013 First-Quarter Financial Results Total first quarter revenue rose to $11.1 million, the highest first quarter in the company's history, as a result of higher services revenue and a recovery in licensee revenue. This compares with total revenue of $6.2 million in the first quarter of fiscal 2012. "NetSol's record first quarter revenue underscores the success of our initiative to build out service and delivery capabilities in Bangkok and China," said Najeeb Ghauri, CEO of NetSol. "Our record results also reinforce the continued demand for our core leasing solution throughout Asia, where we have recently completed a number of NFS(TM) implementations." License revenue increased to $3.2 million from $1.1 million in the comparable first quarter of fiscal 2012, representing new agreements with fortune 500 companies in the Asia Pacific Region. Maintenance revenue was $2.0 million, approximately in line with the same period last fiscal year. Services revenue grew to $5.8 million from $3.1 million for the first quarter of fiscal 2012 as a result of new consulting and customization projects and increased contribution from NetSol's Virtual Leasing Services subsidiary jointly acquired during the second quarter of fiscal 2012. Total operating expenses for the fiscal 2013 first quarter amounted to $3.8 million, down sequentially from the fourth quarter, although up from $3.0 million in the fiscal 2012 first quarter. The increase is principally due to hiring additional NFS and Vroozi personnel and larger headcount as a result of the VLS acquisition. Operating income for the first quarter of fiscal 2013 rose to $1.5 million, compared with an operating loss of $826,000 in the first quarter of fiscal 2012. NetSol achieved net income of $929,000 for the fiscal first quarter, equal to $0.12 per diluted share, compared with a net loss of $1.5 million, or $0.26 per share, in the comparable period of the prior fiscal year. This includes a deduction of net income by $332,000 for non-controlling interest, compared with $137,000 in the comparative period. Weighted average number of diluted shares outstanding for the period was 7.6 million shares, compared with 5.6 million shares for the first quarter of fiscal 2012. The net EBITDA (a non-GAAP measure), was $2.5 million for the fiscal 2013 first quarter, versus a loss of $234,000 for the fiscal 2012 first quarter. The reconciliation of net EBITDA to net income, the most comparable non-GAAP financial measure, as well as a further explanation about adjusted EBITDA, is included in the financial tables at the end of this news release. NetSol's cash and cash equivalents balance rose to $8.0 million at September 30, 2012, compared with $7.6 million at June 30, 2012. 2012 First-Quarter Highlights: • Received new orders for NetSol Financial Suite (NFS(TM)) solution from two new customers, representing more than $4 million in combined license, maintenance, and service billings; • Won a new contract in Europe to provide a Point-of-Sale solution to an existing bank client to support their entry into vehicle finance; • Completed NFS implementations in China with Mercedes-Benz Leasing, Chongqing Auto Finance and JAC Santander; • Completed a custom projects including one LeaseSoft migration project with a European Bank ; • Secured and delivered a leasing and finance consulting project with a Mexico-based subsidiary of one of the largest commercial truck manufacturing companies in the world and completed a consulting engagement with Mercedes-Benz China; • Signed a new contract in the area of information security with a leading telecom company in Pakistan and added a contract to implement a transport department automation system with the government of Punjab. The agreements are collectively valued at approximately $0.7 million; and, • Added key sales, marketing, and implementation personnel to further drive global market penetration and increase delivery and support capability. Most recently, Vroozi welcomed Ivy Montgomery, formerly of SAP, as vice president of marketing. Business and Financial Outlook "With our growth initiatives underway, combined with our new business pipeline visibility, I am ever confident that we will hit our revenue and profitability targets for fiscal 2013, especially considering that NetSol's second half of the year has historically been a stronger period than the first half," Ghauri said. The company maintains its financial guidance, anticipating growing total annual revenue to a range of approximately $46 million to $49 million for fiscal 2013, and achieving earnings per diluted share of approximately $0.80 to $1.00 for the year. .........FYI.......MORE NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide and Riyadh.</Msg><Username>anny.sakana</Username><Timestamp>1352901351061</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 08:55:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352902167662-12</Id><Topic><Title>To whom it may concern.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1276031248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-06-08 17:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$...............</Msg><Username>tomjuliano2000</Username><Timestamp>1352902167662</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:09:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352902215056-13</Id><Title>Congrats!</Title><Msg>Have a great day!</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1352902215056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:10:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352902558347-14</Id><Topic><Title>If insiders and institutions own 80% of this stock and Yahoo buys back 15% of the float then what?</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352848719795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:18:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just a great big bullcrap machine, aren't you?</Msg><Username>sjones8924</Username><Timestamp>1352902558347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:15:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352902630142-15</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Yahoo Under $18 While You Can</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352829534724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo looks like it will go to $18 today.</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352902630142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:17:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352902742227-16</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Yahoo Under $18 While You Can</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352829534724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>chit man. While you were busy treading water for a year I was on Cirrus Logic riding it from $22 to $40 and Apple from 375 to 657. I am out there and got in here a few weeks back before last earnings below 16. I don't waste my time waiting. I just play when my internal signal tells me to. Like flies on chit</Msg><Username>ronnie_james_dio666</Username><Timestamp>1352902742227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:19:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352903008370-17</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats!</Title><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1352902215056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:10:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Welcome! Looks like rewards are finally coming to the patient ones.</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1352903008370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:23:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352903097249-18</Id><Topic><Title>If insiders and institutions own 80% of this stock and Yahoo buys back 15% of the float then what?</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352848719795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 18:18:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True but institutions are also value minded and prone to sell!</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1352903097249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:24:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352903216036-19</Id><Title>Would love to see an over $18 print today.</Title><Msg>And it very well may happen on our way to soon over $20 and, with or without a buyout, over $30.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352903216036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:26:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352904088995-20</Id><Title>Yahoo goes from $15.77 to $18 in three weeks</Title><Msg>Hey hotmodel, are you ready to say your Yahoo is dead money for 6 months to a year prediction was wrong or should we all just laugh at you?</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352904088995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352904551992-21</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo hits $18!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352904140055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:42:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo is now at $18.03. It looks like all the Yahoo shorts and bashers are long gone from being wrong so long.</Msg><Username>smedleypuddles</Username><Timestamp>1352904551992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:49:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352905181606-22</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Yahoo Under $18 While You Can</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352829534724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great advice as always from coldone.</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352905181606</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:59:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352905374102-23</Id><Topic><Title>To whom it may concern.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1276031248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-06-08 17:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo will have $7 trillion in cash soon. They will use the big truck for the second half of Yahoo's stake in Alibaba. That will be for $20 gazillion. In November Yahoo will get $700 umptillion from Yahoo! Japan. Pay a huge special dividend every day in December and buy Microsoft and Apple. Now start seriously buying. We can´t let Yahoo finish under $19. Make a short cry; buy, buy, buy!</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352905374102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:02:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352905431771-24</Id><Topic><Title>To whom it may concern.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1276031248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-06-08 17:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You cry like a Yahoo short that just lost everything.</Msg><Username>remmy12554</Username><Timestamp>1352905431771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:03:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352905665685-25</Id><Topic><Title>$17, the magic number.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352831390157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:29:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy Yhoo in the $17swhile you can....Buy Yhoo under $18 while you can..... they say but no $28 Yahoo long has posted a buy since Yahoo hit $17.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352905665685</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:07:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352905733725-26</Id><Title>Yahoo at $18 is this the Stock buy back from Alibaba proceeds?</Title><Msg>With Yahoo reaching new highs over $18 is yahoo putting the Alibaba sale money into the market in the form of a stock buyback?</Msg><Username>nystromwilliam</Username><Timestamp>1352905733725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:08:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352905976264-27</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo goes from $15.77 to $18 in three weeks</Title><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352904088995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:41:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo Alibaba taking away from Bidu?? is that why Yahoo is rising?? anyone?? love my Yahoo</Msg><Username>estanczyk</Username><Timestamp>1352905976264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352906058963-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo at $18 is this the Stock buy back from Alibaba proceeds?</Title><Username>nystromwilliam</Username><Timestamp>1352905733725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:08:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who knows when and at what price they re buying back,,but this thing just might get me all the money i got sunk into RBY back ! i swear i ll go sit in the corner with a beer and jo.</Msg><Username>toni19601</Username><Timestamp>1352906058963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:14:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352906456640-29</Id><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Msg>....those nut jobs to cover their shorts before $20. coldone is a clown but he sure does get under hotmodel's skin and make him do his little dance.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352907755620-30</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losses?bahahahaha Well if it isn't the loser Darien trying to act tough. I'm up over $3.50, haven't hit max profit, and own ZERO shares giving me an INFINITE return. How??? I put zero down all the while having a LOWER average than anyone whose bought in the last 52wks. Isn't it great how beneath me you really are #$%$ Burns your hide how your dumb topics get buried, as they should. One day, I'll make a topic, just to see if you want a job shining my shoes!hahahahaha</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid121</Username><Timestamp>1352907755620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:42:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352907893321-31</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey hotmodel, are you ready to say your Yahoo is dead money for 6 months to a year prediction was wrong or should we all just laugh at you?</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352907893321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:44:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352907962323-32</Id><Title>A few more days under $18 to prepare for the breakout...</Title><Msg>A few more days under $18 to prepare for the breakout...</Msg><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1352907962323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:46:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352908115341-33</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hotmodel has herself confused with coldone. Her condition is worsening.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1352908115341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:48:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352908603866-34</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats!</Title><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1352902215056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:10:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has taken a loooooooooooooooong time but the worm has turned.</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1352908603866</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:56:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352908625149-35</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you think you should let 6mos-1yr pass before being a d'bag??? At least wait till $20, as you'll finally have a gain but my return is FAR FAR FAR higher then any of your phantom buys. Are you saying getting a lower average then open market was a bad idea? How about not putting any capital in for shares yet get ALL the gains they do? Who cares if I max out in the $19-$20 range as I don't need a homerun like you...you haven't seen EVEN in half a decade.LOL Sad thing is chumps think I'm angry? For what? Calling out #$%$ who try to act tough while in my shadow.hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid121</Username><Timestamp>1352908625149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:57:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352908832576-36</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL!!!!!!!!!!!!! Yahoo is only going higher. Your dead money prediction was your best yet. It was wrong, but it was the best you could do.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1352908832576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:00:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352909029642-37</Id><Topic><Title>You should have listened to coldone</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1352653312441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:01:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coldone was right! I'm glad I listened to him. Too bad for hotmodel, lexi, framer, michan, allymarie, grey, dr.gloom and pearlprue.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1352909029642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352909337122-38</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you the same idiot who opened his yap when I bought puts on a Friday, made 83% Monday and you ate crow? How is your Dendreon you called "a hold" at $32 doing? Last I seen it was at $4. Yep! Clearly an ID as worthless as its creator. You must figure if you can't beat me you might as well annoy huh? Its not my fault you're an UNLOVED d'bag with no friends. Its amazing how many LONGS and SHORTS alike have hated you over the years. Rosie was a long you threw under the bus, MikeT(a war vet), and Morgan.Stanley. Now its Mewag and Basket who can't stand you. I bet your mother tried to throw your 666 a** down the toilet countless times and you just wouldn't flush.</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid121</Username><Timestamp>1352909337122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352909504786-39</Id><Topic><Title>You should have listened to coldone</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1352653312441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 12:01:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sooner or later this baby has to start jumping a couple of bucks a day like amazon did on its rise from 15 to 200 plus!</Msg><Username>gup1x</Username><Timestamp>1352909504786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:11:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352910258623-40</Id><Title>Holy volume Batman!! Gonna trade well over 30+ million shares today.. That is incredible!</Title><Msg>someone desperately trying to short this or let it run into oex on Friday. I just don't know how they are going to fight the Yahoo buyback going on and it could blow up in their faces. jmho</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352910258623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352910279673-41</Id><Title>Anyone know what all Wal*Mart told Marissa Ann</Title><Msg>before she got here? Dang! had to have been something cause here lately over half of my comments ain't getting posted over on the Wal*Mart site. Someone told me it smells in Denmark too.... but I ain't never been there.</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352910279673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:24:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352910757963-42</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone know what all Wal*Mart told Marissa Ann</Title><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352910279673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:24:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sure hope Merissa doesn't sit down wind from that O'fart on the Wal*Mart board of directors...</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352910757963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:32:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352911425106-43</Id><Title>Just read at Charles Schwab........ Aliababa sales last Sunday 3.06 Billion.................</Title><Msg>One Day, unbelievable......</Msg><Username>denehenry</Username><Timestamp>1352911425106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:43:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352911487369-44</Id><Topic><Title>Just read at Charles Schwab........ Aliababa sales last Sunday 3.06 Billion.................</Title><Username>denehenry</Username><Timestamp>1352911425106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know crazy!! The one thing we don't know is the margins on that day... Were they their usual 25% or 2% or somewhere in the middle?</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352911487369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:44:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352911674169-45</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch hotmodel continue to make a fool of herself. When will she just stop?</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352911674169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:47:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352911728007-46</Id><Topic><Title>Just read at Charles Schwab........ Aliababa sales last Sunday 3.06 Billion.................</Title><Username>denehenry</Username><Timestamp>1352911425106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:43:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope we never sell our other 23%...............</Msg><Username>denehenry</Username><Timestamp>1352911728007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352911784860-47</Id><Title>I heard that Shep lady over on the Wal*Mart board has 394,817,625 ID's</Title><Msg>I got one. Why does she rate?</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352911784860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352911812173-48</Id><Title>Yahoo is making another acquisition.</Title><Msg>My sources tell me that Dan Loeb has convinced MM to exchange new shares of Yahoo Preferred (6% Yield) for his stakes in Liberty Global (LBTYK &amp; LBTYA) In exchange for getting Dan out of his positions at a tax free profit with continued income stream, MM can grant her executive team each 500,000 additional Yahoo options and MM is receiving a grant of 100,000 Yahoo Preferred. Dan also approved MM's plan to buy 3 companies that her husband's VC firm owns. My sources believe these deals will close around December 15th of this year. This will expand Yahoo's scope of services to include wind turbines, medical equipment (subject to Obamacares 25% medical equipment tax), and all natural male enhancement.</Msg><Username>ypr4yss</Username><Timestamp>1352911812173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:50:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352912077739-49</Id><Topic><Title>Hello $20's. Goldman Sachs will move PT from $22?</Title><Username>mapiaman</Username><Timestamp>1352903985922</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 09:39:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alvin moved it down to $12.... something about dots....</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352912077739</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 11:54:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352913626432-50</Id><Title>Is it true when you translate "Macallister" into Chinese</Title><Msg>it means "come here."</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352913626432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 12:20:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352913704098-51</Id><Topic><Title>The huge breakout on $18 is coming soon...</Title><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1352835397978</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:36:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is stupid selling now?</Msg><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1352913704098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 12:21:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352914308381-52</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't use the word hate, I believe, but can't stand you is a severe disliking. You called him a jackazz afterall. This guy is pretty simple really. 1. He makes phantom buys boosting only those that turn green 2. Creates ID's to support these buys 3. If you should happen to call him out on his lies he goes ballistic turning it on YOU as the liar and bad guy. 4. Most important of all he HATES HATES HATES people who have real profit!!!! He probably went off his meds this week and about to be placed in a dog kennel for foaming at the mouth!hahaha Oh and for some odd reason he saves my stuff then uses it later. I absolutely agree though as life is way too short. Only 2 have ever made my list, a future female lawyer I went out with who liked to argue and my sister-in-law. 2 out of what 7B people that's damn good!lol</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid121</Username><Timestamp>1352914308381</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 12:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352916748714-53</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Tangible Asset Value is $19.4 billion.</Title><Username>barloparlo</Username><Timestamp>1344014613178</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 13:23:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strong Buy ! $57 end 2013</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1352916748714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:12:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352916773464-54</Id><Title>If there is a room 130 at the Li Ka Shing Center at Stanford Medical School</Title><Msg>call the Jerry Yang Lecture Hall.... Has Marissa Ann Mayer have a room somewhere on the Leland Stanford Junior University campus too... Wal*Mart partnered with Li Ka-shing back in 2006 on a port in Mexico... and wasn't Marissa sitting on Wal*Mart's board before she became Yahoo's CEO.... Hey! anyone know where Jerry is hanging out these days?</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352916773464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:12:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352917067684-55</Id><Topic><Title>Poor hotmodel and Dr. Gloom (same person?) are getting increasingly desperate as their losses mount. Time for....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352906456640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 10:20:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argue??? But I'm never wrong!jk I don't mind a good discussion but admittedly those are few and far between. Last night, I seen that MSFT should pay the $45B again with no facts to back it up. Today, Eric Jackson assigned the core a value of $7.8B, far less then the $20B+ that last nights poster had. Oh and that $7.8B, is ballbark to what I've said all summer and bumped a post to show it. Wierd thing happened a few days ago, Eric Jackson somehow found my Linkedin profile. They gave a list of 5 names from "Executive Leadership in Naples Florida" but the others had no link to me or a handful of contacts so barely used. I did write on the bottom of his Forbes article though which I'm sure he didn't like. Odd as I gave no indication of name or location. That's a very good question! Perhaps cause the ratio of women I've known vs. the number of dudes is skewed in their favor. Besides dudes can "discuss" sports for a few minutes and then drink beer afterwards. Women are like word assassins or ninjas that after thinking about it you're like 'no she didn't"bahahahahaha</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid121</Username><Timestamp>1352917067684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:17:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352917793388-56</Id><Topic><Title>If there is a room 130 at the Li Ka Shing Center at Stanford Medical School</Title><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352916773464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw Jerry in HK 3 weeks ago</Msg><Username>mrs_vomit</Username><Timestamp>1352917793388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:29:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352917824462-57</Id><Topic><Title>If there is a room 130 at the Li Ka Shing Center at Stanford Medical School</Title><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352916773464</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:12:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you know Li Ka-shing controls both ends of the Panama Canal.... that's kinda strange.... One person having that much control....</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352917824462</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 13:30:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352919605069-58</Id><Title>Happy that YHOO is up on this down day but we need a FB like move (up 10% today-just when many shares....</Title><Msg>....shares come on the market and a big fall was expected) to get us into the $20's. When stocks begin big up moves the first steps are often small and then get bigger (that seems to be starting now w/ YHOO). We will get some dollar plus moves and any potential buyer should move soon. From $20, a $30 offer is only a 50% premium.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1352919605069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:00:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352919798537-59</Id><Title>Guys..CXM is a scam like SAPX!!</Title><Msg>Just saying, you don't want what has happened to SAPX to happen to CXM! Not bashing, just saying, I was in this earlier in the year and looks like its done nothing but gone down even more!</Msg><Username>mr.finance22</Username><Timestamp>1352919798537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:03:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352919900657-60</Id><Topic><Title>Guys..CXM is a scam like SAPX!!</Title><Username>mr.finance22</Username><Timestamp>1352919798537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:03:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oops, wrong board!</Msg><Username>mr.finance22</Username><Timestamp>1352919900657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:05:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352923013211-61</Id><Title>Red purdy</Title><Msg>ain't it...</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352923013211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:56:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352926085670-62</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Yahoo Under $18 While You Can</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352829534724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 12:58:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bought at $17.80.</Msg><Username>thurstonthethird</Username><Timestamp>1352926085670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 15:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352926511185-63</Id><Title>Yahoo's Remaining Stake In Alibaba Could Be Worth Its Current Market Cap By Next Year</Title><Msg>Yahoo‘s (YHOO) stock has been on a run in the last 3 months – at least by Yahoostandards. It’s up 21% over that time, while the Nasdaq has dropped 4.6% Yahoo is not dead money. Its current market capitalization is $21 billion. At the moment, Yahoo consists of its core business that new CEO Marissa Mayer has been focusing on improving, its 35% stake in Yahoo Japan, and its remaining 24% stake in Alibaba Group. Yahoo’s got $5B in cash (after they pay the IRS taxes on the first Alibaba stake sale). Its Yahoo Japan is worth $4.1B (post-tax). And its Alibaba stake is worth $6.9B (post-tax) using that group’s last private round of financing just below $50B. Meantime, Yahoo’s core business generated $1.3B in EBITDA last year. If you assigned it the same enterprise value to EBTIDA valuation that AOL (AOL) has, the core business is worth $7.8B. Add it up and you’ve got a collection of assets (post-tax) worth $24B, which is still more than the current market cap. To get to an AOL-type “fair” valuation, you’d need to see the stock rise to $20/share at the current share count. Read more at Forbes</Msg><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1352926511185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 15:55:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352926841688-64</Id><Title>Bought at $17.83</Title><Msg>Grabbed some Yahoo at the close at $17.83.</Msg><Username>trotlightly34</Username><Timestamp>1352926841688</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 16:00:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352927214763-65</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Remaining Stake In Alibaba Could Be Worth Its Current Market Cap By Next Year</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1352926511185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 15:55:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice find, toad!</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1352927214763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 16:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352931413767-66</Id><Title>David Einhorn just bought 4 million shares of Yahoo in the 3rd quarter!!</Title><Msg>Awesome!! Everyone turning to Yahoo!!</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352931413767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:16:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352931621244-67</Id><Topic><Title>David Einhorn just bought 4 million shares of Yahoo in the 3rd quarter!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352931413767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:16:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Among the many moves revealed in Einhorn's latest 13F filing, is the initiation of a hefty position of roughly 4 million Yahoo! shares during the third quarter. Who is short Yahoo?</Msg><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1352931621244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:20:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352931982573-68</Id><Topic><Title>DOW at 5 Month Low, Yahoo at 17 Month High</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352931384504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:16:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe 10-20 million shares at the most, imo. I think the best they can do is 5-7 million a week without spiking the price like crazy. Buybacks take a very long time especially when you are trying to buy back 15%-20% of your float. People are just beginning to realize that yahoo's stock is about $8 too low. The value of COH, Yahoo Japan, and Alibaba, is over 22 billion pretax and that is what we are trading at now. So basically they are valuing Yahoo's business at $0.... Also, Alibaba value may be worth $100-$150b in just a couple of years. There is a put option in Yahoo now at $17+ with little to no risk in investing. I really believe Yahoo will go over $21 by next earnings. Again, all jmho</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352931982573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:26:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352932309020-69</Id><Topic><Title>Greenlight Capital moves in!!</Title><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1304348685000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-05-02 11:04:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was May 2, 2011 and Yahoo closed at $18.14 Then May 16, 2011 Yahoo closed at $15.81</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1352932309020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:31:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352935192460-70</Id><Topic><Title>Greenlight Capital moves in!!</Title><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1304348685000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-05-02 11:04:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bloomberg article from late this afternoon. Einhorn’s fund purchased a 5.05 million-share stake in Yahoo and added 4.16 million GM shares during the three months ended Sept. 30, according to a filing with the Securities and Exchange Commission today. The hedge fund sold 2.29 million shares of UnitedHealth, 4.59 million in CareFusion (CFN) Corp. and 2.09 million in Hess, representing all its shares in each. The Yahoo purchase represents Einhorn’s third foray into the stock in the last year and a half. He announced buying a stake in May 2011, sold it two months later, said he bought another in February and said in May he sold again.</Msg><Username>kenrsmith2003</Username><Timestamp>1352935192460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:19:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352935947798-71</Id><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Msg>That is crazy! 25 million shares in a new initiated holding of Yahoo!! This is great news!</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352936266165-72</Id><Title>Einhorn, Grenn light, and Loeb now own 10% of Yahoo!!</Title><Msg>This is great news. What it says to me is there is less and less float for the company to buy back shares and any time they try the stock will spike!! Everyone now seeing the value! Alibaba will take us over 30 by the end of 2013. jmho</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352936266165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:37:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352936934140-73</Id><Topic><Title>Einhorn, Grenn light, and Loeb now own 10% of Yahoo!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352936266165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another beaten-down tech company also got some hedge fund attention in the third quarter: Yahoo Inc, which nabbed Marissa Mayer to head the company from rival Google Inc. Coleman's Tiger Global opened a new position of 25 million shares, David Einhorn's Greenlight Capital built a 5 million share new position and Dan Loeb's Third Point, already a major Yahoo investor, raised its stake to 73 million shares from 70.5 million three month earlier. Yahoo shares have gained 14 percent since Mayer was appointed chief executive officer on July 16. On Wednesday, the shares lost 2 cents, or 0.1 percent, to close at $17.83.</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352936934140</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:48:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352939103626-74</Id><Topic><Title>DOW at 5 Month Low, Yahoo at 17 Month High</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1352931384504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 17:16:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>David Einhorn's Greenlight Capital (5 million shares) and Chase Coleman and Feroz Dewan's Tiger Global (25 million shares) have been buying Yahoo. Yahoo's recent 21% jump is from outside buying. Yahoo's $3 billion buyback is next. Like Eric Jackson said, Wait Until They Really Start Buying!</Msg><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1352939103626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 19:25:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352939187172-75</Id><Topic><Title>Red purdy</Title><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352923013211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 14:56:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you didn't know you were colorblind... you do now.</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352939187172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 19:26:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352939473384-76</Id><Topic><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sorry for your stupidity. 2.5% new interest means 2.5% more of what they already had and not 2.5% of the whole YHOO shares. For example if you have 1000 shares, adding 25 shares is adding 2.5% more shares. Very soon, YHOO will drop and many newbies will be burnt again. YHOO is a great company but it is overvalued now.</Msg><Username>hajimow</Username><Timestamp>1352939473384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 19:31:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352940082423-77</Id><Topic><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you really invest real money? They initiated a new holding in Yahoo. They previously owned zero shares but bought 25 million during the 3rd quarter. Also, they now own 25 million shares which is 2.5% of Yahoo's 1 billion share float. Please get your facts straight before you mock someone.</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352940082423</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 19:41:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352943538825-78</Id><Topic><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just answered your question. They bought YHOO shares by the end of September when the shares were depressed aand were in $15 range and not today at $18. Three months later when the shares are $15 (let's just assume), you will hear that Tiger capital has sold his shares in November and then you will start to follow Tiger capital and sell your shares at $15 :).</Msg><Username>hajimow</Username><Timestamp>1352943538825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 20:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352944834116-79</Id><Topic><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You hit the nail. Theses reports are always misleading because many people do not realize the huge time lag.</Msg><Username>caixujin</Username><Timestamp>1352944834116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:00:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352945869510-80</Id><Title>Wal*Mart has their Global Procurement Office in China.</Title><Msg>Do you know the reason they ask to see all fifty state capital blueprints? Does Marissa Ann know? She was on their board before she was here.</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352945869510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:17:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352946100467-81</Id><Topic><Title>Tiger Capital takes a 2.5% new interest in Yahoo!! Holy cow 25 million shares!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352935947798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 18:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of these managers will sell until Yahoo is at least $23-$25. There is now a $17 put under the stock for all of its cash on hand and its holdings in Alibaba and Yahoo Japan. Also, it is said that Alibaba is really worth $100 billion. That would put yahoo's stake worth around $24 billion. Again I will state this! Yahoo is worth twice what it is trading at. Why do you think a fund like Tiger Capital invested 5% of its total worth into the company? These guys do more deep research than all of us on this board combined times 100!</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352946100467</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:21:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352946483228-82</Id><Title>I am expecting a 1 time dividend... Too many of Yahoo shares are now tied up and unavailable for trade</Title><Msg>due to big funds now holding even more of the stock... I do not believe Yahoo will be able to repurchase much more stock without spiking the stock to $25+.. People do not understand how long and difficult it is to buy back stock when there is over 90% of you o/s are tied up with insiders, institutions, and long term holders. I believe there may be only 100-200m shares available to trade. I believe that by the next earnings you may get a one time dividend because the company only bought back $300+ million in shares. This of course is jmho... Either way it is good!!</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352946483228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:28:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352947927864-83</Id><Title>my yahoo just lost another link</Title><Msg>No more LA Times available on Myyahoo- basically it's just yahoo news now. But at least no banner ads - which may indicate that Yahoo is hurting financially (more hurting). My Yahoo keeps losing content (no bucks) and losing advertising (no bucks). But they still pay people to muck with the content they provide and their financial message boards. Its all free, so what's to complain about - nothing - I'm just switching over the MSN as my home page. Any other suggestions</Msg><Username>bzusa6</Username><Timestamp>1352947927864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:52:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352949313841-84</Id><Topic><Title>I am expecting a 1 time dividend... Too many of Yahoo shares are now tied up and unavailable for trade</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352946483228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:28:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The longer that wad of money sits in a Yahoo bank account; the less likely it is that a dividend will be paid. If it not done before year end, you can forget about it. XQ</Msg><Username>xquestor</Username><Timestamp>1352949313841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 22:15:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352950777359-85</Id><Topic><Title>my yahoo just lost another link</Title><Username>bzusa6</Username><Timestamp>1352947927864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:52:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not being on the internet would be the best.... most is like Retail anyway... it makes NOTHING.</Msg><Username>madmilker70</Username><Timestamp>1352950777359</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 22:39:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352950781611-86</Id><Topic><Title>my yahoo just lost another link</Title><Username>bzusa6</Username><Timestamp>1352947927864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:52:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're hilarious. Good luck with that.</Msg><Username>lnhirst</Username><Timestamp>1352950781611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 22:39:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352950852060-87</Id><Topic><Title>I am expecting a 1 time dividend... Too many of Yahoo shares are now tied up and unavailable for trade</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1352946483228</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 21:28:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a CEO that is very hard to read her mind. This will only tell me that she is very "sophisticated CEO". We can only speculate what she will do or decide to give shareholders a one-time special cash dividend or not. I hope she will give us shareholders say $1 to $2 special cash dividend as well as continue her share buyback and small to medium acquisition that will help to increase revenue.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1352950852060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 22:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352952634474-88</Id><Title>Anyone hear from Jack Welch?</Title><Msg>Anyone hear from Welch about the re-election of President Obama? Or about the unemployment rate still under 8 percent? Is the old fool still around or gone into hiding?</Msg><Username>abksmin</Username><Timestamp>1352952634474</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 23:10:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>