<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349843512482-1</Id><Title>this whole PC industry going down is full of B and S</Title><Msg>this whole PC industry going down is full of #$%$. it ain't going anywhere but up! Tablets and smartphones aren't taking anything away from PCs. both form factors will co-exist.</Msg><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349843512482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349843677650-2</Id><Topic><Title>DELL was Neutral at Citi, and now tonight Citi inititiated at Sell, isn't that a downgrade ?</Title><Username>rickstewhennberg</Username><Timestamp>1349752868772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:21:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bring the price down further so I can buy at further bargain please.</Msg><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349843677650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349848087656-3</Id><Topic><Title>this whole PC industry going down is full of B and S</Title><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349843512482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agree.</Msg><Username>peterwangy</Username><Timestamp>1349848087656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 01:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349858028252-4</Id><Topic><Title>this whole PC industry going down is full of B and S</Title><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349843512482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All companies have to use PC to do business. Smartphones and tablets are for people in streets, and not for business. I've heard "PC is dying" for years, but don't forget that is computer that bring the new era to the world - the time of IT.</Msg><Username>espero616</Username><Timestamp>1349858028252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 04:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349873167204-5</Id><Title>ADD while the shorts are getting in deeper....</Title><Msg>There is no question that the shorts and their analysts are all out in full force to beat up the PCs just before the Windows 8 release..... Yesterday we got the downwind off Intel's downgrade as last week we got hit by HP's CEO's tragic performance..... Buy all you can as the shorts have to buy it back sooner than they think.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349873167204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349876613924-6</Id><Topic><Title>ADD while the shorts are getting in deeper....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349873167204</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:46:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let Windows 8 kill the shorts!</Msg><Username>king_kim_1</Username><Timestamp>1349876613924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349877033746-7</Id><Topic><Title>Are the shorts trapped?</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349711541585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes they are!</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349877033746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878326345-8</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts' analyst caught lying about DELL....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349395836256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There have been more lies in the past few days.... Keep adding as the shorts need to buy it back sooner than they thought!</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349878326345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349878447429-9</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling on low volume....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349799649571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is all short selling today, although on high volume so far.... They will cover or die poor!</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349878447429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882781447-10</Id><Topic><Title>Are the shorts trapped?</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349711541585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how can you distinguish longs selling from shorts selling? And maybe teh shorts you see on a trading platform are just market makers hedging options.</Msg><Username>kenberthiaume123</Username><Timestamp>1349882781447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349882932079-11</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For DELL</Title><Username>rosariopriscilla416</Username><Timestamp>1349872281501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:31:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>beautiful women always come around when there is money. the game is get those beautiful women to pay for you :)</Msg><Username>huffmanbradford848</Username><Timestamp>1349882932079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349884236547-12</Id><Title>when do they buyback the whole company?</Title><Msg>At $5 I think they can buy the company from cash on hand.</Msg><Username>kenberthiaume123</Username><Timestamp>1349884236547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 11:50:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886397487-13</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling on low volume....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349799649571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's longs selling, not shorts. Stock going down does not equal shorts. To believe it does, means that you think if there were no shorting, then stocks would never fall. That is not true.</Msg><Username>kenberthiaume123</Username><Timestamp>1349886397487</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:26:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349886525813-14</Id><Title>50M shares short...</Title><Msg>that's very little out of 1,750 million. About 3%. Shorting is not the reason this stock is going down. So knock off the idiocy.</Msg><Username>kenberthiaume123</Username><Timestamp>1349886525813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349886753289-15</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For DELL</Title><Username>rosariopriscilla416</Username><Timestamp>1349872281501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:31:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounds good to me. with everything that's happening, i'd hate to be on the sidelines when it pops again.</Msg><Username>bradfordcharles289</Username><Timestamp>1349886753289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349887240049-16</Id><Topic><Title>This is all short selling on low volume....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349799649571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-09 12:20:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Dell shorts are what you call "the smart money." You longs are bagholders with nothing to back up your irrational optimism. </Msg><Username>rmbo47</Username><Timestamp>1349887240049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 12:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349891815936-17</Id><Topic><Title>Plan Your Next Move For DELL</Title><Username>rosariopriscilla416</Username><Timestamp>1349872281501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 08:31:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i am sure we will get a reward .i got some news from the market that the stock would grow double</Msg><Username>oneal_bruce</Username><Timestamp>1349891815936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 13:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896042098-18</Id><Title>Tangent buying will start soon.</Title><Msg>Tangent buying will start soon</Msg><Username>king_kim_1</Username><Timestamp>1349896042098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349896836029-19</Id><Title>M.Dell is such a crook - he settled 100M with SEC</Title><Msg>for committing fraud - BK is ahead!!!!!! he's crooked billionaire! DELL/INTC/BRCM/HPQ/CSCO will file chapter 11 soon or later because CEO/BOD/Employees' bonuses and stock options are outrageous and furious...who pay all that? Hope you stay away from those companies!!!!!!!!! Thanks me later!</Msg><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349896836029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349897849584-20</Id><Topic><Title>M.Dell is such a crook - he settled 100M with SEC</Title><Username>exposecrooks</Username><Timestamp>1349896836029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:20:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did you short ayt $9.35, hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>king_kim_1</Username><Timestamp>1349897849584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 15:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349904251502-21</Id><Title>Death of the PC is the biggest fraud since Y2K....</Title><Msg>A new report predicts worldwide sales of personal computers are bound for their first annual decline in 11 years. The forecast issued Wednesday by the research firm IHS iSuppli projects that nearly 349 million PCs will be shipped this year. That would be a 1 percent decrease from nearly 353 million PC shipments last year. So all this noisy stupidity is about 1% decline from 2011! #$%$ is going on?</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349904251502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349905073544-22</Id><Topic><Title>Death of the PC is the biggest fraud since Y2K....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349904251502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like DELL's overall market share went to 10.5%, from 11.2% in Q3/2012 or just .7% and its market cap got halved!!!! The third quarter was also impacted by customers delaying orders for Windows 8.... "The third quarter was also a transitional quarter before Microsoft‘s Windows 8 operating system release, so shipments were less vigorous as vendors and their channel partners liquidated inventory.” He adds that retailers were conservative in placing orders due to weak back-to-school sales. In the quarter, Lenovo moved past Hewlett-Packard to become the world’s leading PC vendor. Lenovo had 15.7% of the market, up from 13.1% in the year ago quarter. HP’s share dipped to 15.5%, from 17%. Dell dipped to 10.5%, from 11.2%. Acer, with 9.9%, and Asus, with 7.3%, round out the top five". So all this noise, as I wrote before, is to FLEECE the investors before October 25/2012 when Windows 8 is released, as we will kick the shorts in the head on or before that day.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349905073544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349908129592-23</Id><Topic><Title>Death of the PC is the biggest fraud since Y2K....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349904251502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So basically 1 out of 15 DELL customers either delayed purchase waiting for Windows 8 or bought a Tablet and that both would be fixed in two weeks.... I have a feeling we will have much better than expectations for both Rev. and the EPS and hope the management will blunt the shorts with a upgraded guidance in a few days.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349908129592</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349909296163-24</Id><Title>UBS reports on DELL....</Title><Msg>UBS’s Steve Milunovich this morning reiterates a Neutral rating on Dell (DELL) while writing that his recent meetings with Dell executives, in particular Jeff Clarke, Dell’s head of global operations, suggest to him that leaving aside the PC business, Dell could surprise over the longer term based on the strength of its enterprise business. On the one hand, Dell is doing its best to make an encouraging story about future PC growth, despite the pall cast over the industry by the dour outlook from Hewlett-Packard (HPQ) last week : Management maintains that PCs will grow as the world’s middle class almost doubles by 2020. Although we are not convinced, we are impressed by Dell’s efforts to take $1bn of client cost out and by its margin advantage with 70% of PCs sold direct. However, Milunovich is more interested in what Dell’s David Johnson, head of strategy, describes as a more nimble enterprise hardware strategy: CFO Brian Gladden said his recent discussions with investors have been 75% about PCs, 15% about acquisitions, and 10% about everything else. We think investors may be underappreciating Dell’s enterprise potential. The company’s goal is to grow enterprise computing’s operating income contribution from about 43% today to 60% in F2016. Management believes the industry is at an inflection point, not just in moving to cloud computing but in pursuing a lower-cost infrastructure approach. Steve Felice, Chief Commercial Officer, said there is a change in conversations with CIOs in that they increasingly agree with Dell that more agile and modular approach is needed. In fact, he says they are concerned that Cisco, IBM, and other single-solution vendors may not give objective advice, providing an opening for Dell. David Johnson, head of Corporate Strategy, says the last 20 years were about increasing hardware efficiency, most recently through virtualization. The next step is to simplify the architecture through (1) a next-generation memory architecture Dell will begin introducing later this year, (2) multi-tenancy in clouds, and (3) mirroring public cloud with the same private cloud infrastructure, allowing workloads to move seamlessly between the two. No longer do IT departments need to size themselves for peak loads, which run 5x average loads. The new infrastructure dovetails with Dell’s efforts with respect to cloud computing, argues Milunovich: Like HP, Dell controls the server, storage, and network so it can provide a converged infrastructure box (pod). Dell will be introducing its first full- function offering in the next few months. Furthermore, it will need cloud offerings, particularly since SMB could be the cloud sweet spot. Dell expects that private cloud will dominate even SMB, however, as these firms are concerned about losing data. Consequently, most of Dell’s work will be on premise or mirroring customers’ equipment in one of Dell’s 12 data centers. Dell argues that infrastructure providers have the advantage in hybrid clouds; our guess is that selling cloud will be one of Dell’s foremost enterprise challenges. Milunovich’s stock advice is to stay away for the moment because near-term results are under pressure. But he advises to watch for “new converged infrastructure offerings” by the end of this year.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349909296163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 18:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349914030401-25</Id><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Msg>Based on the data published this afternoon, DELL's decline in PC sales is about .7% of its market share of 11.2% or 6.25% of its sales from a year ago.... DELL's earnings come about 50% from the PCs so the net effect from last year's EPS of 54 Cents should be: (27 X .9375) + 27 or (25.3125 + 27 ) = 52.3125 Cents if there was no growth on the Enterprise side.... So when I read the UBS report and sense the confidence of the DELL management, I think we will handily beat the 40 Cents consensus and rocket up.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349914869036-26</Id><Title>What the shorts accomplished this week?</Title><Msg>On Monday we went up to $9.84 despite all the bogus opinions from paid bashers posing as analysts, then came two other bogus downgrades, one for Intel and then for DELL; so we closed today at $9.43 and all they could manage to do was to move the 52 week low by one Cent! Let's hope the management will be issuing a guidance in the coming days.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349914869036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349915414356-27</Id><Title>Next stop 8.25</Title><Msg>Chart not pretty. Dell headed to He11 in a bucket. Michael Dell will need to sell his beach house in the Cayman islands just to pay this months electric bill on his Stadium-Sized Mansion. Poor Michael.</Msg><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1349915414356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:30:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349917407303-28</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Osso, thanks this is good stuff as all the nonsense of the death of PC will be causing massive short squeeze of biblical proportions (will de the death of PC shorts via heartattack). All the shorts managed to do was to rip each other off as there is no sell off and that most of the volume is to short and cover and hope someone panics and sells. Your numbers make good sense.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349917407303</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349918353539-29</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No problem. You see if their PC side was down 6.25% that "cannot and does not" translate to nearly 30% decline in earnings (54 Cents last year for the Q3 vs consensus of 40 Cents for this quarter). Their Enterprise side has been growing in their number 1&amp;2 markets in the US and China so we should expect an uptick or the worst case scenario, even with last year. Finally Windows 8 will settle the score in two weeks as all those who delayed buying will pile into Q4 and with Xmas, it should be a great quarter.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349918353539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349919299222-30</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree as for the earnings to go from 54 to 40 Cents, they had to take a 55% decline in PC sales as half of the earnings come from the enterprise side and with only 6.25% decline in PC shipments in the quarter past, the current estimates look messed up to me.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349919299222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 21:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349923107094-31</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm with you. I would have to guess that, at DELL's current market cap, the PC portion of the business is being valued at zero. Even so, their PC business gives DELL the of cash flow it needs to grow their more profitable business lines, acquire businesses, pay the dividend, etc. Not pounding the table, but I think the selling is overdone.</Msg><Username>dkvw99</Username><Timestamp>1349923107094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 22:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349927145396-32</Id><Topic><Title>Death of the PC is the biggest fraud since Y2K....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349904251502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 17:24:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pc industry eroding is a croc of #$%$. tablets and smartphones aren't taking anything away from pc. both form factors will co-exist. PC industry isn't going anywhere but up. but we ought to be mindful of these facts though... 1. chinese, taiwanese, korean [lenovo, acer, samsung] manufacturers taking market share away from american makers[hp, dell]. these foreign players are definitely making an impact and it is only increasing by the day. got to give it to them...they are bringing more innovative, diversified products to market faster and at a low cost. 2. avg. lifespan of a PC is now longer. in the past, 3 years seemed like an avg. age of a laptop held by a consumer. today, i think that avg. has increased to around 4 or 5 years. [one reason for this could be because the apps are not pushing the performance boundary of today's hardware except for gaming maybe; take the case of consoles - xbox and ps3, the last refresh was over 6 years ago. what they have done is add cheap accessories like move controller, kinect to continue to use 6 year old tech; game makers are perfectly happy with the hardware performance envelope of the systems]</Msg><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349927145396</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:45:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349927262970-33</Id><Topic><Title>this whole PC industry going down is full of B and S</Title><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349843512482</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 00:31:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but we ought to be mindful of these facts though... 1. chinese, taiwanese, korean [lenovo, acer, samsung] manufacturers taking market share away from american makers[hp, dell]. these foreign players are definitely making an impact and it is only increasing by the day. got to give it to them...they are bringing more innovative, diversified products to market faster and at a low cost. 2. avg. lifespan of a PC is now longer. in the past, 3 years seemed like an avg. age of a laptop held by a consumer. today, i think that avg. has increased to around 4 or 5 years. [one reason for this could be because the apps are not pushing the performance boundary of today's hardware except for gaming maybe; take the case of consoles - xbox and ps3, the last refresh was over 6 years ago. what they have done is add cheap accessories like move controller, kinect to continue to use 6 year old tech; game makers are perfectly happy with the hardware performance envelope of the systems]</Msg><Username>andypost167</Username><Timestamp>1349927262970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 23:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>