<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353242200477-1</Id><Title>Shorts are playing DELL like they played RIMM a few weeks ago....</Title><Msg>With the exact same doom and gloom nonsense and drove RIMM to $6.22.... It is now up 50% trading around $9.50 and that DELL is a much bigger company, more diversified and with a much stronger balance sheet.... Windows 8 and our Tablets would turn things around and as the IT spending takes off after 4 years of decline, we would be trading around $20 much sooner than the shorts can say cover!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353242200477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 07:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353251933470-2</Id><Title>TTNP Filed a Priority Review NDA for the Huge Opiate Addiction Market</Title><Msg>Over 14M individuals are addicted to pain meds and illicit drugs. TTNP ha a 6 month, slow release, abuse proof medication. A Big Pharma partnership or buyout is expected any day. Check it out.</Msg><Username>jennifer_jkarim</Username><Timestamp>1353251933470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 10:18:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353266585245-3</Id><Title>Dell is a good buy</Title><Msg>It isn't sexy. But at a PE of 5 you get your money back in 5 years. DELL will buy back half the shares between now and 2018 if the stock stays down. At a PE of 5 they can actually buy back stock faster than the sales of PCs are declining. So as to keep earnings from falling. Makes sense to me anyway.</Msg><Username>csco_brat</Username><Timestamp>1353266585245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 14:23:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353297808400-4</Id><Title>Wow, DELL has a bunch of new and exciting XPS tablets.</Title><Msg>Yeah, like who cares. This company may have turned out its last piece of crap and not a minute too soon. Nobody wants tablets and nobody wants another version of Windows. This is a double yawn fest. Jeeeezus.</Msg><Username>vinnie_baggadonitz</Username><Timestamp>1353297808400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-18 23:03:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>