<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350107677056-1</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend</Title><Username>fatcat49</Username><Timestamp>1350060326091</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will receive dividend on 10/22/2012.</Msg><Username>shen16326</Username><Timestamp>1350107677056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350132433193-2</Id><Title>DELL is Bullish on America. Dell Inc. Never Sleeps</Title><Msg>I couldnt help but marvel at DELL, its been been making headlines all morning and at the rate its moving, it has great potenital to explode. DELL buyers are sure to gain for the short term, and i have no doubt in my mind that it will be a great pick to hold also. Information is essential, so check out this.... for the full report. Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- mcaf.ee/x07ma</Msg><Username>thompsonbryon460</Username><Timestamp>1350132433193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350134706259-3</Id><Topic><Title>DELL is Bullish on America. Dell Inc. Never Sleeps</Title><Username>thompsonbryon460</Username><Timestamp>1350132433193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope this is good. Subscribed!</Msg><Username>rhonda.browning47</Username><Timestamp>1350134706259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:25:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350135773621-4</Id><Topic><Title>What's next for Windows 8?</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350089579743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 20:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Osso, thanks for the details.... The fact is that when DELL dipped under $10.00 after HP's CEO's tragic performance, the shorts knew that the only way to kill the PPs was to get their paid analysts and bashers issue death threats and kill the buy support before the Windows 8 show gets underway.... And as we can see, with a slight hint that "pre-ordering" by DELL has started, the sentiment shifted in matter of seconds and I expect Intel to beat their estimates, as they are also hit by the Windows 8 delays and that their sales will perhaps shrink by 7% as was already announced by Intel and as is priced in and some.... AMD's demise was long anticipated as "I Hate Intel Camp" has been pumping AMD for over a decade or so but to no avail. Short squeeze to start on Tuesday.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350135773621</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350136054172-5</Id><Topic><Title>DELL is Bullish on America. Dell Inc. Never Sleeps</Title><Username>thompsonbryon460</Username><Timestamp>1350132433193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So it is a good buy premarket right now?</Msg><Username>carminecarr840</Username><Timestamp>1350136054172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350150574873-6</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Yahoo Finance charts - all on one screen - for free</Title><Username>kevininthecity72</Username><Timestamp>1350146442585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:40:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ok so as far as I can see this is free. i just tried it and it works pretty well</Msg><Username>peelingoutsummer</Username><Timestamp>1350150574873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350151710811-7</Id><Topic><Title>What's next for Windows 8?</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350089579743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 20:52:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual when so many voices are saying Sell, it only means one thing: they are about to go Long and Buy big. This is the downside of this business as we have a bunch of crooks and felons posing as analysts claiming they have your best interest at heart, who rob the investors blind day in and day out.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350151710811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152033656-8</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Earnings Estimates 50 cents plus....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349914030401</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 20:07:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My analysis is based on the math that describes what actually has happened as opposed to death of the PC slogans as these slogans are broadcast using a PC! Isn't that funny!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350152033656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153181072-9</Id><Title>Short squeeze on Monday as Pre-Launch Order Data will be out....</Title><Msg>Will be blood all over shortland.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350153181072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153714527-10</Id><Title>Dell Puts Its Windows 8 Line-up Up for Pre-order</Title><Msg>After nearly 10 months of trade shows filled to the rafters with Windows 8 devices, we're finally going to see some of them in the flesh. And. with the Windows 8 launch almost upon us, manufacturers are starting to officially announce their Windows 8 wares. Today, Dell put two new XPS PCs and one Inspiron up for pre-order for folks in the United States and Canada. The most interesting of the three is definitely the XPS 12 convertible, which folks will likely remember because of the Dell Inspiron Duo. The laptop features a full keyboard and the usual hinged display. Where it differs from other convertibles is that the entire lid doesn't swivel around or fold backwards. Instead, just the screen itself flips, doing so inside the bezel of the laptop. You simply spin the display and close the lid to turn your computer into a tablet. The base model ships with a third generation Intel Core i5-3317U, Intel 4000 HD graphics, 4GB of DDR3, and a 128GB SSD. Next is the XPS One 27, which is a high performance touch screen all-in-one (AIO) aimed the creative enthusiast. It boasts 27-inch Wide Quad HD Display and an articulating stand that tilts the display to a 60-degree angle. The base model comes with an Intel Core i5 CPU, Intel HD integrated graphics, 6GB of RAM, and 1TB of HDD storage. Lastly, there's the Inspiron One 23, another all in one. It packs a Pentium G645 CPU, Intel integrated HD graphics, 4GB of RAM, and 500GB of HDD storage. The XPS 12 starts at $1,199.99 (both CDN and USD), while the XPS One 27 with touch starts $1599.99 (CDN and USD), and the Inspiron One 23 AIO with touch starts at $799.99 CDN or $779.99 USD. Additionally, Dell is giving the XPS 13 a boost with the addition of Ivy Bridge. It'll start at $999.99 in both the U.S. and Canada. THEY LOOK GREAT, GO ON-LINE AND CHECK THEM OUT.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350153714527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:41:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157621458-11</Id><Topic><Title>DELL is Bullish on America. Dell Inc. Never Sleeps</Title><Username>thompsonbryon460</Username><Timestamp>1350132433193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you should be happy the markets going up...if the market just went down...you wouldnt be able to trade it anymore.</Msg><Username>cabrera.mabel44</Username><Timestamp>1350157621458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350168520214-12</Id><Title>Netflix posts an app tailored for Windows 8</Title><Msg>"Netflix fans will soon have a new medium through which to stream movies and TV shows. Netflix has released to the Windows Store its Windows 8 app, which was reportedly built from scratch to make the most of Windows 8 design and video player features, and is supposedly easy on a computer’s CPU and battery because it uses Windows 8 graphics acceleration capabilities. Anyone running the pre-release version of Windows 8 can download it now—everyone else will have to wait until the arrival of Windows 8 for desktops, notebooks, tablets, and hybrid devices on October 26. Great for Tablets While you’ll be able to use the Netflix app on computers with keyboards, it’s optimized for touchscreen devices, such as the Microsoft Surface tablet. Microsoft has yet to announce pricing or availability for the ARM-based Surface and the x86-based Surface Pro tablets that were announced in June. The company is expected to release the ARM-based device around the same time as Windows 8, and indications are that Surface may ship on October 26, with the Surface Pro following in early 2013. Amping the App Store Even though people have long lamented the dearth of apps in the Windows Store, a Microsoft executive recently made the grandiose proclamation that the company will be aggressively pursuing more than 100,000 apps in the first three months after launching Windows 8. “In order to reach our goal, a conservative estimate of 400 million units in marketplace by July 1, we know we have to have a healthy ecosystem of apps,” Keith Lorizio, Microsoft’s vice president of U.S. sales and marketing, in an interview with Beet.TV. “We’re putting millions of dollars against that effort and working with publishers to get their apps live as soon as possible.” As for the Netflix app in particular, no doubt it will be popular with Windows 8 users—tens of millions of people have downloaded the Apple and Android versions in iTunes and Google Play. The app is free but to use it you need a Netflix membership, which is free of charge for the first month for new members, and costs $7.99 monthly after that." DELL $15.00 by Xmas.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350168520214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350177796347-13</Id><Topic><Title>Netflix posts an app tailored for Windows 8</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1350168520214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:48:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Osso I just checked the DELL Windows 8 line up and it looks incredible. When DELL starts moving up, it will be a violent move upward as with 100 million shares short as of Friday, we will have a lot of blood on the Street.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1350177796347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>