<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349498664810-1</Id><Topic><Title>Windows 8 Launch Date: October 25/2012</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349456316453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:58:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good stuff. Also please note that the Windows 8 launch is the same day as AAPL earnings release. Interesting coincidence!</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349498664810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 00:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349535463375-2</Id><Title>The death Bell for Dell</Title><Msg>Two words: Ipad mini. Dell Laptops are Sooo 2004.</Msg><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1349535463375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 10:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349549921255-3</Id><Title>Dell unveils Windows 8 Latitude Tablet and Ultrabook for "Business"</Title><Msg>"Dell’s Windows 8 tablet" Dell’s most interesting new product is the Latitude 10 tablet. The Latitude 10 is a 10.1-inch Windows 8 tablet with a resolution of 1366 by 768 pixels. It runs on Intel’s Atom system-on-a-chip processor with 2GB of RAM, up to 128GB of flash storage, as well as front and back camera. Dell says it is targeting the tablet at "education, healthcare and government markets", and includes a card reader and fingerprint reader. A separate dock will also be available, but it’s not an attachable keyboard dock as seen with other Windows 8 tablet hybrids. "Windows 8 Dell Ultrabook" Dell’s announced Latitude 6430u “durable” 14-inch Ultrabook is 20mm thin(.9 inches) and weighs just 3.7 pounds. Dell says it is 33 percent slimmer and 16 percent lighter than Dell’s current 14-inch Latitude notebook. It runs on Intel Core i3 to Core 17 processors with up to 8GB or RAM and is designed to meet military testing, which means you can add useful extras such as a spill-resistant keyboard or a free-fall hard disk sensor for preventing data loss. "To fight its Ultrabook from feeling flimsy, Dell is boasting its 6430u was “Designed to meet MIL-STD-810G testing, a United States Military test standard where systems are subjected to the harshest conditions.” "Dell’s all-in-one business PC" Third in Dell’s Windows 8 business lineup is the OptiPlex 9010 23-inch all-in-one PC using Intel’s third-generation Core processors. The OptiPlex also offers options for touchscreen functionality and fixed or rotating webcams for various business use scenarios.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349549921255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349552966036-4</Id><Title>William Langston you are a twit and a fool....</Title><Msg>For someone who has been so wrong on DELL, you keep twitting your crap all day long. AAPL is a toy company while DELL in business, is a standard; and HPQ in technical and engineering environment. You are as clueless and shallow as they come.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349552966036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349553082058-5</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts' analyst caught lying about DELL....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349395836256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WE will hit $12.00 by October 25/2012.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349553082058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349554005475-6</Id><Topic><Title>Dell unveils Windows 8 Latitude Tablet and Ultrabook for "Business"</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349549921255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:58:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Osso, this is what I like best about DELL.... "To fight its Ultrabook from feeling flimsy, Dell is boasting its 6430u was “Designed to meet MIL-STD-810G testing, a United States Military test standard where systems are subjected to the harshest conditions.” DELL is a standard for the business environment and travel.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349554005475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349558800387-7</Id><Title>Death Of The PC Crowd Is A Fraud....</Title><Msg>These folks are mere pranksters as I don't know any serious businessman who would part with his PC and operate on the iphone and that would make them real Phonies.... Unless they are pushing Drugs or working for Zacks.</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349558800387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349561495697-8</Id><Topic><Title>William Langston you are a twit and a fool....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349552966036</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 15:49:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignore him as he is a self-absorbed idiot.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349561495697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349562853555-9</Id><Title>Dell sticks with plan to acquire 8-12 firms "per year"</Title><Msg>DELL Inc will continue its acquisition strategy by buying eight to 12 firms annually in the near term, as it "transforms itself from a personal-computer maker to an information technology service and solution provider" to enterprises and consumers. DELL sees revenue growth rate in China - its No. 2 regional market behind the United States - to be "higher than the industry rate," said Stephen Felice, Dell's president. Dell is a company "selling solutions" rather than "selling devices" now, Felice said in an interview in Shanghai. He was referring to Dell's Enterprise Solutions and Services division, which provides data, security, management, cloud computing and other services to enterprise users. In the second quarter, the division's revenue grew 6 percent year on year to US$4.9 billion, representing a third of the company's total income and above 50 percent of its profit. In the coming years, the division's revenue will account for more than half of the company's total revenue, Felice said. To achieve the revenue target, Dell will continue its acquisition strategy, such as it did for consulting firm Bearing Point in 2009 and Internet security firm Sonicwall in March. Felice said Dell acquired eight to 12 firms on average annually in the past and he hoped to "keep the pace" for the transformation. China has "less legacy" on information infrastructure and "open-minded" clients, but Felice said it will still be Dell's strategic market, including in the enterprise service segment. In the first quarter, Dell's revenue in China gained 9 percent, against an average 4 percent rise in the rest of the BRIC - in Brazil, Russia and India.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349562853555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349567193569-10</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts' analyst caught lying about DELL....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349395836256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 20:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You see we were trading just above $10.00 and there is always a risk that if the market sells off, it could be pushed below $10.00 and then bounce back. So what happened was Phila. Fed Governor spooked the markets by hammering QE-III and the shorts immediately cast doubt on how serious the Fed is about QE-III and shorted the market so we dipped below $10.00 and just when we were trading above $10.00 again, HP CEO had her tragic investor meeting, HPQ tanked and we got pulled down as collateral damage. We have excellent products, have a well defined acquistion strategy into Cloud and Software and Windows 8 will be launched in two weeks.... So if the market holds up, we should be at $12.00 in a couple of weeks. Cheers Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349567193569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 19:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349570900766-11</Id><Topic><Title>Dell sticks with plan to acquire 8-12 firms "per year"</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349562853555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:34:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who ever buys ocz will be glad they did.</Msg><Username>nk499</Username><Timestamp>1349570900766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 20:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349577473175-12</Id><Title>I am Mitt and I approve this message</Title><Msg>My ?itch got a dancing horse</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349577473175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349580961753-13</Id><Topic><Title>Death Of The PC Crowd Is A Fraud....</Title><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1349558800387</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:26:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The shorts trash Pcs while typing all their crap on their PCs.... A bunch of crooks, fools and liars.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1349580961753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 23:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>