<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346760120447-1</Id><Topic><Title>Micheal Dell to take private before Win8 PC upgrade cycle</Title><Username>smb_gt</Username><Timestamp>1346361453756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:17:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Microsoft has ADMITTED that Windows8 is not a certainty for consumers by building in an automatic "downgrade" options that lets users roll back as far as Vista! They're saying, "Yeah, you might hate it so we'll make it easy to go back to Windows7." </Msg><Username>rmbo47</Username><Timestamp>1346760120447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346763414260-2</Id><Title>We will be in Single digits by Friday</Title><Msg>This stock is corkscrewing into the dirt like a plane without a rudder. There is no pilot, and everyone is bailing.</Msg><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1346763414260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:56:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346771236018-3</Id><Topic><Title>3 1/2 year low for Dell.</Title><Username>jack_about_stocks</Username><Timestamp>1346351718288</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:35:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is becoming a daily occurrence! </Msg><Username>rmbo47</Username><Timestamp>1346771236018</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346771245214-4</Id><Title>Google video "Dishonorable Disclosures" video being kept secret for months - real</Title><Msg>YouTube is not allowing the video poster to add links to prevent spread of alarming truth. Please google "Dishonorable Disclosures." Please feel free to read the video description first.</Msg><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1346771245214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346771821413-5</Id><Title>Dell is the American RIMM.</Title><Msg>They are losing market share resulting in the stock constantly being shorted.</Msg><Username>happyperson_1</Username><Timestamp>1346771821413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346772819380-6</Id><Topic><Title>We will be in Single digits by Friday</Title><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1346763414260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 08:56:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Single digits by Friday only if the stock splits this week!</Msg><Username>jack_about_stocks</Username><Timestamp>1346772819380</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346774301327-7</Id><Title>Dell just got upgraded technically to focus list Buy by CS from Hold</Title><Msg>Upside Trade Trade indicators for long trades. Upside Trade &amp; Breakout Help Upside ReCalc™ : Adjust the upside trade &amp; breakout parameters. ( Stock Price: 10.52 ) TRADE QUALITY 90%, Excellent High trade quality is a combination of good profit, profit/loss ratio and target potential. TARGET 1 Price: 11.71 Profit: 11.3% , for a typical rally. Stop Limit/Trailing Stop Limit: 10.35 Loss: 1.6% Profit/Loss Ratio: 7.1 : 1 - Excellent TARGET 1 POTENTIAL Excellent, there are 1 resistance areas on the way to Target 1. Stocks may quickly rise to Targets when there are not many resistance areas blocking the way. TARGET 1 RESISTANCE +1.8% at 10.71 ± 0.18, type Single, strength 1 +11.3% at 11.71 is Target 1 TARGET 2 Price: 12.07 Profit: 14.7% , Profit/Loss Ratio: 9.2 : 1 - Excellent for an extreme rally. BREAKOUT None. Downside Trade Trade indicators for short trades. Downside Trade &amp; Breakdown Help Downside ReCalc™ : Adjust the downside trade &amp; breakdown parameters. ( Stock Price: 10.52 ) TRADE QUALITY 30%, Poor TARGET 1 Price: 10.96 Profit: 0% , There has been a strong pullback and the current stock price has exceeded Target 1. Cover Limit/Trailing Cover Limit: 10.77 Loss: 2.4% Profit/Loss Ratio: 0 : 1 - Poor TARGET 1 POTENTIAL Excellent, there are 0 support areas on the way to Target 1. Stocks may quickly fall to Targets when there are not many support areas blocking the way. TARGET 2 Price: 10.71 Profit: 0% , There has been an Extreme pullback and the current stock price has also exceeded Target 2. BREAKDOWN None</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1346774301327</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346777394588-8</Id><Title>Standpoint Research upgraded Dell (NASDAQ: DELL) from Hold to Buy with a price target of $21.00.Sitting on piles of cash</Title><Msg>Standpoint Research upgraded Dell (NASDAQ: DELL) from Hold to Buy with a price target of $21.00</Msg><Username>nusaiba</Username><Timestamp>1346777394588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346777753624-9</Id><Title>Single digits are coming.</Title><Msg>They are coming as sure as Death and Taxes.</Msg><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1346777753624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346788901576-10</Id><Title>DELL is DONE!!!</Title><Msg>Bankruptcy within a year.</Msg><Username>n16m15</Username><Timestamp>1346788901576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346797372256-11</Id><Topic><Title>The young and Dumb investors are out of DELL</Title><Username>investing30yrs</Username><Timestamp>1346356965216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone is aware of the loss of market share but it won't continue to decline as China gains because the billions of people there are going to be able to afford computers long before more expensive things from Apple (great company) and what many people don't realize is right here in the States is the tablet and other fine products from Apple are not able to produce the amount of graphics that computers can for at least ten years and large institutions that require this are going to stick with computers. Not only that, when graphics improve in small products Apple sells, it will be like the fine Apple computers, too expensive for use in public instiutions. Dell could do itself a favor by buying AMD and likely get the company for $15 a share now. AMD has the graphics needed for DELL. Dell has enough cash that in a worst case, it could be bought out or even change what it does as a company. It has the ability to reach out into many other specialized areas. Dell has cash and is wealthy in patients too that even Apple would like to get its hands on. Apple would only be interested in the patients and graphic thus; Apple could buy both Dell and AMD but I have the idea that Dell will do it its own way like before and perhaps buy AMD. Either way, this is the time for shorts to make money and for longs to get invested in many stocks. This reminds me of 08-09. I think lower prices are coming near term but a year to three from now, AMD, DELL and many others will be trading high again like always. There is no danger here with Dell unless one is attempting to swing or day trade it imo. Shorts do well and then longs clean house.</Msg><Username>investing30yrs</Username><Timestamp>1346797372256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 18:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346804872573-12</Id><Title>Dell should be $20.00, not $10.00</Title><Msg>A PE of 5.8 is just stupid. Look at Fedex key stats, very similar to Dells but valued twice as much.</Msg><Username>johnnygreenapple</Username><Timestamp>1346804872573</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346807715970-13</Id><Title>Dell's Customer Service is destroying the profitability of this company</Title><Msg>Dell's lack of concern for its loyal customers, as well as, its new ones will ultimately be its downfall. Dell just can not continue to think they are going to stay in business if they continue out source their entire customer service department. There are literally thousands of complaints on the internet about the horrible service the customers are getting. Of course these people are calling because the machines they paid good money for are not working, many of which are still under warranty! I am personally a stock holder, and after my latest laptop purchase, its failure to work, and the horrible customer service, which included down right lies from the dell "supervisors"; I am unloaded my stock ASAP. I am shocked by what these guys did and said on the phone, including hanging up on me multiple times. You wonder why this Tech giant share price is sitting at around $10/share, and where Apple is.... Its called customer service, and making machine that works. My advice to all Dell Shareholders...sell now. I challenge any Dell Executive, Board Member, Officer, or anybody to dispute what is going on here. Just do a Google search for "Dell Customer Complaints", it is everywhere. Or even better, I challenge any Dell employee to reach out to me to correct my new opinion of Dell.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1346807715970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346813962158-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dell's Customer Service is destroying the profitability of this company</Title><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1346807715970</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 21:15:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never had a problem with a Dell computer so I've never had to contact customer service, great machines, great prices.</Msg><Username>johnnygreenapple</Username><Timestamp>1346813962158</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346815955852-15</Id><Title>Ultrabooks?</Title><Msg>I was looking for a thin and light laptop, but didn't want to spend $1000. So instead, i picked up a refurbished Dell D420 12 inch laptop on Amazon for $150. This is exactly what I needed. No operating system installed, but that's ok. I installed Linux Mint Maya and it beats the heck out of Windows Vista or Windows 8. I upgraded the memory and installed an SSD myself for less then $100. So now, I have my thin light 'Ultrabook' for only $250 and it runs MY CHOICE of operating systems.</Msg><Username>b52boomer</Username><Timestamp>1346815955852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>