<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344332902000-1</Id><Title>Dell to BUYOUT OCZ Technology Group (OCZ)</Title><Msg>Dell to BUYOUT OCZ Technology Group (OCZ) ventures Sierra World Equity Review Accurate phenom Sierra World Equity Review believes that Dell is planning to acquire OCZ Technology Group and that talks may already be underway! Dell's acquisition of OCZ is in Sierra World Equity Review's opinion part of a strategic ongoing endeavor to expand and truly offer start to finish solutions for it's partner and customer base. After recently purchasing Wyse Technologies as part of this plan, Dell's potential purchase of OCZ will place them in the forefront of solid state drives as OCZ is the innovative leader in this field. Sierra World Equity Review is all over this development, Sierra will be flying out this evening to Texas to visit Dell Corporate offices and try to get an interview with Michael Dell. Check back for the update...</Msg><Username>tvtman</Username><Timestamp>1344332902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 05:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344350525000-2</Id><Title>HP &amp; Dell To Bring Windows RT Tablets In Q4 2012</Title><Msg>Great article @ http://www.thetabarena.com/thetabarena-blog/2012/07/10/hp-and-dell-to-bring-windows-rt-tablets-in-q4-2012/ "HP and Dell have also announced that they will be coming with their own Windows RT tablet device that will be powered by TI OMAP and Qualcomm made processor ships. Of course both PC manufacturing companies will be bringing these new Windows RT tablets during the Q4 of this year. This report has been taken from sources at the Supply chain makers. ...Acer has already announced that they will not enter the Windows RT tablet market and instead they will only focus on the Intel based Windows tablets. There are also chances that Sony and Samsung will also bring their own Windows RT tablets, but we haven’t heard about them yet, so it might take a while..."</Msg><Username>jimch1</Username><Timestamp>1344350525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 10:42:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344354141000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Change In Trend Near?</Title><Username>buironmbm589</Username><Timestamp>1344342308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 08:25:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>leontineqel752</Username><Timestamp>1344354141000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 11:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>