<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353162429155-1</Id><Topic><Title>Folks this is all about the slow economy in the past 4 quarters and NOT about DELL or PCs Health....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353028885844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 20:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm excited about Windows 8 to a point... Upgrade cycles are slowing in the PC/Notebook business from 4 to 6 years in many cases... The ARM based tablets are a great consumer device for on the go, and great on power, and price, and weight... The higher dollar Windows 8 tablets/ultrabook will be the choice of most businesses... Average consumer is moving to Apple, but I do see a flow of users starting to move away from the Apple Monopoly back to Windows.. Because of this I see a steady slow flow back into Windows.. Desktops ( built into the Monitor ) I believe will also become popular as consumers want to large screen display for real work, and get rid of their chassis and case that waste space... How does this relate to Dell..... Dell is making money is servers and gaining market share. I see this continuing as HP is not viewed as stable by IT, and IBM is viewed as stuffy... I feel Dell will recover.. I visit many customers and am surprised to see most laptops and desktops people are on average 3.5 years old running Windows XP... Businesses are not moving to Apple ( outside the ARTs/movies/music )... Also productivity of the workers are no longer good with the old OS and hardware... We should start seeing IT departments allocate more for productivity in 2013.</Msg><Username>qqqqtrdr</Username><Timestamp>1353162429155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 09:27:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353172569467-2</Id><Topic><Title>Folks this is all about the slow economy in the past 4 quarters and NOT about DELL or PCs Health....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353028885844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 20:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had a bad day as the shorts got really aggressive as we did well while the market was selling off in the prior two trading days.... It seems they went through all stop-loss and had to cover, go back to $9.00 and then started shorting again.... I had a chance to look at the numbers, we were really off by "One" cent and the sales were on the lower end of the range and my sense is that $10.00 was reflecting short term PPs for a sold off market and a slow quarter and some.... In grand scheme of things, only 71 million plus shares were traded, which is under 4% of the oustanding shares, we had about $1.3 billion cashflow and ended the quarter with $14.5 billion cash on hand.... One option for DELL will be to go private and offer $12.50-13.00 per share as with over $5 billion of cashflow per year, the insiders can do an LBO with very low interest/financing.... All this would be history as the fiscal cliff negotiations will be concluded by Thanksgiving, Greece will have their financing in place next week and the Xmas shopping season and a strong consumer buying up all the gadget and IT tools in sight, will move up the PPs north of $10.00 starting Black Friday.... We will see IT starting to bounce back in Q4/2012 and our Software/Cloud side of the business deliver more robust results both in the US and in China as Europe will start coming out of its year-long debt crisis.... Add to that aggressive buyback by DELL, as is recommended by many analysts and observers, as we still have $4.5 billion cash allocated to buybacks and that would take out 500 million shares at these PPs leaving us with 1.25 billion shares thus boosting the EPS by 30% to $2.20-2.30 range. Cheers, Osso</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353172569467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 12:16:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353184563379-3</Id><Topic><Title>Hurry Buy Up Dell $10 Tomorrow then $11!! EPS Report Thgursday Afternoon!!</Title><Username>syn1828</Username><Timestamp>1352912583703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-14 12:03:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get to 9.00 first.</Msg><Username>tasalarzin</Username><Timestamp>1353184563379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:36:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353184809251-4</Id><Topic><Title>Michael Dell should have supported Romney.</Title><Username>weightbayou</Username><Timestamp>1353102025699</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 16:40:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dadio, you amybe right.</Msg><Username>tasalarzin</Username><Timestamp>1353184809251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:40:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353185071486-5</Id><Title>Why Dell sees opportunity and profits in Windows 8 tablets designed for business - Source TabTimes</Title><Msg>Dell has high hopes for its recent Windows 8 tablet launches, which it expects to significantly augment its traditional lineup of desktop PCs and notebooks. During an earnings call with analysts Dell answered questions about its tablet strategy, specifically how it impacts business customers. “We also are starting to see a lot of receptivity to the way we've approached the tablet market from a commercial perspective,” said Stephen Felice, Dell’s President and Chief Commercial Officer.  “I've been meeting with lots of customers who continue to say that they're needing to prioritize security and manageability as they try to roll out tablets in their environment,” Felice added. He said Dell hopes to make inroads with these customers with such products as the Latitude 10 that has security features built-in and a smart card feature as well as a replaceable battery. The Latitude 10 is an Intel Atom-based Windows 8 tablet with 64GB priced starting at $649. It goes on sale starting December 12. “These are things that are resonating well on the commercial side,” he said. “So that -- those opportunities are going to broaden that commercial business for us, and that should help us get back to growth.” Responding to a question about price competition, Dell’s CFO Brian Gladden indicated the company was unlikely to compete at the low end. “Well, our focus on tablets has primarily been in the commercial side. And the feature set that is required there matches up with a richer configuration, and we do think that there's a profit stream there,” said Gladden. “It also has a life cycle of profitability attached to it in terms of services agreements and other add-ons that we think is attractive to us.” What tablets are CIOs complaining about?  In an apparent dig at Apple’s iPad and perhaps Android devices as well, Gladden said Dell hears a lot of complaints from CIOs who are having to deal with the added cost and complexity of not having a standards-based product as a tablet. “And so we're pretty encouraged by the reaction to the Latitude 10,” he said, “and we do see this as a profitable product in the commercial space. Dell executive Neil Hand is one of the keynoters at the upcoming TabletBiz conference and expo in New York on November 27.</Msg><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353185071486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:44:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353188505201-6</Id><Topic><Title>Why Dell sees opportunity and profits in Windows 8 tablets designed for business - Source TabTimes</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353185071486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:44:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Osso and I think this would be great success with a price tag of around $650.00 and they could use both Windows 7 and 8 so the customer does not need to upgrade to Windows 8 to use them. And with multiple operating systems needed for using APPL, this should be a hit just before Xmas (I think Dell is taking orders now for Dec 12/2012 shipments).</Msg><Username>longsrboss</Username><Timestamp>1353188505201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 16:41:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353199500711-7</Id><Topic><Title>Folks this is all about the slow economy in the past 4 quarters and NOT about DELL or PCs Health....</Title><Username>ossobucco2012</Username><Timestamp>1353028885844</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 20:21:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Dell was concerned about their stock holders positions, they could easily increase their dividend to 10 cents or even 12 cents a share without hurting their bottom line much.. they currently only pay 21% in dividends and that is with this very down quarter... everyone anticipating next quarter to be bad, but I think they are very wrong and next quarter will be 3 to 5 cents above analyst current estimates... PCs have been slow lately, but they are picking up slowly and in December they should be at least 85 percent of normal.. by february we should be 95 percent of normal or at normal... Dell's got plenty of cash to give back to the share holders, however, what they do with it is anyone's guess...</Msg><Username>yourwishismine</Username><Timestamp>1353199500711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:45:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353201941750-8</Id><Title>Too many analysts saying not to buy=buy</Title><Msg>I have been in IT for the last 18 years and I have always hated Dell, but they have been positioning themselves well via acquisition. If this shakes to the 7's its a nice 12-24 month play.</Msg><Username>steely11</Username><Timestamp>1353201941750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 20:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>