<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343646776000-1</Id><Title>Dell Book value $5.31 / share</Title><Msg>Assets minus Liabilities = shareholder value. This is how much the stock is really worth. Insiders were dumping shares like madmen when it was over $16. If the COO and the CFO are dumping shares, what should we be doing? http://finance.yahoo.com/q/ks?s=DELL+Key+Statistics</Msg><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1343646776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 07:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343676110000-2</Id><Title>I think now worth to start buying some shares</Title><Msg>I still have my Dell old laptop and I will surely buy another one when I will change it, yes now it's a time of little money.. I bought last year a beautiful, compact Optiplex with 2 monitors and I'm fully satisfied. Everybody have a Dell computer, especially in the corporate sector, I can't figure out how I can design an engine or whatever with an ipad... Dell has shown already in the past that is able to turn around.. Come on... Hold on!!!</Msg><Username>stefano_servadei</Username><Timestamp>1343676110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343676548000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Dell Book value $5.31 / share</Title><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1343646776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 07:12:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I must say I have to agree with you 100%. Shame people wont speak the truth on these boards, too busy manipulating buyers and sellers to benefit their own agenda. A fool is born every minute.</Msg><Username>shefreak01</Username><Timestamp>1343676548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343690012000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Caution Must Be Maintained</Title><Username>claribeldfv728</Username><Timestamp>1343651825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 08:37:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I AM UP TODAY!</Msg><Username>rafiltd438</Username><Timestamp>1343690012000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343694406000-5</Id><Title>IWEB fastest growing data storage play under 1</Title><Msg>imo.....off topic, but noticed a bullish article regarding DELL investing over 60mil in small data storage companies. This Week in the Cloud… Dell Ventures Launches $60M Investment Fund for Early Stage Data Storage Startups Learn what Dell is doing for startups in the data storage space. The Dell Fluid Data Storage Fund expects to invest in five to ten early stage startups. Dell says, "Dell is fueling the next big thing in innovation." http://nbtequitiesresearch.com/t/l/QSyRBTU2EyHmxSc</Msg><Username>nostocksnoglory1001</Username><Timestamp>1343694406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 20:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343703976000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Dell Book value $5.31 / share</Title><Username>runningblackbeardog</Username><Timestamp>1343646776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 07:12:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give it a rest with this multiple alias, pure BS... I've never seen a profitable stock trading at book, moreover this stock as a forward p/e of 5.9, that is ridiculos and last but not least a cash per share of $ 7.85. It's just a matter of growing and this multiples can easily double and so the stock from here. GLA</Msg><Username>stefano_servadei</Username><Timestamp>1343703976000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 23:06:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>