<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351786979014-1</Id><Topic><Title>@$9.18 is DELL quietly going out of business?</Title><Username>schule7607</Username><Timestamp>1351706904327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was the point that there is no value asigned to the legacy franchise. The other thing to note is that 10B value doesn't account for ALL the acquistions some were undisclosed and not included in the @10B figure. (e.g. Sonicwall was mentioned in a number of articles @1B - 1.5B) nor would they need to be discounted 50% in fact some are more valuable now then when acquired.</Msg><Username>asd_flintlock</Username><Timestamp>1351786979014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351788172999-2</Id><Topic><Title>@$9.18 is DELL quietly going out of business?</Title><Username>schule7607</Username><Timestamp>1351706904327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 14:08:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>appears that way. not sure if can be salvaged. similar to Compaq situation many years ago.</Msg><Username>use.caution</Username><Timestamp>1351788172999</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351788823074-3</Id><Title>Will EPS Be Bad Like HPQ? Any Pre-Announcements Like BBY and HPQ Coming Then Tanking to $8's!!</Title><Msg>Tell me ANALIST???</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1351788823074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 12:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351789290096-4</Id><Title>Dell is a thief</Title><Msg>He has pocketed $150 billion from my stolen lighted mouse invention and is plotting to steal Windows Electra software from me, Michael Dell is who he is because of my stolen properties. He monitors my phone lines and steals thousands from my stock money. Dell stock will be $5 next year, tablets are tabets are taking over the computer business because of me, I invented the Ipad design. John Gooch Owner and creator of Windows Electtra software since 2002.</Msg><Username>johngooch56</Username><Timestamp>1351789290096</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 13:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351793138990-5</Id><Title>Swing Trading Long Dell Inc. on reversal upward pattern..</Title><Msg>Good Afternoon: Apocalypse for PC era will wait for a while in my humble opinion. PC and laptops are still good tools in factories, offices and nice toys at homes; servers are the heart that store in the cloud and pumps data towards wide world web in our information technology society. DELL manufactures Pc´s,Laptops tablets and servers, but it also manufactures printers, and a wide range of electronic devices, so.. for me is well diversified in its products that reach new and old customers every day. Turn around stories won´t work from one day to another, but it seems to me that DELL´s CEO is working very hard to get a new growing story for his company, Tech. speaking DELL is trading right now in an oversold condition and with divergences between market price and Chaikin Money flow, so it could be ready for an upward reversal with stockastic oscillator crossing in the low band. I recommend starting long positions right now to get into this undervalued company before take off. Have a nice day Longs.</Msg><Username>eaglesssnest</Username><Timestamp>1351793138990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351795049732-6</Id><Title>Dell May Run-Up Into EPS and Pop Up Too Since Last Two EPS Diapponted and Stock Tanked. $12?? Dell Run?</Title><Msg>Hmmmh?</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1351795049732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351795110675-7</Id><Title>Dell! $10 Running Into EPS! Then $12!</Title><Msg>Cover By By Buy!</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1351795110675</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 14:38:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351816924421-8</Id><Title>The Romney---Ryan expensive plan would cost a small fortune for those under 55 years old, and hurt those over 55</Title><Msg>There would be no money left to buy computer products.</Msg><Username>mushy_limpballs</Username><Timestamp>1351816924421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 20:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351819227778-9</Id><Title>Remember - Real Quality of Life Determined By State's Rights - Romney</Title><Msg>Federal control is the alternative</Msg><Username>mackgreene33</Username><Timestamp>1351819227778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 21:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>