<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357189818986-1</Id><Title>Hewlett-Packard Company leaving the PC Business Dell will takes up the slake!</Title><Msg>Good news for Dell has been coming out each and everyday, especially the upgrade today from hold to Buy. Dell will be happy to take HP PC BUSINESS.</Msg><Username>grannybones2</Username><Timestamp>1357189818986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 00:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357225172037-2</Id><Title>Dell the next Ford turnaround success story in the computer world</Title><Msg>Prediction or Fact for Dell Company in 2013 ? It fact folks. You are looking at a company that is doing all the right things to make 2013 a winning year. You wil be wishing you bought in early while the stock is low. You see, Dell is a slow growing stock that will steady creep up in price. Meaning buying 10,000 shares of Dell is secure and rewarding down the line. Dell is only down 3 cents today, not bad for a 300 point rally of yesterday. That what I'am talking about. Proof is in the cherry pie. Thius is how we judge a good stock. BUY recommendation!</Msg><Username>grannybones2</Username><Timestamp>1357225172037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 09:59:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357226133195-3</Id><Topic><Title>Sell DELL with less thatn 20% to PPS target ... buy CIG with over 70% to PPS target</Title><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1356533501746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-26 09:51:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it worth hanging on to DELL ... isn't it better to sell DELL &amp; buy CIG ...</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1357226133195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 10:15:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357227094369-4</Id><Title>Short interest in Dell has decreased a whooping (-9.73) percent, Good Sign!</Title><Msg>Here another sign we look for in a stock that a stick has bottom out and is fixing to go up. Short interest is way down on dell -9.73 percent with 2.5 days to cover. Dell for sure has a 2 1/2 day rally coming possible as high as a $2.00 gain at the low en estimate.. $13.00 to $15.00 and more if we include the company break news forth coming.</Msg><Username>grannybones2</Username><Timestamp>1357227094369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 10:31:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357228652426-5</Id><Title>Millons of people around the world love thier desk top computer.</Title><Msg>I don't like those small hand held computer. Moving my big finger on that little screen just doesn't work for me . That why I love my Dell desk top computer. I can easily drink coffee and prop up my feet and relax while picking my stocks for the day. Pizza you bet, no mess on the screen in case of accidents. Read this report just in. The Internet revolutionized how people view and consume information. From email to social-media networking, users are finding more content to digest than ever before on more devices. According to a new Connected Intelligence report from global information company, The NPD Group, there are 425 million devices connected to the Internet in the United States. The report, which was conducted in the fourth quarter of 2012, found that desktops and laptops were still the most connected device at 183.8 million users. It is a bit of good news for companies like Hewlett-Packard (NYSE:HPQ) and Dell (NASDAQ:DELL), but several other devices are taking market share away from traditional comp</Msg><Username>grannybones2</Username><Timestamp>1357228652426</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 10:57:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357229522174-6</Id><Topic><Title>Prices Trying To Extend Higher&gt;</Title><Username>amliajohn530</Username><Timestamp>1336830649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-05-12 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking cool.</Msg><Username>stevejames355</Username><Timestamp>1357229522174</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 11:12:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357233433960-7</Id><Title>Dell a sexy girl compared to Hewlett-Packard Company</Title><Msg>The Wall St Cheat Sheet article today was right that Dell is a better and sexier name for a girl to date than it competitor name Hewlett-Packard Company. Hewlett-Packard Company is more in debt from all her spending and Dell is currently a high class cheaper date that has the moves. Wall St Cheat Sheet shows why Dells a buy today and future dates. Read article to understand. No problem with Hewlett-Packard Company</Msg><Username>grannybones2</Username><Timestamp>1357233433960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 12:17:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357238639504-8</Id><Title>Halted in last 10 mins?</Title><Msg>More news??????</Msg><Username>dehui616</Username><Timestamp>1357238639504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 13:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357240271014-9</Id><Title>GET IT NOW FOR DOUBLE!!</Title><Msg>undervalued</Msg><Username>monett4</Username><Timestamp>1357240271014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 14:11:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357241211555-10</Id><Title>UBS upgrade</Title><Msg>When UBS finally admitted they made a mistake shorting DELL. The boys in America would not let UBS of the hook easy. They want UBS pay $15/share when DELL fell off the cliff.</Msg><Username>king_kim_1</Username><Timestamp>1357241211555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 14:26:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357247153728-11</Id><Topic><Title>Important Report On DELL!</Title><Username>jhonnyalbert248</Username><Timestamp>1354807296727</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-12-06 10:21:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one</Msg><Username>andygreen749</Username><Timestamp>1357247153728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-03 16:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>