<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360474569581-1</Id><Topic><Title>M. Dell Can Pay Twice His Current Offer and Still Make Lots of Money on Buy Out</Title><Username>thethirdchimp</Username><Timestamp>1360465292867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 22:01:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>here is another option if Dell doesn't raise the offer price for buyer. institution shareholders will vote no and elect new independent BOD members via proxy fight. New BOD can decide to tender offer Mike Dell's 15% at $13.65. Then select a new CEO that is competent and professional to run the company to maximize shareholders value. This way, shareholders will bear the risk and Dell can cash out at $13.65 and get lost.</Msg><Username>pchung6</Username><Timestamp>1360474569581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 00:36:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360477309843-2</Id><Title>If the deal is rejected by shareholders, $13.65 will be the bottom, not the top of dell...</Title><Msg>If most shareholders think $13.65 is too low, we know that at least 50% of the shareholders + Michael Dell will not sell at $13.65 or below. It's hard to get lower than $13.65 (it can with short-seller, but will not be down that much). This is very different than the yahoo takeover from msft. That deal was rejected by the CEO while every shareholder wants to sell, Dell is the exact opposite.</Msg><Username>hmtsorno</Username><Timestamp>1360477309843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 01:21:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360491407769-3</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I plan to vote no until a much better offer surfaces and I think the Southwestern letter will rally the support of many shareholders who think this is a pretty bad deal even if it's supposedly 25% above the price when rumors started. Michael Dell is not looking out for investors, as if he was he'd give an option to shareholders who want to stay in after the LBO to retain their shares. He could have also simply continued executing his plan as a public company that he boasted would boost revenues by 2015 and not try to gain more control of a private company. Nobody would boost their stake of a company that is in decline - he definitely sees a turning point where the company will make more money than previously and start gaining traction in the corporate sector that IBM dominates. The stock has a floor now of 13.65 - and it will go up in anticipation of a better deal.</Msg><Username>mmpsolutionsinc</Username><Timestamp>1360491407769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 05:16:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360491565448-4</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>meant to say southeastern - got tripped up on the energy company for a second</Msg><Username>mmpsolutionsinc</Username><Timestamp>1360491565448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 05:19:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360492182706-5</Id><Title>DELL vs. AMD</Title><Msg>which one?</Msg><Username>m.rally</Username><Timestamp>1360492182706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 05:29:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360499255139-6</Id><Topic><Title>Are You GETTING KILLED?</Title><Username>kathieerwin130</Username><Timestamp>1308234879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-06-16 10:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are best.</Msg><Username>jpeter445</Username><Timestamp>1360499255139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 07:27:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360502556494-7</Id><Topic><Title>Are You GETTING KILLED?</Title><Username>kathieerwin130</Username><Timestamp>1308234879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-06-16 10:34:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>appreciate it</Msg><Username>shorting_warren_buffett</Username><Timestamp>1360502556494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 08:22:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360504819098-8</Id><Title>I have AAPL...hate to see you poor DELL investors getting screwed</Title><Msg>Why is that? Why did you let your PPS drop so low. Of course, someone with major cash would steal your company? Won't happen to AAPL...maybe you should have bought AAPL instead.</Msg><Username>tukkersmom2</Username><Timestamp>1360504819098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360509575166-9</Id><Title>Samsung should make a bid for Dell</Title><Msg>Samsung should big for dell. A) they have the cash B) it will enter them in the PC market to go against their enemy apple C) they will enter the enterprise market which they are pretty much out of D) it just makes sense for them to dominate the PC market as well since they own every other electronic goods they make</Msg><Username>qualityrams</Username><Timestamp>1360509575166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 10:19:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360518548327-10</Id><Topic><Title>I have AAPL...hate to see you poor DELL investors getting screwed</Title><Username>tukkersmom2</Username><Timestamp>1360504819098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, I just love the graph on AAPL. Maybe you should have bought Dell. LOL</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1360518548327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 12:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360520458340-11</Id><Title>Dell, Is That Really A Fair Offer?</Title><Msg>Congratulations are in order for Mr. Dell and his partners on the announcement to pay $13.65 per share to take Dell (DELL) private. However, it was surprising that Dell's board agreed to the price. Here is why. When Dell purchased Perot Systems this is the discussion on premium paid: On September 18, 2009, the last full day of trading before the public announcement of the terms of the Offer and the Merger, the closing price of the Shares on the NYSE was $17.91 per Share. On October 1, 2009, the last full day of trading before the commencement of the Offer, the closing price of the Shares on the NYSE was $29.72 per Share. The Offer Price represents a premium of approximately 67.5% over the closing price of the Shares on the NYSE on September 18, 2009, the last full day of trading before the public announcement of the Offer and the Merger, a premium of approximately 76.5% over the average closing price of the Shares one month prior to such announcement and a premium of approximately 115.4% over the average closing price of the Shares for the one year period ended September 18, 2009. With the Quest Software purchase the discussion was: The current and historical market price of the Company common stock, including the fact that the Per Share Merger Consideration represents a premium of approximately 44% over the closing price of the Company common stock on March 8, 2012, the day before the Company announced its entry into the Insight Merger Agreement, and 37% and 42% premiums over the 1-month and 2-month average trading price prior to such announcement, respectively; The Compellent purchase. The fact that $27.75 per share represents a premium of 46% to the estimated unaffected stock price of $19 per share. See "The Merger - Opinions of Compellent's Advisors" for a description of the estimation of an illustrative "unaffected" share price of Compellent common stock. The fact that $27.75 per share represents a premium of 26% to the three month average closing trading prices of share of Compellent common stock; the fact that $27.75 per share represents a premium of 133.9% to Compellent's stock price of $11.86 per share on the day prior to the date of announcement of Dell's initial offer to acquire 3PAR and a premium of 84.9% to Compellent's stock price of $15.01 per share on the day prior to September 1, 2010, the first day of the speculative rumors about Compellent's possible acquisition; This is in the Dell proposal to go private: Under the terms of the agreement, Dell stockholders will receive $13.65 in cash for each share of Dell common stock they hold, in a transaction valued at approximately $24.4 billion. The price represents a premium of 25 percent over Dell's closing share price of $10.88 on Jan. 11, 2013, the last trading day before rumors of a possible going-private transaction were first published; a premium of approximately 35 percent over Dell's enterprise value as of Jan. 11, 2013; and a premium of approximately 37 percent over the average closing share price during the previous 90 calendar days ending Jan. 11, 2013. The buyers will acquire for cash all of the outstanding shares of Dell not held by Mr. Dell and certain other members of management. On February 4th, 2013 the day before the merger announcement Dell closed at $13.27. If Dell offered the 84.9% premium that Compellent enjoyed before rumors, then the price would have been roughly $20.00 If Dell offered the 44% premium Quest Software enjoyed the day before the merger announcement, then the price would have been roughly $19.00. If Dell offered the 67.5% premium that Perot Systems enjoyed, then the price would have been roughly $22.00. If Dell offered a 25% premium on the more recently purchased, treasury stock then the price would have been roughly $19.00. If Dell offered the average price of the treasury stock on the balance sheet, then the price would have been $26.67. So why is Dell only offering $13.65? It would appear that a price in the range of $19.00 to $26.67 might be more appropriate. At $13.65, the board is agreeing to sell the entire firm for roughly $25 billion. Is this an admission that the $32 billion of owners' money given to departing owners was a mistake? Owners provided departing owners with roughly $7 billion more than has been agreed to sell the entire firm. This is a huge difference. Had the $32 billion been returned to owners via dividends, then the total enjoyed by owners would have been $57 billion.</Msg><Username>sexylawgirl1</Username><Timestamp>1360520458340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:20:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360521494163-12</Id><Title>smart trade..buy dell bonds 105'sh / they were at 135..delayed deal or no deal..bonds trade up</Title><Msg>and you have the majority of the voting rights..if not bonds trade to 101'sh..nice risk reward upside to downside and your votes are senior..no brainer (and get paid a 6% coupon)..yawn</Msg><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360521494163</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:38:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360521689088-13</Id><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Msg>I have a small investment in Dell. Roughly 9000 shares. I purchased most of these believing in Michael Dell at roughly 30 to 35 dollars a share. I have purchased numerous Dell computers in past 18 years. This deal is so unfair. I am voting against it. If this deal goes through, Michael Dell is trying to steal the company and rob me who has believed in him and his company for so many years. Anyone associated with this deal who is conduit to stealing my family money I will make sure I will never deal with them again. i will never buy a dell computer again. If it comes to vote , i will vote every board member who voted for this deal out of the board if I can. I am talking to all my friends and relatives in detail about this bad deal who is taking money off the table and enriching Dell, Microsoft, and few people in Silver Lake and their bankers. They are all crooks. I think I will start buying only apple products/ computers. I will steer clear anything that has Microsoft's name on it. How could our board of directors vote on such a lop sided deal in favor of dell? Part of the whole deal is financed by our companies cash / bonds that are off shore. Out of $24 billion dollars needed, Silver Lake Michael Dell, Microsoft and bankers have found a way to use $11 to $12 billion to pay for it. If this group backs out or higher bid comes in, they get penalty hundreds of millions of dollars? Where is sense of fairness? I am considering putting in a complaint with the government on multiple levels.</Msg><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360522173054-14</Id><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Msg>it doesn't matter what the stock holders say..its the bond holders..they just saw their bonds decrease 25%..if there is no deal..the bonds WILL trade back to 130</Msg><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360522299117-15</Id><Topic><Title>I have AAPL...hate to see you poor DELL investors getting screwed</Title><Username>tukkersmom2</Username><Timestamp>1360504819098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL is the future DEll, Kodak,Palm, Edsel ......AAPL would make a good value investment for a few years with a higher Dividend.</Msg><Username>mr.phil2u</Username><Timestamp>1360522299117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:51:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360522349538-16</Id><Title>the filing is right there on bloomberg..Vanguard just bought 7 million more Dell bonds..they own the most</Title><Msg>Vanguard isn't stupid</Msg><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522349538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:52:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360522597410-17</Id><Title>How can we throw Michael Dell out of Dell?</Title><Msg>He showing all of us he is smart and cunning on how to manipulate the board and steal the company and all those who had faith in him and his company. He is not fit to be an officer or chairman of our company.</Msg><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360522597410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360522839474-18</Id><Topic><Title>How can we throw Michael Dell out of Dell?</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360522597410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>his 15% ownership ..are NON VOTING rights..so shareholders could vote him out</Msg><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522839474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:00:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360523217059-19</Id><Topic><Title>I have AAPL...hate to see you poor DELL investors getting screwed</Title><Username>tukkersmom2</Username><Timestamp>1360504819098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 09:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not every Dell investor is getting screwed, bought under $11 a month ago an I'm ahead also have Apple and Friday bought More Apple. Will use proceeds from Dell to buy even more Apple. So it is not wise to post something like you did</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1360523217059</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:06:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360525659415-20</Id><Title>pure example of corporate greed, Dell, Facebook etc</Title><Msg>It is all about how much money a CEO can scam from loyal investors and workers. Is everyone blind, look a smile of ZUCKERBERG!!! Stock Market is legal fraud</Msg><Username>predator117a2000</Username><Timestamp>1360525659415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360525880772-21</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#1 you may own 900 shares. 9,000 shares? not a chance. #2 a buyout offer at $13.65 might be in lopsided in favor of the seller #3 if $13.65 was at all a "lowball" or "unfairly low" bid, then other buying groups would have emerged to make their own offer. #4'compliant with the government? Really, sainimd you are full of #$%$</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1360525880772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:51:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360528025895-22</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree.agree.agree. Will never buy dell again. And BF....the village idiot, why not 9000 shares?? You are insulting and naive</Msg><Username>sexylawgirl1</Username><Timestamp>1360528025895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 15:27:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360528061609-23</Id><Topic><Title>pure example of corporate greed, Dell, Facebook etc</Title><Username>predator117a2000</Username><Timestamp>1360525659415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:47:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody makes you buy a stock. If you don't like the stock market then put your money in a savings account. Hope this helps.</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1360528061609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 15:27:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360528140491-24</Id><Topic><Title>How can we throw Michael Dell out of Dell?</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360522597410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:56:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong. He cannot vote on this buyout offer but otherwise his shares are not non-voting.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1360528140491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 15:29:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360530522458-25</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen honey, hush your mouth about subjects you know nothing about, like DELL. Try to make yourself look pretty , fix me some dinner, go lie down in the bedroom and wait for me. If you are lucky I might oblige you. Hope this helps.</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1360530522458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:08:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360532140171-26</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you change your tune so often bashford???.... last night you said the vote WILL pass: "For conversation let's say DELL is a pie of 100 shares. Mike has 16 shares, and we will remove those from the pie, making the voting pie 84 shares.Southeastern has 8 shares, which they are threatening to vote against the merger. Add to that a few other large shareholders who comibned have 8 votes. So, worst case scenario 16 of 84 votes (from significant shareowners)will be NO. But let's add a bunch of passionate little amateurs like fluteman or CTG or mrphile who are sitting at home in t-shirt and jeans, sweating their 500 share positions here. But, because they watched some 15 year old Hollywood movie about Wall Street , they think they know how the game is played. For conversation let's add every little fools share count to the mix and call it 25 NO votes out of 84. Understand, the overwehleming majority of shareowners never cast a vote, And, plenty are very pleased to get $13.65 for their shares, becase that's a lot better price than $10, where DELL traded much of last year. Get the picture now? hope this helps." now you're saying the vote WILL NOT pass: "Considering that nost stockholders never actually vote , this nearly ensures Mike Dell's buyout offer will not be accepted." seriously, make up your mind. you can't have it both ways!</Msg><Username>jj0850</Username><Timestamp>1360532140171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:35:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360532936380-27</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was only two days ago I learned stockholders not voting their shares will be registered as NO votes. That is an unusual condition, which I expect Dell's LBO team installed to protect itself against litigation. Considering the reluctance stocholders have to ever cast a vote, it is most likely the LBO team's offer will not receive enough votes. I estimate a 95% chance the LBO team offer doesn't receive enough votes and Dell will remain a public company.</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1360532936380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 16:48:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360533921469-28</Id><Topic><Title>Vote on Dell merger - I am extremely mad</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360521689088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:41:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I estimate a 95% chance the LBO team offer doesn't receive enough votes and Dell will remain a public company." "My guess is that there is a 50-50 chance there will be a buyout, with the price being about $12.50" so far your guesses haven't panned out....hopefully your estimates do better!</Msg><Username>jj0850</Username><Timestamp>1360533921469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:05:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360536220276-29</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Due to the significant gap between the current LBO price and Southwestern Group's cost basis, there is no way the LBO group can raise the price enough to satisfy Southwestern Group. One scenario I think can happen is to let Southwestern Group to swap its stock holding to get a stake in the private Dell, while sweeten the deal a little to mollify the others smaller institutional and individual stock holders.</Msg><Username>exwmci</Username><Timestamp>1360536220276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:43:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360536984339-30</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell does not owe Southeastern anything.</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1360536984339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 17:56:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360538565255-31</Id><Topic><Title>pure example of corporate greed, Dell, Facebook etc</Title><Username>predator117a2000</Username><Timestamp>1360525659415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 14:47:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buyout way too low and you know it.</Msg><Username>jcsj00</Username><Timestamp>1360538565255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360540737599-32</Id><Title>Caryle Group Will Make and Offer</Title><Msg>Just watch...true value of Dell is beginning to be revealed, it won't be 24, but they will take a run at DELL for 14-15.50...just watch and learn!</Msg><Username>magoo_danny</Username><Timestamp>1360540737599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:58:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542166565-33</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares what the bondholders say, as long as dell doesn't default on loan convenants and pay it's interest payments, bondholders don't matter. unless dell has a slave loan...regular loans, just pay the interest and bondholders couldn't care less whether it's private company that is not listed in nasdaq anymore. shareholders don't have to sell and can sell their outside NYSE in the street corner. get your shares from dell management since the shares won't be sold to the public markets. dell is a 'private' company..public company just means it's sold in the public in the street or in nasdaq. buying or selling shares in the private market is much more difficult than in nasdaq. and less costly to dell. it cost dell 1 million to be public company to comply with SEC reporting and accounting etc. and deal with complaints from retail peon investors..</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542166565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:22:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542308673-34</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bondholders have no say whether board of directors is private or public listed company. and it doesn't matter to bondholders if dell is private or public listed...their bonds are still traded in the bond market though over the counter. minimum bond purchase is $5000 or more if I'm correct. stock market is waste of time for dell. peon retail investors.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542308673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:25:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542389639-35</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you sure don't know what you are talking about, do you,,dell can redeem the bonds at face value too when they expire.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542389639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:26:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542421198-36</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bondholders have no say.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542421198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:27:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542459714-37</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only shareholders have the decision making power or management authority when to take the company private or delist from nasdaq.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542459714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542518702-38</Id><Topic><Title>after further review..81% of dell bonds are institutional owned..they will all VOTE NO</Title><Username>nickmathews960</Username><Timestamp>1360522173054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 13:49:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bondholders are not shareholders...totally different class of stakeholders. bondholders are gauranteed interest payments. dividends are not gauranteed anything for shareholders. a</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542518702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542638139-39</Id><Topic><Title>Caryle Group Will Make and Offer</Title><Username>magoo_danny</Username><Timestamp>1360540737599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:58:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no money for a 25 billion or even 30 billion cash,,you guys think 30 billion is peanuts or grows in trees. it's freaking 25 billion for shares? this isn't pocket change...25 billion.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542638139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:30:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542698714-40</Id><Topic><Title>Caryle Group Will Make and Offer</Title><Username>magoo_danny</Username><Timestamp>1360540737599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:58:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you guys are just greedy and think your shares are more than 25 billion..25 billion is very generous offer. nobody will pay any higher for no growth company.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542698714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:31:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542772446-41</Id><Topic><Title>Caryle Group Will Make and Offer</Title><Username>magoo_danny</Username><Timestamp>1360540737599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 18:58:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do you think dell is going private, nobody wants to buy the shares and not worth the cost of being a private company. there is only a handful of shareholders less than 500 significant shareholders.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542772446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:32:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360542877746-42</Id><Topic><Title>Samsung should make a bid for Dell</Title><Username>qualityrams</Username><Timestamp>1360509575166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 10:19:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bid 5 billion not 25 billion. dell and microsoft can have it for 25 billion.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360542877746</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 19:34:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360545914641-43</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bashford - It is perplexing to me that you agree that $13.65/sh. fairly values Dell. Having followed the statements of Mason Hawkins for many years, and recognizing that he has deep experience in valuing firms, I can not understand why shareholders should not demand a $5 - $6 special dividend, a Dutch auction or some other mechanism by which @ $20/sh could be realized. How the BOD approved this is baffling, and, ostensibly, a conflict of interest.</Msg><Username>ubermunch77</Username><Timestamp>1360545914641</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 20:25:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360552881544-44</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because dell has 9 billion in debt. paying a 500 million dollar /year dividend and the company has 9 billion in debt. the shareholder have already decided no dividend. now if you don't like zero dividend you can sell your peon shares in the street corner. the shares are not listed in nasdaq and there is no market makers for your stock zero bid.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360552881544</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:21:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360553022977-45</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the facdt you even suggest $5 dividend shows you don't know what your are talking about. that would 5 billion in dividend. that company has 9 billion in debt and no growth. fool! where doe the company get the money to pay $5/dividend?</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360553022977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:23:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360553076878-46</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid public peon investors is the reason companies go bankrupt. it waste management time and energy. and money. and way too much market manipulation and insider trading abuses if it's a public company.</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360553076878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:24:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360553174308-47</Id><Topic><Title>What do you think will happen? from your experience...</Title><Username>kkkk200928</Username><Timestamp>1360435421768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-09 13:43:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if dell becomes a private company, investors will all be accredited investors or insitutitons. usually minimum investment is $1 million. it cost more money to transfer shares of private companies. you have to send your shares to the company etc.and pay for transfer fees. not $5/commissions</Msg><Username>freemarketcapitalc</Username><Timestamp>1360553174308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:26:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360553988453-48</Id><Title>Bashford and other people trying to scare us</Title><Msg>These are guns hired by Silver Lake and Michael Dell and Microsoft to scare people to sell so that they make tons of money. Some of the comments made by Bashford are stupid. I have to wonder why such an idiot spends all day on this board and other boards telling us we have to sell. Otherwise, the stock will go even lower. The only people who make money in this case by Bashford are people who bought the stock under 13.65 in past few months. Just about everyone who purchased stock in past 18 yrs and holding it is going to lose money on this deal. Bashford, why don't you post your real picture on this post. Do you have a job? What else do you do other than spend the whole day looking at these posts and say things to scare. Tell us who pays you. Is it Silver Lake or Dell or Microsoft? Are you going to change names and post other stupid things under other names?</Msg><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360553988453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:39:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360554600604-49</Id><Topic><Title>Bashford and other people trying to scare us</Title><Username>sainimd</Username><Timestamp>1360553988453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:39:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you think bashford is a hired gun, I have a water pistol I want to sell you. Bashford is simply an idiot with no experience at anything.</Msg><Username>ellerbebil2</Username><Timestamp>1360554600604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-10 22:50:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>