<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370163154350-1</Id><Topic><Title>Dont vote for the Dell offer vote your proxie to southestern instead.</Title><Username>suggp</Username><Timestamp>1370112259159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 14:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only Analysts say MD is winning, as they lie usually. I saw one analyst saying about a telecom stock" This stock will go through roof" After few weeks stock went through floor! These analysts are paid by companies to fool investors.</Msg><Username>arif77_9</Username><Timestamp>1370163154350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 04:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370163229378-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mike Dell Tells Shareholders His Offer is Better.................</Title><Username>market_maker_2000</Username><Timestamp>1370029704778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 15:48:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joke of the Year!</Msg><Username>arif77_9</Username><Timestamp>1370163229378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 04:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370198823854-3</Id><Title>Who in their right mind would buy this stock?</Title><Msg>WHO? Probably one of the most underperforming tech stocks out there. Stick a fork in Dell.</Msg><Username>schule7607</Username><Timestamp>1370198823854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 14:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370207884311-4</Id><Title>$16.65-16.35+0.08=$0.38 per share</Title><Msg>That's more than Dell's one year dividend in just about two months, assuming deal closes by August and there is no Icahn deal. Dell will announce its quarterly dividend of 0.08 by end of this week.</Msg><Username>value_oriented_123</Username><Timestamp>1370207884311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370214054253-5</Id><Title>Icahn has been living in the Bizarro Universe the past few years, how could he run a company!?</Title><Msg>Seriously he is an Ill man. He has destroyed so much he has become involved in. Being part of the whole BB fiasco for several years he had either arranged some back-door deal with Ergen to make himself and himself alone a profit (certainly nobody else made any) or he has some form of dementia. Everything he did was irrational and illogical. The CFO of Dish even went on record a little while back stating that Dish was able to purchase the assets for far lower than book value. Everyone got shafted, all debt holders and obviously shareholders. So morale of the story, whatever Icahn is promising don't trust him no matter how good it sounds he will shaft you in the end.</Msg><Username>susan.mcan</Username><Timestamp>1370214054253</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 19:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>