<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365861034509-1</Id><Topic><Title>DOES ANY ONE HAVE CORRECT INFO ABOUT DELL BUY OUT</Title><Username>parrothead032000</Username><Timestamp>1365818149704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 21:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares. Dell is competing with JCP at this point.</Msg><Username>vgerphonehome</Username><Timestamp>1365861034509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 09:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365903471524-2</Id><Topic><Title>Icahn walking away</Title><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1365780299657</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 11:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart money values dell PC business at only $3 a share - there is much more value in this company than PC business.</Msg><Username>dogwood1855</Username><Timestamp>1365903471524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 21:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365905005967-3</Id><Title>Offer Going Higher and here is why...</Title><Msg>If Michael Dell wants to take company private - offer will be going higher. Reasons:] 1. Southeastern controls 7% of the company and will NOT agree to this price. Southeastern has stated in their analysis Dell is worth $24 and they are only assigning $3 of that to Dell's PC business that everyone is hung up on over due to recent slower world PC numbers. Further, there is T Rowe Price that will not agree to Michael Dell's offer either. 2. You have not one, but two players with money who are willing to pay more than Michael Dell's current offer who are Carl Icahn and Stephan Schwarman of Blackstone. 3. Let's say Dell only has a 3B profit in 2014 ($1.30 earnings per share). The bottom line is when you take out the cash, Michael Dell offer is less than 8 times earnings. You are not going to see a company like Dell sell this cheap. Offer either goes up or company is staying public (just like it is). Michael Dell can try to spin the recent PC numbers, pull the wool over the board's eyes, try to pay Icahn to go away. However, Southeastern and T Rowe Price are smart and will look out for the small investors.</Msg><Username>dogwood1855</Username><Timestamp>1365905005967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365909843937-4</Id><Topic><Title>Offer Going Higher and here is why...</Title><Username>dogwood1855</Username><Timestamp>1365905005967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 22:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thia whole DELL thing is getting boring... I'm out</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1365909843937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 23:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>