<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364808862888-1</Id><Topic><Title>M Dell is greedy and wants a gefilte fish party ! Yummy</Title><Username>oregon_bob</Username><Timestamp>1364775788207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 20:23:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't everyone? This is capitalism.</Msg><Username>fv215b</Username><Timestamp>1364808862888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 05:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364814037532-2</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>marioblu576</Username><Timestamp>1362329669381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice</Msg><Username>rbischin</Username><Timestamp>1364814037532</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:00:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364814991827-3</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Bounce Report</Title><Username>wiliam.keneddy</Username><Timestamp>1363122793646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 17:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>iop78tmor7</Msg><Username>rbischin</Username><Timestamp>1364814991827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364815059240-4</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH DELL Analyst Report</Title><Username>sergiovialueva</Username><Timestamp>1363016548804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 11:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>drjh876j8</Msg><Username>rbischin</Username><Timestamp>1364815059240</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 07:17:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364817833100-5</Id><Title>I do not trust Mihael Dell</Title><Msg>Therefore, selling the stock would be a wise mower.</Msg><Username>madam_hillary07</Username><Timestamp>1364817833100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:03:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364819444668-6</Id><Title>Throw Michael Dell Out</Title><Msg>Sucker has not done anything to bring the company or stock value up. Lost the entire mobile opportunity. Needs to be fired.</Msg><Username>investorindividual</Username><Timestamp>1364819444668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 08:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364822243617-7</Id><Topic><Title>M.DELL say take $13.65 or face stock to crash in the future to shareholders: So retail take $13.65 or face hell roars LION</Title><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1364655036925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:50:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Greg Roumeliotis and Poornima Gupta NEW YORK/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Dell Inc warned on Friday that it would be dangerous to take on a lot of debt and remain a public company given its worsening profit outlook, in a sign that it views proposals from Blackstone Group LP and billionaire investor Carl Icahn as fraught with risk. The No. 3 maker of personal computers published a 274-page preliminary proxy statement to inform Dell shareholders of how a $24.4 billion buyout proposal from founder and Chief Executive Michael Dell and private equity firm Silver Lake Partners was put together, and why it is the best of all the alternatives the company's board had explored. Icahn has proposed paying $15 per share for 58 percent of Dell, while Blackstone has indicated it can pay more than $14.25 per share -- both deals involve saddling the company with a lot of debt and keeping it on public markets. Silver Lake's $13.65 per share all-cash offer would see Dell go private. Dell's proxy statement did not directly pass judgment on the Blackstone and Icahn bids, yet it warned that any leveraged recapitalization was risky if the company was to remain public. "Even when taking into account the certain value distributed to stockholders, (a leveraged recapitalization) would be unlikely to result in an aggregate value exceeding the $13.65 per share merger consideration and would present a number of risks and challenges," Dell said in the statement, referring to its special committee's review. Such a move would decrease employee, customer and supplier confidence in the company's long-term prospects and potentially limit the company's ability to aggressively implement its long-term business strategy, Dell added. Under all scenarios examined by Boston Consulting Group, which carried out an independent analysis for Dell, revenues are seen slipping every year to 2016. Dell's board expects fiscal 2014 operating income of $3 billion, down from last summer's internal forecast of as much #$%$6 billion, the proxy shows. LONG NEGOTIATIONS Dell painted an account of arduous negotiations. It set up a special committee to evaluate all the company's options aiming to placate concerns over potential conflicts of interest facing Michael Dell. The CEO owns 15.7 percent of the company he started in 1984 out of his college dorm room with $1,000. Under his take-private deal, Michael Dell and his investment firm would own 75.9 percent of the company, with Silver Lake owning the rest. Dell said Michael Dell's and Silver Lake's post-buyout plan anticipated adding a significant number of sales personnel and boosting spending on research and development. There are no plans to embark on major assets sales following the buyout, it added, The restructuring plan envisioned, were it to be carried out with Dell as a public company, would not be palatable to shareholders and the stock could suffer, Dell said. Dell also said a strategic party, whose identity it did not disclose, expressed interest on January 24 to acquire its financial services business for its book value, estimated at between $3.5 billion and $4.5 billion, excluding debt. A standalone deal of this kind would not benefit the company, Dell concluded. BLACKSTONE MEETINGS Michael Dell met with Blackstone and its buyout partner Francisco Partners on March 7 and 8 during a 45-day, so-called "go-shop" period when other bidders are invited to make offers, the proxy said, indicating that Blackstone explored early on the possibility of keeping Michael Dell as CEO. Michael Dell also met earlier this week with Blackstone's senior managing directors Dave Johnson and Chinh Chu, although the outcome of those discussions has yet to become clear, a person familiar with the matter said on Friday. Michael Dell has expressed concern that Blackstone's offer would dismantle the PC maker he founded in 1984, two people close to Michael Dell have told Reuters. The founder is worried that the buyout firm's plans would be inconsistent with his strategy to reinvest in the company, they added. Blackstone has already made an unsuccessful push to recruit Oracle Corp President Mark Hurd to run Dell if it takes over the company, one source familiar with the situation said last week. Dell revealed that its special committee, chaired by businessman Alex Mandl and set up to assess all possible strategic alternatives for the company, also comprises of board members Laura Conigliaro, Janet Clark and Kenneth Duberstein. The proxy statement shows how Silver Lake raised its bid six times by about $4 billion, or over 20 percent, during the course of the negotiations. The final agreed price of $13.65 per share in cash is below where Dell shares ended trading on Thursday at $14.33. Before approving the deal and announcing it on February 5, Dell spent more than five months evaluating alternatives that included a leveraged recapitalization and selling all or part of the business. Dell was regarded as a model of innovation as recently as the early 2000s, pioneering online ordering of custom-configured PCs and working closely with Asian component suppliers and manufacturers to assure rock-bottom production costs. But as of 2012's fourth quarter, Dell's share of the global PC market had slipped to just above 10 percent from 12.5 percent a year earlier, according to research house IDC. The proxy statement shows how the special committee wrested with the notion of staying public as the company's financial fundamentals weakened. Dell's detailed regulatory filing also showed how Microsoft Corp's Windows operating system - which once had a chokehold over the whole PC market, is being undermined by other software. Dell said it is seeing uncertain adoption of Microsoft's new Windows 8 operating system, which was launched with much fanfare last year, and an unexpected slowdown in Windows 7 upgrades by businesses. (Reporting by Gregory Roumeliotis in New York, Poornima Gupta in San Francisco; Editing by Chizu Nomiyama, David Gregorio, Tiffany Wu and Leslie Gevirtz) Less</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1364822243617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 09:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364824858184-8</Id><Title>Can some smarter minds than mine enlighten me</Title><Msg>in the first place why would Icahn want 58% of the stock in a company he thinks is failing? In one of the million news stories he said he thought the company was worth $24 -- why doesn't he just offer @ say 17.50 or 18 - take it to the shareholders - and just buyout the company? Do you really think M. Dell is going to dump his stock in a hissy fit (well, I'll take my ball and go home) and drive down the value of his own stock? Frankly, if he would do something like that he doesn't even deserve to be CEO!</Msg><Username>stkmkter</Username><Timestamp>1364824858184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364830362123-9</Id><Topic><Title>Can some smarter minds than mine enlighten me</Title><Username>stkmkter</Username><Timestamp>1364824858184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ichan likes to get his name in the news, and he can afford to lose $200 million playing around with some DELL stock.</Msg><Username>bashfordcapital</Username><Timestamp>1364830362123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364831246084-10</Id><Topic><Title>Can some smarter minds than mine enlighten me</Title><Username>stkmkter</Username><Timestamp>1364824858184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess that's my problem - I don't like losing money!! Even if I were a billionaire I wouldn't like flushing $200 million down the drain just for fun or something to do - it's stupid. Thought Icahn was all about winning - this makes him look silly!!!!</Msg><Username>stkmkter</Username><Timestamp>1364831246084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 11:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364832105154-11</Id><Title>Easy as 1, 2, 3</Title><Msg>All you have to do is follow their picks. They send them right to your phone. Text “stocks” to 555888</Msg><Username>austinfox928</Username><Timestamp>1364832105154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 12:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364835644994-12</Id><Topic><Title>Can some smarter minds than mine enlighten me</Title><Username>stkmkter</Username><Timestamp>1364824858184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 10:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With 58% of the stock he can run it as he likes, and drain the assets over time much like the Dell management has done over the last two years. Plus he doesnt have to invest the other 42%.</Msg><Username>suggp</Username><Timestamp>1364835644994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364835957239-13</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH DELL Analyst Report</Title><Username>sergiovialueva</Username><Timestamp>1363016548804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 11:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome</Msg><Username>kaim.dawis</Username><Timestamp>1364835957239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364836126473-14</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Bounce Report</Title><Username>wiliam.keneddy</Username><Timestamp>1363122793646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 17:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow</Msg><Username>kaim.dawis</Username><Timestamp>1364836126473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364836437224-15</Id><Title>About to Make Biggest Run in Market</Title><Msg>Concurrent (CCUR) fundamentally is extremely undervalued, needs to double to reach comparable valuation ratios vs. its #1 rival Seachange (SEAC). CCUR has gained 12 straight months and 8 of the past 9 trading days, giving it the best looking chart with the most momentum in the market. CCUR is currently $7.91 and as soon as CCUR breaks through $8 strongly, it could rally to $12-$15 range within following 2-3 trading days. CCUR is $7.91 with only 9.2mm o/s $24.6mm in cash no debt and enterprise value of $48.17mm or 0.77X revenue of $62.59mm. CCUR's gross margins of 58.81% exceed SEAC's gross margins of 50.18%, yet SEAC is trading with enterprise value/revenue ratio of 1.89, which would value CCUR at $15.53. CCUR's net income last quarter was up 100% from previous quarter and up 300% from two quarters ago. CCUR has $24.6mm or $2.67 per share in cash and no debt. After subtracting its cash per share from share price of $7.91, its business is being valued at $5.24 per share. CCUR's non-GAAP EPS last quarter of $0.125 equals $0.50 annualized, valuing CCUR's business at an insanely low 10X earnings! SEAC is currently $11.89 and expected to report fiscal year 2013 non-GAAP EPS next week of $0.40. This means SEAC has a P/E of 30. With CCUR's annualized non-GAAP EPS of $0.50, a P/E of 30 would value CCUR at $15! CCUR is the global video on demand (VOD) leader with reach of 50mm VOD homes worldwide and clients in the U.S. including Time Warner Cable, Cox, Charter, and Bright House. CCUR is about to revolutionize industry with new cloud based network DVR technology that will make today's DVR boxes obsolete!</Msg><Username>asj48493</Username><Timestamp>1364836437224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364836637306-16</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>marioblu576</Username><Timestamp>1362329669381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>56ib764i</Msg><Username>kaim.dawis</Username><Timestamp>1364836637306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364837149844-17</Id><Topic><Title>Barrons</Title><Username>chicadee75</Username><Timestamp>1364767240251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 18:00:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know where Southeastern stands. I have sold all of my Dell in the mid $14's. After reading your many posts on here I am puzzled what your position is - Clearly not long but much of what you have said also doesn't make sense if you are short. Just curious.</Msg><Username>mike.crew</Username><Timestamp>1364837149844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 13:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364839319473-18</Id><Topic><Title>Reality Check</Title><Username>starcushing</Username><Timestamp>1364489435266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:50:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dell and his group haven't really come up with $24B. In fact, the reports are that Dell is doing what you say about Exxon - they are using company assets to pay for part of the buy-out. The actual money Dell and his group bring to the table is pretty small.</Msg><Username>kid_owens</Username><Timestamp>1364839319473</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364839514201-19</Id><Topic><Title>Reality Check</Title><Username>starcushing</Username><Timestamp>1364489435266</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 12:50:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There may be lawsuits if Dell's bid is approved, too.</Msg><Username>kid_owens</Username><Timestamp>1364839514201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364841257953-20</Id><Topic><Title>Secret DELL Info Revealed</Title><Username>carterhoward166</Username><Timestamp>1363887951696</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Helpful report</Msg><Username>walkerssteve</Username><Timestamp>1364841257953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 14:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364850849642-21</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Upgraded to STRONG BUY (EXCLUSIVE REPORT)</Title><Username>marioblu576</Username><Timestamp>1362329669381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-03 11:54:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ghuytujht</Msg><Username>noahicona</Username><Timestamp>1364850849642</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364851610799-22</Id><Topic><Title>DELL Bounce Report</Title><Username>wiliam.keneddy</Username><Timestamp>1363122793646</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 17:13:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>j76867j</Msg><Username>noahicona</Username><Timestamp>1364851610799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364851679844-23</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH DELL Analyst Report</Title><Username>sergiovialueva</Username><Timestamp>1363016548804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 11:42:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ynetur</Msg><Username>noahicona</Username><Timestamp>1364851679844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 17:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364858867079-24</Id><Title>"Best days are still ahead..."</Title><Msg>If Michael Dell is being sincere, the company's value will increase and that is, perhaps, why he, SilverLake, Blackstone and Icahn are interested in buying the company. I think the deal will get done at a price of $15 or more. With Icahn's offer on the table, it would be hard to get shareholder approval for less. If Michael teams up with Blackstone, they don't have to pony up for his 4B and can increase their offer to get it done. If SilverLake really wants it, they will have to come up with something more than current offers. Icahn can continue to be a fly in the ointment unless he gets the premium/profit he wants. Just my thoughts.....</Msg><Username>stockmamma</Username><Timestamp>1364858867079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 19:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364860234345-25</Id><Topic><Title>"Best days are still ahead..."</Title><Username>stockmamma</Username><Timestamp>1364858867079</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 19:27:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was what I thought too..but I have been wrong so far These were my presumptions 1) Dell would not cooperate with BX because (a) BX wants to keep a public stub , which belies M Dell's whole purpose of this buyout anyway (b) BX wants to sell parts of DELL which Dell might not be open to 2) With Icahn's $15 offer already on the table (with a public stub), a fully private offer of</Msg><Username>gaptun</Username><Timestamp>1364860234345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 19:50:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364872888760-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mike Dell, why do you need to stay in control. Arent you worth 16 billion dollars ?</Title><Username>gitreelonce</Username><Timestamp>1364870763522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 22:46:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Question: How much are the hard assets of the company actually worth? If Michael Dell were to buy the company, how much would he be paying for the name and goodwill portion of the company? Would this number be in the billions? Maybe he should just walk away and start a new company. He has the name that people would trust if they were to buy a product from him. If he started a new computer company, the products could be manufactured in China. With him being behind the new company, he could quite possibly accomplish this with no money out of his pocket. The manufacturing companies and investors would most likely cover all of the costs.</Msg><Username>tlee22202</Username><Timestamp>1364872888760</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-01 23:21:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>