<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366208956608-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Slow Drift Back to $13.65</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1366158990212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubt it. This thing has ridiculous downside protection at 14. You won't see it get below 13.98 today, machines won't let it.</Msg><Username>stanleysharptrader</Username><Timestamp>1366208956608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366209192177-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Slow Drift Back to $13.65</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1366158990212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't matter what the market is doing, what the sector is doing, how grim PC sales look, none of that matters with this stock right now. Every index could plummet -5% today and this guy won't stay under 14.</Msg><Username>stanleysharptrader</Username><Timestamp>1366209192177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366214189703-3</Id><Topic><Title>The Slow Drift Back to $13.65</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1366158990212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is much arbitrage buying in Dell by smart money that have done detail review on the parts of this company. I would never recommend buying anything on margin or credit. If you own it for cash you own it. Now there is an exception to this rule if you are smart and have much money, and that’s if you are doing anarbitrage transaction, or you have a set short-term time limit involved, and you must be able to cover a margin call if it ever happens. Warren Buffett contrary to public knowledge is very big in arbitrage, and he is one of the best at it. Very few people know this about him, and over the past 20 years or so and maybe much longer than that, Buffett has demonstrated about a 70% annual return on his arbitrage account. I am sure Dell's agreement so Carl would not buy more stock will but a lid on price for a while. But, there is more smart big money out that that is slowly buying shares above Michael Dell's offer price for they know company is worth more than his offer.</Msg><Username>dogwood1855</Username><Timestamp>1366214189703</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366228656046-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Slow Drift Back to $13.65</Title><Username>debbie_downer_does_dallas</Username><Timestamp>1366158990212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 20:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is much arbitrage buying in Dell by smart money that have done detail review on the parts of this company. I would never recommend buying anything on margin or credit. If you own it for cash you own it. Now there is an exception to this rule if you are smart and have much money, and that’s if you are doing anarbitrage transaction, or you have a set short-term time limit involved, and you must be able to cover a margin call if it ever happens. Warren Buffett contrary to public knowledge is very big in arbitrage, and he is one of the best at it. Very few people know this about him, and over the past 20 years or so and maybe much longer than that, Buffett has demonstrated about a 70% annual return on his arbitrage account. I am sure Dell's agreement so Carl would not buy more stock will but a lid on price for a while. But, there is more smart big money out that that is slowly buying shares above Michael Dell's offer price for they know company is worth more.....</Msg><Username>dogwood1855</Username><Timestamp>1366228656046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 15:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366229569558-5</Id><Title>So what if we have pc sales falling off a cliff?</Title><Msg>Why should that lower what all of these bidders will pay for a dinosaur business?</Msg><Username>jctuttle13</Username><Timestamp>1366229569558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>