<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370935373522-1</Id><Title>Michael Dell is the Bernie Maddff of the computer industry</Title><Msg>First of all, Michael Dell has a delusion that he owns Windows Electra software that I created, Michael Dell has pocketed more money on the lighted mouse theft invention of mine provided by John Paul Gray of Newport Beach, CA and Vickie Terranova, he has stolen more money on the lighted mouse theft than anyone in the world. He threatens me thinking he owns Windows Electra software with bribes. Michael Dell will NEVER con Windows Electra sofware out of me with John Paul Gray and Vickie Terranova. John Gooch Owner and creator of Windows Electra software since 2002</Msg><Username>goochandassociates</Username><Timestamp>1370935373522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 03:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370977816932-2</Id><Topic><Title>I got a phone call this weekend from the Wall Street firm representing Michael Dell and the Board</Title><Username>pj1998</Username><Timestamp>1370902079992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well lets take a look at the facts. Under Michael Dell's leadership this company has continued to decline at an ever faster rate. He invests ton's of $$ in the Dell Smart phone development, makes a ton of acquisitions in the market and none of them have been successful and continue to divide Dell and loose marketshare in the process. The numbers last quarter raise some questions as to was this planned to make it easier for Michael to take the company private. When is the SEC and stockholders going to start lawyering up. I am not saying Carl Icon is the right choice either but I can tell you I don't have any faith in the BOD or Mr. Dell at this point. Whitman and HPQ have to be excited to see this debacle.</Msg><Username>kavack</Username><Timestamp>1370977816932</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370977867126-3</Id><Title>OT: Check out RAYS for Huge Fun and Profit....</Title><Msg>Small Float Way Oversold and Shorts are being squeezed$$ Money WILL be Made!</Msg><Username>steveboonlertheidbrider</Username><Timestamp>1370977867126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370983039882-4</Id><Topic><Title>I got a phone call this weekend from the Wall Street firm representing Michael Dell and the Board</Title><Username>pj1998</Username><Timestamp>1370902079992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If anyone votes against this deal, since there is NO alternative deal. Icahn has no deal. The stock will drop to 9. Almost instantly. This company is in severe decline. Both desktop and laptop lines are nearly unprofitable. 13.65 is a good deal. It really is. No serious deal has ever been presented by anyone for $15. So you want to send Michael away and ask for more? What if he just sells his position and gets out now? He gets out and you become the bagholder at $9. Then he comes back and offers $9.65. See how this works?</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1370983039882</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370983117013-5</Id><Topic><Title>Proxy vote</Title><Username>bhigdon21</Username><Timestamp>1370898358594</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why bother. Sell your shares now. If the deal fails, buy back at $9. Where is the upside? Nobody will offer a penny over $13.65. They shopped the company for a year. NOTHING.</Msg><Username>cspanosmwc</Username><Timestamp>1370983117013</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371008371142-6</Id><Topic><Title>I got a phone call this weekend from the Wall Street firm representing Michael Dell and the Board</Title><Username>pj1998</Username><Timestamp>1370902079992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 18:07:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know how it works. MD is trying his best to convince all the holders of Dell that is a fair offer at $13.65. Only MD knows the true value of a company that could become the next IBM. I am betting that Mr. Dell will not stand to loose his rein of the company he founded. He is determined to bring his company back to importance to the tech world. I might be wrong but I am betting on a $15.00 bid.</Msg><Username>currantim55</Username><Timestamp>1371008371142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>