<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356260046099-1</Id><Topic><Title>Targeting is the MAGIC WORD of Mobile Search</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1356184136207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>•The ‘Soccer Mom’ demo »Aged between 25-45 with one or more child at home »Controls significant portion of the household spend »Typically spends 80% of that money within 20 miles of home •89% of in-store purchasers in key categories have conducted online research** •82% of people visiting local search sites follow-up with offline action (store visit/call)** •Soccer mom + local + commercial = ad sponsors »~70% of revenue is CPC; 20% subscriptions; 10% display •57% of Local.Corp's flagship-site and 80% of Spreebird traffic is this demo This targeting is very important, why Local Corp can better monetize bought traffic from Google and Yahoo than this both more universal companies with a general approach. The relaunched Local Corp's flagship-site provides a lifestyle enhancing local search environment including the vertical categories of Businesses, Coupons, Events and Activities, each of which contain rich content that is of great interest to Local Corp's target audience -- busy "household managers/soccer moms." This target is broadly defined as women between the ages of 25-45 with one or more children at home. The site incorporates many new features and improved functionality, including the ability for users to engage in their communities by sharing information, and reviewing and becoming fans of businesses.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1356260046099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 05:54:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356272640740-2</Id><Title>Vodka /CEDC/ up big</Title><Msg>EV (enterprise value) 1:10 ratio, DEO 7:8 no wonder</Msg><Username>valuufindr</Username><Timestamp>1356272640740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 09:24:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356289426127-3</Id><Title>$700 plus dollars a share and their damn EMail service is down again Mucking Fonderful</Title><Msg>simply mucking fonderful...yahoo does the same sloppy service for less than 20 bucks</Msg><Username>truth_is_the_mother_of_hatred</Username><Timestamp>1356289426127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:03:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356295022032-4</Id><Topic><Title>$700 plus dollars a share and their damn EMail service is down again Mucking Fonderful</Title><Username>truth_is_the_mother_of_hatred</Username><Timestamp>1356289426127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:03:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOGLE EMAIL WORKS FINE WHY ARE YOU SCREAMING?LOL GOOGLE BANGS AMAZON IN 2013 BIG TIME</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1356295022032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:37:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356302429431-5</Id><Topic><Title>Targeting is the MAGIC WORD of Mobile Search</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1356184136207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 08:48:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Each site is expected to include educational articles and other content about specific topics, the ability to request and receive a quote from licensed industry professionals by completing a brief form, and a directory that enables consumers to search for and locate service providers in their local area, including contact information and, where available, user ratings and reviews. . The First New Vertical Site: InsuranceLow is a comprehensive car insurance site designed to help serve you with making the best choice you can in picking the most affordable insurance solution that fits your needs. The more you know, the better you are to find the right type of car insurance coverage for you and your family. We thank you for visiting InsuranceLow and wish you the best of luck in picking the best car insurance solution for you!</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1356302429431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 17:40:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356311437037-6</Id><Title>Looks like no special divy from Google</Title><Msg>Too cheap to pay shareholders.</Msg><Username>biotechh</Username><Timestamp>1356311437037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 20:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356317346819-7</Id><Topic><Title>Gambled on Sept. 28 760 Calls...Bought 100 @ .50</Title><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1348844205190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent play? He lost everything just like you Jboy...what a sad pathetic #$%$ you are.</Msg><Username>sonw_13</Username><Timestamp>1356317346819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 21:49:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>