<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349584718554-1</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a Mormon vs. Obama is a Christian, you choose!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349494714457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 23:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Schooled by the formidable Reverend Jeremiah Wright to 20 years</Msg><Username>stockstar17</Username><Timestamp>1349584718554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349618574909-2</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a Mormon vs. Obama is a Christian, you choose!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349494714457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 23:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a Socialist....he freely admits it. If he gets another term, this country will really decline fast.</Msg><Username>bonnett_tim</Username><Timestamp>1349618574909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349619825665-3</Id><Title>Our tax dollars now being used to offset legal costs to delay layoffs until after election</Title><Msg>October 6, 2012 Major defense companies said this week they will not send out layoff notices to warn of big job cuts in January, taking away the prospect of embarrassing layoff notices right before the November elections. That's led to charges that the White House overstepped when it told the industry the notices are not needed. EADS, the aerospace giant that includes Airbus, says it remains very worried about automatic cuts that could wipe out around 10 percent of the defense budget on Jan. 2, 2013. But spokesman Guy Hicks says the company now believes it will have some time to trim its workforce. "We assume because it's the law that it will occur," Hicks says. "But the implementation of it is not necessarily going to take place on the second of January. It's likely to unfold over a longer period of time, which gives us the latitude to wait." Lockheed Martin has come to the same conclusion. Layoffs Look Bad In Politics The decisions followed reassurances from the Obama administration that these cuts are not unavoidable. After all, Congress can decide at any time to come to a budget agreement, and toss out those automatic cuts known as sequestration. In addition, some defense jobs rely on ongoing contracts that won't be affected — not right away, at least. For those reasons, the White House said, the defense industry doesn't have to send out notices under a law called the WARN Act, which is supposed to help workers prepare for layoffs. "Even if it begins on Jan. 2 ... there will be no plants closed, there will be no massive layoffs on Jan. 4th or Jan. 5th or Jan. 6th," says Dan Gordon, who used to work in the Obama White House and now teaches at George Washington University. But Republicans say the White House is just trying to head off embarrassing layoff announcements right before the election. Republican Sen. Lindsey Graham of South Carolina told Fox News the White House is dodging the law. "It is a mini-coup," Graham said. "You're having the executive branch unilaterally telling the private sector to ignore a congressional statute." The White House went a step further, promising to cover any legal costs the industry might face because workers can sue if they're fired without proper notice. Republican Sen. John McCain said he will block the use of government funds for that purpose. Of course, that only comes into play after the election. In the meantime, workers are caught in the middle. Jobs Are Still On The Chopping Block "Nobody has talked to workers or their unions about the impact of this," says Thomas Buffenbarger, president of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers. Buffenbarger says the White House took care of management's concerns, but ignored workers, who still might lose their jobs next year. He says the White House is trying to manipulate his members. "With a pink slip in one hand and their ballot in the other, how do you think they're gonna vote?" Buffenbarger says. "Well, I would suspect they would vote against whoever the incumbent is, Republican or Democrat." The truth is that defense workers know full well that next year may be a rough one. Many have attended rallies urging Congress to stop the automatic cuts from happening. The question is who will get the blame for the whole budget mess. As GWU's Gordon says, this battle is not about some obscure law that requires layoff notices. "The WARN Act is, in my humble opinion, a red herring," he says. "The real issue is reaching budget agreements so that we don't have sequestration." Both parties still appear very far from any agreement to avoid those automatic budget cuts, so the issue will return during what promises to be a raucous lame duck session. That return, however, won't come until after the election.</Msg><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1349619825665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:23:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349622315367-4</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE is down after hours due to that news of recall</Title><Username>amit1234510</Username><Timestamp>1349493326212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 23:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Googlers- go to the VRNG board if you want to see what might unfold for Google in the next few days. VRNG is a tiny little ringtone company that owns the key patents that suddenly has caused a judge to basically pressure the two in to settling before the Oct. 16 trial date. Google, Amazon, Gannett and Target all have infringed owned by VRNG. VRNG has a market cap under $500 million. Just think what will happen if Google settles and then has to pay royalties forever. It won't kill Google but VRNG will then have precedent to force all the other big companies to settle. Buy VRNG monday and get ready for it to take off.</Msg><Username>baxterjames120</Username><Timestamp>1349622315367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349624065913-5</Id><Title>I went to 5Verizon stores and 5 AT+T stores on Saturday. iPHONES</Title><Msg>sales is very strong , they said supply keep coming and we keep selling all every week.buyers are crazy to buy iphone 5, few gliches are there but who cares, it is beautiful phone, handy, If you have iphone -people will look at you, if you have galaxy -they will ignore you. iphone makes your image..</Msg><Username>amit1234510</Username><Timestamp>1349624065913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:34:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349624188394-6</Id><Title>Too many negatives investors are writing</Title><Msg>watch mini iPAD comes -this version has very strong features.and these made for schools and retail stores.you can buy all items in store by going on ipad you do not need to go cash register at all.</Msg><Username>amit1234510</Username><Timestamp>1349624188394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349624755583-7</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG SETTLEMENT WITH VRNG! GOOG LOOSING LAW SUIT!</Title><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349464444926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VRNG has a strong case and excellent patent lawyers on staff - Should be a $1 + billion settlement.</Msg><Username>dvb6000</Username><Timestamp>1349624755583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:45:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639213961-8</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG vs GOOG: VRNG getting ready for Oct 16, 2012 TRIAL!!!!!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349450415547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:20:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is from the latest SEC Form 4 filing for Lang, which was October 5, 2012: It says Lang is "(President &amp; CTO, Director and 10% owner)" FORM 4 UNITED STATES SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE COMMISSION Lang Andrew Kennedy (President &amp; CTO Director 10% owner) Shares Ownership: 3,003,042 (Indirect) By Innovation Spring LLC ( 2 )Mr. Lang is the manager of Innovation Spring LLC ("Innovation Spring") and has the sole power to dispose or direct the disposition of the securities held by Innovation Spring. Innovation Spring Trust is the sole member and 100% owner of Innovation Spring and has the sole power to vote or direct the vote over the securities held by Innovation Spring. Mr. Lang does not have power to vote or direct the vote over the securities held by Innovation Spring. ============== Now lets do the math and see if we can match Langs 10% ownership to current Vringo's latest numbers, including 10,, which is pending to be verified on October 9, 2012: 1) the latest SEC Form 4 filing, for Lang who's owner of 3,003,042 VRNG shares, which was October 5, 2012, and indicates Lang is "(President &amp; CTO, Director and 10% owner)" 2) The Vringo Preferred Stock shall be convertible into an aggregate of 21,026,637 shares of Vringo Common Stock, which was announced May 14, 2012 The Vringo Preferred Stock shall be convertible into an aggregate of 21,026,637 shares of Vringo Common Stock (subject to a provision that restricts conversion in the event the holder will acquire more than 9.99% of Vringo Common Stock after such conversion but shall be non-voting, except as required by law and in certain defined instances, including a change of control. In addition, except for certain excluded issuances, the Vringo Preferred Stock will be adjusted for issuances below the initial conversion price (as adjusted for stock splits, stock dividends and similar events) until the date Vringo Common Stock has traded an aggregate of 100,000,000 shares at above $3.00 per share (as adjusted for stock splits, stock dividends and similar events). 3) Vringo Announced sale of 9.6 million shares of its common stock or Registered Direct Offering of Common Stock, announced on August 9, 2012 Vringo, Inc. entered into subscription agreements for the sale of 9.6 million shares of its common stock in a registered direct offering at a price of $3.25 per share, 4) Vringo Announced the sale of 10,344,998 shares of its common stock in a registered direct offering or Registered Direct Offering of Common Stock, announced on Oct 5, 2012 ringo, Inc. (NYSE MKT: VRNG) today announced that it has entered into subscription agreements for the sale of 10,344,998 shares of its common stock in a registered direct offering at a price of $4.35 per share, The sale and issuance of the shares is expected to close on or about October 9, 2012, pending NYSE MKT approval. 5) Assuming there might be some new options/bonuses given to Vringo's BOD/employees, Now adding the numbers: 21,026,637 09,600,000 ---------- 30,626,637 By October 3, 2012, Vringo common stock might've been 30,626,637. Adding the bonuses given between May and October 3, 2012 will end up with a little bigger number. ---------------------- Vringo common stock Should be on or after October 9, 2012.Adding the bonuses given between May and October 3, 2012 will end up with a little bigger number. 30,626,637 10,344,998 ----------- 40,971,635</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349639213961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639335850-9</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG SETTLEMENT WITH VRNG! GOOG LOOSING LAW SUIT!</Title><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349464444926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a joke! If GOOG had to pay 1 billion to VRNG. It's a "drop in the bucket" for GOOG and will NOT have any significant effect on GOOG's revenues!</Msg><Username>ricky_manz</Username><Timestamp>1349639335850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639390594-10</Id><Topic><Title>_ GOOGLE SPLIT TO BE ANNOUNCED ON EARNINGS RELEASE DATE _</Title><Username>yexemew</Username><Timestamp>1349487215831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 21:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking forward to the split soon!</Msg><Username>ricky_manz</Username><Timestamp>1349639390594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639449705-11</Id><Topic><Title>* _ Google Overtakes Microsoft to Make Investors Cheer, 10/6/12 PM Article _ *</Title><Username>stk_analyzt</Username><Timestamp>1349578522794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:55:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG IS NO. 1 in big cap stock performance!</Msg><Username>ricky_manz</Username><Timestamp>1349639449705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349639542984-12</Id><Topic><Title>* ~ PREDICTION: GOOG STOCK WILL REACH $1,000 BY DEC. 31 ~ *</Title><Username>stk_analyzt</Username><Timestamp>1349558610182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I concur! Well said! I agree on all your reasons why GOOG will hit $1000/share by year's end!</Msg><Username>ricky_manz</Username><Timestamp>1349639542984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349642738192-13</Id><Title>Tina Brid Brain Fey back for all the dem retards!</Title><Msg>Notice just as the Palin family releases a book delineating the truly decent patriotic person Governor Palin is and Romney gives Obamadungdufus and rump thumping in the debate Lame Stream MSM co[-arm of the dem party comes out with some new TINA BIRDBRAIN FEY SNL entertainment for all the dem DUNCES that seated the community orgaznizer. The nerve to call anyone DUMB with this RETARD community organizer at the helm. The lot of you DEM DUMBOS could not see Russia from Moscow. Now gear up as Uncle Joey Biden comes on Thursday night with more empty suit class warfare nonsense. Ryan has going for him exactly what Romney has going for him THE TRUTH about Obama/Biden MISERABLY FAILED RECORD!!! What this is truly about is 100 years of primary democrat party failed control for which their chickens indeed have come home to roost and they spent all our money (SS/Medicare, income taxes etc..) on welfare to lock in democrat votes moving forward. 1913 dem Wilson Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE that has debt leveraged our currency to zero intrinsic value, 1933 dem FDR failed SS Ponzi that was only to cost $.03 per pay, 1964 dem LBJ failed Medicare Ponzi now completely broke necessitating socialized medicine with the death panels to preclude costly care for the boomers now retiring in mass and being told all the money taken from them was squandered on welfare, and now Obama under dem Pelosi Congress more debt increase than all prior Presidents combined in less than 3.6 years.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1349642738192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349644388920-14</Id><Title>Slippery SLopes for Google in VRNG trial. Too many forces working against them.</Title><Msg>Losses could be Greater than 5billion if it reaches the trial</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1349644388920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349645125958-15</Id><Topic><Title>Slippery SLopes for Google in VRNG trial. Too many forces working against them.</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1349644388920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a bunch of typical shorter rhetoric Bee Sss... Read the articles...a maximum of 1 billion dollars is mentioned... OR GOOG WILL BUY OUT VRNG!!!</Msg><Username>ricky_manz</Username><Timestamp>1349645125958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349645285066-16</Id><Topic><Title>* ~ PREDICTION: GOOG STOCK WILL REACH $1,000 BY DEC. 31 ~ *</Title><Username>stk_analyzt</Username><Timestamp>1349558610182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loser shorters have been squezzzzzzzzzzzzed all the way up from $570 to $770... AND THEY ARE STILL BEING SQUEZZZZZZZZZZZZZZED!!!</Msg><Username>xumpoz</Username><Timestamp>1349645285066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349645457939-17</Id><Topic><Title>Slippery SLopes for Google in VRNG trial. Too many forces working against them.</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1349644388920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>James Altucher continues to be correct. Min 1.8 to 5 billion plus royalties</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1349645457939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349645751671-18</Id><Title>~ LOSER WISHFUL-THINKING GOOG SHORTERS CONTINUE TO BE SQUEEZZZZZZZZZZZZED SINCE 3 MONTHS AGO!!!</Title><Msg>GOOG IS the BEST performing stock... Do your own chart comparisons!... GOOG buyers "continue" to BUY GOOG and drive GOOG's price UP, UP, and UP!!! Shorters have been "unsuccessfully" attempted to "create" negative sentiment on GOOG since GOOG was $570... Now GOOG is ~$770... And will GOOG will be $1000 SOON!!!... Shorts ARE "wasting" their time shorting the "wrong" stock!!!... Go back to shorting FB!!! The shorts that are posting on this board ALL flunked the "Clever Shorter Message Board Posting 101"!!! LOL</Msg><Username>xumpoz</Username><Timestamp>1349645751671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648686940-19</Id><Title>"Blue Horseshoe Likes Bonanza Goldfields"</Title><Msg>Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is a junior gold mining start-up company with tremendous potential. The new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Financing secured. Gold production will begin at the company's Tarantula site soon. Read the recent Yahoo news. 300-500% upside over the next 90 days is possible. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1349648686940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:24:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349649643429-20</Id><Topic><Title>"Blue Horseshoe Likes Bonanza Goldfields"</Title><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1349648686940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:24:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ATTD is MUCH better than BONZ</Msg><Username>xumpoz</Username><Timestamp>1349649643429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657825977-21</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG SETTLEMENT WITH VRNG! GOOG LOOSING LAW SUIT!</Title><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349464444926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still probes GOOGLE stole art property and has been making money based in just smart business men that robbed a great mind like KEN LANG capice in bocca al lupo</Msg><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349657825977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657934616-22</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE is down after hours due to that news of recall</Title><Username>amit1234510</Username><Timestamp>1349493326212</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 23:15:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bull stuff goog is gonna start tanking vrng will get large settlement and ongoing royalities and goog will feel the pain and go through correction downward trend VRNG ALL THE WAY BABY patent infringer thieves</Msg><Username>pkraus12</Username><Timestamp>1349657934616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658068395-23</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is a Mormon vs. Obama is a Christian, you choose!!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349494714457</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 23:38:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eat s h i t and d i e hopefully u to will feel the pain and lose all your money by by little piggie OINK OINK</Msg><Username>pkraus12</Username><Timestamp>1349658068395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658153309-24</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG vs GOOG: VRNG getting ready for Oct 16, 2012 TRIAL!!!!!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349450415547</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:20:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VRNG ALL THE WAY TO THE BANK by by little piggies OINK OINK</Msg><Username>pkraus12</Username><Timestamp>1349658153309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:02:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658236689-25</Id><Title>GOOG IS NOTHING BUT PATENT INFRINGING CREEPS BY BY LITTLE PIGGIE OINK OINK</Title><Msg>SUFFER FEEL THE PAIN AND HAVE NOTHING</Msg><Username>pkraus12</Username><Timestamp>1349658236689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659304534-26</Id><Topic><Title>~ LOSER WISHFUL-THINKING GOOG SHORTERS CONTINUE TO BE SQUEEZZZZZZZZZZZZED SINCE 3 MONTHS AGO!!!</Title><Username>xumpoz</Username><Timestamp>1349645751671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree! This board has the worst shorter message posters I've seen on any board!!!</Msg><Username>xumpoz</Username><Timestamp>1349659304534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659450109-27</Id><Topic><Title>* ~ PREDICTION: GOOG STOCK WILL REACH $1,000 BY DEC. 31 ~ *</Title><Username>stk_analyzt</Username><Timestamp>1349558610182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 17:23:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I could not have said it better myself! No doubt GOOG will see $1000 by end of 2012!!!</Msg><Username>nokia_is_back</Username><Timestamp>1349659450109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659572156-28</Id><Title>- This GOOG board has the MOST STUPID shorter posts I've ever seen on any board! -</Title><Msg>eom</Msg><Username>nokia_is_back</Username><Timestamp>1349659572156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660669301-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG SETTLEMENT WITH VRNG! GOOG LOOSING LAW SUIT!</Title><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349464444926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of course it will be a drop in the bucket. The important fact is VRNG stock is going to triple in less than a week. GOOG might go up 1% ooooooooooo sign me up nah wait id rather take a nap than buy GOOG.</Msg><Username>burritowithstuffonit</Username><Timestamp>1349660669301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660985363-30</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG SETTLEMENT WITH VRNG! GOOG LOOSING LAW SUIT!</Title><Username>explorer_gypsy</Username><Timestamp>1349464444926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:14:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wishful thinking on your part--like if you already no that VRNG has won the verdict. This lawsuit trial has not even gone to trial yet--GOOG is no push over.</Msg><Username>nokia_is_back</Username><Timestamp>1349660985363</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349661589143-31</Id><Title>* _ GOOG MADE $43 BILLION LAST 4 QUARTERS. ANY LAWSUIT LOSS PAYOUTS WOULD BE AN INSIGNIFICANT "DROP IN BUCKET" _</Title><Msg>People are saying that Google has lost to Vringo. I SAY Bee Sss to that! Even if they lose, (1) they can appeal a verdict against them which will take up to 2 years and delay what they would have to pay for up to 2 years and (2) if Google has to pay out millions, that is an "insignificant" DROP IN THE BUCKET for GOOG!</Msg><Username>nokia_is_back</Username><Timestamp>1349661589143</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:59:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349661998506-32</Id><Title>Sell Google, buy Vringo, Inc. (VRNG)</Title><Msg>Google Inc. (GOOG) loses patent case to Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) I am so excited for this work week! There is one company you may have not heard of until now, that company is.... Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) -NYSE Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) is suing Google Inc. (GOOG) for search engine patent infringement!! Google's source of revenue! Courts have already ruled in favor of Vringo, Inc. Google has been forced into settlement talks with Vringo, Inc. (VRNG), damages are in the 100's of millions to billions to be awarded to Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) News was leaked out in aftermarket hours in favor of (VRNG) stock rose 5% in late trading with heavy buying on the stock. Institutions all want to buy Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) stock now and they are investing big money! They invested about 50 million dollars into (VRNG) at $4.35 a share! $4.35 is close to (VRNG) 52 week high! Bullish trend, bullish stock and company! Tomorrow is the day to buy Vringo, Inc. (VRNG) short term price target $20.00</Msg><Username>conceptdetailingcenter</Username><Timestamp>1349661998506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349663234299-33</Id><Title>SELL Vringo. BUY GOOG.</Title><Msg>GOOG WILL no doubt defeat Vringo in court. I'm LONG on GOOG!</Msg><Username>nokia_is_back</Username><Timestamp>1349663234299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349663695293-34</Id><Title>_ GOOG BUYERS HAVE BEEN IGNORING GOOG SHORTER POSTS... GOOG HAS GAINED 35% in 3 MONTHS!!! _</Title><Msg>enough said.</Msg><Username>norry_72</Username><Timestamp>1349663695293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349666848545-35</Id><Title>GOOG about to get WHACKED.</Title><Msg>Check the Asian news. Ouch.</Msg><Username>sfrieberg_88</Username><Timestamp>1349666848545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349667107165-36</Id><Title>I'm long GOOG, but expect a sell-off near term....</Title><Msg>We've seen this story before especially with AAPL. Rally hard just before earnings than a percentage pullback just before the report. My expectations was a touch of $800 than pullback to $700-$725 but for now I think it comes this week.</Msg><Username>oldhanginlownutsgranddaddy</Username><Timestamp>1349667107165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:31:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>