<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349236892496-1</Id><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!</Title><Msg>In five key areas, Barack Obama has shown himself to be an extraordinary leader: 1. Sending Thirty Thousand Additional Troops to Afghanistan Despite strong opposition from his own party, Vice President Biden and his chief of staff, President Obama ordered thirty thousand more troops to be sent to Afghanistan in December 2009, raising the total number of troops there to more than one hundred thousand, an increase of more than sixty thousand since he took office earlier that year. He accelerated the timetable of the deployment, sending the troops there more quickly than initially anticipated. But the president also set a clear timetable for the beginning of troop withdrawals, a commitment he kept by starting to bring them home from Afghanistan in July 2011. In May 2012, he signed a strategic partnership agreement with Afghan president Hamid Karzai, ensuring that all combat troops would be withdrawn by 2014 and establishing a solid foundation to guide our commitment to Afghanistan for the next decade. 2. Saving GM and Chrysler Though most Americans and nearly all Republicans were against the auto bailout, President Obama recognized that letting Detroit go bankrupt, as Mitt Romney had suggested, would destroy the American automotive industry and wreak tremendous havoc on the entire U.S. economy. Over a million jobs would have been lost, and the federal government would have been stuck with paying a $14.5 billion tab for the two companies' pension plans. Today GM is back as the world's number one auto manufacturer and more profitable than ever, and the auto industry has created 230,000 jobs in three years (the most in a decade). All loans have been repaid to the government. 3. Pushing Health Care Reform During the 2008 campaign, Barack Obama repeatedly pledged to sign a universal health care bill into law by the end of his first term as president. In the face of staunch opposition from Republicans, President Obama realized that if he wanted to deliver on his promise, he would have to push through health care reform immediately, while he had Democratic majorities in both houses of Congress, or risk losing the opportunity, as had so many presidents before him. Fighting against near unanimous opposition from Republicans, unprecedented lobbying by the insurance industry, and pushback from the more liberal wing of his own party, Obama signed the Affordable Care Act just a little over a year after taking office. In summer 2012, the Supreme Court upheld the law. 4. Osama bin Laden Raid Many of his top advisors, including Vice President Biden, Defense Secretary Robert Gates, and Vice Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff James Cartwright, were against the attack. Bush's secretary of defense, Donald Rumsfeld, had called off a similar raid six years earlier. Success was far from guaranteed, and the costs of failure would have been enormous. But President Obama was convinced that the raid was the only option to ensure that the United States could finally remove the threat posed by Osama bin Laden, and he alone made the call to send in SEAL Team Six. 5. The Stimulus Plan Facing the greatest economic crisis in eighty years, Barack Obama signed the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act less than a month after being sworn into office. The package of tax cuts, aid to the states and investment in infrastructure cut taxes for 95 percent of working Americans saved as many as 3.5 million jobs (according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office), and is credited with preventing another Great Depression. The bill passed the House without a single Republican vote. Since then, the U.S. economy has experienced eleven consecutive quarters of expansion and registered twenty-eight straight months of private-sector job growth, adding 4.4 million new jobs. Character. Strength. Determination. Perseverance... These are the qualities of a true leader.</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349236892496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349249833280-2</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mobile ads are "the only advertising medium available continuously all day," says Millennial Media CEO Paul Palmieri, making a bull case for a platform whose effectiveness has been questioned due to concerns about tiny displays and the ability to turn clicks into purchases. Palmieri notes mobile still only accounts for 1% of ad spend, in spite of accounting for 10% of media consumption - it might not be necessary for that gap to be eliminated for the market to grow rapidly</Msg><Username>tomsaga25</Username><Timestamp>1349249833280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 03:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349254744417-3</Id><Title>GOOG Stock, this is some great stuff, your thoughts</Title><Msg>For compelling information and for developing a proper base for understanding of GOOG, visit, vippennystocksite dotcom</Msg><Username>marshall5842</Username><Timestamp>1349254744417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 04:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349264463572-4</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks KingCuffs, I went long thinking 770 was in the cards because of your posts</Title><Username>missmarket30</Username><Timestamp>1349204133030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:55:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goog vs Vrng going to trial oct 16. I got out! I say this goes lower</Msg><Username>assclownposse</Username><Timestamp>1349264463572</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349265288505-5</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Robbing a country's wealth from any direction: October 3, 2012 Tehran bazaar closed as currency fall The rial hit 34,500 against the U.S. dollar Tuesday on the unofficial street trading rate. Two years ago, it was close to 10,000 rials for the dollar. Tehran bazaar closed as currency falls Associated Press – 1 hr 38 mins ag TEHRAN, Iran (AP) — Tehran's main bazaar has been closed as authorities tighten controls trying to halt the fall of Iran's currency after it hit a record low. The semiofficial Mehr news agency says the bazaar — the traditional commercial hub in Iran's capital — was closed for security reasons on Wednesday. Iranian officials have faced increasing public anger over the plummeting rial and rising prices, blamed partly on Western sanctions over Tehran's nuclear program. The Mehr report quoted Ahmad Karimi Isfahani, a bazaar official, as denying reports that merchants staged a protest. Police are patrolling streets where freelance money dealers work. Exchange shops are closed. The rial hit 34,500 against the U.S. dollar Tuesday on the unofficial street trading rate. Two years ago, it was close to 10,000 rials for the dollar.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349265288505</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349265543273-6</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Iran Human Rights Memorial Human rights violations in this case One person's story Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar (Kamali) Date of execution June 9, 1980 Location Evin Prison, Tehran, Iran Mode of execution shooting Charges Collaborating with the political police SAVAK About this Case The execution of Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar was reported in the Jomhuri Eslami daily (June 10, 1980). Arrest and detention Based on the report, Mr. Kamangar was arrested by Revolutionary Guards towards the end of the year 1979 in Evin Prison, where he allegedly had gone to receive his salary. Trial The report mentioned that the defendant was tried at the First Branch of the Islamic Revolutionary Tribunal “a while ago.” The final verdict, however, was issued on the morning before the sentences were carried out. Charges Regarding Mr. Kamangar’s charges, the report reads as follows: “Seifollah Faraji Kamangir, the torturer and SAVAK interrogator also known as Dr. Kamali,</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349265543273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 07:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349267205186-7</Id><Title>Patent Infringement, APPLE &amp; GOOGLE royalties MUST READ !!</Title><Msg>Patent Infringement, APPLE &amp; GOOGLE royalties MUST READ !! Within the next thirty days, ATC will serve cease and desist notices upon Google Inc. for its Android-based Voice Recognition system within Jelly Bean, Apple Inc. because of its Siri system, Vlingo, Inc., and many other software and hardware providers that have adopted systems similar to the patent. Each of the above technologies appear to have copied the invention since they have the user speak into their device, the voice is transmitted to a central data processing facility, the sounds are converted to text and returned to the device. ATC believes that these procedures clearly infringe on the patent and that those who misuse its technology must either license it, pay royalties, or cease using the products. If royalties cannot be achieved through negotiations, ATC will initiate litigation and seek injunctions against those who infringe on the patent. ATC recognizes that its patent provides a technology that benefits the public, so it remains amenable to work with companies such as Google and Apple as long as it receives proper royalties on each of their units sold that use the patented technology. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/accredited-transcription-corp-acquires-100-040200901.html</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1349267205186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349267529669-8</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google has been on quite a tear for the past year, with its stock hitting new all-time highs almost every day - including its most recent on Monday at $765. This price saw the search engine giant reach a monumental milestone as a public company. It usurped Microsoft (MSFT) by taking its place as the second-largest stock on the Nasdaq 100 index. Its market cap of $249 billion now makes it second to Apple's $618 billion.</Msg><Username>lindontomson</Username><Timestamp>1349267529669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349268552961-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Best President Ever!!!</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1349236892496</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 00:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AKA-Obullshit</Msg><Username>stockbard</Username><Timestamp>1349268552961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 08:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349269562695-10</Id><Title>What GOOG Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Msg>Been Hearing Rumors On The Street That GOOG Is About To Take Off. Could Just Be A Bunch Of #$%$. (We All Know These Things Move On Nothing More Than Rumors Alone) Check Out This Report, Opinions Please! Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser ---------- goo.gl/XmyzC</Msg><Username>thurman.lewis39</Username><Timestamp>1349269562695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349269744916-11</Id><Title>Stock Market Soaring --Thank You President Obama</Title><Msg>What a job he's done!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1349269744916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349269860960-12</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $6.7 ..Up 50c….Breaking Out!!......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings/strong guidance......This is just the start of a prolonged rally to double digits…,.Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Very cheap based on steady growth and strong guidance of over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income in 2013</Title><Username>accountislate</Username><Timestamp>1348254181486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incredible chart. It looks like it's heading to $10+ before expected record 1Q earnings per guidance in about a month. The stock took a pause last week to create another solid base at $6.5 and to close gaps for a sustained rally past $10/share Exponential growth of new cloud divisions will cause valuations to multiply as revenues from these divisions continue to impact the top and bottom lines positively Analysts average target is $16/share</Msg><Username>jonny.deener</Username><Timestamp>1349269860960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349270697330-13</Id><Title>$FB Facebook Cantor Fitzgerald Reiterates Buy Rating, $26 on Facebook. Topeka Capital Reaffirms Buy Rating on Nasdaq Facebook $FB. Trefis Targets FB at $28+. Oppenheimer reiterated its rating of Outperform on Facebook Target price $FB $26!!! aone goog</Title><Msg>...</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349270697330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349271738839-14</Id><Title>BEARISH ENGULFING PATTERN CONFIRMED</Title><Msg>what happened to this message -- it is odd that I posted this and then it disappeared - yesterday, it occurred - we will see what happens.</Msg><Username>missmarket30</Username><Timestamp>1349271738839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:42:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349271795558-15</Id><Topic><Title>this makes news, ALL TIME HIGH, and down 10?</Title><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1349204882761</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 15:08:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bearish Engulfing Pattern from yesterday.</Msg><Username>missmarket30</Username><Timestamp>1349271795558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272418913-16</Id><Title>BUY BUY BUY 770 coming</Title><Msg>...........</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1349272418913</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:53:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272436976-17</Id><Title>I don't like this set up - I have a feeling it is going to go to 700 today</Title><Msg>It seems impossible - but this twirling around at this area is HFTs again screwing around - until someone drives it back down to 750 then 740 - 730 by this afternoon.</Msg><Username>missmarket30</Username><Timestamp>1349272436976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272437875-18</Id><Title>buyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy</Title><Msg>yyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy</Msg><Username>causinginflation</Username><Timestamp>1349272437875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272663871-19</Id><Title>Time for the Rug to be Pulled...... Be Careful....</Title><Msg>Guys, we've seen this before. Strong rally into earnings and just before earnings the stock has it rug pulled out for $50. I expect GOOG will be closer to $700 than $750 in the next few days.... Saw this too many times so I'll wait until day before earnings to set my bullish trade.</Msg><Username>mrcrapmaster</Username><Timestamp>1349272663871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272939556-20</Id><Title>BUY IT.</Title><Msg>..........</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1349272939556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349272994943-21</Id><Title>GODF DAMMIT!!!!!!!!! BUY</Title><Msg>.......</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1349272994943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273022912-22</Id><Title>here that sound? thats the sound of millions of android tablets not SELLING</Title><Msg>ipad mini</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1349273022912</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349273243950-23</Id><Title>#$%$, buy!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1349273243950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349273978004-24</Id><Topic><Title>What GOOG Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>thurman.lewis39</Username><Timestamp>1349269562695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice analysis</Msg><Username>alstonjanie74</Username><Timestamp>1349273978004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:19:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349274734730-25</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google's stock to continue rising for the time being, and eventually increase at a faster rate as Motorola launches its next generation of Android phones.</Msg><Username>jamesgordon99</Username><Timestamp>1349274734730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349275416112-26</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for GOOG: Mobile ads are "the only advertising medium available continuously all day," says Millennial Media (MM) CEO Paul Palmieri, making a bull case for a platform whose effectiveness has been questioned due to concerns about tiny displays and the ability to turn clicks into purchases. Palmieri notes mobile still only accounts for 1% of ad spend, in spite of accounting for 10% of media consumption - it might not be necessary for that gap to be eliminated for the market to grow rapidly.</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1349275416112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276164507-27</Id><Title>760+ before the close</Title><Msg>.........</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1349276164507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349276330701-28</Id><Title>FACEBOOK SHARES UP AGAIN $FB also check out $AONE $AXPW $AUMY $GOOG</Title><Msg>FACEBOOK SHARES UP AGAIN $FB also check out $AONE $AXPW $AUMY $GOOG</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349276330701</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 10:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349277563197-29</Id><Title>762 coming,</Title><Msg>then I'd sell</Msg><Username>riskreversal777</Username><Timestamp>1349277563197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349278796749-30</Id><Title>missmarket30</Title><Msg>Calm down .Google (goog) is doing just fine.You panic too easy.Cuffs</Msg><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1349278796749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279544681-31</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Joll is the problem...how many times will investors fall for this scammer?</Msg><Username>jarred.randolph</Username><Timestamp>1349279544681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349279676789-32</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joll is only interested in himself and taking a fat salary company furnished housing and business trips with his wife. What kind of company doing business with the DoD hires a CEO who has 3 citizenships and a judgement against him in Federal court?</Msg><Username>jarred.randolph</Username><Timestamp>1349279676789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:54:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279836282-33</Id><Title>Split this #$%$!</Title><Msg>I see a 4:1 split coming...Finally.</Msg><Username>captjamestkirkussenterprise</Username><Timestamp>1349279836282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:57:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349279863904-34</Id><Title>GOOG and VRNG Instructions to Settle by Judge</Title><Msg>ORDER DENYING Defendants' 237 MOTION for Summary Judgment Defendants AOL Inc., Google Inc., IAC Search &amp; Media, Inc., Gannett Company, Inc., and Target Corporation's Motion for Summary Judgment filed by Google Inc., AOL Inc., IAC Search &amp; Media, Inc., Target Corporation, Gannett Company, Inc. It is further ORDERED that parties engage in settlement discussions before United States Magistrate Judge Lawrence R. Leonard @ 10:30 a.m. on Tuesday, 10/9/12. Entered and filed 10/3/12. (Signed by District Judge Raymond A. Jackson on 10/3/12). (ecav, ) (Entered: 10/03/2012)</Msg><Username>noseptic</Username><Timestamp>1349279863904</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 11:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349280126343-35</Id><Title>VRNG Goog!! Settlement baby!!</Title><Msg>:) Long VRNG!!</Msg><Username>investorsuccess</Username><Timestamp>1349280126343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:02:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280165916-36</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bivio has been trying to sell this dog of a product for over a year so they can focus on what is making money. That should have been an indication to the ISC8 crew that it was a stinky deal but it seems like that is what theyaa re shooting for.</Msg><Username>jarred.randolph</Username><Timestamp>1349280165916</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349280183075-37</Id><Title>oblivious money managers herded into GOOG at all time highs while vrng</Title><Msg>is about to steal their whole business model back</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1349280183075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349280245754-38</Id><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Msg>Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle By edward.mulwa . 5 minutes ago . Permalink Full docket text for document 572: ORDER DENYING Defendants' [237] MOTION for Summary Judgment Defendants AOL Inc., Google Inc., IAC Search &amp; Media, Inc., Gannett Company, Inc., and Target Corporation's Motion for Summary Judgment filed by Google Inc., AOL Inc., IAC Search &amp; Media, Inc., Target Corporation, Gannett Company, Inc. It is further ORDERED that parties engage in settlement discussions before United States Magistrate Judge Lawrence R. Leonard @ 10:30 a.m. on Tuesday, 10/9/12. Entered and filed 10/3/12. (Signed by District Judge Raymond A. Jackson on 10/3/12). (ecav, )</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349280562850-39</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They were trying to SCARE VRNG shareholders to "kill" but the MAIN difference was/is that Vringo counsels are in the case to HUNT Google and get as much as they can for the shareholders: VRNG Short Interest as of Sep 14, 2012: 7,432,484 By casp321 . 6 minutes ago . Permalink VRNG Short Interest INCREASE, more than a million shares in volume from 6,423,289 on 8-31-2012 to 7,432,484 on Sep-14-2012 they say it's 56% plus of the vrng float??</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280562850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281300561-40</Id><Title>Warrants of VRNG only $1.62 WOW</Title><Msg>Great opportunity...shhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh</Msg><Username>robertsimbelt</Username><Timestamp>1349281300561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281401626-41</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2007, when ON2 announced acquiring Hantro, at one point, ONT PPS went up whil e Short were busy to bring it down. As, at the other corner, ON2's CEO called Bill Joll was busy withFALSIFYING the financial reports some times that year. For about 90 minutes 7.2 million ONT shares, 80K per minutes, changed hands. That day more than 25 million ONT/ON2 shares changed hands, a stock ticker that was trading under 500K for years. This the next one I see might have hight volume but a reliable cOUNSELs at the helm directing the shareholders to VICTORY.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349281401626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349281714166-42</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VRNG volume as growing: Volume: 7,778,147</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349281714166</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349281942259-43</Id><Title>VRNG now up 27% Exploding on decision!</Title><Msg>..and when the VRNG shorts find out..ooooooooooooooo baby</Msg><Username>robertsimbelt</Username><Timestamp>1349281942259</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282051305-44</Id><Title>767 any minutes</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>wingofeaglets</Username><Timestamp>1349282051305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:34:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282216607-45</Id><Title>Do not sell below $762.80!!</Title><Msg>Going higher still. Cuffs</Msg><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1349282216607</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349282305373-46</Id><Title>Will GOOG settle.....how much...read this</Title><Msg>Full docket text for document 573: Settlement Conference Order: This case has been referred to the undersigned for a settlement conference. In order to facilitate the just and expeditious resolution of this case, it is ORDERED as follows: All parties and their lead counsel are required to appear at a settlement conference scheduled in the United States District Court, 600 Granby Street, Norfolk, Virginia 23510, at10:30 a.m. on Tuesday, October 9, 2012, for the purpose of conducting discussions, in good faith, towards a compromised resolution of this case. Counsel must notify parties attending the settlement conference that electronic equipment (cell phones, pagers, laptops, etc.) is not permitted in the courthouse without the express permission of the Court. (See Order for further specifics) Additionally, The parties must: Submit a brief memorandum of five pages or less directly to the chambers of the undersigned (do not file in the clerk's office) by noon on Friday, October 5, 2012. Do not serve a copy of the letter on the opposing party unless you wish to disclose your settlement position. The memorandum can be faxed to (757) 222-7257. Identify the lawyers and party representatives who will attend the conference. (See Order for further specifics) Entered and filed 10/3/12. (Signed by Magistrate Judge Lawrence R. Leonard on 10/3/12). From the VRNG board..WOW</Msg><Username>imready2moveon</Username><Timestamp>1349282305373</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349282458954-47</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Target range $4.25 to $30 from ... By hebert_art . Sep 1, 2012 2:56 PM . Permalink sec filing. Directors accept stout and sinclair can sell in a manner with minimal market i... sec filing. Directors accept stout and sinclair can sell in a manner with minimal market impact, sounds like they think it can go to $30 a share. On August 31, 2012, Vringo, Inc. (the "Company") released members of the Board of Directors of the Company (the "Board"), with the exception of Donald E. Stout and H. Van Sinclair, from certain restrictions on sales and other dispositions and public announcement or disclosure which were included in that certain Lock-Up Agreement, dated July 19, 2012 (the "Lock-Up Agreement"), entered into between the Company and each of the directors and executive officers, as previously disclosed on the Company's Current Report on Form 8-K filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission on July 20, 2012 (the "Current Report") in connection with the establishment of pre-arranged trading plans that comply with Rule 10b5-1 under the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended (the "Exchange Act"). The Lock-Up Agreement was filed as Exhibit 10.6 to the Current Report. All other provisions of the Lock-Up Agreement have remained unchanged. On August 31, 2012, members of the Board, excluding Donald E. Stout and H. Van Sinclair, began establishing stock trading plans with respect to shares of common stock owned by them or underlying warrants, restricted stock units or stock options owned by them in accordance with Rule 10b5-1 under the Exchange Act. All of such transactions will be made subject to the volume limitations under Rule 144. The transactions under these trading plans will be disclosed publicly through Form 144 and Form 4 filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission. The trading plans are designed to align the interests of directors and officers with the Company's investors by allowing them to monetize a portion of their equity positions when the market prices of the Company's common stock are between $4.25 and $30.00 per share, in a systematic, nondiscretionary manner with the goal of minimal market impact, and compliance with federal securities laws and regulations adopted by the Securities and Exchange Commission.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349282458954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349282685331-48</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While Bill Joll in 2007, 2008 and ON2 Interim were busy with helping Short, anyway you want to look at it, ON2 PPS was kept under $0.40 while SI went up 18+ million at one point. Vringo management and BOD on the other hand: The trading plans are designed to align the interests of directors and officers with the Company's investors by allowing them to monetize a portion of their equity positions when the market prices of the Company's common stock are between $4.25 and $30.00 per share, in a systematic, nondiscretionary manner with the goal of minimal market impact, and compliance with federal securities laws and regulations adopted by the Securities and Exchange Commission.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349282685331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349282801495-49</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a shame: Re: Why Google "Retiring" Nexus with Flash 10.1 and Android 2.2? By casp321 . Jan 31, 2011 11:23 PM . Permalink . Go to topic Why Google IS STEALING from small companies SHAREHOLDERS like ON2 and WHO is Google's... Why Google IS STEALING from small companies SHAREHOLDERS like ON2 and WHO is Google's ORIGINATORs??? Proxy as of Nov 3, 2009: Page 90: -----On2 further agreed that, except (a) as expressly contemplated by the merger agreement, (b) as specifically set forth in On2’s disclosure schedule that was delivered to Google at the time of signing the merger agreement, (c) as required by applicable law or (d) with Google’s prior written consent, On2 will not, and will not permit any of its subsidiaries to, among other things, undertake the following actions: • make any capital expenditure or enter into any capital commitment or capital transaction exceeding $250,000 individually or $500,000 in the aggregate;</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349282801495</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283039006-50</Id><Topic><Title>April 02, 2008: Hantro TRADEmark &amp; Google: #77437662</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1301961211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-04-04 19:53:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was there any ON2 technical or other STAFF consulted on HOW the HANTRO logo should look like before Google accepting the design? If so, WHO was it?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349283039006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283143150-51</Id><Topic><Title>Sold all my calls - VRNG settlement later during the week/early next week.</Title><Username>bob_willis66</Username><Timestamp>1349110220932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does not matter who/where it is coming from. GOOG will be forced to settle with VRNG by early next week. I expect AT LEAST $1.5 billion dollars, based on what is happening. By this time next week, the whole world will know the real deal</Msg><Username>bob_willis66</Username><Timestamp>1349283143150</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349283425293-52</Id><Title>EOD close $725 or lower</Title><Msg>Stampede at the exit, may recover after earnings !!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bil_murphy</Username><Timestamp>1349283425293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349283980732-53</Id><Topic><Title>Sold all my calls - VRNG settlement later during the week/early next week.</Title><Username>bob_willis66</Username><Timestamp>1349110220932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still about three hours left to market close Vringo is UP more than 34% and its Volume: Volume: 12,316,867</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349283980732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:06:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349284800545-54</Id><Title>pre-earnings - $725</Title><Msg>Post earnings - $625</Msg><Username>bil_murphy</Username><Timestamp>1349284800545</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349284866903-55</Id><Title>Over priced - goes below $600 post earnings</Title><Msg>$580 is the right price to catch before the year end. IMO</Msg><Username>bil_murphy</Username><Timestamp>1349284866903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285343970-56</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Court order: By ran.dog80 . 31 seconds ago . Permalink Full docket text for document 573: Settlement Conference Order: This case has been referred to the undersigned for a settlement conference. In order to facilitate the just and expeditious resolution of this case, it is ORDERED as follows: All parties and their lead counsel are required to appear at a settlement conference scheduled in the United States District Court, 600 Granby Street, Norfolk, Virginia 23510, at10:30 a.m. on Tuesday, October 9, 2012, for the purpose of conducting discussions, in good faith, towards a compromised resolution of this case. Counsel must notify parties attending the settlement conference that electronic equipment (cell phones, pagers, laptops, etc.) is not permitted in the courthouse without the express permission of the Court. (See Order for further specifics) Additionally, The parties must: Submit a brief memorandum of five pages or less directly to the chambers of the undersigned (do not file in the clerk's office) by noon on Friday, October 5, 2012. Do not serve a copy of the letter on the opposing party unless you wish to disclose your settlement position. The memorandum can be faxed to (757) 222-7257. Identify the lawyers and party representatives who will attend the conference. (See Order for further specifics) Entered and filed 10/3/12. (Signed by Magistrate Judge Lawrence R. Leonard on 10/3/12). From the VRNG board..WOW</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349285343970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349285534246-57</Id><Title>Mitt armed with Quiver full of Zingers!!</Title><Msg>Watch this #$%$-bag shoot himself on to his foot tonight.</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349285534246</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349285662570-58</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>James Altucher article Buy out coming? By asia2468 . 35 minutes ago . Permalink kind of think Google's only option is to buy Vringo. A couple of thoughts: A) if they go to trial they risk all of their customers getting sued. Nobody wants that. B) if they go to trial they risk MSFT or AAPL or YHOO buying VRNG when things look good and now GOOG would be up against a much more terrifying competitor. C) if they go to trial, Quinn Emmanuel risks losing too big high profile cases in a row. That seems insane to me. D) There are other things: The NOK patent portfollio is very valuable. Possibly worth billions (I'm looking into this in detail right now). If GOOG buys VRNG they can begin collecting immediate cash flows plus eventual litigation flows on that portfolio. So they have an "out" in that they saw the value in this portfolio E) Once they own the search patents they can sue MSFT's Bing. This is a slam dunk on a $10 deal. Let's see if GOOG takes it higher (15-30) depending on how close we get to trial and where VRNG goes. Sentiment: Buy</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349285662570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349286065187-59</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: StreetInsider - Same news but wanted to confirm.. GO..Baby go... By casp321 . 23 seconds ago . Permalink Vringo, Inc. (AMEX: VRNG) shares spiked following a federal judge ordering settlement talk... Vringo, Inc. (AMEX: VRNG) shares spiked following a federal judge ordering settlement talks with Google, Inc. (Nasdaq: GOOG) over pending patent litigation. The judge refused to end the case in Google's favor, according to documents. The talks are scheduled for October 9th. From US District Judge Raymond Jackson [In part]: "Before the Court is Defendants' Motion for Summary Judgment pursuant to Rule 56 of the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure. The Cour finds that oral argument of this motion will not aid is decisional process. Having carefully reviewed the parties' pleadings, the Court finds that summary judgment is inappropriate at this time as there are genuine issues of material fact is dispute. Accordingly, it is ORDERED that Defendants' Motion for Summary Judgment is DENIED. It is further ORDERED that parties engage in settlement discussions before United States Magistrate Judge Lawrence R. Leonard at 10:30 am on Tuesday, October 9, 2012."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349286065187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 13:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349287703980-60</Id><Title>Apple 15.6 PE, Forward PE 12.6 GOOG PE 22.5, Forward PE 16</Title><Msg>Why would anyone sell AAPL. I wouldn't sell GOOG either, but why sell a better performing stock, just because it;s run up? Lots of new products will keep coming, iPhone and tablet markets barely saturated. I think this fall was a ploy to scare retail out of shares. it's the mutual funds that lose every single time.</Msg><Username>tangos88888</Username><Timestamp>1349287703980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349288494755-61</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on its rapidly rising online revenue, Google recorded revenue of $12 billion for Q2 2012 compared to $9 billion in the Q2 2011, a 33% year-over-year increase. It is set to overtake Facebook next year, in total revenue generated by advertisements.</Msg><Username>timtomson42</Username><Timestamp>1349288494755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:21:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349290187316-62</Id><Title>GOOG ordered by Judge to settle with VRNG</Title><Msg>This could but GOOG on the hook for many millions of dollars,and hit their stock price, Mark Cuban bought a lot of VRNG stock because of this risk.</Msg><Username>hedge1fader</Username><Timestamp>1349290187316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349290672955-63</Id><Topic><Title>Sold all my calls - VRNG settlement later during the week/early next week.</Title><Username>bob_willis66</Username><Timestamp>1349110220932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 12:50:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shhh.fidelity, and others who are blindly in this..don't care. they love paying top dollar for a 80+ RSI stock for no reason with a failing motorola business and their tablets about to drop off a cliff due to ipad mini facts are facts</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1349290672955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349290684725-64</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG is green according to your tip. Thanks!</Msg><Username>timtomson42</Username><Timestamp>1349290684725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 14:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349290882726-65</Id><Title>HP CEO Warns Company's Earnings Will Fall in 2013</Title><Msg>RED LIGHT!</Msg><Username>gbor</Username><Timestamp>1349290882726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349291385484-66</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is 12.76% of the float, not 56%. Shares Outstanding is 58,245,000 and as you stated "7,432,484 on Sep-14-2012" VRNG is a strong buy right now, all aboard.</Msg><Username>j.qpublic30</Username><Timestamp>1349291385484</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349291562787-67</Id><Title>WITHOUT WARNING GOOGLE CAN FALL $25 OR $50 ANYTIME SOON.</Title><Msg>HAVE FUN &amp; GOOD LUCK!</Msg><Username>gbor</Username><Timestamp>1349291562787</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292216187-68</Id><Title>Obama will use his fake black accent in the debate tonite</Title><Msg>Wants to solidfy the base.</Msg><Username>ghetto_trash</Username><Timestamp>1349292216187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292327108-69</Id><Title>GOOG is the next HPQ</Title><Msg>looses $100 this week......... IMO</Msg><Username>bil_murphy</Username><Timestamp>1349292327108</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349292347362-70</Id><Title>straight up to 1,000..</Title><Msg>shiat the facebook.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1349292347362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293130004-71</Id><Title>GOOGLE TRADING : PROVE ONE THING YOU CAN BE RICH AND VERY STUPID</Title><Msg>LIKE IT WAS IN 1929.</Msg><Username>gbor</Username><Timestamp>1349293130004</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293319780-72</Id><Title>google not going to 1000 if they lose multi billion dollar lawsuit against VRNG</Title><Msg>Beware this will reck your high share price! Google is not getting this case dismissed it is going to trial soon.... goo.gl/Ym7nT</Msg><Username>contezta</Username><Timestamp>1349293319780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293332372-73</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG should offer 1 share of GOOG for 10 shares of VRNG and merge. This will settle the things very easily.</Msg><Username>stock_fool</Username><Timestamp>1349293332372</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:42:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293431957-74</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from Yahoo financial board: Shares Outstanding5: 33.67M Float: N/A % Held by Insiders1: 22.72% % Held by Institutions1: 1.00% Shares Short (as of Sep 14, 2012)3: 7.43M Short Ratio (as of Sep 14, 2012)3: 2.20 Short % of Float (as of Sep 14, 2012)3: 56.60% Shares Short (prior month)3: 6.42M</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349293431957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349293530797-75</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then someone should report Yahoo Financial to SEC, FBI, DOJ that they are not calculating their fiancial statistic properly.?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349293530797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:45:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349293903455-76</Id><Title>Google Vs. VRNG</Title><Msg>It seems to be a trouble to goog. Buy VRNG</Msg><Username>sabbahnedal</Username><Timestamp>1349293903455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 15:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349294416950-77</Id><Title>VRNG: Buy on Google settlement or jury verdict loss, this will cost google billions either way!</Title><Msg>goo.gl/E66OY See here for details.</Msg><Username>contezta</Username><Timestamp>1349294416950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349294436304-78</Id><Topic><Title>What GOOG Shareholders Do Not Know</Title><Username>thurman.lewis39</Username><Timestamp>1349269562695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 09:06:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for all your supports and views.It would bring back my confidence i would like to share my money with this organisition.</Msg><Username>larsens83</Username><Timestamp>1349294436304</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349295278781-79</Id><Title>Why Google will NOT go to 1000: VRNG (buy)</Title><Msg>Buy VRNG. Do you research and see why. VRNG owns the patents on online ads. Google's sole source of income, right? VRNG has a claim on 12 years or more of Google's US profits! Do not see your shares go down quickly when Google loses this case. Sell a bit and buy VRNG while it is still very cheap at 4 something! This was helpful in doing research: /goo.gl/Ym7nT</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914556</Username><Timestamp>1349295278781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349295377958-80</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>buying more tomorrow. wow what a pick VRNG is! so much real potential and the best patent lawyers in USA.</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914556</Username><Timestamp>1349295377958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:16:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349296293789-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why Google will NOT go to 1000: VRNG (buy)</Title><Username>johnkelly6914556</Username><Timestamp>1349295278781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fully agree with you. buying more tomorrow on this amazing news for VRNG and against Google. Looks like Google will lose this case and have to pay huge amount if they settle or they lose both of which are highly likely.</Msg><Username>contezta</Username><Timestamp>1349296293789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:31:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349296887823-82</Id><Title>mark cuban bought lots of VRNG: Hedge against Google losing big time - regular shareholders should buy as a hedge too.</Title><Msg>any google shareholders as a smart policy going forward must buy as a hedge to protect themselves! look how much google stock has risen on no news. dump some google shares and buy VRNG.</Msg><Username>contezta</Username><Timestamp>1349296887823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349297096113-83</Id><Topic><Title>Why Google will NOT go to 1000: VRNG (buy)</Title><Username>johnkelly6914556</Username><Timestamp>1349295278781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VRNG has better lawyers than Google. All google shareholders should know about this case! goo.gl/Ym7nT</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914556</Username><Timestamp>1349297096113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 16:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349298592618-84</Id><Title>TARGET Price: 700.88</Title><Msg>Downside Trade Trade indicators for short trades. Downside Trade &amp; Breakdown Help Downside ReCalc™ : Adjust the downside trade &amp; breakdown parameters. ( Stock Price: 762.5 ) TRADE QUALITY 90%, Excellent TARGET 1 Price: 700.88 Profit: 8.1% , for a typical pullback. Cover Limit/Trailing Cover Limit: 772.39 Loss: 1.3% Profit/Loss Ratio: 6.2 : 1 - Excellent TARGET 1 POTENTIAL Excellent, there are 1 support areas on the way to Target 1. Stocks may quickly fall to Targets when there are not many support areas blocking the way. TARGET 1 SUPPORT -6.8% at 710.7 ± 9.24, type Single, strength 1 -8.1% at 700.88 is Target 1 TARGET 2 Price: 683.46 Profit: 10.4% , Profit/Loss Ratio: 8 : 1 - Excellent for an extreme pullback. BREAKDOWN None.</Msg><Username>bil_murphy</Username><Timestamp>1349298592618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349298739130-85</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vringo Receives Positive Patent News October 3, 2012 | 8 comments by: EXPstocktrader [seekingalpha] | about: VRNG, includes: GOOG Disclosure: I am long VRNG. I wrote this article myself, and it expresses my own opinions. I am not receiving compensation for it (other than from Seeking Alpha). I have no business relationship with any company whose stock is mentioned in this article. (More...) In June 2012, Vringo (VRNG) received four out of six positive construction Markman rulings in its cases against tech giants; Aol (AOL), Google (GOOG), and Target Corp (TGT). If you are new to this story please read a previous article written back a few months ago talking about some current Global Patent Wars that are currently taking place. New Details Just Released Today Today in court, the judge overseeing the company's legal battle with Google denies Google's request for a summary judgment, and has further ordered that the parties engage in settlement discussions between United States magistrate, Judge Lawrence R. Leonard at 10:30am, Tuesday October 9, 2012. There are other talks scheduled to take place on October 5th. What's Next? Either a settlement or trial with Google looks likely, but will Google risk a huge judgement against them? And, what about the recent ZTE shot across the bow letter that was just sent to this Giant telecom company in China? People don't seem to be giving the Nokia (NOK) patent acquisition much value, at least not yet. This may soon change, so please stay tuned for more Nokia updates that may soon be forthcoming.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349298739130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349299313544-86</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice to see diifferent news on Goog board By hockeyfantrophy . 11 minutes ago . Permalink Goog message baord lite up as well with VRNG news and discussion, Why Reuters news there and not here? One person stated 1 share of goog for every 10 of VRNG that would be nice!!! Boom we blew up larger than ARNA who will buy VRNG or settle this is huge!! 0 users liked this posts 0 users disliked this posts Reply Ignore User | Report Abuse Re: Nice to see diifferent news on Goog board By casp321 . 27 seconds ago . Permalink for the same reason Yahoo pulled MF's same NEGATIVE article four times against Vringo ... for the same reason Yahoo pulled MF's same NEGATIVE article four times against Vringo on VRNGO board, three times around 10 AM in a few minutes intervals another one at a later time but the same day. Also Yahoo pulled MF's NEGATIVE report against AOL on AOL Yahoo Finacial Board but not that one on VRNG board until two days after. NOW, Yahoo pulling MSJ on GOOG Board to SCARE Google shareholders but NOT on VRNG finacial Board? So, is it Yahoo, MF, Reuter or all are in to SCARE for Short???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349299313544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349303912308-87</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Re: Re: Magistrate judge named for Norfolk federal court By casp321 . 2 minutes 15 seconds ago . Permalink Google can NOT find easy way out of it, I would say: Lawrence R. Leonard, a managing assi... Google can NOT find easy way out of it, I would say: Lawrence R. Leonard, a managing assistant U.S. attorney, has been named a new magistrate judge for the Norfolk federal court. The 55-year-old Virginia Beach resident manages the day-to-day operations of the Norfolk office and handles civil actions involving the Department of Justice, such as medical malpractice cases and actions against the military or other federal agencies.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349303912308</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349304493608-88</Id><Topic><Title>Re: Judge Has Denied MSJ and ORDERED Google et al to Settle</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349280245754</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 12:04:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June 13, 2012 Magistrate judge named for Norfolk federal court Leonard will replace U.S. Magistrate Judge F. Bradford Stillman, who is retiring this fall. Leonard will join the court Oct. 1 and will be one of three magistrate judges in Norfolk. ----------------- January 30, 2012 US Magistrate Judge Stillman to Retire in September 2012 US Magistrate Judge F. Bradford Stillman has announced that he will retire from his position on September 30, 2012. ----------------------------- Re: 3 different Judges, 3 different Ccases, 3 different Decisons? By casp321 Sep 7, 2012 11:41 AM ON2's judge screwed up by letting a "lead-plintiff-with-100-ONT-share" make $450,000 for his counsels but nothing for himself, as they want you believe, and causing a huge damage to ON2 shareholders, and might be in trouble down the road once another case like ON2 bring more attention to her ruling? Oracle's judge tried to make it look better after he ruled against Oracle, but later on quietly called it quit and "complete? Vringo's judge retires less than two working weeks of Vringo vs Google trial starting on October 16, 2012, and here is the "reasons": US Magistrate Judge Stillman to Retire January 28, 2012 Hislast day will be Sept. 30. The Virginian-Pilot reports that Stillman has no plans for retirement other than to enjoy his family</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349304493608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 18:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349305503901-89</Id><Title>Google charts indicate a surge coming!</Title><Msg>Yes we are going to $770.00 missmarket30 . Cuffs</Msg><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1349305503901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349305819059-90</Id><Title>Good for VRNG vs Google, but just part of ON2 vs Google case</Title><Msg>Good for VRNG vs Google, but just part of ON2 vs Google case To understand some of those "handshake" under the table, you can check: Tim Armstrong as Google EXEC Tim Armstrong &amp; United Football League (UFL): this was done when Armstrong was Google exec. Tim Armstrong &amp; AOL: I believe he was moved there as a "safe house" as they did move Marrisa Mayer to Yahoo to safe her from procecution or investigation and possibly later on Google can use it as leverage to distort Yahoo against MS deals? Hambrecht &amp; ON2 and Oppenheimer Hambrecht &amp; Google Hambrecht &amp; Schmidt Hambrecht &amp; Motorola Hambrecht &amp; Tim Armstrong Hambrecht &amp; AOL Hambrecht &amp; UFL Hambrecht &amp; P.P. husband of congresswoman Nancy Hambrecht &amp; Icahn Hambrecht &amp; Marck Cuban which's two sided "sword" as I see "friends" "turned" "enemies to DISTANCE each other from trouble on the way Ichan &amp; Cuban Ichan &amp; Motorola Ichan &amp; Google Icahn &amp; LionsGate and Cuban, who was PLACEHOLDER for Icahn as LGF management claimed in court filing, or something like it, which I think Cuban doing for Google in VRNG case casp321</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1349305819059</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349320338562-91</Id><Title>Truth is on Romney's side/Obama now has a record abysmal at that</Title><Msg>Romney won tonight for one simple reason 'Truth is on his side and Mr.Obama now holds that abysmal record that if not addressed now will spell the end of the USA for sure. Romney emphasized that Obama has now ran up more debt increase than all prior Presidents combined in less than 4 years and there's now way the nation can stand another 4. He also hammered home the RIGHT MA has under the 10th Amendment to instill state run healthcare if they so desire unlike the Fed whom Justice Roberts clearly remanded DOES NOT! As the Roberts ruling continues to be analyzed I believe his words say it all: 1. It is a tax just as we all surmised from the beginning and 2; most importantly the court cannot protect the citizens from the consequences of an election. So you see, just as I and many said, Obama has indeed changed the country forever in a very bad way. We indeed will now have the UK failed system of socialized medicine, to replace our very outstanding previously profit driven capitalistic form of medicine that being the very factor that made it so great. What this is truly about is 100 years of primary democrat party failed control for which their chickens indeed have come home to roost and they spent all our money (SS/Medicare, income taxes etc..) on welfare to lock in democrat votes moving forward. 1913 dem Wilson Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE that has debt leveraged our currency to zero intrinsic value, 1933 dem FDR failed SS Ponzi that was only to cost $.03 per pay, 1964 dem LBJ failed Medicare Ponzi now completely broke necessitating socialized medicine with the death panels to preclude costly care for the boomers now retiring in mass and being told all the money taken from them was squandered on welfare, and now Obama under dem Pelosi Congress more debt increase than all prior Presidents combined in less than 3.6 years. Yes Justice Roberts is correct that the court cannot be responsible for the consequences of an election, indeed Obama Care is a huge cost and most importantly this decision will cost many more jobs and the USA as once known is now finished. Hopefully Romney can stand on the 10th Amendment which is correct asserting that healthcare in MA was a states issue and this Federal mandate is not but repealing it now will be tough and impossible without Repubs taking House, Senate and POTUS. Without Harry Reid gone nothing will ever be accomplished.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1349320338562</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349321794757-92</Id><Title>ROMNEY "whoops" NOBAMA !! NOBAMA KNOWS NOTHING !!!!!</Title><Msg>GOODBYE NOBAMA...about time !</Msg><Username>wallysworld18</Username><Timestamp>1349321794757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 23:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>