<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347790933951-1</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Money laundring and creating fake company and ON2 and Powerlinx AND later on Bill Joll and ...??? ------ casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know By wmhjr99 3 months ago ------ on Sep 15, 2012 Re: Re: casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know By jarred In his recent webcast it turns out Mr Joll forgot to mention that they didn't acquire any of the appliances in those pictures and they just have to hope that whoever buys the hardware from Bivio (it's up for sale as well) will continue to sell it to ISC8 and considering their financial status that seems unlikely so they really wound up with virtually nothing other than another debt and the ability to issue more shares of stock diluting the rest of us even further. ------- Re: ON2: GREAT Short-selling/Insider Study case for ON2 Sharehlders OPT-OUT By casp321 1 year 1 month ago f you is, you can start from 2004: On2 Technologies and PowerLinx Launch Strategic Alliance for Surveillance, Security and Video-on-Demand Markets Products Will Use PowerLinx's Patented Powerline Technology And On2's VP6 Codec and TrueCast Server Software August 5th, 2004 In September 2004, PowerLinx again violated the antifiaud provisions by issuing materially misleading press releases and filing materially misleading reports with the SEC concerning a purported $23 million sales contract with a defense contractor known as Universal General Corporation ("UGC"'). In fact, UGC had no revenues, no assets, and no means to satisfy any portion of its $23 million contractual obligation to PowerLinx. PowerLinx had performed virtually no due diligence prior to issuing the press releases and reports in question to determine whether UGC was legitimate and could meet its contractual obligations. ----- ----- Re: Lion Gate??? By casp321 2 years 3 months ago I hope so but I doubt with the report that Google is working with NSC and CIA and ON2 and Powerlinx deal had their own scam in 2004. Public company in a sense that its investors money , which Shorts COVERED a few HUNDRED million dollars of it, might have been used for Money "laundering" might NOT be actually a real investing public company. Why too many involved to cover crimes COMMITTED against ON2 shareholders is a mistery to me? Even with interim and ON2 BOD aids it took more than once or twice for Google to "declare" "merger completion" without providing ON2 shareholders with any vote percentage and after BLOCKING ON2 shareholders from voting, as some reported on ON2 Yahoo message board, on Feb 16 2010, the last day of voting period. I doubt there would be any investigation should USA and another Governments are part of all of these SCAM!!! It is troublesome and scary but it might be true. ON2 shareholders have EXPOSED enough of them and I do NOT think they will be able to operate in the same manner, no matter what might happens to ON2 shareholders investment in the end. They will NOT be able to operate and use another small company in this fashion. Too many involved but they might have "never" thought they would get CAUGHT and be EXPOSED this way. ?????? Re: Re: ON2's Video technlogies flying in the CHINESE CLOUD??? By casp321.20 hours ago Why in the Europe and NOT in the USA they had to SCAM ON2 shareholders? Who was Jill Joll, ON2 CEO in 2007 contact that "promised" or made oral deal for two or three deals with about $300K but DENIED them later on? Was BJ lieing or it was part of a BROADER SCAM? Why did they let BJ land a CEO positition at a Homeland Security related company after FALSIFYING ON2 financial reports in 2007? Here I have some answer for you. It's FBI and DOJ jobs to get to the bottom of the SCAM, all I can do is bringing you to the DOORSTEPs of those might have involved in ON2 SCAM and trying to get away from the backdoor. I'm taking you to the front door: Re: This is why yahoo and google getting away with ... By casp321.21 days ago.PermalinkGo to topic . No wonder why ON2 robbery is too complicated and ON2 shareholders had break too many "codes" to simplify it, Housing Obama for "party" Who are also familiar to ON2 shareholder through camany named Google dealing with ON2, Amazon, Zencoder, Salesforce, September 19th, 2011 Obama Hits Up Silicon Valley One More Time at Google exec Marissa Mayer’s Palo Alto house [on October 22, 2010] --Google CEO Eric Schmidt --and attended an exclusive meetup in February [2011?] at Kleiner Perkins VC John Doerr’s house --Obama also hung out at Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff’s house in April [2011?].</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347790933951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 06:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347791449899-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual they changed the company name assuming no one would be able to track/trace the company after Bill Joll joining it. As we know this is how they operated in dealing with ON2 and with those financial advisor, audithors, ON2's technical staff, .... ????????? --------- on Sep 15, 2012 Re: Re: casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know By jarred In his recent webcast it turns out Mr Joll forgot to mention that they didn't acquire any of the appliances in those pictures and they just have to hope that whoever buys the hardware from Bivio (it's up for sale as well) will continue to sell it to ISC8 and considering their financial status that seems unlikely so they really wound up with virtually nothing other than another debt and the ability to issue more shares of stock diluting the rest of us even further. ------- Re: casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know By casp321 3 months ago ISC8 INC. /DE - 10-Q - Management's Discussion and Analysis of Financial Condition and Results of Operations. (Edgar Glimpses Via Acquire Media NewsEdge) In this report, the terms "ISC8 Inc.," "ISC8," "Irvine Sensors," "Irvine Sensors Corporation," "Company," "we," "us" and "our" refer to ISC8 Inc. ("ISC8") and its subsidiaries. 18 [...] Table of Contents We have historically derived a substantial majority of our total revenues from U.S. Government-funded sources and anticipate this to continue in the immediately foreseeable future. ????????? --------- Re: casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know By casp321 3 months ago June 23, 2003 Irvine Sensors is developing a special version of the miniaturized camera you see pictured here in a special program for the U.S. Army's Research, Development and Engineering Command CERDEC Night Vision and Electronic Sensors Directorate. This is a Phase II award, meaning Phase I was successful, and commercialization is coming closer to reality. June 23, 2003 IRSN pioneered the technology of "chip stacking". The company has 50 patents and over $200 million invested in the process of bonding microprocessors to create super high powered computing chips. The stock traded to a high of $365 at the top of the technology bubble. Despite having the best year in their 20 year history in fiscal 2002 (end of September), and being on track to have another record year by the end of September this year, the stock is only trading at about $1.50 as of today's close. From fiscal 1998 through 2001, IRSN averaged $10 million in sales each year. In fiscal 2002 the company hit the $15 million mark, and this year it is possible we could see $20 million. There are less than 11 million shares issued and outstanding, so the $15 million market cap is ridiculously low in my opinion. Irvine Sensors is developing a special version of the miniaturized camera you see pictured here in a special program for the U.S. Army's Research, Development and Engineering Command CERDEC Night Vision and Electronic Sensors Directorate. This is a Phase II award, meaning Phase I was successful, and commercialization is coming closer to reality. The camera will be used for night vision weapons sites for infantry weapons. Because of the super computing component, the camera is very small, lightweight, and doesn't require the enormous power and cooling current infrared sites require. Once implemented, this infrared camera will reduce the weight and size of night vision weaponry considerably. Note the key sitting next to the camera for size comparison purposes.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347791449899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 06:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347796020045-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Joll FALSIFIED ON2's Financial earning reports in 2007 and getting the position in a "safe-house" with HIGH security clearance. That must be ALARMING and telling how USA intelligence agencies using SMALL companies shareholders investment as a HIODE-OUT for the CRIMINAL activities under the name of "national-security"?? How criminal and why FBI and DOJ let these criminals get away with it??? Published: Sept. 10, 2012 Updated: Sept. 11, 2012 9:04 a.m. O.C. cybersecurity firm pays $10.5 million for technology Costa Mesa-based ISC8 has purchased key technology and customer accounts from Bivio Networks Inc. in Pleasanton. By JAN NORMAN / THE ORANGE COUNTY REGISTER Costa Mesa-based ISC8, formerly Irvine Sensors Corp., has purchased key technology and customer accounts from Bivio Networks Inc. in Pleasanton for up to $10.5 million in cash and stock. ISC8, founded in 1974, provides cybersecurity protections for companies' computer networks. It clients have included the U.S. government. ------------- Bivio Networks - Leading Cyber Security and Network Control Solutions A leader in cyber security and network control solutions, Bivio has deployed its products in a wide range of environments. Bivio’s global customer base includes leading enterprise organizations, intelligence agencies, military organizations and service providers. Bivio is privately-held and is headquartered in the San Francisco Bay Area with office locations worldwide</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347796020045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347796237051-4</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All you need to INVESTIGATE and find out about WHO bill Joll was dealing and what are their relation to USA intelligence agencies and Obama Government are ALL summarized under these threads. You need to go to those who had party in their house for Obama fo find out MORE!!!!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347796237051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 07:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347803907703-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, Yahoo ADMIN blocking posting this message, LOL!!!! ON2's Yahoo accounts were HACKED in October 2009, days prior to the oN2's "LEAD-plaintiff-with-100-ONT-ON2-share" settling the scammed ON2/Google "merger," which was a combined lawsuits of ON2 shareholders, on October 26, 2009? Why Yahoo did NOT inform the account holders about the hacking and WHO were involved in it? Bill Joll was ON2's CEO in 2007 when he FALSIFIED ON2's financial reports for the same year while Short were busy with shorting ON2 and taking its PPS way under $0.40, from around $4 in 2007, until august 2009: ISC8 Acquires Key Assets of Bivio Networks to Expand Into "Big Data" Network Cybersecurity Market September 4, 2012 ISC8 will purchase the NetFalcon and Network Content Control System business units of Bivio Networks, including all related intellectual property, sales, engineering, managerial, and other operational resources. ------- Bivio NetFalcon Big Data Solution for Network Traffic Bivio NetFalcon is the first Big Data solution for network traffic that performs real-time analytics on long-term, large scale records of network communications. Currently sold to and deployed by law enforcement agencies, government agencies and telecom operators, the product has been successfully installed in a variety of cyber security and intelligence applications around the world, enabling cyber security professionals to “look back in time” in their networks. With the proliferation of headline-grabbing cyber attacks and cyber threats, network security professionals have recognized that real-time detection and protection must be complemented by offline collection and analysis of data. To date, offline technologies have focused either on machine-to-machine data or small scale network activity utilizing packet capture technologies. Bivio NetFalcon fills in the “coverage gap” by providing the first solution for collecting and analyzing long-term, large scale network activity. Built to scale at every level, the system supports a complete range of networks - from enterprise to nationwide telecom networks - managing aggregate throughputs of up to hundreds of gigabits per second and timescales of months and years. Utilizing patent-pending technologies, the system performs real-time multi-source correlation of network activity data, resulting in a contextualized view of network activity history. These techniques dramatically shorten the time it takes to locate actionable information. Queries performed on legacy systems that typically take hours and days to complete are retrieved instantaneously on Bivio NetFalcon. The result is an unrivalled view of long-term network activity, enabling users to enhance the security of their organizations by efficiently conducting incident response, threat detection, event attribution and compliance investigations within their networks. ------------- Parental Control for Internet &amp; Mobile Service Providers High Performance Web Filtering and Content Control Solution Bivio’s Network Content Control System (NCCS) is a carrier-grade web filtering and content control solution that allows high capacity service providers to offer personalized, per-subscriber parental control services. Deployed as a fully transparent and in-line network device, Bivio NCCS is purpose-built for broadband mobile and wireline networks and far superior to proxy-based systems that are ill-suited for high-capacity environments. Bivio NCCS delivers comprehensive Safe Internet and parental control services with unmatched coverage and accuracy. Cost-effective to deploy and cost-effective to scale, Bivio NCCS offers service providers a revolutionary system to protect subscribers from accessing inappropriate content on a network-wide or per-user basis.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347803907703</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347808445280-6</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This Hate Groups must be stop, before they got our innocent by-stander killed, that includes that Koran burning Preacher. I do hope Muslims targeted them, instead of the innocents. I'm not going to have any qualm about it either. Death to all this Freaking Wackos !</Msg><Username>brasileiro_uno</Username><Timestamp>1347808445280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347810403452-7</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet all this Cowards are now hiding, scared to face their so called enemies.</Msg><Username>brasileiro_uno</Username><Timestamp>1347810403452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 11:46:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347834958083-8</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I havent watched the video nor do I care to see it. All I am going to say is many in the ME have a primitive mentality and the're proud of it. Heck some even dress like people who lived in the 12 century. I do not care if my statement above sounds politically incorrect...it's just a fact and truth hurts sometimes. Having said that, I believe the vid should be taken down because its mobilizing the fanatics and i care more about our troops then i do for a vid. Take it down, NOW.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1347834958083</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 18:35:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>