<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345380447918-1</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would yahoo want to chanmge format that they were using for different purposes until they got exposed?? Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system email story to a friendprint version Published: 10 August, 2012, 11:23 Edited: 11 August, 2012 "In a 2009 email included in the Anonymous leak, Stratfor Vice President for Intelligence Fred Burton is alleged to write, “TrapWire is a technology solution predicated upon behavior patterns in red zones to identify surveillance. It helps you connect the dots over time and distance.” Burton formerly served with the US Diplomatic Security Service, and Abraxas’ staff includes other security experts with experience in and out of the Armed Forces."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380447918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345380563562-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is funny they have changed some of Yahoo Message Board format after their CRIMINAL activities being EXPOSED on their very own tool that their AGENTs are using to CRASH or monitors devices they do NOT like what they re-post publicly reported articles links. Here is one example: Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system email story to a friendprint version Published: 10 August, 2012, 11:23 Edited: 11 August, 2012</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380563562</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:49:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345380765774-3</Id><Title>Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system</Title><Msg>Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system email story to a friendprint version Published: 10 August, 2012, 11:23 Edited: 11 August, 2012 "In a 2009 email included in the Anonymous leak, Stratfor Vice President for Intelligence Fred Burton is alleged to write, “TrapWire is a technology solution predicated upon behavior patterns in red zones to identify surveillance. It helps you connect the dots over time and distance.” Burton formerly served with the US Diplomatic Security Service, and Abraxas’ staff includes other security experts with experience in and out of the Armed Forces."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380765774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:52:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345380897303-4</Id><Topic><Title>Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380765774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:52:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google, Salesforce were allegedly offered 'TrapWire' spy tool Summary: Stratfor emails placed in the wild by WikiLeaks have revealed that a video-surveillance program developed by ex-CIA members may be in place in US government organisations and multinational corporations. By Michael Lee | August 13, 2012 In a separate email, vice president Fred Burton wrote: "Salesforce HQs in San Fran is interested in TrapWire after I briefed them on their wonderful capabilities". He also wrote that "the timing is right to revisit our relationship with Google and sense growing frustration (and chaos) on their part in light of the Chinese penetrations and intellectual property theft".</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380897303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345381091888-5</Id><Topic><Title>Surveillance: drone and video</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1298979573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-03-01 06:39:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2 Product: "digital signage and security and surveillance" How did Bill Joll get the HIGH security lob at Homeland Security company after FALSEFYING ON2 accounting in 2007? How is it possible?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345381091888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345382466396-6</Id><Topic><Title>Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380765774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:52:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny yahoo blocking what made them change the format: It is funny they have changed some of Yahoo Message Board format after their CRIMINAL activities being EXPOSED on their very own tool that</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345382466396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345382518069-7</Id><Topic><Title>Stratfor emails reveal secret, widespread TrapWire surveillance system</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345380765774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 08:52:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rest of .. their AGENTs are using to CRASH or monitors devices they do NOT like what they re-post publicly reported articles links.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345382518069</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345397027344-8</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 as Rumi says "Never lose HOPE"</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1335444261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-04-26 08:44:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To ON2 shareholders, we must see Vringo (symbol VRNG) CTO effort as an example of how he is trying to get what is his after twenty years or so: never lose hope when the Beloved sends you away. If you’re abandoned if you’re left hopeless tomorrow for sure you’ll be called again. If the door is shut right in your face keep waiting with patience don’t leave right away. Seeing your patience your love will soon summon you with grace raise you like a champion. ~Rumi</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345397027344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345414912947-9</Id><Title>Vrng court date</Title><Msg>GOOG will tank on setlement announcement on court date in October</Msg><Username>gointocalif58</Username><Timestamp>1345414912947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 18:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420178220-10</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: Please Show the difference to the Judge, if there is any?????</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1306588810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-05-28 09:20:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suicide of Deloitte partner Daniel Pirron linked to Standard Chartered's Iran scandal By Kamal Ahmed | Telegraph – Sat, Aug 18, 2012 Deloitte denies the DFS allegations that have led to Standard Chartered agreeing to pay a fine of $340m . Speaking publicly for the first time about the incident, Mr Pirron’s brother, Mike, said the family believed the two events were connected and that Daniel Pirron had warned his daughters the day before his death that there was “big trouble” ahead. “My brother didn’t discuss the case but he told me they were in big trouble with this case in London,” he said. “He was clearly apprehensive about a case that was about to come out. It is just extraordinary, when he was fine, that somebody would take his life.” Asked directly if he believed the two events were connected, Mr Pirron said: “The circumstances are just too much of a coincidence. Mr Pirron, a leading businessman who owns a construction company in Chicago, said his brother had been acting strangely the day before he shot himself. “He was with his daughter on Sunday and she said he was acting very apprehensive. He kept going to the newsstands, looking for an important story to come out to do with Deloitte,” he said. The family has hired a lawyer to try to retrieve his laptop, which Deloitte is not releasing. Mr Pirron said that they had been left devastated and confused by his death and are determined to uncover the reasons behind it. ----------- Iraqis helping Iran to skirt sanctions: US The country's central bank has $60 billion in foreign exchange reserves, with which it can meet the insatiable demand for dollars James Risen &amp; Duraid Adnan / Washington Aug 20, 2012 When President Obama announced last month that he was barring a Baghdad bank from any dealings with the American banking system, it was a rare acknowledgment of a delicate problem facing the administration in a country that American troops just left: For months, Iraq has been helping Iran skirt economic sanctions imposed on Tehran because of its nuclear programme.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345420178220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345425760307-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is this Start of GOOG Parabolic-Move, like AAPL had?</Title><Username>aiwal1</Username><Timestamp>1345252151803</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 21:09:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except GOOG's only back to its higher price range of 2007, long before it had 500,000,000 people (growing at over 1,000,000 activations per day now) using ANDROID PHONES, and so added to GOOG's worldwide search and ad sales. The reason GOOG is able to up sales 25% last quarter, even though they are cutting ad-prices-per-click by over 10% each year, is because number of ad-clicks is rising 40% (last quarter's earnings report). This is a tremendous business. Lower your price 10 - 15% per year, usage going up 40% per year, sales up 25% per year. The other FUNDAMENTAL thing you guys 'only considering statistical analysis of past price moves' (technical analysts) have missed, is besides GOOG has real unit growth and tremendous growth in sales and profits since 2007 (but the stock's barely up), it now has gotten the Motorola acquisition under cash-flow control. GOOG has the Patents-Trove it wanted from Motorola already, but now also has a likely profitable business, cash-flow pos. subsidiary.</Msg><Username>aiwal1</Username><Timestamp>1345425760307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345427536248-12</Id><Title>Wow..1987?</Title><Msg>Please go to SPY board since new message boards do not allow links. Very good read.</Msg><Username>bigheart_md</Username><Timestamp>1345427536248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>