<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-18"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347959305953-1</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They shred their own so they can erase the evidence blaming their friendly "enemy" who taking care of what they usually can not do because of USA legal system? Now they are using video clip through Googler Youtube to do what they ould not do before: Re: Another October, is it "Surprise"?? By casp321.9 months ago The reason of North leaving iran-contra, NOT iran-hostages in 1979, without shredding was so obvious that I do NOT understand why they sound it confusing. Any how some, involved in Iran-hostage-1979, did NOT survive cancer to "testify" the "shredding" and ... Re: You dumaz: mark it with one-star??? 11-Dec-11 09:16 am Iran Arms Trip Informant in Court August 16, 1987|From Times Wire Services NICOSIA, Cyprus — The man who leaked news of last November's secret trip to Tehran by former U.S. National Security Adviser Robert C. McFarlane and Lt. Col. Oliver L. North is being tried in a "spiritual court," Iran's official news agency said Saturday. Hashemi's arrest, which came almost immediately after word was leaked of the U.S. trip, at first clouded the political future of his brother-in-law, the Ayatollah Hussein Ali Montazeri, the handpicked successor to Iran's supreme leader, the Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini. ------ In October, 1985, Congress agreed to vote 27 million dollars in non-lethal aid for the Contras in Nicaragua. However, members of the Ronald Reagan administration decided to use this money to provide weapons to the Contras and the Mujahideen in Afghanistan. The following month, Ted Shackley traveled to Hamburg where he met General Manucher Hashemi, the former head of SAVAK’s counterintelligence division at the Atlantic Hotel. Also at the meeting on 22nd November was Manucher Ghorbanifar. According to the report of this meeting that Shackley sent to the CIA, Ghorbanifar had “fantastic” contacts with Iran. Buckley had also worked closely with William Casey in the secret negotiations with the Iranians in 1980. Buckley had a lot to tell his captors. He eventually signed a 400 page statement detailing his activities in the CIA. He was also videotaped making this confession. Casey asked Ted Shackley for help in obtaining Buckley’s freedom. Three weeks after Buckley’s disappearance, President Ronald Reagan signed the National Security Decision Directive 138. This directive was drafted by Oliver North and outlined plans on how to get the American hostages released from Iran and to “neutralize” terrorist threats from countries such as Nicaragua. This new secret counter terrorist task force was to be headed by Shackley’s old friend, General Richard Secord. This was the beginning of the Iran-Contra deal. On 15th October, leaflets were given out in Tehran stating that high-ranking advisers to President Ronald Reagan had been visiting Iran the previous month to negotiate a deal to release hostages for arms. Two days later, Charles E. Allen provided Casey with a seven-page assessment of the "arms-hostage machinations". Allen wrote: "The government of the United States, along with the government of Israel, acquired substantial profit from these transactions, some of which profit was redistributed to other projects of the U.S. and of Israel." At the beginning of November, newspapers in the United States began running stories about the Iran-Contra conspiracy. On 6th November, President Ronald Reagan told reporters that the story that Robert McFarlane had been negotiating an arms for hostages deal "has no foundation". He also argued that he would not carry out talks with Iran as its government was part of "a new international version of Murder Incorporated". Casey was due to appear before the HSCI on 16th December. The day before, CIA physician, Dr. Arvel Tharp went to visit Casey in his office. According to Tharp, while he was being examined, Casey suffered a seizure. He was taken to Georgetown University Hospital and was not able to appear before the HSCI. Tharp told Casey he had a brain tumor and that he would have to endure an operation. Casey was not keen and asked if he could have radio therapy instead. However, Tharp was insistent that he needed surgery. Casey entered the operating room on 18th December. The tumor was removed but during the operation, brain cells were damaged and Casey lost his ability to speak. As his biographer, Joseph E. Persico, points out (The Lives and Secrets of William J. Casey): "one school of rumors ran, the CIA or the NSC or the White House had arranged to have a piece of the brain removed from the man who knew the secrets". William Joseph Casey died on 6th May, 1987.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347959305953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347959780682-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Wonder how much is a drone? By casp321.3 months ago . Ghorbanifar, as ex-Savak under the Shah, was member of "Hostage-Rescue" mission crue under the command of Secord, represting Carter Government in 1980. He was "responsible" turning/keeping the Tehran-Soccor-Stadium's LIGHTs ON, during the Hostage "rescue" mission, to make it possible for helicopers to land-takeoff from Tehran-Stadium. Hakim was "responsible" providing "housing" for the "rescued" hostages until they could be taken out of Tehran/Iran. Now COLLASPE the hostage TIME-DATE taking place in 1984-1985 in Beirut with the one in Iran in 1979-1981, and bring all involved in these two in different place at different time under the SAME CIRCLE and let them run in the CIRCLE. What would you get it all ending at the same "spot" of the "circle" that they started from after turning 360 degrees. You can repeat it as many time you wish. All in one circle, Kangarlu, Shackley, Ghorbanifar, Secord, Hakim, Poindexter, MacFarlane, then ask this question: "How could Poindexter and Nort NOT know Ghorbanifar and Secord activities and RELATION long before 1984-1985?" How is it possible for Ghorbanifar blame all Beirut "activities" to Kangarlu from INSIDE Iran to keep the rest OUSIDE clean: This is what called FRIENDs as "enemies" they are PAINTING for the world. So what today "cyber" are for? You be the judge but you also would need many DIGGIN the internet to see it sound DIFFERENT CIRCLE at different TIME with RECENT technologies. No one needs to traval, as North and Mackfarne had done more than once to Iran, to play their game again. It's cyber they call??? Kangarku, Mosavi's deputy; and as Mosavi had said once to North or those on Reagan side, "we let you get-rid of Democrats as USA president" during the time of Hostge "crisis" in 1979-1981?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347959780682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:16:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347962249433-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just ask yourself a question of how these contradictort reports in the USA Media can get away with their misleading report: Reneades "Out of Bush", but who'll be "In the Bush?" Re: USA "Plot" SCAMs and Saudi Involvement? By casp321 10 months ago Ronald Reagan From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia The Reagan Presidency began in a dramatic manner; as Reagan was giving his inaugural address, 52 U.S. hostages, held by Iran for 444 days were set free. ------------------ John Hinckley, Jr. From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia Reagan assassination attemptMain article: Reagan assassination attempt On March 30, 1981, at approximately 1:30 PM local time,[2] Hinckley shot a .22 caliber Röhm RG-14 revolver six times at Reagan as he left the Hilton Hotel in Washington, D.C., after addressing an AFL-CIO conference. Bush–Hinckley family connections According to the March 31, 1981, edition of the Houston Post, and reported by AP, UPI, NBC News and Newsweek, Hinckley is the son of one of George H.W. Bush's political and financial supporters in his 1980 presidential primary campaign against Ronald Reagan; John Hinckley, Jr.'s elder brother, Scott Hinckley, and Bush's son Neil Bush had a dinner appointment scheduled for the next day.[19][20] Associated Press published the following on March 31, 1981: The family of the man charged with trying to assassinate President Reagan is acquainted with the family of Vice-President George Bush and had made large contributions to his political campaign ... Scott Hinckley, brother of John W. Hinckley, Jr., was to have dined tonight in Denver at the home of Neil Bush, one of the Vice-President's sons ... The Houston Post said it was unable to reach Scott Hinckley, vice-president of his father's Denver-based firm, Vanderbilt Energy Corporation, for comment. Neil Bush lives in Denver, where he works for Standard Oil Company of Indiana. In 1978, Neil Bush served as campaign manager for his brother, George W. Bush, the Vice-President's eldest son, who made an unsuccessful bid for Congress. Neil lived in Lubbock, Texas, throughout much of 1978, where John Hinckley lived from 1974 through 1980... Sharon Bush, Neil's wife, said Scott Hinckley was coming to their house as a date of a girl friend of hers. "I don't even know the brother. From what I know and I've heard, they (the Hinckleys) are a very nice family and have given a lot of money to the Bush campaign. I understand he was just the renegade brother in the family. They must feel awful," she said.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347962249433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347962256588-4</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just ask yourself a question of how these contradictort reports in the USA Media can get away with their misleading report: Reneades "Out of Bush", but who'll be "In the Bush?" Re: USA "Plot" SCAMs and Saudi Involvement? By casp321 10 months ago Ronald Reagan From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia The Reagan Presidency began in a dramatic manner; as Reagan was giving his inaugural address, 52 U.S. hostages, held by Iran for 444 days were set free. ------------------ John Hinckley, Jr. From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia Reagan assassination attemptMain article: Reagan assassination attempt On March 30, 1981, at approximately 1:30 PM local time,[2] Hinckley shot a .22 caliber Röhm RG-14 revolver six times at Reagan as he left the Hilton Hotel in Washington, D.C., after addressing an AFL-CIO conference. Bush–Hinckley family connections According to the March 31, 1981, edition of the Houston Post, and reported by AP, UPI, NBC News and Newsweek, Hinckley is the son of one of George H.W. Bush's political and financial supporters in his 1980 presidential primary campaign against Ronald Reagan; John Hinckley, Jr.'s elder brother, Scott Hinckley, and Bush's son Neil Bush had a dinner appointment scheduled for the next day.[19][20] Associated Press published the following on March 31, 1981: The family of the man charged with trying to assassinate President Reagan is acquainted with the family of Vice-President George Bush and had made large contributions to his political campaign ... Scott Hinckley, brother of John W. Hinckley, Jr., was to have dined tonight in Denver at the home of Neil Bush, one of the Vice-President's sons ... The Houston Post said it was unable to reach Scott Hinckley, vice-president of his father's Denver-based firm, Vanderbilt Energy Corporation, for comment. Neil Bush lives in Denver, where he works for Standard Oil Company of Indiana. In 1978, Neil Bush served as campaign manager for his brother, George W. Bush, the Vice-President's eldest son, who made an unsuccessful bid for Congress. Neil lived in Lubbock, Texas, throughout much of 1978, where John Hinckley lived from 1974 through 1980... Sharon Bush, Neil's wife, said Scott Hinckley was coming to their house as a date of a girl friend of hers. "I don't even know the brother. From what I know and I've heard, they (the Hinckleys) are a very nice family and have given a lot of money to the Bush campaign. I understand he was just the renegade brother in the family. They must feel awful," she said.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347962256588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 05:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347966872188-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2 shareholders were not dumb, after all, as ON2's interim or Google originators tried to JUSTIFY the STEAL. But the question is why ON2 BASHERs were calling on Page to "not give in to terrorists demand?" How did a handle know the POWER of ON2 shareholders SEARCHING with NO tools without having access to INTERNAL and PERSONAL profile? Another question is WHO is/was PROVIDING those information to ON2 bashers and Google supporters? Why Government agents are ACTIVILELY INTIMIDATING a regular shareholders on a SCRATCH Yhoo Messages Board? Who and why? Intimidation is NOT what scares me but NOT fighting for my STOLEN ... does!!!! Thios is one of the MAIN reasons for Yahoo to change its "Yahoo format" to COVER what's already EXPOSED. They're using their agents to enen post SIMUTANEOSLY with you post, but again HOW did/do these agents have access to your typing text on a scratch board before you posting them?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347966872188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 07:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347971643479-6</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How stupid are you people?? This was NOT about a stupid video. The attacks were planned. They were given warnings three days prior. The administration does not want to admit it, it is not convenient. This is also NOT the first terrorist attack. The shooting of Fort Hood was a terrorist attack on our soil but of course it was not classified as such! WAKE UP AMERICA. you are being lied to.</Msg><Username>shorthound</Username><Timestamp>1347971643479</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:34:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347973089748-7</Id><Title>FB Facebook OVERSOLD and UNDERVALUED Techincal BOUNCE coming!!! Watch ZNGA PCFG too</Title><Msg>FB Facebook OVERSOLD and UNDERVALUED Techincal BOUNCE coming!!! Watch ZNGA PCFG too imho</Msg><Username>wworld933</Username><Timestamp>1347973089748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347973555624-8</Id><Title>Brin, Page, no joking around....Biotech symbols (ANX), (ACAD), (PACB), will rise 100+%</Title><Msg>100% minimum.</Msg><Username>gale_soon4dollars</Username><Timestamp>1347973555624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347975156956-9</Id><Topic><Title>In every scenario Google Inc. is a Crack in One Stock</Title><Username>singletonw23</Username><Timestamp>1323782618000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-12-13 08:23:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>wilson.son10</Username><Timestamp>1347975156956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:32:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347978318064-10</Id><Title>FB into search? what is the impact on GOOG?</Title><Msg>I would say not lower than 650.</Msg><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1347978318064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347980030909-11</Id><Title>wish i had held, not sold yesterday</Title><Msg>guys please pull this back so I can get back in</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347980030909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347981684949-12</Id><Title>WHY IS GOOG GOING HIGHER, BECAUSE OF IPHONE 5 more clicks.....???</Title><Msg>WHAT A BUBBLE</Msg><Username>tamermou</Username><Timestamp>1347981684949</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347983156501-13</Id><Title>$714.87 was the highest past close in 2007</Title><Msg>Four weeks before $747.24 was an intraday high. Maybe the today we will have a new high close ... after 5 years!!</Msg><Username>airstockman</Username><Timestamp>1347983156501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347983934880-14</Id><Title>Historical High.</Title><Msg>Cheers.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347983934880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347983935028-15</Id><Title>Historical High.</Title><Msg>Cheers.</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1347983935028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:58:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347987043062-16</Id><Title>Bac has 600 Billion in cash more than apple and goog combined and tripled!!!!</Title><Msg>...............and bac sells at a discount</Msg><Username>hcl815</Username><Timestamp>1347987043062</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347987380438-17</Id><Title>Buy SHF - going to $100 soon</Title><Msg>for sure</Msg><Username>drhollars</Username><Timestamp>1347987380438</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:56:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347989589594-18</Id><Title>just bought 740 weekly calls</Title><Msg>the train is moving</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347989589594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347989828766-19</Id><Title>when this was at 660 karen finerman indicated that it had a huge run would not buy BUT was NOT selling</Title><Msg>when this was at 660 karen finerman indicated that it had a huge run would not buy BUT was NOT selling: No selling we keep going up</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347989828766</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347992638415-20</Id><Topic><Title>just bought 740 weekly calls</Title><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347989589594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u should have sold them instead... i sold a s#itload of the 730s myself.</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347992638415</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:23:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347994512652-21</Id><Topic><Title>just bought 740 weekly calls</Title><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347989589594</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:33:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>best of luck</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347994512652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347994979398-22</Id><Title>who thinks this looks like a top?</Title><Msg>Thanks! (my straddle getting some 700 puts to go with the 740 calls)</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347994979398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347995446172-23</Id><Title>Velti Just Closed A $27 Million Mobile Marketing Deal</Title><Msg>velt is the real player in mobile ads</Msg><Username>shavitmi</Username><Timestamp>1347995446172</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347995673028-24</Id><Topic><Title>Brin, Page, no joking around....Biotech symbols (ANX), (ACAD), (PACB), will rise 100+%</Title><Username>gale_soon4dollars</Username><Timestamp>1347973555624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:05:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, if they purchased 1-5 million shares of each they would easily double their money in those names.</Msg><Username>teragr50</Username><Timestamp>1347995673028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347995887881-25</Id><Topic><Title>Brin, Page, no joking around....Biotech symbols (ANX), (ACAD), (PACB), will rise 100+%</Title><Username>gale_soon4dollars</Username><Timestamp>1347973555624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:05:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CPRX may be acquired by Pfizer for $4.00 per share due to CPP patent portfolio. Developer of Lyrica has developed another blockbuster drug but this time it is for cocaine and tobacco addiction.</Msg><Username>biopsied5x</Username><Timestamp>1347995887881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:18:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347997737218-26</Id><Title>They better NOT be buying Fartbook!</Title><Msg>Or is AAPL buy GOOG? Why the pop?</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1347997737218</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347998207493-27</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG vs FB</Title><Username>lockkey110</Username><Timestamp>1347992883084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tells us Fagbook bagholder, how bad of an a## #$%$ did you suffer on Fartbook?</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347998207493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347998264568-28</Id><Title>GOOG : THE BUBBLE, NO IPHONE 5, NO 117 bil in cash, JUST CLICKS</Title><Msg>The crash will be very bad</Msg><Username>tamermou</Username><Timestamp>1347998264568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347998423224-29</Id><Title>Hedgies buying like crazy...720 in AHs, watch and learn!</Title><Msg>Someone knows something.</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347998423224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347998613866-30</Id><Title>What the #ell happened...why the high volume gap up today?!</Title><Msg>Was some deal announced?</Msg><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1347998613866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347999672174-31</Id><Topic><Title>What the #ell happened...why the high volume gap up today?!</Title><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1347998613866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HFs buying...shorts covering. Will open @ +723 tomorrow...another new 52-week high. So just sit back and enjoy the ride.</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347999672174</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348000741303-32</Id><Title>$719.19 in After-Hours Trading.</Title><Msg>Volume is good as well indicating hedge funds are still buying.</Msg><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348000741303</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348001656667-33</Id><Topic><Title>What the #ell happened...why the high volume gap up today?!</Title><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1347998613866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. Volume would indicate institutional accumulation. Plus, I think we're starting to see a run-up towards earnings on 10/10.</Msg><Username>ideadirect</Username><Timestamp>1348001656667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:54:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348002406134-34</Id><Topic><Title>What the #ell happened...why the high volume gap up today?!</Title><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1347998613866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe the split has been approved...just a thought...a nice thought at that...booyah</Msg><Username>estanczyk</Username><Timestamp>1348002406134</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348003738234-35</Id><Topic><Title>What the #ell happened...why the high volume gap up today?!</Title><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1347998613866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:03:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot about that... You might be right. Google did plan for their two-for-one stock split to take effect sometime after June 21. And being that we're already in mid Sept. I'm guessing the split could happen at anytime now.</Msg><Username>tek9c</Username><Timestamp>1348003738234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348003957384-36</Id><Title>2-for-1 Stock split could happen at anytime now.</Title><Msg>After all, Google did plan for their 2-for-1 stock split to take effect sometime after June 21 of this year, which means it could happen at anytime now.</Msg><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348003957384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:32:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348004156189-37</Id><Title>Up another buck in after-hours trading to +719 now...</Title><Msg>Futures are also moving higher. Looks like we could see the 730s this week, possible even the 740s if this keeps up.</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1348004156189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348004321216-38</Id><Title>THIS IS WHY GOOG IS UP BIG TIME, LINK</Title><Msg>Goog up on iphone 5 release up because samsung and htc lost their android patents to apple up because of their mega growth in hardware up because of looming anti trust and anti competitive suit by eu up because people are clicking every one sec and ads are flooding them biggest ever bubble,!!</Msg><Username>tamermou</Username><Timestamp>1348004321216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348009090027-39</Id><Title>Google going to file bankruptcy.</Title><Msg>I believe FB and AAPL together are going to put AMZN and GOOG out of business.</Msg><Username>greenmacheen001</Username><Timestamp>1348009090027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348010845811-40</Id><Topic><Title>2-for-1 Stock split could happen at anytime now.</Title><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348003957384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was a 3-1 ....one was a non voting .issue??? unsure how it all goes down...to be continued</Msg><Username>estanczyk</Username><Timestamp>1348010845811</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348015351106-41</Id><Title>My guess we get up around 727 tomorrow then pull back</Title><Msg>Just a guess</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348015351106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348015427715-42</Id><Topic><Title>2-for-1 Stock split could happen at anytime now.</Title><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348003957384</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be great then it could run back up to the same price and have a forward PE of 45 and current PE of 70</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348015427715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>