<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355131414785-1</Id><Topic><Title>Targeting is the MAGIC WORD of Mobile Search</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1355006725439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:45:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, and isn't it amazing that ipads controls 88% of all mobile commerce. Throw in iphones and its well above 90%. So, AAPL basically owns mobile commerce and consequently mobile advertising revenues. And since mobile is the future of search, it looks like AAPL owns the future of mobile search. Too bad GOOG, looks like you #$%$ in the wrong sand box. Android was your answer, huh? You saw the writing on the wall years ago, huh? This was your scared desperate attempt to survive, huh? Well, it didn't work. You don't make any money selling andriod devices and AAPL owns mobile commerce. Game over.</Msg><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1355131414785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 04:23:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355143489024-2</Id><Title>GRPN - rumor is GOOG may buy them!!!</Title><Msg>I think that's a smart move by Google!!</Msg><Username>robzuc15</Username><Timestamp>1355143489024</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 07:44:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355145002194-3</Id><Title>ON2 Shareholders please take a note, you might not get your money but justice?</Title><Msg>You can still check their connections to those transitions at the "nodes" which makes hard to ytack the traces those illegally involved after they cross throgh the connecting nodes: Hambrecht, O'hare &amp; Hieb-these two work as a "team" and move as a tem from one company to another, John Fargis, Tomi Jalonen, Mike Kopetski, ON2's two CTOs. Some might say these are nonsense and are "imagination" not "real." It is possible, but those intending to INVESTIGATE will have some places and relations to look and check to see if there are any clue leading to solving any puzzles SEC, DOJ, FBI, do nOT want or can NOT solve becaose of being complex. What I'm trying to do make it simple, at least the imagination of those relations/connections to make those to diffentiaste and then integrate to create the COMPEXITY is easier to see comparing to the complex and entangled networks of ... Up to this point Google terminated Hantro trademak on November 12, 2012 after holding it for more than four years since April 2008, AND UFL ceased its operation immediately starting in October 2012. On December 8, 2012 Google replaced its head of A&amp;M, Lawee, by Don Harrison, who became ON2 president and CEO after Feb 2010 and after renaming ON2 as "LLC". What is still left unresoved for Google and I do NOT think they can find any better solution is relation among Pete Wendell and Eric Schmidt, as a results Sierra ventures and Google involvement with Hantro and verisilicon. In the center of all of these are Dai's dynasy from China who are brothers and sister running as CEO and Chairman Verisilicon, Marvell and Vinvante companies. In addition, you should ask the question why ON2 BOD let Ms. Naimollah continue "contact and discussion with Google regarding ON2" and what might be the relations and connection among Naimollah, Amin Zoulonoon, Lawee, Kordestani, and Don Harrison? --------------- just giving two example you can search for more under my handle and ask Yahoo unblock for you those they'ce archived when you go beyond and serious about putting any one of those involved in ON2 theft into jail. It's about USA andChina relation with ON2 the contact point for all their SCAM but EXPOSING their trelation will warn those who concern to do something about it no matter if they have USA president behind snd hsving parties in their house for him. Tomi Jalonen PAST: Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. | Spoke Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. of On2 Technologies, Inc CURRENT: Re: VeriSilicon Releases New Generation of Hantro Video IP Products 24-Feb-12 11:30 pm Tomi Jalonen VeriSilicon and WebM Support Monday, January 24, 2011 | 4:43 PM Guest blogger Tomi Jalonen is Director of Product Marketing for Hantro video IP at VeriSilicon ------- --Pete Wendell and Eric Schmidt --O'Hare, Oppenheimer, Hambrecht and Hantro ---They &amp;... --Pete Wendell and Eric Schmidt --O'Hare, Oppenheimer, Hambrecht and Hantro ---They "completed ON2 and Hantro deal on Nov 1, 2007 --William/Bill Hambrecht and Eric Schmidt, --Michael Kopetski, Chinese EXPERT, and one of ON2's BOD ---Many ON2 Flix Engine and Chinese companies deal ---ON2 USA and Verisilicon from China deal --Pete Wendell and Eric Schmidt thought "entrepreneurship" COURSE together --Pete Wendell Managing director of Sierra Ventures --Sierra Ventures is/was one of Verisilicon Semiconductors INVESTORs --Verisilicon FROM CHINA MADE deals with ON2 under "ON2 Finland", and NOT "ON2 USA" as Google and MF wanted the world believe-possibly because of "double irish" taxing --Verisilicon FROM China --ON2 and 50 Semiconductor companies --ON2's "G1" Decoder and 8290 Encoder --Ceva and Google and ON2 PRODUCTS/Chipset and what: from August 5, 2009 to Feb 16, 2010?? ------- Mike Kopetski USA congressman, ON2 bOD, and expert in China asking USA congress in 1990 to recnize China as Most Valued Nation and one of those involved in more than dozen ON2 dals with Chinese without making any red-cent for ON2 shareholders? just one example. Fargis had worked at Motorola, then GIPS and then ON2 which Google acquired three of them? Re: Re: Is Judge Ruling New Precedent? casp321 by casp321 . Nov 1, 2012 9:23 AM Shanghai InfoTM Feb. 16, 2008 ---"We are extremely pleased to add Shanghai InfoTM to our growing list of licensees in China," says John Fargis, VP APAC sales, On2 Technologies. ????????????</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355145002194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 08:10:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355145419409-4</Id><Topic><Title>what the heck is Groupon? Buy Priceline</Title><Username>hey_rob69</Username><Timestamp>1291178879000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-11-30 23:47:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alan Wade served as the Chief Information Officer of Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) since 2001. Mr. Wade retired from federal service in 2005 after a thirty-five-year career in the Central Intelligence Agency. He was involved in technical programs in the United States and oversaw, principally in the areas of telecommunications and technical security. While at the CIA, he held a series of senior positions , including the Director of Communications, Director of Security</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355145419409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 08:16:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355150863794-5</Id><Title>GOOG different with AAPL</Title><Msg>There's exactly a big different between GOOG and AAPL.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1355150863794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 09:47:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355151697819-6</Id><Topic><Title>Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" versus Charlie Sheen---</Title><Username>crookedhedgefundmanager</Username><Timestamp>1355073795248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:23:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't let your friends read Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star"-----Then they'll be a LOT smarter than you ...INTOLERABLE!!!</Msg><Username>crookedhedgefundmanager</Username><Timestamp>1355151697819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 10:01:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355153136044-7</Id><Topic><Title>INVERTED HEAD &amp; SHOULDER FORMING</Title><Username>bullish2003</Username><Timestamp>1354908739868</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:32:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you post, its helpful to provide some kind of evidence/ reason. us "little fish" cant affect the market w/ our puny post; this should be about helping each other.</Msg><Username>bullish2003</Username><Timestamp>1355153136044</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 10:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355153246896-8</Id><Topic><Title>BARRON'S FRONT COVER BUY APPLE NOW</Title><Username>mrcmeguy</Username><Timestamp>1355071747112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 11:49:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does that track like the Sports Illustrated cover jinx?</Msg><Username>robynrokn</Username><Timestamp>1355153246896</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 10:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355153669419-9</Id><Title>Growth is gone...funds dumping $630 by close today..see PCLN</Title><Msg>game over here</Msg><Username>crmisgoingto50</Username><Timestamp>1355153669419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 10:34:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355155195455-10</Id><Title>get out of PCLN and GOOG folks. also GS report says APPLE will beat goog in the war</Title><Msg>was out late friday no one read until weekend</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1355155195455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 10:59:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355158239580-11</Id><Topic><Title>A sure DOuble</Title><Username>lucieguilbeau937</Username><Timestamp>1326650533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-01-15 13:02:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good move.</Msg><Username>nancy.mortin</Username><Timestamp>1355158239580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 11:50:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355158284757-12</Id><Topic><Title>@@@ GOOG Featured on SQUAWK BOX @@@</Title><Username>neckanderson</Username><Timestamp>1350579474131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 12:57:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good alert</Msg><Username>ryanlee700</Username><Timestamp>1355158284757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 11:51:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355158439085-13</Id><Title>GMAIL is down,down,down...</Title><Msg>#$%$ kind of customer service is that when they can't keep the mail running? Says a lot about the company and it's frail infrastructure.</Msg><Username>sniffmydigits</Username><Timestamp>1355158439085</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 11:53:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355160372124-14</Id><Topic><Title>8000% on KROGER and (ATTD) deal, Phase III Recover drink ATTD's product will now be sold in KROGER</Title><Username>greatpennies</Username><Timestamp>1354049588326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attd's product is on amazon. Google phase iii recovery drink.</Msg><Username>hugedoubler</Username><Timestamp>1355160372124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 12:26:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355163615920-15</Id><Title>Potential stocks......</Title><Msg>Why trade GOOG and AAPL...too risky EW....hod...going higher LVS...read art icicle from Thestreet this morning. 50% undervalued. Adelson is smart, he will spinoff REIT.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1355163615920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:20:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355164115799-16</Id><Topic><Title>Potential stocks......</Title><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1355163615920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:20:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SODA....good entry on pullback ONVO......good potential....read ONTO message board. I posted there FB.....like FB fir holding longer....</Msg><Username>real_sugardad</Username><Timestamp>1355164115799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355164819829-17</Id><Title>Nokia pounding apple</Title><Msg>STOMP STOMP STOMP!!!</Msg><Username>realestatestock1972</Username><Timestamp>1355164819829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:40:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355165225921-18</Id><Title>goog showing strength</Title><Msg>with a good market this could go back over 700 this week</Msg><Username>fbtb3905</Username><Timestamp>1355165225921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:47:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355166837859-19</Id><Topic><Title>VELT ($3.75) - With 6 billion mobile phone users MOBILE ADVERTISING &amp; BRANDING = future</Title><Username>icgemanagementloser</Username><Timestamp>1355092260593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:31:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Checkout 1300+ corporate customers of Velti in mobile advertising and branding market which will be $15 bln in a few yrs. GOOG needs VELT before FB, YHOO or MM grabs it. Check today's news on VELT to see why everyone will use VELT from their cell phones imho.</Msg><Username>icgemanagementloser</Username><Timestamp>1355166837859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 14:13:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355167510322-20</Id><Topic><Title>Every and each trader it is an apt time to tow up your GOOG profits</Title><Username>valenzuelafannie84</Username><Timestamp>1354198527691</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-29 09:15:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great one!</Msg><Username>adamsjames133</Username><Timestamp>1355167510322</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 14:25:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355189045396-21</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders please take a note, you might not get your money but justice?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355145002194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 08:10:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capital:£30,079,102.71 ON2 TECHNOLOGIES (UK) LIMITED Legal Information Company Registration No.: 02674066 Incorporation Date: 24 Dec 1991 20 Years old Financial Year End: 30 Jun Capital:£30,079,102.71 on 5 Jan 2012 People connected with this Company JOHN WALKER 22 Feb 2012 director - Appointment ended DONALD STEWART HARRISON 16 Feb 2012 director - Appointed JOHN KENT WALKER 18 May 2011 director - Particulars Changed GRAHAM LAW 28 Oct 2010 director - Particulars Changed JOHN KENT WALKER 28 Oct 2010 director - Particulars Changed JOHN KENT WALKER 9 Apr 2010 director - Appointed GRAHAM LAW 9 Apr 2010 director - Appointed JANET WILKINS 9 Apr 2010 secretary - Appointment ended PAUL WILKINS 9 Apr 2010 director - Appointment ended MATTHEW FROST 9 Apr 2010 director - Appointment ended MATTHEW FROST 6 Jan 2010 director - Particulars Changed MR PAUL GORDON WILKINS 6 Jan 2010 director - Particulars Changed Previous Company Names METAVISUAL CREATIONS LIMITED Changed 7 Feb 2008</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355189045396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 20:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355189508918-22</Id><Title>Goog made the right choice</Title><Msg>move money out of the U.S. to avoid the upcoming tax fiasco.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1355189508918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 20:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355189950683-23</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders please take a note, you might not get your money but justice?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355145002194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 08:10:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Wednesday, June 13, 2007, a U.S. federal trademark registration was filed for ON2 by Google Inc., MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94043. The USPTO has given the ON2 trademark serial number of 77204994. The current federal status of this trademark filing is REGISTERED. The correspondent listed for ON2 is Christine Hsieh of Google Inc. This is a brand page for the ON2 trademark by Google Inc. in MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA, 94043. Write a review about a product or service associated with this ON2 trademark. Or, contact the owner Google Inc. of the ON2 trademark by filing a request to communicate with the Legal Correspondent for licensing, use, and/or questions related to the ON2 trademark. On Wednesday, June 13, 2007, a U.S. federal trademark registration was filed for ON2 by Google Inc., MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94043. The USPTO has given the ON2 trademark serial number of 77204994. The current federal status of this trademark filing is REGISTERED. The correspondent listed for ON2 is Christine Hsieh of Google Inc., 1600 Ampitheatre Parkway, Mountain View CA 94043 . The ON2 trademark is filed in the category of Computer &amp; Software Products &amp; Electrical &amp; Scientific Products . The description provided to the USPTO for ON2 is Computer software for digital compression and decompression of video information. Word Mark: ON2 Status/ Status Date: REGISTERED 1/29/2008 Estimated Renewal Deadline: January 29, 2014 See Trademark Renewal Services Serial Number: 77204994 Filing Date: 6/13/2007 Registration Number: 3375806 Registration Date: 1/29/2008 Goods and Services: Computer software for digital compression and decompression of video information Mark Description: NOT AVAILABLE Type Of Mark: TradeMark Published For Opposition Date: 11/13/2007 Last Applicant/Owner: Google Inc. MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94043 Why is this contact information displayed? Mark Drawing Code: Standard Character Mark Design Search: (NO DATA) Register Type: Principal Disclaimer: (NOT AVAILABLE) Correspondent: Christine Hsieh Google Inc. 1600 Ampitheatre Parkway Mountain View CA 94043 Classification Information International Class Code(s): 009 US Class Code(s): 021, 023, 026, 036, 038</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1355189950683</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 20:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355191803099-24</Id><Title>scam</Title><Msg>scam</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1355191803099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 21:10:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355195429617-25</Id><Topic><Title>Targeting is the MAGIC WORD of Mobile Search</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1355006725439</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:45:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mobile search is one thing. increased targeting of anything that looks or smells like an actual ad is a waste of f*cking time, even somebody actively looking to buy a kayak isn't going to buy yours just because you shove it in their #$%$ face right when they get the idea they might want one.</Msg><Username>brunopuno</Username><Timestamp>1355195429617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 22:10:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355199108636-26</Id><Topic><Title>Nokia pounding apple</Title><Username>realestatestock1972</Username><Timestamp>1355164819829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 13:40:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How, How, How, Please???</Msg><Username>dogeater20088</Username><Timestamp>1355199108636</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 23:11:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>