<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351483407148-1</Id><Title>Washinton Post finally on to Obama too</Title><Msg>THE WASHINGTON POST HITS OBAMA Finally, the Washington Post and Newsweek speak out about Obama. This is timely and tough. As many of you know, the Washington Post and Newsweek have a reputation for being extremely liberal. The fact that their editors saw fit to print the following article about Obama and the one that appears in the latest Newsweek, makes this a truly amazing event, and a news story in and of itself. At last, the truth about our President and his agenda are starting to trickle through the “protective wall” built around him by the liberal media. ___________________________ I Too Have Become Disillusioned. By Matt Patterson (columnist - Washington Post, New York Post, San Francisco Examiner) Years from now, historians may regard the 2008 election of Barack Obama as an inscrutable and disturbing phenomenon, the result of a baffling breed of mass hysteria akin perhaps to the witch craze of the Middle Ages. How, they will wonder, did a man so devoid of professional accomplishment beguile so many into thinking he could manage the world's largest economy, direct the world's most powerful military, execute the world's most consequential job? Imagine a future historian examining Obama's pre-presidential life: ushered into and through the Ivy League, despite unremarkable grades and test scores along the way; a cushy non-job as a "community organizer;" a brief career as a state legislator devoid of legislative achievement (and in fact nearly devoid of his attention, so often did he vote "present"); and finally an unaccomplished single term in the United States Senate, the entirety of which was devoted to his presidential ambitions. He left no academic legacy in academia, authored no signature legislation as a legislator. And then there is the matter of his troubling associations: the white-hating, America-loathing preacher who for decades served as Obama's "spiritual mentor"; a real-life, actual terrorist who served as Obama's colleague and political sponsor. It is easy to imagine a future historian looking at it all and asking: how on Earth was such a man elected president? Not content to wait for history, the incomparable Norman Podhoretz addressed the question recently in the Wall Street Journal: To be sure, no white candidate who had close associations with an outspoken hater of America like Jeremiah Wright and an unrepentant terrorist like Bill Ayers, would have lasted a single day. But because Mr. Obama was black, and therefore entitled in the eyes of liberal Dom to have hung out with protesters against various American injustices, even if they were a bit extreme, he was given a pass. Let that sink in: Obama was given a pass - held to a lower standard - because of the color of his skin. Podhoretz continues: And in any case, what did such ancient history matter when he was also so articulate and elegant and (as he himself had said) "non-threatening," all of which gave him a fighting chance to become the first black president and thereby to lay the curse of racism to rest? Podhoretz puts his finger, I think, on the animating pulse of the Obama phenomenon - affirmative action. Not in the legal sense, of course. But certainly in the motivating sentiment behind all affirmative action laws and regulations, which are designed primarily to make white people, and especially white liberals, feel good about themselves. Unfortunately, minorities often suffer so that whites can pat themselves on the back. Liberals routinely admit minorities to schools for which they are not qualified, yet take no responsibility for the inevitable poor performance and high drop-out rates which follow. Liberals don't care if these minority students fail; liberals aren't around to witness the emotional devastation and deflated self-esteem resulting from the racist policy that is affirmative action. Yes, racist. Holding someone to a separate standard merely because of the color of his skin - that's affirmative action in a nutshell, and if that isn't racism, then nothing is. And that is what America did to Obama. True, Obama himself was never troubled by his lack of achievements, but why would he be? As many have noted, Obama was told he was good enough for Columbia despite undistinguished grades at Occidental; he was told he was good enough for the US Senate despite a mediocre record in Illinois ; he was told he was good enough to be president despite no record at all in the Senate. All his life, every step of the way, Obama was told he was good enough for the next step, in spite of ample evidence to the contrary. What could this breed if not the sort of empty narcissism on display every time Obama speaks? In 2008, many who agreed that he lacked executive qualifications nonetheless raved about Obama's oratory skills, intellect, and cool character. Those people - conservatives included - ought now to be deeply embarrassed. The man thinks and speaks in the hoariest of clichés, and that's when he has his Teleprompters in front of him; when the prompter is absent he can barely think or speak at all. Not one original idea has ever issued from his mouth - it's all warmed-over Marxism of the kind that has failed over and over again for 100 years. And what about his character? Obama is constantly blaming anything and everything else for his troubles. Bush did it; it was bad luck; I inherited this mess. Remember, he wanted the job, campaigned for the task. It is embarrassing to see a president so willing to advertise his own powerlessness, so comfortable with his own incompetence. But really, what were we to expect? The man has never been responsible for anything, so how do we expect him to act responsibly? In short: our president is a small-minded man, with neither the temperament nor the intellect to handle his job. When you understand that, and only when you understand that, will the current erosion of liberty and prosperity make sense. It could not have gone otherwise with such a man in the Oval Office.</Msg><Username>foretherun</Username><Timestamp>1351483407148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 00:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351494441362-2</Id><Topic><Title>interesting rumor from benzinga msft to offer 90 dls a share for nflx!</Title><Username>terry_mcowen</Username><Timestamp>1351467369033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 19:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are no market makers for nflx???</Msg><Username>shorthound</Username><Timestamp>1351494441362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 03:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351525034408-3</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe it is premature to conclude that Google's is stumbling with secular migration from desktops to tablets. Far from it. In my opinion, Google has the right initiatives to prosper in the mobile markets.</Msg><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1351525034408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 11:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351530359829-4</Id><Title>Ss grupenfuhuer Herman Otto FEGELEIN...</Title><Msg>Responsible for deaths of 17000 Js in Belorussian Pripyat swamps. Shot for desertion 1945 Eva Braun brother in law Nuf said.. Z</Msg><Username>taratara144</Username><Timestamp>1351530359829</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351530852299-5</Id><Topic><Title>ANALYST Predicts Decline To $ 685!!!! SEE REPORT</Title><Username>danwilliam291</Username><Timestamp>1350578884360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 12:48:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report</Msg><Username>darkstockss</Username><Timestamp>1351530852299</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351530991162-6</Id><Title>vrng vs goog</Title><Msg>Trial should go to the jury by Wed. I think GOOG will settle before that! What do you GOOG folks think?</Msg><Username>rtbigger</Username><Timestamp>1351530991162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351531290684-7</Id><Topic><Title>vrng</Title><Username>golfmanthree</Username><Timestamp>1351434554232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 10:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think GOOG will settle or more likley buy VRNG for all the patents. My guess it doesn't go to the jury.</Msg><Username>rtbigger</Username><Timestamp>1351531290684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351532700179-8</Id><Topic><Title>googs employees ratting on them in vringo case</Title><Username>audsct97</Username><Timestamp>1351277814207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:56:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better talk to your BOD, this is going to cost u alottttt</Msg><Username>golfmanthree</Username><Timestamp>1351532700179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351533071312-9</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With NY today</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1351533071312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 13:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351536589981-10</Id><Topic><Title>ANALYST Predicts Decline To $ 685!!!! SEE REPORT</Title><Username>danwilliam291</Username><Timestamp>1350578884360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 12:48:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great news!</Msg><Username>munsontom537</Username><Timestamp>1351536589981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351536675317-11</Id><Topic><Title>googs employees ratting on them in vringo case</Title><Username>audsct97</Username><Timestamp>1351277814207</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-26 14:56:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatz BOD mean.</Msg><Username>audsct97</Username><Timestamp>1351536675317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351537195654-12</Id><Title>700+ on Wednesday. The new Ipad killer is here...</Title><Msg>Nexus 10 baby... watch for upgrades all over this ...</Msg><Username>enoughps</Username><Timestamp>1351537195654</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 14:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351544877090-13</Id><Title>hottest stock of the month!!</Title><Msg>TAGG</Msg><Username>c_alex_p</Username><Timestamp>1351544877090</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 17:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351548276264-14</Id><Title>hi</Title><Msg>hi</Msg><Username>willosjack</Username><Timestamp>1351548276264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1351548458176-15</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG board claims early victory GOOG support $550</Title><Username>borbys7</Username><Timestamp>1351448101945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-28 14:15:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u better listen to him</Msg><Username>golfmanthree</Username><Timestamp>1351548458176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 18:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351559985572-16</Id><Title>obam stocks</Title><Msg>The Obama and Romney camps made some last-minute pitches and attacks Monday before cancelling events through Tuesday as Hurricane</Msg><Username>c_alex_p</Username><Timestamp>1351559985572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 21:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1351566443852-17</Id><Title>GOOGLE TOTALLY SUCKS...they are a part of the entire media machine that is protecting obama</Title><Msg>and all the crooks in the white house...NO MENTION OF BENGHAZI!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!.....they watched in real time while these 4 americans died then went to sleep.....then lied about it for weeks and still dont have their story straight.....jail time for all involved for withholding evidence!!!!!!</Msg><Username>cakillac777</Username><Timestamp>1351566443852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-29 23:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>