<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188468268-1</Id><Topic><Title>FTC’s Summer Grilling Menu: Google Guys</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1339191225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-06-08 17:33:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The finding shows that environmental exposures can be used to uncover novel candidate genes in complex phenotypes. It also shows that genes may work via the environment to shape the IQ, helping to close the nature versus nurture debate. Moderation of breastfeeding effects on the IQ by genetic variation in fatty acid metabolism Avshalom Caspi, Benjamin Williams, ... Medical Research Council Social, Genetic, and Developmental Psychiatry Centre, Institute of Psychiatry, King’s College London, London SE5 8AF, England; Edited by William T. Greenough, University of Illinois at Urbana–Champaign, Urbana, IL, and approved October 9, 2007 (received for review May 14, 2007) Children’s intellectual development is influenced by both genetic inheritance and environmental experiences. Breastfeeding is one of the earliest such postnatal experiences. Breastfed children attain higher IQ scores than children not fed breast milk, presumably because of the fatty acids uniquely available in breast milk. Here we show that the association between breastfeeding and IQ is moderated by a genetic variant in FADS2, a gene involved in the genetic control of fatty acid pathways. We confirmed this gene– environment interaction in two birth cohorts, and we ruled out alternative explanations of the finding involving gene–exposure correlation, intrauterine growth, social class, and maternal cognitive ability, as well as maternal genotype effects on breastfeeding and breast milk. The finding shows that environmental exposures can be used to uncover novel candidate genes in complex phenotypes. It also shows that genes may work via the environment to shape the IQ, helping to close the nature versus nurture debate. ---------------- A connection with our distant past may be revealed in these fatty acids since some are also prominent in fish oils and present in human milk in trace amounts.The human cerebrum does not exist in isolation, but in close proximity to the cerebellum, or literally small brain. Communication occurs between both tissues and the remit of the cerebellum was once thought to be merely an exercise in fine-tuning of incoming electrical impulses. It is now known that the cerebellum is more complex and undertakes many other important tasks. It too can be subdivided into cortical and white matter regions, the delineation being less precise than in the cerebrum. In evolutionary terms the cerebellum, in predating the cerebrum, is more primitive with a faster rate of maturation. Less than one-tenth the size of the cerebrum, the cerebellum accumulates fatty acids in similar proportions, a process which was also compromised in infants receiving artificial milks omitting DHA. Despite requiring lesser amounts, relative reductions in cerebellar membrane DHA were equivalent to those in the cerebrum.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344188468268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344189911227-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Interim MF distorting Hantro ownership as of June 2006???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343961875237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 22:44:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HOW could ON2 Interim MF clain to be Hantro's chairman in June 2006 when: By chocofanta . 1 year 11 months ago REHASH 2: It is about ON2 &amp; Google andThanks to Bornie By chocofanta . 1 year 11 months ago . Permalink Who from ON2's BOD introduced WR Hambrecht to the BOD? ----On December 20, 2006, On2’... Who from ON2's BOD introduced WR Hambrecht to the BOD? ----On December 20, 2006, On2’s board of directors engaged WR Hambrecht &amp; Co. (“Hambrecht”) to act as its financial advisor in connection with a proposed transaction with Hantro. page 43 from Google/ON2 proxy ver 1 ------In the course of On2’s business, representatives of On2 regularly engage in discussions with existing and potential customers, market participants, content distributors and others regarding its products, technology and the video codec industry generally. Since 2005, when On2 licensed On2’s Flix Engine product to Google, representatives of On2 have from time to time had informal discussions with representatives of Google regarding On2’s technology and products. Page 39 from Hanto/ON2 Proxy Transaction Background and Timeline In 2005, employees of On2 and Hantro began to discuss cross-licensing their respective technologies. During the fall of 2006, several of On2’s marketing personnel met with representatives of Hantro to further investigate possible business transactions between the two companies. As a result of those discussions, on October 25, 2006, Bill Joll, On2’s chief executive officer, traveled to Helsinki, Finland, where he met with Eero Kaikkonen, Hantro’s chief executive officer, and Pekka Salonoja, a director of Hantro, to discuss a potential business relationship. In that meeting, Mr. Joll, Mr. Kaikkonen and Mr. Salonoja discussed the potential acquisition of Hantro by On2, without discussing any principal terms or conditions. On October 25, 2006, Mr. Joll presented to On2’s board of directors the possibility of a business combination and briefly outlined the principal benefits of an acquisition of Hantro and its subsidiary. The board instructed Mr. Joll to report to the Executive Committee of the board on a regular basis with respect to any discussions with Hantro’s representatives. Mr. Joll made a presentation to the Executive Committee of On2’s board at its meeting held on December 1, 2006. At the meeting, he outlined the advantages and disadvantages of a potential business combination with Hantro. The Executive Committee authorized Mr. Joll to proceed with negotiations with Hantro and its principals and approved the principal terms of the On2 offer. On2 sent its initial written offer to the Hantro security holders and their financial advisors on December 8, 2006. The written offer comprised a draft letter agreement pursuant to which On2 would hold exclusive rights to pursue an acquisition transaction with Hantro and a proposed summary of principal terms and conditions proposed for the transaction. In the summary of terms, On2 proposed that Hantro would merge with a to-be-formed Finnish subsidiary of On2 and that shareholders of Hantro would receive 50,372,567 shares of On2’s common stock in the merger, representing 30% of On2’s issued and outstanding shares post-transaction. Page 40 of Hantro/ON2 proxy: Opinion of On2’s Board’s Financial Advisor Overview On December 20, 2006, On2’s board of directors engaged WR Hambrecht &amp; Co. (“Hambrecht”) to act as its financial advisor in connection with a proposed transaction with Hantro. William A. Newman On November 19, 2008, William A. Newman resigned from On2's Board of Directors, effective that same day.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344189911227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344190765415-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Google "merger" from different "angle"?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1337797551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-05-23 14:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>adding Mani Aliabadi 1) Salar Kamangar, CEO of YouTube Google dispatched one of its longtime employees, Salar Kamangar, to help Hurley [Youtube CEO at the time] steer YouTube in 2008. 2) Amin Zoufonoun, director of corporate development at Google, has been hired away by Facebook to lead its mergers and acquisitions team, Amin Zoufonoun work included leading some of these deals in the U.S. and internationally, including On2, ... Amin Zoufonoun's Summary: Corporate Development, primarily strategic initiatives and partnerships, and the evaluation, negotiation and execution of mergers, acquisitions and investments 3) Mike Jazayeri, Google's director of product management for WebM 4) Afsaneh Naimollah, BOD of On2 Technologies, Inc. Ms. Naimollah has been the Managing Partner of Chela Capital Partners, a mergers and acquisition advisory firm that she founded. 5) Homa Zaryouni in New York ??? FT Reporter: "An Adobe takeover of On2 has been speculation for some time, the insider said. “We do from time to time hear from third parties that a company is interested in On2,” the insider added." 6) Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development Mar. 18, 2009 Woodside will be VP-Americas Operations, reporting to Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development. May 22, 2012 Google, which made the deal to gain access to Motorola's vast trove of technology patents, said on Tuesday that Motorola Chief Executive Sanjay Jha has stepped down and has been succeeded by Dennis Woodside, former president of Google's Americas region. 7) Mob of "mobs" is the "bridge" but not like a chess game even if its Page might be the same while it's "flashing" under this "digit" is NOT as pretending to be part of a WHOLE after all the HOLE might be part of it but still is NOT uniform any how! 8) Mani Aliabadi Mani Aliabadi General Counsel, Widevine Technologies, Inc Mani Aliabadi serves as General Counsel of Widevine Technologies Inc. Mr. Aliabadi joined Widevine in March 2005 as the head of Widevine's legal department focused on corporate and intellectual property law. At Widevine, Mr. Aliabadi leads a legal group responsible for the management and oversight of corporate governance, mergers/acquisitions, business development activities, intellectual property protection and licensing, regulatory compliance, risk and litigation management. ------------- On2, Widevine Collaborate on Securing Flash Video Platform By Patrick Hoffman 2007-04-13 On2 Technologies and Widevine have partnered to provide consumers with digital rights management capabilities, allowing users to protect the distribution and use of content on Adobe's Flash Video Player 8 and 9. --------- WideVine: Google overpaid offered to buy the company for $150 million [in cash]</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344190765415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344194626697-4</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to Buy VRNG Patents and Ruin Google?</Title><Username>vrnger</Username><Timestamp>1343592802826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo blocking this report from 2003 for OBVIOUS reasons??? Lycos joins Google’s AdSense Network« Previous Article Posted By Hollis Thomases on Sep 30th, 2003 “With the addition of Lycos, Google continues to add quality properties to the Google AdSense program,” said Omid Kordestani, senior vice president of Google’s Worldwide Sales and Field Operations. “As well as providing Lycos with an additional revenue opportunity and an enhanced experience for their users, Google enables its advertisers to reach some of the most valuable audiences on the web.”</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344194626697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344194777911-5</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG/AAPL correlation</Title><Username>tomsongarry</Username><Timestamp>1343280708626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 01:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Fiber: AT&amp;T and Verizon have used government to create a shared monopoly covering both wireless and wireline service. But there's a cloud on their profitable horizon. The Google Cloud.</Msg><Username>wine_bread</Username><Timestamp>1344194777911</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 15:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>