<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344265362329-1</Id><Title>Vringo &amp; AOL and WHY Yahoo REMOVING the PUBLIC reports?</Title><Msg>Criminal intent on Yahoo ADMIN to remove public report to HIDE the LEGAL case AGAINST ...</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344265362329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344265702658-2</Id><Topic><Title>Vringo &amp; AOL and WHY Yahoo REMOVING the PUBLIC reports?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344265362329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo ADMIN REMOVING the public reports related to Google: Is it why they MOVED Google as Yashoo CEO??? Is USA government running Google and Yahoo? The MOVING is JUST a NORMAL USA goverment operation to keep their agents in "safe" hands? August 6, 2012 AOL Agrees to Settle Part of Vringo Patent Case By Ben Fox Rubin</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344265702658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344266370668-3</Id><Topic><Title>casp321</Title><Username>geeezer00</Username><Timestamp>1289358789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-11-09 22:13:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: casp321 By casp321 . 1 year 9 months ago . Permalink Does it worth to SELL a NATION to $30,000 per plate/person "donation"??? ---Pre... Does it worth to SELL a NATION to $30,000 per plate/person "donation"??? ---President Obama went to the home of Google executive Marissa Mayer for a $30,000-per-person Democratic Party fundraiser." Watchdog wants probe of Google's 'unusually close' ties to Obama By Sara Jerome - 11/09/10 After Google admitted last month that it collected and stored private user information, including passwords and entire e-mails, from Wi-Fi networks,</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344266370668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:19:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344266450583-4</Id><Topic><Title>Vringo &amp; AOL and WHY Yahoo REMOVING the PUBLIC reports?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344265362329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:02:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: casp321 By casp321 . 1 year 9 months ago . Permalink Does it worth to SELL a NATION to $30,000 per plate/person "donation"??? ---Pre... Does it worth to SELL a NATION to $30,000 per plate/person "donation"??? ---President Obama went to the home of Google executive Marissa Mayer for a $30,000-per-person Democratic Party fundraiser." Watchdog wants probe of Google's 'unusually close' ties to Obama By Sara Jerome - 11/09/10 After Google admitted last month that it collected and stored private user information, including passwords and entire e-mails, from Wi-Fi networks, ------------ Marissa Mayer Moving around those like T. Armstrong, from Google to become ALO CEO, and Marrisa Mayer, from Google to become Yahoo CEO, and ...? To keep them in the "safe" houses? In what price? Why in the Expenses of those companies shareholders investments instead of USA government paying them what they are doing for them?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344266450583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344268458441-5</Id><Title>group of FEW billionaires ROBBING small companies shareholders</Title><Msg>A group of FEW billionaires ROBBING small companies shareholders by paying a few dollars or million to a few technical staff or BOD, or execs in those companies...??? Then they DESIGNATE a few TRUSTED indivuduals as EXECs or CEO ofthese companies while provideng the "legal" PROTECTION by moving them around when they are EXPOSED of when their operation/activities are under other USA or European agencies are under investigation: To give example of small companies: ON2 and Vringo Hambrecht, Schmidt, Wendell, Doerr, Armstrong, Cuban, Icahn, of course I can say who is who but their ACTIVITES regarding ON2 need to be INVESTIGATED, if you have not started yet???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344268458441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344268640932-6</Id><Topic><Title>group of FEW billionaires ROBBING small companies shareholders</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344268458441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had to create different Page for P.P. to keep its "sound" in different Page should it have any: Paul P. husband of Congresswoman Nancy P.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344268640932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 11:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344271935243-7</Id><Topic><Title>MSFT to Buy VRNG Patents and Ruin Google?</Title><Username>vrnger</Username><Timestamp>1343592802826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:13:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you might find a few or one or two or ... of these involved in ON2 and vringo through different "rings" or "links" directly or indirectly. Just check their relations: in BOD assignment, in stock shares exchanging of a company, or having few TRUSTED CTOs or EXECs "planted" WITHING a company for a few dollars or a little more against BILLIONS of those companoies shareholders INVESTMENTs: Hambrecht, Schmidt, Wendell, Doerr, Armstrong, Cuban, Icahn, of course I can say who is who but their ACTIVITES regarding ON2 need to be INVESTIGATED, if you have not started yet??? Equity Briefing: AOL Settles Vringo Patent Suit Press Release: Equity Briefing – 1 hour 39 minutes ago According to public filings, AOL has settled on their own Patent infringement suit with Vringo, Inc.(VRNG) but still remains a defendant in the Litigation against Google. Now that the merger is complete, expert damages reports are expected to be filed with the court any day. According to several publications, a settlement in favor of Vringo could be worth hundreds of millions of dollars in while a win could top over into the billions of dollars, but investors will have to wait until October 16, 2012 when Vringo is scheduled to go to trial on the larger case.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344271935243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 12:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344272755632-8</Id><Topic><Title>either FED news leaked ..or this will end very badly for market</Title><Username>mrpopcorna</Username><Timestamp>1343415633452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 15:00:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>took one? not sure what you mean?</Msg><Username>mrpopcorna</Username><Timestamp>1344272755632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 13:05:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344275490134-9</Id><Title>Reversal at hand? Thoughts? Opinions?</Title><Msg>Nasdaq breaks 2994 I think yes?</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1344275490134</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 13:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344277914610-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG/AAPL correlation</Title><Username>tomsongarry</Username><Timestamp>1343280708626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 01:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google is outspending Apple by more than two times in research and development, which will result in new products to promote continued growth.</Msg><Username>cris.chest</Username><Timestamp>1344277914610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 14:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344279472000-11</Id><Title>...WHAT just happened with stock-price DROP ??</Title><Msg>ANy news for fall ?</Msg><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1344279472000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 14:57:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344280987000-12</Id><Title>YouTube thrown out of Apple phone.</Title><Msg>Sell Goog</Msg><Username>robo_lexington</Username><Timestamp>1344280987000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344282597153-13</Id><Title>nice going longs.... I was wrong</Title><Msg>limited my losses.... with the battle between Apple and Google now underway I'm going to put my money on Apple to win in the long run... no more short term trading Google... just stockpile leaps and see how long takes for the effects of lost Apple revenue (via fees for maps and apps) and other lost revenue directly or indirectly related to Apple begins to impact Google... way to go for now longs... see you on the other side.... thanks for the fun ride..... goog luck...</Msg><Username>cardizemcd</Username><Timestamp>1344282597153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344288542586-14</Id><Topic><Title>nice going longs.... I was wrong</Title><Username>cardizemcd</Username><Timestamp>1344282597153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:49:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the MAN... I like that when somebody accepts that he was wrong. I for one traded on the +ve side of GOOG. Was heavily in Red a few weeks back but cut down all of my losses due to the upswing of GOOG. Got out today though still under loss.</Msg><Username>ramas1964</Username><Timestamp>1344288542586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 17:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344288867088-15</Id><Topic><Title>Google Settlement Could Drive Vringo Shares Above $30 - google search this !!!</Title><Username>mcuban2017</Username><Timestamp>1343998361782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 08:52:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i like the way you're thinking mcuban! I've only got 1500 shares, but hey at $70 that's over $100,000 Love the way that sounds!!!! Good luck VRNG!!!!!!</Msg><Username>billypecosbilly</Username><Timestamp>1344288867088</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 17:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344290258036-16</Id><Title>Google canceled the youtube deal not apple</Title><Msg>was misreported</Msg><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1344290258036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 17:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344292102790-17</Id><Topic><Title>nice going longs.... I was wrong</Title><Username>cardizemcd</Username><Timestamp>1344282597153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:49:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no problem admitting I was wrong.... didn't think the company's earnings would be as strong... didn't/doesn't add up right to me.... today the stock had a really hard time cracking 650.. will watch it for a few days... if it can't get over the hump I'll get back in buying puts for December/Jan... and some way of the money leaps.... Google going to war with Apple can't be good for Google... (see RIMM, Dell, Nokia, etc).... I have made a lot of money and lost a lot of money trading... it's all part the game.. have no problem admitting I was wrong (no am I shy about being right!!)... good luck with your investments... (just search cardizemcd on the yahoo message boards.. I have been at this for awhile...)..</Msg><Username>cardizemcd</Username><Timestamp>1344292102790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:28:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344292916123-18</Id><Title>Obvious</Title><Msg>Everything-You-Need-to-Know-About-Vringo-VRNG-Versus-Google-GOOG/s/via/1789/article/view/p/mid/3/id/196/</Msg><Username>larry_boe</Username><Timestamp>1344292916123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344293671360-19</Id><Topic><Title>UFL Forms Historic Partnership With YouTube</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1298402856000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-02-22 14:27:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As far as I could do provide you ENOUGH links and related CONNECTIONs, BOD, CTOs, EXECs, for you to go after and INVESTIGATE should you want to follow the LAW if NOT, still I have the CORE lists for you. You can NOT sweep them under the rug even if you extend beyond NY: Hambrecht, Schmidt, Wendell, Doerr, Armstrong, Cuban, Icahn, of course I can not say who is who but their ACTIVITES regarding ON2 need to be INVESTIGATED, if you have not started yet???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344293671360</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:54:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344297126100-20</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG: This is something interesting, your thoughts</Title><Username>theclick5842</Username><Timestamp>1343779790790</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:09:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No doubt this is the best site for GOOG</Msg><Username>tammy6285</Username><Timestamp>1344297126100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 19:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344304937235-21</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Google "merger" from different "angle"?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1337797551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-05-23 14:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a difference one make the WORLD proud of him another sells the world for a penny or so: You did NOT have be too cheap to deal with ON2 shareholders the way you did, BUT at least be PROUD of one of your very own who has TOTALLY different mentality from what you own. What a GREAT difference one can make ...to make EVERYONE proud of him. Why you could not, at least pretend, to be like him instead of involving on two sides of the isle? 2012/08/06 NASA's Mohawk Guy marvels at newfound fame ... and Mars mission It's been a crazy 24 hours for flight director Bobak Ferdowsi, and not just because he and the rest of his team at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory landed an SUV on Mars. Bobak Ferdowsi, a flight director for the Mars Science Laboratory Curiosity mission, piqued the public's curiosity with his unique style. NBC's Brian Williams reports.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1344304937235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344309222970-22</Id><Topic><Title>nice going longs.... I was wrong</Title><Username>cardizemcd</Username><Timestamp>1344282597153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 15:49:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG hasn't been able to trade above $650 for more than two days since 2008. This could be the top once again.</Msg><Username>rodgwag</Username><Timestamp>1344309222970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 23:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344310657840-23</Id><Title>CRM starting to warm up still 40 points off 52 week high b4 earnings aug 17th</Title><Msg>Look at this picture ok. AMZN and PCLN looking like they might be losing steam AAPL and GOOG could have a pullback or a shakeout. Meanwhile CRM is just now warming up for that Aug 17th conference call. You have all the way to the 17th (earnings for CRM) to really load and build up a position because earnings are going to blowout and send CRM to between 220 and 240! Goog and aapl could both pullback, not saying they for sure will but it could easily happen, meanwhile my software has confirmed selling in 4 different sectors and 90% of that money flow going into the cloud software sector. It has seemed in the past that when money goes in the cloud sector stocks, it seems to go in everytime all at once over a 6-8 week period!</Msg><Username>dramatic_move_up</Username><Timestamp>1344310657840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 23:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>