<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353409782211-1</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S&amp;P has raised its rating on Google's debt to AA from AA-, with a stable outlook.</Msg><Username>bakert82</Username><Timestamp>1353409782211</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 06:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353418840360-2</Id><Topic><Title>(CASP 321) New ON2 info to the previous owners of ON2 Technologies</Title><Username>docalan55</Username><Timestamp>1348087684719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:48:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Docalan!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353418840360</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353419441777-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2's "lead" "plaintiffs" and ON2 defendants?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1281513126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-08-11 03:52:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Abandonment Notice! On Monday, November 12, 2012, status on the HANTRO trademark changed to ABANDONED - NO STATEMENT OF USE FILED. Apply Now for this name starting at $159! ---Terri Chen, Chief Trademark Counsel who trademarked HANTRO on April 2, 2008. ---Michelle K. Lee Top Patent Lawyers Leave Google, By Amy Miller July 24, 2012 Lee arrived at Google in 2003, before its IPO, after spending seven years at Fenwick &amp; West advising high-tech companies on IP and patent matters. Under Lee, Google's patent department has grown from a handful of people to a team of about 70 as its portfolio of patents went from a few to thousands. Lee has been credited with a key role in strategic patent acquisitions, such as Google's $12.5 billion acquisition of Motorola Mobility and its patent assets in August.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419441777</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:50:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353419886392-4</Id><Title>ON2 Shareholders: I want you know it too!</Title><Msg>From VRNG Yahoo Board: Re: Re: Re: Re: Re: ON2's two CTOs and Interim CEO sold ON2 for million or so $ but Vringo has EXCELLENT counsels in the house By casp321 . Nov 19, 2012 12:30 PM Thanks Trustme_1st! Usuall I try not to engage with anyone into these kinds of detail discussion, but since I did not see mean spirit in Alafrikan discussion and it was interesting to know how a meaning of a word, misspelled, would give wrong impression to someone with lack of exposure to the subject, in this case spelling Shams as Shems, I appreciated his making that clear to me. Getting oneself into discussion of subjects such Google/Yahoo providing Iranian accounts to Iranian secret agencies and Iran-USA-Hostages in 1979-1981 or CIA activitities in Beirut and didgging out those presumed involved and displaying the results in a scratch and public blog like Yahoo Board is a dangerous game zone to get into and there might not be pleasant outcome once someone entering into these kind of territories. Since it's became interesting discussion I'l give you the reasons why I had to bring up those subjects to open and cause myself trouble. ON2 shareholders were bringing up different public informations or their understanding about how Google, ON2's Interim, ON2's BOD and some others from Google, Adobe, ..., screwed up ON2 shareholders and there should be justice about it. At some point one or more of ON2 bashers were using different name game to hide the real intention and real players from different companies. Interestingly enough one of ON2 bashers called ON2 shareholders "terrorists" on GOOG Yahoo scratch Board and asked Page in that text not to "give-in" their "demands". Why would a basher call a shareholder or shareholders of a public company terrrorists, after all these are stock market that one will gain in the expenses of the others without any blood being shed. Sensing the activities of different bashers, handles appearing/disappearing on the Borad, I felt some of the bashers possibly were looking for, and had interest in, something other than the given stocks, say google ot ON2, they possibly were reading Pages beyond a single one but how could that be possible? I do nOT believe there is any thing called privacy and anything I do on this scratch board is BEING monitored and controled but why would they let some use private information to walk on a scratch Board is something made me bring up more of their scam to let them know that calling a shareholders a "terrorist" because he might be from Iran would cOST them more than they could IMGINE. How dumb their intention and activities was is beyond me. My simplre question is why they let a simple minded peolpe run their "intelligence operation? Being Iranian does not mean anything unless someone is trying to HIDE their cRIMINAL intenion to make is complicated as it should NOT be. ????????? Reagan, Bush, Casey, Shackley, Buckley, Secord, Hakim, Ghorbanifar, Ghotbzadeh, Rafsanjan, Mousavi, Kangarlou, Nabavi, Robert Gate, North, Poindexter, Mcfarlane, .... Reneades "Out of Bush", but who'll be "In the Bush?" By casp321 . Nov 3, 2011 7:16 AM Reneades "Out of Bush", but who'll be "In the Bush?" Why they are using the same plan in the bush and then calling it "renegate" out of the bush?? ---John Warnock Hinckley, Jr...."renegade brother in the family" ---Osama has been the family's shame, as if some renegade Rockefeller decided to become a terrorist. ---------- John Warnock Hinckley, Jr., (born May 29, 1955) attempted to assassinate U.S. President Ronald Reagan in Washington, D.C., on March 30, 1981,... According to the March 31, 1981, edition of the Houston Post, and reported by AP, UPI, NBC News and Newsweek, Hinckley is the son of one of George H.W. Bush's political and financial supporters in his 1980 presidential primary campaign against Ronald Reagan; Associated Press published the following on March 31, 1981: Sharon Bush, Neil's wife, said Scott Hinckley was coming to their house as a date of a girl friend of hers. "I don't even know the brother. From what I know and I've heard, they (the Hinckleys) are a very nice family and have given a lot of money to the Bush campaign. I understand he was just the renegade brother in the family. They must feel awful," she said. ----------------------- It is alleged that President Reagan sent Silberman in the fall of 1980 to make sure the Iranians weren’t planning to give up the US hostages taken at the American embassy, thus creating an "October surprise" that would help reelect Jimmy Carter. Silberman was rewarded for his role in Iran with the judgeship that later allowed him to overturn the conviction of Oliver North for his role in the Iran-Contra affair. ----------------------- Re: You dumaz: mark it with one-star??? By casp321 . Oct 13, 2011 7:37 AM October 1980: Osama’s Oldest Brother Allegedly Involved in ‘October Surprise’ Salem bin Laden, Osama’s oldest brother, described by a French secret intelligence report as one of two closest friends of Saudi Arabia’s King Fahd who often performs important missions for Saudi Arabia, is involved in secret Paris meetings between US and Iranian emissaries this month, according to a French report. Frontline, which published the French report, notes that such meetings have never been confirmed. Rumors of these meetings have been called the “October Surprise” and some have speculated that in these meetings, George H. W. Bush negotiated a delay to the release of the US hostages in Iran, thus helping Ronald Reagan and Bush win the 1980 Presidential election. All of this is highly speculative, but if the French report is correct, it points to a long-standing connection of highly improper behavior between the Bush and bin Laden families. [PBS Frontline, ==================== Re: Re: ON2's two CTOs and Interim CEO sold ON2 for million or so $ but Vringo has EXCELLENT counsels in the house By casp321 . Nov 19, 2012 9:55 AM Iranian descendants involved on Google side DIRECTLY/INDIRECTLY: Re: Re: Re: RE: ON2 Lawsuits in August 2009 and Google/Youtube EXECs departures from August to Dec 2009 By casp321 . Oct 20, 2012 5:47 PM . Permalink . Go to topic 1) Salar Kamangar, CEO of YouTube Google dispatched one of its longtime employees, Salar K... 1) Salar Kamangar, CEO of YouTube Google dispatched one of its longtime employees, Salar Kamangar, to help Hurley [Youtube CEO at the time] steer YouTube in 2008. 2) Amin Zoufonoun, director of corporate development at Google, has been hired away by Facebook to lead its mergers and acquisitions team, Amin Zoufonoun work included leading some of these deals in the U.S. and internationally, including On2, ... Amin Zoufonoun's Summary: Corporate Development, primarily strategic initiatives and partnerships, and the evaluation, negotiation and execution of mergers, acquisitions and investments 3) Mike Jazayeri, Google's director of product management for WebM 4) Afsaneh Naimollah, BOD of On2 Technologies, Inc. Ms. Naimollah has been the Managing Partner of Chela Capital Partners, a mergers and acquisition advisory firm that she founded. 5) Homa Zaryouni in New York ??? FT Reporter: "An Adobe takeover of On2 has been speculation for some time, the insider said. “We do from time to time hear from third parties that a company is interested in On2,” the insider added." 6) Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development Mar. 18, 2009 Woodside will be VP-Americas Operations, reporting to Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development. May 22, 2012 Google, which made the deal to gain access to Motorola's vast trove of technology patents, said on Tuesday that Motorola Chief Executive Sanjay Jha has stepped down and has been succeeded by Dennis Woodside, former president of Google's Americas region. 7) Mob of "mobs" is the "bridge" but not like a chess game even if its Page might be the same while it's "flashing" under this "digit" is NOT as pretending to be part of a WHOLE after all the HOLE might be part of it but still is NOT uniform any how! 8) Mani Aliabadi Mani Aliabadi General Counsel, Widevine Technologies, Inc Mani Aliabadi serves as General Counsel of Widevine Technologies Inc. Mr. Aliabadi joined Widevine in March 2005 as the head of Widevine's legal department focused on corporate and intellectual property law. At Widevine, Mr. Aliabadi leads a legal group responsible for the management and oversight of corporate governance, mergers/acquisitions, business development activities, intellectual property protection and licensing, regulatory compliance, risk and litigation management.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419886392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:58:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353422317873-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders: I want you know it too!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419886392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:58:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: A simple Q that U might've IGNORED 2 ASK: What did judge Leonardo BRING to judge Jackson TABLE? By casp321 . Nov 2, 2012 6:20 AM Re: Re: RE: ON2 Lawsuits in August 2009 and Google/Youtube EXECs departures from August to Dec 2009 By casp321 . Oct 20, 2012 5:12 PM March 15, 2011, 4:59 am Mergers &amp; Acquisitions | Revolving Door Facebook Said to Hire Google Executive for M.&amp;A. Amin Zoufonoun, director of corporate development at Google, has been hired away by Facebook to lead its mergers and acquisitions team ---Amin Zoufonoun work included leading some of these deals in the U.S. and internationally, including On2, -------- On April 2, 2009, the On2 board of directors met to discuss, among other things, Google’s oral indication of interest in a potential business combination. ---the On2 board of directors accepted Ms. Naimollah’s abstention/recusal proposal. The board of directors requested, however, that she continue to participate in discussions regarding any potential transaction with Google even though she would abstain from voting upon such a transaction. ----------------------- Omid R. Kordestani[5] is an Iranian-American businessman who works as Senior Advisor to Office of the CEO and Founders at Google.[6] Kordestani was the Senior Vice President for Worldwide Sales and Field Operations of Google until he stepped down on April 16, 2009 was Google's senior vice president of worldwide sales and field operations until April 16, 2009. He joined Google in May 1999, leading the development and implementation of the company’s initial business model. He played a part in Google's worldwide revenue generation efforts as well as the day-to-day operations of the company’s sales organization. ?????????????????????? spixleatedlifeform: ON2 Long shareholder; casp321 Re: ON2's "lead" "plaintiffs" and ON2 defendants? By spixleatedlifeform . Apr 11, 2011 5:28 AM [Start quote; I had to change what SPLF used to prevent text removal by Yahoo] Most of the "bashers" were right about On2's management and products. So, did that really make us bashers? I just called it like I saw it.[End quete] How interesting. Bashers, FUDsters, outright liars, mis-directors, obfuscationists, mis-interpreters, and all sorts of other miscreant boiler room hirelings had been harassing On2 shareholders on ONT message boards long before you came along. Considering they ran part and parcel to the illegal, destructive manipulation of On2's stock price, they are also guilty of aiding and abetting that illegal activity. SPLF ps. Gee, don't you just love it when year-old threads get revived? Kinda' like its own sort of Karma. Better hope you got a good legal team backing your employer. And they aren't cheap, either. Too bad they're going to lose in your defense. You have no idea what's going on behind the scenes and won't either, until they slap on the cuffs. Looking forward to the perp walk. It'll be historic. And long, too. Maybe even rival the crackdown on the mob. Maybe you ought to consider a lighter sentence by turning states' evidence and appealing to the mercy of the courts. They'll only consider the first few who do. The rest will do the full hard time. --------------------- docalan55: ON2 Long shareholder; casp321 Re: ON2's "lead" "plaintiffs" and ON2 defendants? By docalan55 . Apr 11, 2011 10:32 PM The other plaintiffs were led to believe that he was a major shareholder. He was represented by a major NY Attorney as I remember. Everything is still in the Just hands of the Court. No final outcome yet? Maybe Larry Page will make things right with On2 shareholders, he may have a conscience, remember do no evil. How about right a wrong. He has the opportunity as CEO to present a settlement to On2 holders. Do the right thing. Who knows time will tell. Best to all those who were On2 shareholders. ---------------- ON2 basher: Re: ON2's "lead" "plaintiffs" and ON2 defendants? By aintgottacover . Apr 12, 2011 8:16 AM "Maybe Larry Page will make things right with On2 shareholders" "He has the opportunity as CEO to present a settlement to On2 holders" HAHA! No, I don't think he'll give into terrorists demands.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353422317873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 09:38:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353422815419-6</Id><Topic><Title>ATTD October News,Distribution Agreement Announcement, 2200% GAINS POSSIBLE, UNDERVALUED, CHEAP@ 0.001 BUY,READ</Title><Username>greatpennies</Username><Timestamp>1351880194214</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-02 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Attd just announced it's product phase iii recovery drink is being sold by the largest &amp; biggest grocery chain in the whole country. quick buy in range 0.0007 to 0.00018. attd reminds me of monster drinks. It take a smart investors to see the potential here. this stock is a rare under the radar find. With just a few thousand bucks, a trader can own several millions of shares. this stock has the potential to make a lot of people rich like monster drinks did. please see most recent press release for recent major press release.</Msg><Username>bigprofittrade</Username><Timestamp>1353422815419</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 09:46:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353422821737-7</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders: I want you know it too!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419886392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:58:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This being human is a guest house. Every morning a new arrival. A joy, depression, a meanness, some momentary awareness comes as an unexpected visitor. Welcome and entertain them all! Even if they are a crowd of sorrows, who violently sweep your house empty of its furniture, still, treat each guest honorably. He may be clearing you out for some new delight. The dark thought, the shame, the malice, meet them at the door laughing, and invite them in. Be grateful for whoever comes, because each has been sent as a guide from beyond. Rumi</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353422821737</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 09:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353423847923-8</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders: I want you know it too!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419886392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:58:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How shame one can not name? "A Star Without a Name" Always in my mind. Appreciated! Don’t cry: “Woe, parted!” at my burial— For me, this is the time of joyful meeting! Don’t say “Farewell” when I’m put in the grave— It is a curtain for eternal grace (Diwan-i, 911). Rumi A Star Without a Name When a baby is taken from the wet nurse, it easily forgets her and starts eating solid food. Seeds feed awhile on ground, then lift up into the sun. So you should taste the filtered light and work your way toward wisdom with no personal covering. That's how you came here, like a star without a name. Move across the night sky with those anonymous lights. Rumi</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353423847923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353424182147-9</Id><Title>Back to $650 after options settlement which will happen today end of the day or tomorrow in the AM.</Title><Msg>Any thoughts on this scam?</Msg><Username>sharerahs</Username><Timestamp>1353424182147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:09:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353424476372-10</Id><Title>What do you think of todays BIDU move ?</Title><Msg>Also looks like Technicians taking GOOG to 687-690's</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1353424476372</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:14:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353424695622-11</Id><Title>and now you can trim if you caught that easy trade..gap waiting to be filled below</Title><Msg>how you are strong enough to hold on bull. will fill it</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1353424695622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:18:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353427458612-12</Id><Topic><Title>and now you can trim if you caught that easy trade..gap waiting to be filled below</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1353424695622</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:18:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hows it feel to know you bought the exact swing high?</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1353427458612</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 11:04:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353427814773-13</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Shareholders: I want you know it too!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353419886392</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 08:58:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are drunk and i'm intoxicated no one is around showing us the way home Again and again i told you drink less a cup or two I know in this city no one is sober one is worse than the other one is frenzied and the other gone mad Come on my friend step into the tavern of ruins taste the sweetness of life in the company of another friend Here you'll see at every corner someone intoxicated and the cup-bearer makes her rounds I went out of my house a drunkard came to me someone whose glance uncovered a hundred houses in paradise rocking and rolling he was a sail with no anchor but he was the envy of all those sober ones remaining on the shore Where are you from i asked he smiled in mockery and said one half from the east one half from the west one half made of water and earth one half made of heart and soul one half staying at the shores and one half nesting in a pearl I begged take me as your friend i am your next of kin he said i recognize no kin among strangers I left my belongings and entered this tavern i only have a chest full of words but can't utter a single one ~ Rumi Ghazal 2309 Translated by Nader Khalili Rumi, Fountain of Fire Cal-Earth, September 1994</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1353427814773</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 11:10:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353431137452-14</Id><Title>MCP</Title><Msg>..</Msg><Username>diamondsgold939</Username><Timestamp>1353431137452</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 12:05:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353434755989-15</Id><Topic><Title>Mannkind - MNKD - Next Blockbuster Drug to Treat Diabetes</Title><Username>smittysamigo</Username><Timestamp>1352223496673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 12:38:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy a few shares for the Afrezza approval run-up.</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1353434755989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 13:05:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353435964965-16</Id><Title>I really like why Bernanke just said</Title><Msg>He has no tools to save the economy if there is a FC. Our leaders in Washington must take it seriously to solve this serious issue that they have been busy to do campaigning ...I hope you are happy with Obama in the last four years.. Ms. Perosi as a leader??? Best joke in the world..cluless..cluless.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1353435964965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 13:26:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353437587376-17</Id><Topic><Title>I really like why Bernanke just said</Title><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1353435964965</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 13:26:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short term pain but they will have to come up with a solution especially what Obama said in Asia. He can not loose face, Buy on pullback.</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1353437587376</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 13:53:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353439956598-18</Id><Title>Basic pattern......</Title><Msg>Up 200 points, next day profit taking then buyers coming in and next day is continuation of retrace until ma-50 .. GOOG to $705. Like I said Berkanake tried to scare and push pressure to Obama....good!!!</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1353439956598</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 14:32:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353441559555-19</Id><Title>shorts are working hard to keep this stock down</Title><Msg>all day, but goog wants to go up. Shorts may give up and goog may pop going into closed.</Msg><Username>willoftexas</Username><Timestamp>1353441559555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 14:59:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353444756286-20</Id><Topic><Title>Back to $650 after options settlement which will happen today end of the day or tomorrow in the AM.</Title><Username>sharerahs</Username><Timestamp>1353424182147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 10:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the way to $650 and then $600....</Msg><Username>sharerahs</Username><Timestamp>1353444756286</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 15:52:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353454220075-21</Id><Title>Igt paid 115 mil 4 entraction- closes doors in record time</Title><Msg>Instead of learning from mistake They bet the house and double down Going to end badly When u give a female a platinum Amex And let her loose in a shoe store results r predictable Take a looksy at meg &amp; Hpq...</Msg><Username>taratara144</Username><Timestamp>1353454220075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 18:30:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353469634592-22</Id><Topic><Title>shorts are working hard to keep this stock down</Title><Username>willoftexas</Username><Timestamp>1353441559555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 14:59:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think you realize what you are looking at. What you are seeing is the Goldman market maker holding it above 665 area... It is trying to drop but there are two market makers who wrote a bunch of 650 puts. Watch and learn. They were trying to close those positions all darned day long.</Msg><Username>obamasuxcockwithnegrolips</Username><Timestamp>1353469634592</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 22:47:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>