<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350103318519-1</Id><Title>Google's "search grab" revenue model has the FTC salivating....</Title><Msg>Better get out that check book Boys, the FTC wants some payback.....</Msg><Username>samsonp65</Username><Timestamp>1350103318519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:41:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350113876888-2</Id><Title>....forming a HEAD &amp; SHOULDERS Top &amp; ready to test the 50DMA !!</Title><Msg>I say ALOT lower after E.R. on Friday Morning</Msg><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1350113876888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 03:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350131240500-3</Id><Title>The Right Way To Trade GOOG</Title><Msg>I am watching Google Inc. (NasdaqNM: GOOG ) very closely and about to go in for a trade. Rumors have it that significant news will be released shortly and Google Inc. (NasdaqNM: GOOG ) will be swinging in one direction depending on how Wall Street takes the news.. Stay up to date on Google Inc. (NasdaqNM: GOOG ) and other hot stocks: Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- goo.gl/tZvTj</Msg><Username>sandovalgibbs107</Username><Timestamp>1350131240500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350131562080-4</Id><Title>Joe Biden</Title><Msg>Biden has been a corrupt DC politico since 1972 and surely appeals to you government dependent dems that so need such bafoons to drag you along. Fortunate for Romney and Ryan he came off as the complete jackass he truly is. He's been like that the whole time so nobody expected anything else adn fortunately it worked out well especially with woman who truly disdain such disrespect. As Andrea Tantoros said on The Five 'he reminds her of the ole boy office club type that belittles women overall and tells them to go make some coffee honey.' Man that's Joey to the max. Two things will hurt him real bad as FACT CHECKER spelled out: 1. They indeed stripped $786,000,000,000 (billion baby) from Medicare and that lying sack of manure said they put it back HA! I wonder when that happened as I don't seem to recall such transaction to date; 2. That intelligence did not tell them the attack at Bengazi Those two will do him and Biden in more less the obvious disrepect he showed Ryan. No class but then that's Joey the dumbo! by Joel B. Pollak12 Oct 2012230post a comment Once again, Joe Biden lied his way through a Vice Presidential debate--just as he did in his contest with Sarah Palin in 2008. This time, the media caught a few of Biden's worst "malarkey" moments--as did his opponent, Paul Ryan, when he could get a word in edgewise. Here are the top ten worst lies told by Biden during the debate: Update - Honorable Mention: "There's not one Democrat who endorsed his...plan." Biden lied--as Ryan pointed out, amidst the Vice President's interruptions--about the fact that Ryan had worked with both Democratic Sen. Ron Wyden of Oregon and former Clinton budget director Alice Rivlin in developing his entitlement reforms. While it's true that neither have endorsed the Romney-Ryan ticket's separate plan--which is different--Ryan's own plans, to which Biden referred, were endorsed by Democrats, and Biden knows it. 10. "With all due respect, that’s a bunch of malarkey....not a single thing he said is accurate." At the outset of the debate, Biden tried to paint Ryan as a liar--when Biden, in fact, was the one lying. Ryan had pointed out: 1) that the White House had distanced itself from the Cairo embassy's apologies on 9/11; 2) that Obama had failed to speak up for Iranian protestors in 2009; 3) that the Obama administration called Syria's dictator a "reformer"; 4) and that the Obama administration is imposing defense cuts and projecting weakness. All of that is true. 9. "The president has met with Bibi [Netanyahu] a dozen times....This is a bunch of stuff." While they have met several times--not a dozen--that includes a meeting at which Obama made the Israeli prime minister enter the White House through a back entrance, refused to take a picture with him, and left him on his own for dinner. Specifically, Ryan had criticized Obama's refusal to meet Netanyahu in New York last month, and to tape talk show interviews instead--a clear snub that sent the wrong signal, again, to Israel's enemies. 8. "Just let the taxes expire like they’re supposed to on those millionaires." Biden's "millionaires" are actually households earning more than $250,000 a year, which includes many middle-class families with two earners, and small business owners in particular who report business earnings as personal income. Biden and Obama have repeatedly labeled those earning over $250,000 as "millionaires and billionaires," distorting the actual impact of their tax plan on the non-millionaires it would hit hardest, who create a vast proportion of small business jobs. 7. "You know, I heard that death panel argument from Sarah Palin. It seems that every vice presidential debate, I hear this kind of stuff about panels." Biden's cheap shot against Palin was an attempt to diminish both her and the man sitting across from him. But Palin never talked about "death panels" in her debate with Biden, for the simple reason that Obamacare had not yet been proposed. Nor did Ryan mention "death panels"--he had addressed the undeniable fact that Obamacare proposes a board to impose cost controls. 6. "The congressman here cut embassy security in his budget by $300 million below what we asked for." Biden's lie about Ryan's budget was an attempt to dodge responsibility for lax embassy security--and to cover up that the Obama administration called for new cuts to embassy security just days after the 9/11 attacks. Ryan's proposal, which called for a 19% overall decrease in non-defense discretionary spending, does not even mention embassy security--the Obama campaign merely made up that number by applying 19% across the board. 5. "No, they are not four years closer to a nuclear weapon." Biden's attempt to lie about the glaring reality of the Iranian nuclear program fell flat. Iran is indeed four years closer to a nuclear weapon, and the Obama administration--believing it knew better than its predecessors--tried to reinvent the wheel on talks with Iran, causing frustration to our allies in Europe and the Middle East. Meeting after meeting this year has failed to produce results, and the loophole-filled sanctions, while hurting Iran somewhat, are not stopping its nuclear program. 4. "No religious institution, Catholic or otherwise...has to be a vehicle to get contraception in any insurance policy they provide. That is a fact." No, it is not a fact--it is the opposite of a fact, and saying "that is a fact" does not make it any less a blatant lie. The Obama administration is forcing religious institutions to provide contraceptive and abortion drugs through their insurance policies. That is the reason several dozen religious institutions are suing the administration to defend their First Amendment freedom of religion. 3. "It came from this man voting to put two wars on a credit card...I was there. I voted against him." Biden voted for both the Iraq war and the Afghanistan war. He did not vote for George W. Bush's plan to extend coverage of Medicare to prescription drugs (though he voted for an earlier, similar proposal), nor did he vote for the Bush tax cuts. But he voted for both of the wars he derided last night. To quote Bill Clinton's speech to the Democratic National Convention: "It takes some brass to attack a guy for doing what you did." 2. "What we did is we saved $716 billion and put it back -- applied it to Medicare." Biden repeated the lie the Obama administration has been telling since before Obamacare passed in 2010: that cuts to Medicare today were savings that extend the life of the program. They would be--if the same $716 billion wasn't also being used to pay for Obamacare. As Ryan pointed out in 2010, and again last night, you can't double-count the same cuts. Taking $716 billion out of Medicare means exactly that--and hurts, not helps, the program's solvency. 1. "Well, we weren’t told they wanted more security again." Biden lied through his teeth about the fact that the administration--specifically, the State Department--had been told again and again that security on the ground in Libya, and in Benghazi in particular, was inadequate. The day before, in Congressional hearings on the Libya attacks, former regional security director Eric Nordstrom described his frustration with having those requests turned down by the government bureaucracy: "For me the Taliban is on the inside of the building."</Msg><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1350131562080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350149103838-5</Id><Title>GOOG ready to crash</Title><Msg>When they go to trial on Oct. 16 and Lose to Vringo in the patent case. Stupid Google management about to lose $50B market cap when they could have just bought VRNG for 1/5th that. lmfao</Msg><Username>tech_six_sense</Username><Timestamp>1350149103838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:25:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149148534-6</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden</Title><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1350131562080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:32:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally, an intelligent person, who can see clearly through the rhetoric and noise......Obama is trying to complete his father's dreams to destroy America.</Msg><Username>actionspread</Username><Timestamp>1350149148534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149363252-7</Id><Topic><Title>The Right Way To Trade GOOG</Title><Username>sandovalgibbs107</Username><Timestamp>1350131240500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a ton of helpful information on that site, so glad I found this.</Msg><Username>estrada_sandoval</Username><Timestamp>1350149363252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350149466563-8</Id><Title>Win-Win-Win-Win: for all parties: heres why..</Title><Msg>Vringo wins major case, gets reasonbly what they want. Google, Gets away clean: No willful infringement.. They dont look like thieves, just a mistake, great for pr, nobody loses their jobs Ken lang gets vindicated Quinn emmanuel looks great defensively: they protected google from Nuclear Thermal war</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350149466563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350149989048-9</Id><Title>If Quinn Emmanuel gets a buyout deal, WI is not issue, google Creates a litigation fortress to fight FTC,</Title><Msg>Will totally look great. QE look like winners</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350149989048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350150164489-10</Id><Title>What is a better buy ? AAPL or GOOG</Title><Msg>Wondering what is a better buy for the long term ? (say 10 years)</Msg><Username>snlsn77</Username><Timestamp>1350150164489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350150292445-11</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG ANTITRUST, MSFT SUING GOOG, FREE ANDROID IN RETURN FOR KICKBACKS, GOOG DOWN TO 640, AAPL TO 750</Title><Username>tamermou</Username><Timestamp>1350081157313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:32:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is just noise ... all big companies have gone thru this, msft, ibm, csco etc ......</Msg><Username>biotechh</Username><Timestamp>1350150292445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350151863991-12</Id><Title>Goog is screeweedddd!</Title><Msg>Your last shot for a bit was to BUY VRNG on Friday and whole week. Now that Feds are going to sanction Google for huge antitrusts violations you think this drives Google stock higher?? Lay of the crack pipes!</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914561</Username><Timestamp>1350151863991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350151886719-13</Id><Topic><Title>nomura raised PT</Title><Username>cirillusii</Username><Timestamp>1349960172447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>loollllll</Msg><Username>johnkelly6914561</Username><Timestamp>1350151886719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152870914-14</Id><Topic><Title>Goog is screeweedddd!</Title><Username>johnkelly6914561</Username><Timestamp>1350151863991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:11:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a crack pipe!</Msg><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1350152870914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350153007956-15</Id><Topic><Title>nomura raised PT</Title><Username>cirillusii</Username><Timestamp>1349960172447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 08:56:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Third class posts. Why do you both to wake up?</Msg><Username>loop_around</Username><Timestamp>1350153007956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:30:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153962093-16</Id><Title>DO you think google's customers Stock is being affected by the uncertainty with vrng?</Title><Msg>Tell me..</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350153962093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350154108007-17</Id><Topic><Title>DO you think google's customers Stock is being affected by the uncertainty with vrng?</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350153962093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Na.</Msg><Username>aurin_res</Username><Timestamp>1350154108007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350154934532-18</Id><Title>Trial means: google opens pandora's box for its customers!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Good luck with that</Msg><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350154934532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350162490711-19</Id><Title>Make money shorting goog starting Monday</Title><Msg>Just saying</Msg><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350162490711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350163345607-20</Id><Title>Where will pps be after FCC,MSFT,VRNG get done with them</Title><Msg>Think people</Msg><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350163345607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163432198-21</Id><Topic><Title>Where will pps be after FCC,MSFT,VRNG get done with them</Title><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350163345607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FTC=TYPO=ANYHOO</Msg><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350163432198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164126262-22</Id><Topic><Title>What you need to know....</Title><Username>burritowithstuffonit</Username><Timestamp>1350098630387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:23:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you know it?</Msg><Username>burritowithstuffonit</Username><Timestamp>1350164126262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171597475-23</Id><Topic><Title>Make money shorting goog starting Monday</Title><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350162490711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:08:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shorted this #$%$ at 770.</Msg><Username>amedaris</Username><Timestamp>1350171597475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350176213847-24</Id><Title>NeoMagic Corporation Announces The Acquisition Of MercadoMagico</Title><Msg>MercadoMagico will provide a platform where users will be able to buy and sell products from one another or buy premium electronic products directly from MercadoMagico.</Msg><Username>pr.investor</Username><Timestamp>1350176213847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180081682-25</Id><Topic><Title>DO you think google's customers Stock is being affected by the uncertainty with vrng?</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350153962093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Na is not an answer. I think they are. But then again, that is low profile info. :)</Msg><Username>juron_4u2</Username><Timestamp>1350180081682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180681479-26</Id><Topic><Title>DO you think google's customers Stock is being affected by the uncertainty with vrng?</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350153962093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course. By Friday I imagine Google will be down $50 give or take.... I have 10 shares of Goog, selling five and going to ONCS. VRNG will probably get a nice settlement, not a huge amount but at least 150% pps.</Msg><Username>burritowithstuffonit</Username><Timestamp>1350180681479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180788813-27</Id><Topic><Title>Make money shorting goog starting Monday</Title><Username>walter_mitty_investor</Username><Timestamp>1350162490711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:08:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably a good idea, at least for the next few months.</Msg><Username>burritowithstuffonit</Username><Timestamp>1350180788813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180889564-28</Id><Topic><Title>DO you think google's customers Stock is being affected by the uncertainty with vrng?</Title><Username>marketneutral1001</Username><Timestamp>1350153962093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:46:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think GOOG will be down on Friday when they report after hours on Thurs? Expecting a poor quarter? I would expect a big bounce when they report after having a blow out quarter.</Msg><Username>aurin_res</Username><Timestamp>1350180889564</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350185490131-29</Id><Title>the decision won' come down for more than a month....the mm's are pulling it back to get in</Title><Msg>cheap before blow out earnings.</Msg><Username>actionspread</Username><Timestamp>1350185490131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 23:31:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>