<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817911847-1</Id><Topic><Title>2009: Stanford professor mentored Google founders apparently drowned in his pool</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346793412063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rajeev Motwani he quickly became one of the best-connected figures behind the scenes in Silicon Valley. Rajeev Motwani Brilliant computer scientist who mentored the founders of Google Bobbie Johnson, technology correspondent The Guardian, Tuesday 9 June 2009 When approached by Brin for advice, he was initially sceptical that a new web search engine could make a difference in a crowded market. However, he saw something different in their work and co-authored several papers that developed their strategy for finding information online - taking on the role of informal adviser to Google as a result. In return for his involvement, Motwani was rewarded with a stake in the company, a relationship that paid off when Google reached the stockmarket in 2004, making Page and Brin billionaires and reaping great rewards for himself. Although Motwani did not get the mainstream recognition that his former students achieved, the experience turned him even further towards helping nascent technologists and he found entrepreneurial zest intoxicating. As an adviser and investor to a string of other companies, including the internet payments service PayPal and venture capital firm Sequoia Capital, he quickly became one of the best-connected figures behind the scenes in Silicon Valley.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346817911847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817913528-2</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Mormon and Obama is Christian,,,, you choose - a Christian that KILLS BABIES!!</Title><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346752034234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 05:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Satan! you are the father of lies.... and you and your Mormon Followers will burn in Hell...</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346817913528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817973441-3</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Mormon and Obama is Christian,,,, you choose.....</Title><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346705873803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 16:57:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama Saved America! God Bless Our Christian Brother OBAMA... God will deal with u Mormon Followers soon</Msg><Username>jbhdallas2000</Username><Timestamp>1346817973441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 00:06:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346837278825-4</Id><Title>Mormon bible that teaches Jesus and Satan r brothers?</Title><Msg>As Huckabee said at the convention 'I'd rather elect a pro life Morman than a self proclaimed Christian that supports all forms of abortion including the most horrific partial birth abortions wherein th so called doc sticks a prong in the babies brain at the stem cord then sucks out it's brains.' If you call that a Christian dude you must also be living the self centered form of USA Christianity where anything goes! As the radio preacher once said, 'Not God bless America but America needs to start blessing God!' Amen brother! Then you have Obamadungdufus peracher racists Jeremiah Wright that gives his version, 'Not God Bless America but God Damm America.' Now there's Obamadungdufus type of self serviing Christianity (oh I forgot he sat there 20 + years and did not hear anything. HA! You dems is DUMBOS!!! It does not matter though for Romney WILL NOT ALLOW Obamadungdufus and his cronies to pull this race off ot the failed economy this DUNCE Obamadungdufus has and is presiding over. The blame Bush stuff won't work for stats reveal the truth and that is Obamadungdufus has spent more in 3.7 years than both Bush terms combined and more debt increase than ALL prior Presidents combined. The Charlotte Show won't work and will soon be over culminating with BOY CLINTON (the vaginal cigar Lewinski dipper then licking them down while other world leaders waited to meet with him) telling the Charlotte Show crowd of dem dunces what true leadership is then Sandra Fluck whining about FREE RUBBERS FOR ALL and BABY KILLING CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHTS, then on back to reality where Romeny/Ryan keep posing the question are you/we better off than we were 4 years ago and the answer to all but the die hard dem DUNCES is a resounding NO! It was funny watching all the dem pundits flounder over the weekend at that question. THE ANSWER WILL REMAIN A RESOUNDING NO! And unless there are 500,000 new jobs created in this Friday's report Obamadungdufus is FLUCKED again!!!</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346837278825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 05:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346840670033-5</Id><Title>This is the best for GOOG stock</Title><Msg>The information provided at VIP is very compelling and it has assisted me in the decision making process and it has also created a better base for me to understand stock GOOG, visit it at, vippennystocksite dotcom</Msg><Username>best5842</Username><Timestamp>1346840670033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346840743647-6</Id><Topic><Title>This is the best for GOOG stock</Title><Username>best5842</Username><Timestamp>1346840670033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:24:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing it is nice and very well structured</Msg><Username>khalid5842</Username><Timestamp>1346840743647</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:25:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346842458526-7</Id><Title>Cramer forget one of biggest winner of mobile: Local Corp - and this company is with 0.4-times-reveneus extreme undervalued</Title><Msg>While Google (GOOG) and Yelp (YELP) work better on mobile, companies like Facebook will be left in the dust until they find a way to monetize mobile. Cramer thinks Facebook’s problems are not hopeless, but its stock should be trading at a lower price, and there is no reason to buy FB right now.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346842458526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346843580345-8</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer forget one of biggest winner of mobile: Local Corp - and this company is with 0.4-times-reveneus extreme undervalued</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346842458526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yelp for example is with 10-times-revenues extreme overvalued.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346843580345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346845539090-9</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer forget one of biggest winner of mobile: Local Corp - and this company is with 0.4-times-reveneus extreme undervalued</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346842458526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Compare of Monthly Unique US-Visitors Numbers of Flagshipsite of L o c a l Corp: 25,322,291 Unique Visitors, 0.73%% increase in July against June, 35.30% increase against last year Numbers Yelp: 21,665,670 Unique Visitors, 3,39%% increase in July against June, 18,19% increase against last year Numbers of Google: 166,472,109 Unique Visitors, 1.27% increase in July against June</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346845539090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346845585283-10</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer forget one of biggest winner of mobile: Local Corp - and this company is with 0.4-times-reveneus extreme undervalued</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346842458526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the market-cap of Local Corp. is idiotic low 43 million.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346845585283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346846120575-11</Id><Topic><Title>Cramer forget one of biggest winner of mobile: Local Corp - and this company is with 0.4-times-reveneus extreme undervalued</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346842458526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:54:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mobile traffic continued to grow strongly, representing over 6.5 million Monthly Unique Visitors in May 2012, up over 368% from 1.4 million Monthly Unique Visitors during the year ago period.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1346846120575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 07:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346848364345-12</Id><Title>GOOGLE-PATENTS</Title><Msg>Does Google have any of their own patents or do they just use(steal) other companies. No wonder they keep saying this is too easy!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346848364345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346848948651-13</Id><Topic><Title>THIS PUMPED SCAM WILL COLLAPSE LIKE RIMM VERY SOON</Title><Username>pharmaherobk</Username><Timestamp>1346848605927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:36:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait till Vrng gets ahold of them</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346848948651</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849067777-14</Id><Title>VRNG Lurking</Title><Msg>Oct. 16</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346849067777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346849607980-15</Id><Title>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google it</Title><Msg>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google it you may be surprized</Msg><Username>serenityloveh69</Username><Timestamp>1346849607980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346851191306-16</Id><Topic><Title>FALSE STATEMENTS AND LIES TO SUX IN DUMMIES</Title><Username>pharmaherobk</Username><Timestamp>1346848577205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how trapped are you shorty?</Msg><Username>shorthound</Username><Timestamp>1346851191306</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346851194029-17</Id><Title>IDCC will blow up today - Check</Title><Msg>Apple hoards LTE patents to deflect Samsung attack Possible defensive move to stop Samsung marching iPhone 5 to court By Phil Muncaster • Get more from this author Posted in Networks, 5th September 2012 05:44 GMT Free whitepaper – Enabling Datacenter and Cloud Service Management for Mid-Tier Enterprises Apple has been hoarding LTE patents in a bid to head off a possible legal attack from fierce rival Samsung on its forthcoming iPhone 5, according to reports from Korea. Apple has gone from holding zero LTE patents last year to having 318 filed away today. That's around five per cent of the world’s total, today, the Korea Intellectual Property Office (KIPO) told local news site The Chosun Ilbo. Cupertino apparently developed just 44 of those patents itself while the rest were bought from once-proud Nortel as it was broken up. The Rockstar Bidco consortium which Apple joined with EMC, Microsoft and others to bid for further Nortel patents owns a further 116 LTE patents, effectively bumping Apple’s number up in excess of 400. By comparison, Samsung has the largest share of the patents on the planet with 819 (12.7 per cent), while US patent firm InterDigital is second with 780 (12.1 per cent). "This shows that Apple has been taking strategic steps to acquire intellectual property to prepare for potential legal disputes before it launches its own LTE smartphones," a KIPO official told Chosun Ilbo. The report echoes claims in the Korean Times on Friday that Samsung – still smarting after its defeat to Apple in a Californian court last month – was readying a move to strike back at the fruity tech brand. It claims that Samsung confirmed it would “immediately sue” Apple if the Californian phone-maker releases an LTE device. With the iPhone 5 possibly set to sport such functionality when it is announced next week, we should find out sooner rather than later. However, patent expert Florian Mueller warned that the Korean electronics giant would do well to rethink its strategy, telling The Reg: “4G/LTE won't be Samsung's key to a free pass for infringement”. “I would strongly discourage Samsung from trying to use 4G/LTE-essential patents to shut down the iPhone 5,” he added in a blog post. “It won't improve Samsung's position. It will only make things worse, especially with antitrust regulators. In my view, the reasonable approach for Samsung would be to sue for FRAND royalties over its Standard Essential Patents, not injunctions.”</Msg><Username>patentsaddicted</Username><Timestamp>1346851194029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852399158-18</Id><Title>Shorted now at 681 - looks real weak - easy money</Title><Msg>sold my long shares at 680.7 for $3000 gain and now short</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346852399158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346852655573-19</Id><Title>news out</Title><Msg>GFMD - Embark Holdings Subsidiary ERA Client Randy Keisler to Start Opposite Roger Clemens. Read the full release at goo.gl/w0ici Get news on your mobile phone, text STOCK to 545454</Msg><Username>craigsoto777</Username><Timestamp>1346852655573</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346852905451-20</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted now at 681 - looks real weak - easy money</Title><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346852399158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice call, lol</Msg><Username>mavi027</Username><Timestamp>1346852905451</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853122023-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is Mormon and Obama is Christian,,,, you choose - a Christian that KILLS BABIES!!</Title><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346752034234</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 05:47:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is muslim, 2 weeks ago he celebrated the ramadan in the white house, only muslims celebrate ramadan, also try to see the movie, 2016 the movie. you will see clear what's going on.</Msg><Username>bernierosado</Username><Timestamp>1346853122023</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346853724404-22</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted now at 681 - looks real weak - easy money</Title><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346852399158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:39:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's see how quickly you lose that $3,000 and cry to your mommy. This company is ready to breakout with it's stock price funamentally and technically. I see this beast going to $900 by the end of the year and there's only 4 months left...I'll check for reply at the end of the day to see the despair in this smartypants...lol</Msg><Username>kupi23</Username><Timestamp>1346853724404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855288784-23</Id><Title>The problem with Wall Street is</Title><Msg>We have too many old brokers that don't understand todays technology and young minds this is why they don't know how to play the market and are under performing They don't get that shopping at COST TGT TJX is cool that those days are over when shopping at TGT was only for people with food stamps They don't know how to shop on line or book a hotel on iPhone</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1346855288784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855421597-24</Id><Title>OK, doubled up on my short at 684 - now 600 shares at 682.5 ave</Title><Msg>I think this market peters out later today. GOOG is stuck in a range and should go down</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346855421597</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346855767227-25</Id><Title>OK - good to short now - GOOG looking weak here</Title><Msg>all clear fellow shorters Will close under 680</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346855767227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:36:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346855878468-26</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: Is it a "goldmine" or is it a "landmine"???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1276979012000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2010-06-19 16:23:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2: Is it a "goldmine" or is it a "landmine"??? By casp321.2 years 2 months ago.Permalink . Is it "landmine" or "gold mine", it depends on the where sounds is coming. Is it from the end ot the "tunnel?" Is it a "singing qanary" or is it just a "ticking" sounds? Some of us ON2 shareholders have already STEPPED into the "mine" that's is really a DANGEROUS zone to be in, BUT still much better than living in FEAR of not being able to to raise the voice of BEING ROBBED in the day light. Will there be any JUSTICE for ON2 shareholders, I doubt with the MAGNITUDE of those involved in the SCAM and in the way a few hundred million dollars COVERED by Shorts, by Shorting and Covering and Shorting and Covering Cycle, by generating "FEAR" factors "legally"..</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346855878468</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346856271190-27</Id><Title>Settlement with Vringo soon</Title><Msg>that's the rumor</Msg><Username>premiumdm</Username><Timestamp>1346856271190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346856715249-28</Id><Title>strong strong sell on valuation, chart</Title><Msg>and all the apple products coming out</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1346856715249</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:51:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346856851042-29</Id><Title>YES, now green on my shorts!!!!! follow my calls people</Title><Msg>market heading down from here rest of week.</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346856851042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857121806-30</Id><Topic><Title>2009: Stanford professor mentored Google founders apparently drowned in his pool</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346793412063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2009: Stanford professor mentored Google founders apparently drowned in his pool</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346857121806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 10:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346857407183-31</Id><Title>669 possible today</Title><Msg>for sure this week</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346857407183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346857431323-32</Id><Title>already up $1200 on my short today</Title><Msg>this is so easy</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1346857431323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346857565078-33</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samad Behrangi The best known Iranian writer of children's stories Behrangi was only twenty-nine when drowned in a swimming accident in Aras River in September 1968. It is commonly believed that SAVAK, Shah’s security service, was behind this accident. At the time, his most famous children's stories, including "Ma’hi-e Sia’he Kochoulou" (The Little Black Fish), his most famous work, were at the press; they were published posthumously. Later in 1969, "24 Sa'at Dar Khab Va Bidary" (24 Restless Hours) and "Yek Hulou, Yek Hezar Hulou" (One Peach, A Thousand Peaches), two of his other works were published. Behrangi was a critique of both contents and methodology of the state-sponsored textbooks and curriculum. He believed the entire educational system is outdated and alien to the Iranian children and in particular the rural children.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346857565078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346859401784-34</Id><Topic><Title>casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know</Title><Username>wmhjr99</Username><Timestamp>1337952121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-25 09:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I remember ON2 financial earning report in 2007 were falsified by Bill Joll, ON2 CEO at the time. It's interesting to see that he's a CEO of a HIGH SECURITY company producing products for Homeland Security and also have some PhD program REASERCHERs with HIGH SECURITY working under BJ managrment at this company. Instead of INVESTIGATING his activities they've granted him a "safe" and "secure" position, something similar to ON2 "lead-plaintiff-with-100-share" that was NOT being inmvestigated of how his leading 178+ million ON2 shares could be legal? How is all these possible? What was the rush? A big mistake when they have not the right people running their operations assuming "dumb" shareholders will let them get away with it as usuasl. ----- Camel placed his feet in the water and took a few steps, then came back. He said, "Come on, the water is shallow. It's only up the knees." The mouse said, "Yes-but from knee to knee..." Camel said, "Do you repent? Don't be so bold and, if you are, be with someone whose knees are like yours." FRom Shams who traine Rumi and paid for that! ----- Re: ON2 SI and 3 pdf docs: They can NOT say they did NOT know!!!! By casp321.1 year 3 months ago.Permalink . A mouse took the rein of a camel and started walking. The camel, unhappy because of recalcitrance toward his master, was obedient to the mouse-because of quarrel with the master. The mouse fancied that it was the strength of his own hand. A ray of that fancy struck the camel. He said to himself, "I'll show you." When they reached water, the mouse stopped. Camel said, "What caused this halting?" The mouce said, "A great stream of water has come forth." The camel said, "Let me see how deep the water is. You stand back." Camel placed his feet in the water and took a few steps, then came back. He said, "Come on, the water is shallow. It's only up the knees." The mouse said, "Yes-but from knee to knee..." Camel said, "Do you repent? Don't be so bold and, if you are, be with someone whose knees are like yours." Mouse said, "I repent but take my hand." The camel lay down: "Come on, climb on my hump- whether it's a stream or the [...], even if it's ocean, I'll swim. I have no fear." From Shams who trained Rumi</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346859401784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346859910636-35</Id><Title>GOOG will be 0.00 after it pays VRNG for Patent law suit</Title><Msg>Pay may be 5billion or more to VRNG</Msg><Username>subpreeti</Username><Timestamp>1346859910636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346860566613-36</Id><Title>GOOG may loose all customers if VRNG wins in patent law suit and GOOG will be 0.00</Title><Msg>All those who advertise on GOOG will be part of Law Suit and may have to pay damages to VRNG</Msg><Username>subpreeti</Username><Timestamp>1346860566613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 11:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861130757-37</Id><Title>Watch our for wild revenue number for this quarter.</Title><Msg>Tablets are flying off the shelves. Sales will be up 10% this quarter on the nexus alone. September will be a big month. This is another reason to short Amazon.</Msg><Username>sammmy220022</Username><Timestamp>1346861130757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861215684-38</Id><Title>AAPL or MSFT will buy VRNG and sue GOOG for Patent and GOOG will be 0.00</Title><Msg>!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>subpreeti</Username><Timestamp>1346861215684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861381463-39</Id><Title>today marks the slow demise of Android! IOS, W8 and BB10 will dominate</Title><Msg>android will move to lower end and pre paid ... its done</Msg><Username>joe_cramer_booyaah</Username><Timestamp>1346861381463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346861432268-40</Id><Title>GOOG will be 0.00 after Oct 16</Title><Msg>VRNG Law suit will bankrupt GOOG</Msg><Username>subpreeti</Username><Timestamp>1346861432268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:10:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346861769697-41</Id><Topic><Title>MORE BRUTAL DUMPING BY INSIDERS WARNING</Title><Username>pharmaherobk</Username><Timestamp>1346840535407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 06:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INSIDERS can see the drop in traffic since Penguin update way before us mortals.</Msg><Username>miltonbob66</Username><Timestamp>1346861769697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346862924579-42</Id><Title>Just had a nooner with my sister</Title><Msg>While all you loser where in your pajamas watching Jerry springer</Msg><Username>coolrob15</Username><Timestamp>1346862924579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863286627-43</Id><Topic><Title>$100-200 COLLAPSE ANY DAY NOW ON BAD OUTLOOK NEWS</Title><Username>pharmaherobk</Username><Timestamp>1346862270655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:24:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? People have been buying and buying and buying, huge blocks. It gets to 680 and up up up to 685 and yet it is going to drop 100 to 200 points? Does that make any sense. All these people that have been buying like crazy from 620 up (and the volume on some days has been above average) and they are going to sell at 585, 485 really?</Msg><Username>burtwalsh123</Username><Timestamp>1346863286627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:41:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863352275-44</Id><Topic><Title>BAD EARNINGS SOON AGAIN =$500 AND LOWER COMING</Title><Username>pharmaherobk</Username><Timestamp>1346860808091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:00:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would their earnings be bad. The world is using Andriod, and Goog search, and ....</Msg><Username>burtwalsh123</Username><Timestamp>1346863352275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346863980138-45</Id><Topic><Title>Just had a nooner with my sister</Title><Username>coolrob15</Username><Timestamp>1346862924579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:35:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>explains your affinity towards banjos and mountains</Msg><Username>jd_bozeman</Username><Timestamp>1346863980138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865138748-46</Id><Title>shorts just join the party</Title><Msg>Target is 720 for the year and we know we will get close before a pull back. Enjoy the ride!</Msg><Username>burtwalsh123</Username><Timestamp>1346865138748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865303655-47</Id><Title>Sixty Ate by the end of the day.</Title><Msg>Burn those shorts! lol.</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346865303655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865485460-48</Id><Title>Sorry, mistype. I mean Six hundred and atety ate. hehe.</Title><Msg>sorry.</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346865485460</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346865562670-49</Id><Title>Coach at Investment Tool says $700 is the near term target.</Title><Msg>Easy $700 coming!</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346865562670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:19:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346866176349-50</Id><Title>Coach at Investment Tool says to load up Goog now.</Title><Msg>Goog is an easy $700!</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346866176349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346866177072-51</Id><Title>Just filed Form 4: Sergey Brin dumped 83,334 shares...</Title><Msg>...on 9/4; various prices ranging from 674-684...</Msg><Username>kwooozie</Username><Timestamp>1346866177072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:29:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346867233813-52</Id><Title>Let's all move quietly to the exit.</Title><Msg>That's right. Ease it.</Msg><Username>jbs_trader</Username><Timestamp>1346867233813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346867298993-53</Id><Topic><Title>Let's all move quietly to the exit.</Title><Username>jbs_trader</Username><Timestamp>1346867233813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:47:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try not to alarm the children please.</Msg><Username>jbs_trader</Username><Timestamp>1346867298993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 13:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346869927344-54</Id><Title>guys, its very overvalued up here right into serious competive threats</Title><Msg>what r the #$%$ thinking in this? FIDELITY is BONZO again</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1346869927344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346871597120-55</Id><Title>Six hundrad and atety ate! Six hundrea and atety ate!</Title><Msg>$688, $688, $688 then $700!</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346871597120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 14:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346872126242-56</Id><Topic><Title>2009: Stanford professor mentored Google founders apparently drowned in his pool</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346793412063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jun 5, 2009 - 6:10PM PT Goodbye Old Friend. R.I.P. Rajeev Motwani By Om Malik Updated with additional details: Rajeev Motwani, one of the savviest angel investors in Silicon Valley, a Stanford professor and most importantly a close and personal friend passed away earlier today. My feelings and thoughts on the passing of one of the quiet influencers of Silicon Valley. Updated, June 7, 2009: Rajeev Motwani, one of the savviest angel investors in Silicon Valley, a Stanford professor and most importantly a close and personal friend passed away earlier today. He was 47 and is left behind by his wife Asha and kids. It is hard for me to write this post — this morning the news of Steve Jobs’ improving health put me in a good mood. My day is ending with a broken heart and tears in my eyes. It is the day which reminds you of the unpredictability of life. Rajeev and I had been swapping emails, hoping to get together for a cup of coffee and discussions about technology. Alas, that shall never be. After working tirelessly in anonymity, his tutelage of two Stanford University young grad students, Larry Page and Sergey Brin, made him a household name in Silicon Valley. He started the Mining Data at Stanford project (MIDAS) and was one of the earliest backers of Google. He was an early investor in Paypal and a special adviser to Sequoia Captial. That success never came in the way of Rajeev’s quest for knowledge and innate desire to help others. There wasn’t a startup he didn’t love. Like his chosen specialization of search, Rajeev was searching for the unknown. He was still active as a professor and was teaching a couple of classes as recently as the last semester.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346872126242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346872342339-57</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Samad Behrangi The best known Iranian writer of children's stories Behrangi was only twenty-nine when drowned in a swimming accident in Aras River in September 1968. It is commonly believed that SAVAK, Shah’s security service, was behind this accident. Behrangi was a critique of both contents and methodology of the state-sponsored textbooks and curriculum. --------- SAVAK SAVAK (Persian: ساواک, short for سازِمانِ اطلاعات وَ امنیَتِ کِشوَر Sāzemān-e Ettelā'āt va Amniyat-e Keshvar, Organisation of Intelligence and National Security) was the secret police, domestic security and intelligence service established by Iran's Mohammad Reza Shah with the help of the United States' Central Intelligence Agency (the CIA).[1] SAVAK operated from 1957 to 1979, when the Pahlavi dynasty was overthrown. SAVAK has been described as Iran's "most hated and feared institution" prior to the revolution of 1979 because of its practice of torturing and executing opponents of the Pahlavi regime.[2][3] At its peak, the organization had as many as 60,000 agents serving in its ranks according to one source</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346872342339</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346873235217-58</Id><Title>Apple will fall to $650 and GOOG will get to $700!</Title><Msg>That's going to happen.</Msg><Username>stocker4949</Username><Timestamp>1346873235217</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 15:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346875280677-59</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG attains in One Trades for NasdaqNM shoppers</Title><Username>ralden86</Username><Timestamp>1324747495000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-12-24 12:24:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big deal in the making!!!</Msg><Username>lolamcgowan213</Username><Timestamp>1346875280677</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346875751987-60</Id><Title>Study the data</Title><Msg>Research the moving daily average trend, learn the charts, read the headlines of Goog,AAPL,. Understand before you invest. If you do a little research you will become a savvy investor!</Msg><Username>tyronica_seaton2002</Username><Timestamp>1346875751987</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 16:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346890440422-61</Id><Topic><Title>Just had a nooner with my sister</Title><Username>coolrob15</Username><Timestamp>1346862924579</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 12:35:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same idiots posted this message on the Apple Board.</Msg><Username>aiwal1</Username><Timestamp>1346890440422</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346890946445-62</Id><Title>got android device 4.0. it is a EPIC FAIL</Title><Msg>got android device 4.0. it is a EPIC FAIL. no sound when watching youtubing. lol, lol....</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346890946445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346891165710-63</Id><Topic><Title>got android device 4.0. it is a EPIC FAIL</Title><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346890946445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>samsung galaxy tab 2, cant access microsd due to lousy android 4.0.</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346891165710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346893588714-64</Id><Topic><Title>got android device 4.0. it is a EPIC FAIL</Title><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346890946445</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 20:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>also dim display issue. you start the android and the display is dim. fine, but it should switch to bright mode when i tab on any where in screen. no no nonono, i have to go setting and play around with display setting for it to bright up. EPIC FAIL!!!!!</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346893588714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346901072337-65</Id><Title>Funny the party of women showcases Clinton the Impeached Hummer POTUS</Title><Msg>What better introduction for FLUCKING CLINTON than FLUCK herself admonishing dem women need FREE RUBBERS FOR ALL AND FREE BABY KILLING (all of course at taxpayers continued expense even now wanting us to cover gender identity surgery.) Wow folks we is in big trouble! They just don't seem to understand that looming $16 TRILLION DEBT (1/3 belonging to Obamadungdufus alone) is about to TAKE US UNDER. The Charlotte Show is turning out JUST THAT with all IMAGEONLY hype that landed us here with a community organizer Saul Alinsky radical child prodigy POTUS that has been ran shod over by the most left are of the dem party. Funny as today dems cancelled the 74,000 capacity stadium and moved the entire venue inside to the 20,000 seater. HA! They know the truth THIS AIN'T 2008 AS FOLKS NOW KNOW OBAMADUNGDUFUS. Hilarious to see them out spinning today saying they fear the weather could be real bad. There's currently a 30% chance of rain and I am praying it turns out QUITE SUNNY AND NICE as we cruize toward 11/2012 and the MOST FESTIVE OF ALL HOLIDAY SEASONS!!!! What this is truly about is 100 years of primary democrat party failed control for which their chickens indeed have come home to roost and they spent all our money (SS/Medicare, income taxes etc..) on welfare to lock in democrat votes moving forward. 1913 dem Wilson Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE that has debt leveraged our currency to zero intrinsic value, 1933 dem FDR failed SS Ponzi that was only to cost $.03 per pay, 1964 dem LBJ failed Medicare Ponzi now completely broke necessitating socialized medicine with the death panels to preclude costly care for the boomers now retiring in mass and being told all the money taken from them was squandered on welfare, and now Obama under dem Pelosi Congress more debt increase than all prior Presidents combined in less than 3.6 years.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346901072337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>