<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345461477000-1</Id><Title>lots of insider selling. is it time to cash in</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/it?s=GOOG+Insider+Transactions why so much selling and no buying?</Msg><Username>sew69kid</Username><Timestamp>1345461477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 07:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345465407492-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wow..1987?</Title><Username>bigheart_md</Username><Timestamp>1345427536248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can't find what you're referring to. But if you know anything much about the '87 Crash, you'd know it was caused by the Europeans, in particular Germany raising rates again and again to cool off inflation (and the US $ going down, forcing USA to raise rates as well). Opposite of Situation now. Nowadays we have Central Banks around the world fostering super-low rates. You'd also know PE Ratios of the Stock Market had gotten to over 21 by start of summer of 1987. Again opposite of what we have now -- now PE Ratios are still at or below their long-term historical average of 16. Thus in 87, before the Crash stocks were over-valued by about 30% (the Crash merely brought them back to normal to slightly below normal values). I know all this since I made money on the '87 Crash, and worked at stockbrokerage then.</Msg><Username>aiwal1</Username><Timestamp>1345465407492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345467043447-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 ACCOUNTING issue in 2007 that USA goverment seems had involvement in it???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345306459194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So they pained ON2 shareholders as a target to ROB? Who brought in MF and BJ and why there is sdtill NO investigations of those criminal activities related to ON2'sd SI?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345467043447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345467607008-4</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 ACCOUNTING issue in 2007 that USA goverment seems had involvement in it???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345306459194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>25 Cutting Edge Firms Funded By The CIA Thursday, August 16, 2012 It’s no secret the Central Intelligence Agency has an investment firm that funds startups that could have a big impact for the Agency. If there is a company out there doing intelligence research, it’s likely that In-Q-Tel, the CIA’s personal investor, either looked them up or made a check out to them. It’s all to ensure that the Agency remains on the forefront of tech. Not long ago, In-Q-Tel invested heavily in a company called Keyhole. Never heard of them? Maybe you know their work, a little project eventually known as Google Earth. So, want to know what’s next for technology? Keep an eye on these 25 companies. The company 3VR Inc develops software enabling organizations to mine data from video. In-Q-Tel first invested in the company in 2005. 3VR works with leading banks, governments, law enforcement and retailers at the moment. 3VR is a video surveillance company that is changing the game</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345467607008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345467720351-5</Id><Topic><Title>When an INTELLIGENCE agency FINAANCE a PUBLIC company???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1290026623000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-11-17 15:43:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: When an INTELLIGENCE agency FINAANCE a PUBLIC company??? By casp321.1 year 4 months ago.Permalink . Just different EXAMPLE of In-Q-Tel related product: Our [3VR] History 3VR Security, Inc., was founded in 2002 by a team of former Inktomi, USWeb and TiVo executives. In the wake of 9/11, their vision was to create a product that would allow for the mining of video data to stop crimes and protect lives. Investors Since 2002, 3VR has been invested in by Menlo Ventures, Kliener Perkins, In-Q-Tel, DAG Ventures, and VantagePoint Venture Partners</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345467720351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345467835875-6</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 ACCOUNTING issue in 2007 that USA goverment seems had involvement in it???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345306459194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2008: the year they intentified their activities with robbing ON2 sharehoders is the year ON2 also joined: In-Q-Tel ... venture capital firm that invests in high-tech companies for the sole purpose of keeping the CIA equipped with the latest in information technology ----------- Participating companies are working to deepen relationships with our delegation of elected officials, expand understanding of New York State procurement processes, as well as connect with relevant New York State agencies. Newest Participants On2 Technologies - On2 provides optimized video compression technologies, Notable Connections The Innovation Center ... we have been pleased to help our participants get to know: Facilitated direct discussions with In-Q-Tel, an intelligence community funding entity</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345467835875</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:03:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345468431736-7</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 ACCOUNTING issue in 2007 that USA goverment seems had involvement in it???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345306459194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2 shareholders yahoo accounts were hacked in October 2009, and I wonder who they were and why the uSA government never tried to warn or find out about it eventhough some ON2 bashers, during that time, said they had fun playing with the .... How could it be possible other than trying to create fear or SCARE ON2 shareholders because of upcoming October 26 in 2009?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345468431736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345469114062-8</Id><Topic><Title>casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know</Title><Username>wmhjr99</Username><Timestamp>1337952121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-25 09:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is bill joll now? On2 Technologies Announces Financial Results for Fourth Quarter of 2007 and First... * Reuters is not responsible for the content in this press release. Wed Jul 2, 2008 5:34pm EDT On2 Technologies Announces Financial Results for Fourth Quarter of 2007 and First Quarter of 2008 As previously disclosed, during the preparation of On2's annual 2007 financial statements, management uncovered evidence that certain documentation provided to the company relating to two sales accounts for which revenue had been recognized in the third quarter of 2007 had been falsified.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345469114062</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474460534-9</Id><Title>Most boring board ever</Title><Msg>most dead board I've ever seen. Zero interest here</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1345474460534</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345478282301-10</Id><Title>Our turn is finally here!</Title><Msg>685 today</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1345478282301</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345479432360-11</Id><Title>kramer said 700</Title><Msg>Enjoy the run. aapl 700, pcln 600. goog 700. still low price and growth strong.</Msg><Username>hinghing1998</Username><Timestamp>1345479432360</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345479547499-12</Id><Title>Has Google Become the Perfect Stock?</Title><Msg>By Dan Caplinger, The Motley Fool Posted 9:53AM 08/20/12 Posted under: Investing - - - - - - Every investor would love to stumble upon the perfect stock. But will you ever really find a stock that provides everything you could possibly want? One thing's for sure: You'll never discover truly great investments unless you actively look for them. Let's discuss the ideal qualities of a perfect stock, then decide if Google (NAS: GOOG) fits the bill. The quest for perfection Stocks that look great based on one factor may prove horrible elsewhere, making due diligence a crucial part of your investing research. The best stocks excel in many different areas, including these important factors: Growth. Expanding businesses show healthy revenue growth. While past growth is no guarantee that revenue will keep rising, it's certainly a better sign than a stagnant top line. Margins. Higher sales mean nothing if a company can't produce profits from them. Strong margins ensure that company can turn revenue into profit. Balance sheet. At debt-laden companies, banks and bondholders compete with shareholders for management's attention. Companies with strong balance sheets don't have to worry about the distraction of debt. Money-making opportunities. Return on equity helps measure how well a company is finding opportunities to turn its resources into profitable business endeavors. Valuation. You can't afford to pay too much for even the best companies. By using normalized figures, you can see how a stock's simple earnings multiple fits into a longer-term context. Dividends. For tangible proof of profits, a check to shareholders every three months can't be beat. Companies with solid dividends and strong commitments to increasing payouts treat shareholders well. With those factors in mind, let's take a closer look at Google. Factor What We Want to See Actual Pass or Fail? Growth 5-Year Annual Revenue Growth 15% 26.3% Pass 1-Year Revenue Growth 12% 29.5% Pass Margins Gross Margin 35% 63.2% Pass Net Margin 15% 25.7% Pass Balance Sheet Debt to Equity 1.3 3.84 Pass Opportunities Return on Equity 15% 19.0% Pass Valuation Normalized P/E 2% 0% Fail 5-Year Dividend Growth 10% 0% Fail Total Score 7 out of 10 Source: S&amp;P Capital IQ. Total score = number of passes. Since we looked at Google last year, the company has kept its seven-point score. But shareholders are impressed with the fact that the search giant's stock has gained more than 30% in the past year. Google has long impressed investors with its command of the search-engine market. Yet the company hasn't stopped there. With its Android mobile operating system, the company took square aim at Apple (NAS: AAPL) and the smartphone dominance of the iPhone. With Chrome, Google got itself into the Internet browser market in a major way, upending Microsoft (NAS: MSFT) and Mozilla to become the browser with the highest market share. But Google hasn't gotten everything right. Its Google+ foray into social networking has largely fallen flat even in the face of Facebook's (NAS: FB) bungled IPO. Moreover, the company still relies almost entirely on ad revenue for its sales, demonstrating its inability to monetize other offerings despite devoting huge amounts of resources to them. One possible game-changer, though, is the Google Wallet electronic payments system. Although the system has been available for a year, Google is taking big steps toward boosting its presence in the marketplace, fixing privacy concerns, and improving its mobile-wallet app to broaden its availability. If Google can beat rivals like eBay's (NAS: EBAY) PayPal and a host of financial institutions to the punch, it could reap some impressive rewards. For Google to improve, it will need to join the growing group of tech stocks that pay dividends. With its impressive earnings, though, that shouldn't be a major problem, and it could create even more interest in the stock. Keep searching No stock is a sure thing, but some stocks are a lot closer to perfect than others. By looking for the perfect stock, you'll go a long way toward improving your investing prowess and learning how to separate out the best investments from the rest. Google may not be perfect, but we've got some other ideas you might like better. Let me invite you to learn about three smart long-term stock plays in the Fool's latest special report. It's yours for the taking and is absolutely free, but don't miss out -- click here and read it today. Also, don't miss out on insight from our top tech analysts on the prospects for both smartphone giant Apple and social-media darling Facebook. Find out all about them in our latest premium reports on Apple and Facebook today.</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1345479547499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345481058474-13</Id><Title>GOOG rolling over due to AAPL move lower</Title><Msg>AAPL was way up, but as soon as it started to roll over GOOG started to roll over. The only difference was that AAPL was up $15 and GOOG was only up $1.</Msg><Username>psusteelers1</Username><Timestamp>1345481058474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345482017874-14</Id><Title>Google or Apple buy TIVO....</Title><Msg>CNBC at 2 says it will be apple....</Msg><Username>chessnotcheckersed</Username><Timestamp>1345482017874</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345482488036-15</Id><Title>up 200 on bad earnings, laying off motorola people, LOL</Title><Msg>its hilarous they haven't done 1 thing right in a 1 year and wall st has pumped this turkey to hgihs</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1345482488036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345483919611-16</Id><Topic><Title>up 200 on bad earnings, laying off motorola people, LOL</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1345482488036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:08:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know it is crazy, but I went long. Totally agree with your points though. Not married to it, just a trade off the lows this morning.</Msg><Username>psusteelers1</Username><Timestamp>1345483919611</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345485336851-17</Id><Title>GOOG and Coal BTU/ANR/ACI Strong Today, Buy more here</Title><Msg>GOOg target 1600, Coal easy to see double reward here. I bought some of them</Msg><Username>chasestockhigh</Username><Timestamp>1345485336851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487104181-18</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG/AAPL correlation</Title><Username>tomsongarry</Username><Timestamp>1343280708626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 01:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG and AAPL are GREEN in RED market. Congrats!</Msg><Username>lindontomson</Username><Timestamp>1345487104181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487904891-19</Id><Topic><Title>up 200 on bad earnings, laying off motorola people, LOL</Title><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1345482488036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:08:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're not alone. I sold my 3M shares @ 670 &amp; bought 10 calls @ 675. "Every time I think I'm out they pull me back in"</Msg><Username>captart7</Username><Timestamp>1345487904891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345489490944-20</Id><Title>The GOOG gap up lg tues morning GO GOOG !!!</Title><Msg>If you cant take it down must go up.Monday is the worst day of week .Huge news pending..shorts will start to cover above 700-800</Msg><Username>lggorillastock</Username><Timestamp>1345489490944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345489600928-21</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 ACCOUNTING issue in 2007 that USA goverment seems had involvement in it???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345306459194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>STill whipping that dead On2 horse geez what a loser</Msg><Username>bigdaddycass15</Username><Timestamp>1345489600928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345490751288-22</Id><Title>Buy GOOG now...</Title><Msg>...at $676,starting tomorrow it will start climbing.imho</Msg><Username>augispr</Username><Timestamp>1345490751288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345493183624-23</Id><Title>AAPL +$17 , GOOG -$1.60</Title><Msg>Just when I buy GOOG it goes flat. LOL!</Msg><Username>psusteelers1</Username><Timestamp>1345493183624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495818863-24</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL +$17 , GOOG -$1.60</Title><Username>psusteelers1</Username><Timestamp>1345493183624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:06:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>goog decoupled from the qqq in the last few hours, looks bearish to me</Msg><Username>sky02316</Username><Timestamp>1345495818863</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495822067-25</Id><Topic><Title>Buy GOOG now...</Title><Username>augispr</Username><Timestamp>1345490751288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:25:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be humbled very shortly if you buy Google now. 20% downside by the end of the year. I have one word for you - VRINGO!</Msg><Username>richardkoeberle</Username><Timestamp>1345495822067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345499658402-26</Id><Title>GOOG Great news.GOOG REPLACES CREDIT CARDS..Sneak Release Today</Title><Msg>Google Play Gift Cards Already Available At Some Target Stores Brad | August 20, 2012 | 0 Comments You may or may not have know, but Google Play gift cards are coming to a store near you very soon. A recent update to the Google Play store boasted of adding support for gift card balances and etc. Soon after, Android Central treated us with some leaked photos of stacks and stack for $10 and $25 Google Play gift cards, and then said that they would probably be available for purchase by the end of August. That’s cool and all, but they were wrong. Not wrong in a bad way of course, but various media outlets have been spotting something else. Droid-Life actually reported that they’ve seen Google Play gift cards as of today. Not in all stores mind you, the picture above is a bunch of Google Play cards for sale at a Target. That said, many different Target stores are already putting up the Google Play gift cards up for sale. It’s finally time that those without a credit card will get some money to spend in the Google Play store! If you look at the photo above, you can tell that Google has done a fantastic job when it comes to marketing the gift card. I mean, really. Just look at it. It stands out from the rest, thus making the Facebook gift/credit card look like it’s not even there. That You may or may not have know, but Google Play gift cards are coming to a store near you very soon. A recent update to the Google Play store boasted of adding support for gift card balances and etc. Soon after, Android Central treated us with some leaked photos of stacks and stack for $10 and $25 Google Play gift cards, and then said that they would probably be available for purchase by the end of August. That’s cool and all, but they were wrong. Not wrong in a bad way of course, but various media outlets have been spotting something else. /google-play-gift-cards-already-available-at-some-target-stores/#lgT40DrOhls2lIkv.99also could have something to deal with that the photo is focused in on the Google Play cards, but, you do have to admit that the cards still really stand out with its triangular design filled with many different colors. I can image that Google will be experiencing a rise in their checkbooks after the Google Play gift cards get their full release in all retailers that have chosen to sell the gift cards. Actually, I may be wrong. With how much money they already have in their checkbooks, it’s no doubt that an extra $1 billion is going to be anything noticeable next to the $100 billion+ they already have. Whatever the case is though, I can tell that this is going to be some seriously good business for Google as they follow the ways of other companies in this area. There’s no doubt that a lot of consumers that don’t use credit cards for the purchases are going to be really, and I mean really happy with this new product in stores.</Msg><Username>starsstoodstil</Username><Timestamp>1345499658402</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345509515286-27</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG and Coal BTU/ANR/ACI Strong Today, Buy more here</Title><Username>chasestockhigh</Username><Timestamp>1345485336851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:55:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Touche' My man , no doubt - Coal rearing it's head- The most beat down sector . Kinda like the rebound in homebuilders but real!</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345509515286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345509742954-28</Id><Title>Goog going to get torched in Court by -</Title><Msg>Vrng, They should go ahead and buy them. A no brainer!</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345509742954</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345509826599-29</Id><Title>NEWS ARTICLE** Why Google Will Beat Apple to $1,000</Title><Msg>article... Why Google Will Beat Apple to $1,000 By MoneyShow Aug 20, 2012 11:10 am With all the love that gets heaped upon Apple, it's easy to lose perspective on other tech juggernauts and their ability to soar.After more than a year of waiting, Google (GOOG) appears ready to break out past $630 resistance. As I first mentioned in April, $630 (blue line) has proved to be a thorn in Google’s side since December 2009. That’s right, for nearly three years Google shares were subdued by $630 resistance. Though the bears persistently dragged Google lower each time the stock neared $630, buyers rarely let the stock slip below $500. And in recent months, the bulls built support for Google near $565 This is a great company, and the rally that’s been in the making for years may have started. Google has already passed the first challenge by moving above $630. If the rally has truly begun, the shares should bounce to $700 as early as this month. In addition to the rally up to $700, buyers should provide support near $630 (the once-formidable resistance level). A move higher makes sense on a valuation basis, too. Analysts following Google stock expect it to earn $49.36 per share in 2013. If the EPS estimate is accurate, the shares will carry a 14 P/E ratio upon reaching $700. A 14 P/E ratio is cheap for a company that consistently increases earnings by more than 16%. Forget about Apple (AAPL) reaching $1,000. Google stock looks ready to hit the $1,000 mark first.</Msg><Username>lggorillastock</Username><Timestamp>1345509826599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345509985042-30</Id><Title>Goog is not the perfect stock ,</Title><Msg>VRNG is fixing to ring the ringtone bell to the tune of billions on patent infridgement. A pure play!</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345509985042</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510118448-31</Id><Title>This is the best site for GOOG stock information</Title><Msg>For excellent and compelling information on GOOG stock, visit, vippennystocksite dotcom</Msg><Username>jack7551847</Username><Timestamp>1345510118448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345510256985-32</Id><Title>Goog better buy vrng pretty quick!</Title><Msg>If they want to avoid bad press and beat aapl to a grand a share.</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345510256985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510305435-33</Id><Topic><Title>This is the best site for GOOG stock information</Title><Username>jack7551847</Username><Timestamp>1345510118448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The site is fantastic and I have subscribed to it</Msg><Username>khalid5842</Username><Timestamp>1345510305435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510345419-34</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL +$17 , GOOG -$1.60</Title><Username>psusteelers1</Username><Timestamp>1345493183624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:06:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vrng is going to toast them! Thats why!</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345510345419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:52:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510503472-35</Id><Topic><Title>This is the best site for GOOG stock information</Title><Username>jack7551847</Username><Timestamp>1345510118448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vippennystocksite, is a very well structured site</Msg><Username>tammy6285</Username><Timestamp>1345510503472</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345511838000-36</Id><Title>Mark Cuban- Astute investor</Title><Msg>Every outstanding share of the Co VRNG. Whether a naked short or in possesion . They are in control of the share price till they make a forward move as A trade in possesion. They have the money they are just figuring the best way to spend less. Cuban knows this too! Goog has little time to decide as demand for stock outstrips available. Cuban is a smart man - He worked this and saw it coming!It,s not a goog killer by ay means they have infinite pockets but a boon to vrng holders as Cuban Knows - A pure straight up pay day!</Msg><Username>rainmaker7140</Username><Timestamp>1345511838000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345518210512-37</Id><Topic><Title>NEWS ARTICLE** Why Google Will Beat Apple to $1,000</Title><Username>lggorillastock</Username><Timestamp>1345509826599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true. Apple will be at $1000 1st.</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345518210512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345518629610-38</Id><Title>Why iPhone makes more money than Google?</Title><Msg>Why does Google make more money from iPhone than from Android?</Msg><Username>obamanure</Username><Timestamp>1345518629610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>