<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347252443842-1</Id><Topic><Title>Goog Pullback To $650 This Week</Title><Username>frtgrdn21</Username><Timestamp>1347234637876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>haha..... that's a good one!... you shorted and now trying to scare people into selling?? HAHA.... why don't you just buy stocks in good company's like google and enjoy the ride up like everyone else....</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1347252443842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 00:47:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347280598028-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why did ON2 have two CTOs: From 2007 to 2010?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1329807903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-02-21 02:05:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nufront NS115 Adopts Hantro Video IP Press Release: 　VeriSilicon – Tue, Sep 4, 2012 7:30 PM EDT "Nufront is a fabless semiconductor company with strong R&amp;D ability and technology capability. We are proud to support their efforts in integrating Hantro video IP into their product," says Dr. Wayne Dai, President and CEO of VeriSilicon. "We are confident that VP8 video format based technologies will become ubiquitous in multi-media smart devices." SHANGHAI, Sept. 5, 2012 /PRNewswire/ -- VeriSilicon Holdings Co., Ltd. ... ("VeriSilicon"), a world-class, custom silicon solutions and semiconductor IP provider, announced today that Hantro G1 Multi-format Decoder and Hantro H1 Multi-format Encoder have been integrated by Nufront, a leading fables semiconductor company in China, in a high performance application processor chip, NS115. VeriSilicon's Hantro video IPs enable Nufront's NS115 to achieve full HD video encode and decode capability, while supporting multiple video formats such as VP8 for WebM and WebRTC, H.264, MVC, MPEG-2/4, DivX, VC-1, RealVideo, AVS, etc. NS115 integrates two 1.5GHz ARM Cortex-A9 cores and is designed and manufactured in advanced 40nm LP process node. Through the integrated Hantro G1 Multi-format Decoder... and Hantro H1 Multi-format Encoder, -------- October 26, 2009 SELECTED CONSOLIDATED HISTORICAL FINANCIAL DATA OF ON2 ON2's Research and development 1) Year Ended December 31, 2004 $884,000 2) Year Ended December 31, 2005 $1,035,000 3) Year Ended December 31, 2006 $972,000 4) Year Ended December 31, 2007 $3,833,000 5) Year Ended December 31, 2008 $10,736,000 ---------------- 1) Six Months Ended June 30, 2008 $5,817,000 2) Six Months Ended June 30, 2009 $3,885,000</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347280598028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347280797808-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Hantro, Verisilicon, Google: Was it spin-in or reverse-merger?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1335274336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-24 09:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tomi Jalonen PAST: Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. | Spoke Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. of On2 Technologies, Inc CURRENT: Re: VeriSilicon Releases New Generation of Hantro Video IP Products 24-Feb-12 11:30 pm Tomi Jalonen VeriSilicon and WebM Support Monday, January 24, 2011 | 4:43 PM Guest blogger Tomi Jalonen is Director of Product Marketing for Hantro video IP at VeriSilicon</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347280797808</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347280972842-4</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: MOVING/REMOVING: Is it "NORM"?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1301831620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-04-03 07:53:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Hare and Hieb were moved from Hambrecht to Oppenheimer and then to anotjher company after completing ON2 acquisition of Hantro AND They Moved Tomi from ON2 to Verisilicon to CONTINUE promoting ON2's Hantro with semiconductors companies: Pete Wendell, Erich Schmit's friend is INVESTED in Sierra and Sierra and Verisilicon: Tomi Jalonen PAST: Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. | Spoke Tomi Jalonen, On2 Technologies, Inc. of On2 Technologies, Inc CURRENT: Re: VeriSilicon Releases New Generation of Hantro Video IP Products 24-Feb-12 11:30 pm Tomi Jalonen VeriSilicon and WebM Support Monday, January 24, 2011 | 4:43 PM Guest blogger Tomi Jalonen is Director of Product Marketing for Hantro video IP at VeriSilicon</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347280972842</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347281294964-5</Id><Title>OBAMA-Huge lead now in Polls</Title><Msg>Romney falling way behind!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347281294964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347281967368-6</Id><Topic><Title>Keep your eyes on the Newswires for a Google settlement or acquisition of Vringo</Title><Username>video_investor</Username><Timestamp>1346454471483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google has to do something, they are definitely at fault of infringing on VRNG Patents. Time is running out ,OCT. 16 coming quick.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347281967368</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347282399830-7</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Hantro, Verisilicon, Google: Was it spin-in or reverse-merger?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1335274336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-04-24 09:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wayne Dai [the founder, Chairman, President and CEO of VeriSilicon Holdings Co., Ltd] talked to Eric Schmidt about Android ecosystem in China at The Sierra Venture CIO Summit in Sept. 2010.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347282399830</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282762388-8</Id><Title>Having been up 155 points in a little over a month, this pig is way overbought at this point, especially with that big wick on the daily chart</Title><Msg>I would not be long until the Fed nuts decide to print more money, even then the pop should be short lived</Msg><Username>jd_bozeman</Username><Timestamp>1347282762388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284865826-9</Id><Title>720 coming</Title><Msg>soon</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1347284865826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347291499380-10</Id><Title>Goog should reduce the price on nexus 7 16GB to 199 and</Title><Msg>The 8GB to 179 and do away with $25 play credit. It will attract more buyers with not much diff in profit margin. It should also sell through 3rd party online so people can buy with out paying sales tax.</Msg><Username>cpataxweb</Username><Timestamp>1347291499380</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347291611234-11</Id><Title>cant u just taste the greed dripping from the mouths of people in this</Title><Msg>most overvalued its ever been..right here</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1347291611234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:40:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347291878048-12</Id><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...GUIDES FOR 40% 2013 REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE NET INCOME. NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.process of testing our new message boards. Please provide your feedback so that we can optimize the user experience.</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347291878048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347293991851-13</Id><Title>Any update on split? Is that why this stock is running up?</Title><Msg>Hi: Do any of you folks have any links to news on the split. It was supposed to happen in September. And once the details are announced, all current options will become adjusted to handle the split. That will cause a drop in volume on the adjusted options. At that point MMs start increasing the spreads on adjusted options. Is this why the stock is running up - to trap option holders whose options become adjusted due to the split and harder to trade? Appreciate the inputs of the expert traders on this board. I personally think this stock is going down because the problems with their Motorola acquisition are just beginning. Just watch how their margins shrink over the next couple of quarters. I worked closely with Motorola at the highest levels and its worse and slower than a government agency. TIA</Msg><Username>cbolaki</Username><Timestamp>1347293991851</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347300713543-14</Id><Title>AAPL &amp; GOOG are the BIGGEST JOKES in the MKT...this no DIVIDEND, over hyped, Cramer pushin', CNBC pumpin', kiddie lovin', parent haten', no return, Idiot-phone 5 floppin' trash is the GREATEST SHORT in U.S. HISTORY !!</Title><Msg>sell nut cases......</Msg><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1347300713543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:11:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347302086233-15</Id><Title>Lots of stocks that got trashed bashed to death showing life!!!</Title><Msg>From OPEN FSLR CSTR GMCR SODA and list goes on Getting feeling that some funds that were shorts are getting out of the market way Risk on</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347302086233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347302208037-16</Id><Title>Google, I'm putting 720 out there, 707 by close</Title><Msg>today</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1347302208037</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347304999926-17</Id><Title>Time for leadership for Google, 739, lowest 1 yr target</Title><Msg>Can lift the Nasd</Msg><Username>chairman_westgate</Username><Timestamp>1347304999926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:23:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347305570695-18</Id><Title>Chart says 680 by Friday.</Title><Msg>Profittaking pullback imminent.</Msg><Username>tc8848</Username><Timestamp>1347305570695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306155551-19</Id><Topic><Title>Chart says 680 by Friday.</Title><Username>tc8848</Username><Timestamp>1347305570695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>my pivot calculator says different 740.00 by Friday close, GLTA!</Msg><Username>tyronica_seaton2002</Username><Timestamp>1347306155551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308813137-20</Id><Topic><Title>Goog Pullback To $650 This Week</Title><Username>frtgrdn21</Username><Timestamp>1347234637876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$5 down and another 7% drop by Friday's close. Major moves on Thursday and Friday, when the Fed won't announce a new QE3 and the markets crash. Watch and learn.</Msg><Username>frtgrdn21</Username><Timestamp>1347308813137</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347310118950-21</Id><Topic><Title>TWO STOCK TO RETIRE WITH....AONE &amp; AMEL :::::: Lithium batteries are the new way to save the planet. Soon these two stocks will skrocket to the moon.</Title><Username>frankmalone90</Username><Timestamp>1347301066590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They say that a fool is born every minute. I guess you were the latest one to enter the world. Go back and look at a chart on this stock genius.</Msg><Username>bingolingo1234</Username><Timestamp>1347310118950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347313526682-22</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL &amp; GOOG are the BIGGEST JOKES in the MKT...this no DIVIDEND, over hyped, Cramer pushin', CNBC pumpin', kiddie lovin', parent haten', no return, Idiot-phone 5 floppin' trash is the GREATEST SHORT in U.S. HISTORY !!</Title><Username>zip_i_t_do_da</Username><Timestamp>1347300713543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:11:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so what positions u have in these stocks? would be interesting to know!</Msg><Username>hypocritrepublican</Username><Timestamp>1347313526682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 17:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347317003955-23</Id><Title>Why can't so many see through Obama??/</Title><Msg>Quote taken from above link on Yahoo Finance Home Page titled: 'Romney Tax Plan: The Math Does Add Up Says Romney Advisor Glenn Hubbard': "President Obama wants to extend tax cuts for middle class Americans and raise them on households making more than $250,000 a year." That sentence is ridiculous and another dem complete OXYMORON just as is any talk of financial reform by dems with the BIGGEST TAX EVER YET TO KICK IN 2014 Obamacare Unaffordable Care Act. Again why do you think the dems delayed it from kicking in until 2014? Easy to blame repubs for the obvious failure if Romney gets in and to gloat if Obama wins and the USA is indeed 100% on the dole now favoring a UK socialist type government. One has to be completely naïve to believe $250,000 per year is rich (even though it may seem so to us not making that much.) Two things must be kept in mind:1. And most important all S-Corps and LLC's filing as corporations pay taxes at the individual level with the corporate taxes flowing through their personal returns as a conduit. This means under the Obama plan all such corporations earning over 250K get hit killing more jobs. 2: Ron Paul is correct in his assertion that a dollar today is worth about $.03 (3 cents) when compared to a 1913 silver dollar (the year dems signed the Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE into law.Do the math $250,000 x $.03 and there you have it the real Obama con about those evil filthy rich over $250K.</Msg><Username>rldcis</Username><Timestamp>1347317003955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347320791557-24</Id><Title>ROMNEY-The RIDDLER</Title><Msg>He talks in riddles, then his staff tries to put together what he said ,then spin it. It'll be like '00-'08 all over again, it just didn't work.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347320791557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347321085629-25</Id><Topic><Title>shorting more of GOOG going to 100.00</Title><Username>raystock48072</Username><Timestamp>1215869676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2008-07-12 09:34:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Goog going to 100.00 a share this year. Shorting is the way to make money" Raystock has been posting bad advice and losing money for many years.</Msg><Username>raystock_psychiatrist</Username><Timestamp>1347321085629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:51:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347321194790-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why can't so many see through Obama??/</Title><Username>rldcis</Username><Timestamp>1347317003955</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really think the super rich recieving the tax breaks are really creating jobs, take your blinders off. The Bush tax cuts from 00-08 lead us down this road. The super rich are coating their own pockets. What a joke!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347321194790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347321327056-27</Id><Topic><Title>Goog Pullback To $650 This Week</Title><Username>frtgrdn21</Username><Timestamp>1347234637876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 19:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have watched and learned already.... i have watched this stock rise over 100 points in the last few months and learned exactly how much further it will go up... you make yourself sound educated on knowing about this stock... because obviously EVERY stock goes up and down... and so it drops 5 today and your like see look i know what i am talking about... well if you knew what you were talking about you would realize that this stock will see 800 a share well before it ever sees 600 again.... your just like all the other negative posters on here.. when i was buying in at 580... they were saying sell sell sell short short short.... then it was at 625.. and they were like sell sell sell.... short short short..... and at 650... 670.... 680... 690... 700.... 700+ they continued..... so who cares if it drop 5 or even 15.... while you sit there and claim victory and say you were right.. i'll be at my computer buying more shores... and writing another message to you in a few months when i have eb more shares and they are 800+ a share,....</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1347321327056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347322445353-28</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA-Huge lead now in Polls</Title><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347281294964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody noticing Romney's decline.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347322445353</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347324565690-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bullish video on DOM</Title><Username>traderperfect</Username><Timestamp>1347215006810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:23:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the post, it looks like he nailed the call today.</Msg><Username>r.perry1971</Username><Timestamp>1347324565690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 20:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347334404304-30</Id><Topic><Title>Keep your eyes on the Newswires for a Google settlement or acquisition of Vringo</Title><Username>video_investor</Username><Timestamp>1346454471483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you really think VRNG would be trading flat at 3.5 if those in the know thought they had a shot to win or be bought out?</Msg><Username>bagholderagain</Username><Timestamp>1347334404304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347335108153-31</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA-Huge lead now in Polls</Title><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347281294964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 08:48:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These Pollsters are in the bag for Obama and the numbers are a scam. Carter was 17 points ahead of Reagan and Reagan won. Polls are meaningless until ONE WEEK before the election. Then they give you real numbers so they don't look so stupid. Now, they are just trying to get Omama some momentum.</Msg><Username>captart7</Username><Timestamp>1347335108153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347335917120-32</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY-The RIDDLER</Title><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347320791557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing that doesn't work is Obama. He's present but absent from any important decision. He avoids them because he is unable to draw upon any knowledge or experience. He is just and empty "clean" suit. His time has past and the only job he will ever create is the one opened after he is thrown out like yesterday's trash. A total &amp; complete failure at every leavel. They should build him an empty library to house his engo and nothing else.</Msg><Username>captart7</Username><Timestamp>1347335917120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 23:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>