<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343469110860-1</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG/AAPL correlation</Title><Username>tomsongarry</Username><Timestamp>1343280708626</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 01:31:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google Inc. is shifting 3,000 jobs from its newly acquired Motorola Mobility unit to downtown Chicago in a move Mayor Rahm Emanuel hopes will anchor a burgeoning tech sector in the nation's third largest city. The jobs were based in Libertyville, a suburb an hour outside of Chicago, but will be relocated next summer following Google's purchase of the company for $12.5 billion in May. Mr. Emanuel said he hoped Google's presence would attract start-up technology companies and stem the Midwestern brain drain. This offers Chicago an opportunity to be a game changer, to be a digital Mecca</Msg><Username>bakert82</Username><Timestamp>1343469110860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 05:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343472995443-2</Id><Topic><Title>Patent war: VirnetX (VHC) from 1 to 41+ and can Vringo ( VRNG) does the same thing?!!!</Title><Username>hblodgett500</Username><Timestamp>1343459470620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 03:11:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>M. Cuban: VRNG management must check on Ichan, Hambrecht, T. Armstrong, Schmidt, relations then UFL/Youtube, ... AND here is different story: Vringo's Stout Trumps 13 Tech Giants In NTP Patent Suit July 25, 2012 NTP Inc. -- the company cofounded by Donald Stout, who is a Vringo (VRNG) director and Chairman of Vringo's intellectual property committee -- announced Monday that it has reached settlements with 13 tech companies. These companies have been infringing on NTP patents for years, and NTP is finally going to be compensated. The settlement figure, though not disclosed, could go beyond anything we have ever seen. The list of companies that agreed to settle with NTP is impressive. ================ Issued March 2012 different ones: Why Google Might Be Going to $0 James Altucher Saturday, March 31st, 2012 Editor’s note: James Altucher is an investor, programmer, author, and entrepreneur. He is Managing Director of Formula Capital and has written 6 books on investing. His latest books are I Was Blind But Now I See and FAQ ME. --------------- "... The trial is October 16 in the Eastern District Court of Virginia and will last 2 weeks. An appeal process can take, at most, a year. ..." "... Think: NTP suing RIMM on patents. NTP had nothing going on other than the patents. Like Vringo/Innovate. NTP won over $600 million from RIMM once Research in Motion realized this is a serious issue and not one they can just chalk up to a bad nightmare. ..." "... Guess who NTP's lawyer was? Donald Stout. Guess who Vringo's patent lawyer is? Donald Stout. Why is Donald Stout so good? He was an examiner at the US Patent Office. He knows patents. ..."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343472995443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 06:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343473291019-3</Id><Topic><Title>What a SCAM court sysem: with 100-share lead vs 178 million ON2 shares???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1303700884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-04-24 23:08:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember Weiner, Universal, ON2, and New York: Politics in NY: What a SCAM court sysem: with 100-share lead vs 178 million ON2 shares??? By casp321 . 1 year 3 months ago . Permalink What a SCAM court sysem: with 100-share lead vs 178 million ON2 shares??? He or she [Lead Plaintiff ] must be capable of representing the interests of all the members of the class action. Participating companies are working to deepen relationships with our delegation of elected officials, expand understanding of New York State procurement processes, as well as connect with relevant New York State agencies. Newest Participants On2 Technologies - On2 provides optimized video compression technologies</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343473291019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343473907212-4</Id><Topic><Title>Patent war: VirnetX (VHC) from 1 to 41+ and can Vringo ( VRNG) does the same thing?!!!</Title><Username>hblodgett500</Username><Timestamp>1343459470620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 03:11:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clip from youtube Search Advertising With Google: Part 3 - What is Quality Score? Why Google Might Be Going to $0 James Altucher Saturday, March 31st, 2012 Well, Google must have a defense? Even though their AdWords results are sorted by click-throughs in the way described by the patent maybe they sorted in a different way (a “work-around” of the patent), and didn’t infringe on the patent. Maybe: But look at Google economist Hal Varian describing their algorithm right here in this video. And compare with the patent claim filed in court by Vringo. You decide. But it looks like the exact same to me. Maybe: But does Google want to risk losing ten billion dollars plus having all of their customers sued. The district the case is getting tried in rules 70% in favor of the plaintiff in patent cases. Most patent trials get settled on the court steps. Maybe: But then there’s still Microsoft /Yahoo search which, by the way, sorts based on click-throughs and has not been sued yet.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343473907212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:11:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343476223526-5</Id><Title>GOOG: Special, What do you think</Title><Msg>Whypennystocks, should be visited for compelling information and for developing a proper base for understanding of AAPL</Msg><Username>theclick5842</Username><Timestamp>1343476223526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343477079234-6</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG: Special, What do you think</Title><Username>theclick5842</Username><Timestamp>1343476223526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whypennystocks, is a very well structured website.</Msg><Username>tammy6285</Username><Timestamp>1343477079234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343477211854-7</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG: Special, What do you think</Title><Username>theclick5842</Username><Timestamp>1343476223526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 07:50:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic site, I have subscribed to it</Msg><Username>khalid5842</Username><Timestamp>1343477211854</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343491666734-8</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: BELIEVE it or NOT: Google SCREWED up!!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1298984629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-03-01 08:03:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New York, politics and Weiner/Universal: why there is NO INVESTIGATION regarding these relation? Just wonder since WHEN Universal are/WERE getting FREE-RIDE from ON2 shareholders that Comcast working too HARD to SLOW-DOWN or BLOCK the SERVICE that have already got PAID for. Is not this CRIMINAL acts on its own??? Why tracing/tracking/blocking a SERVICE that's paid and LEGAL? Believe it or not, Google and its ORIGINATORs SCREWED up by letting AMETUREs and DUMBs handle the "INTELLIGENCE" agencies's OPERATIONs USING a small and PUBLIC company's, called ON2, RETAIL INVESTORs MONEY by ASSUMING these investors would be "dumb" enough to let them run their OPERATIONs using ON2's Video products including "digital signage and security and surveillance." They pushed, by DUMPING ON2's money making products--FlixEngine, FlixCloud, miniature-VP8 NOT OPTIMIZED one--, from one side to HIDE but it STuCK up from the other side and EXPOSED Google's relation to Chinese PRIVATE compay, called Verisilicon. When a PLAN does NOT have a solid FOUNADTION because of those involved in it, NO MATTER HOW HARD Google and its ORIGINATORs planners trying to FIX it, they make it WORSE.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343491666734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343492692592-9</Id><Topic><Title>Patent war: VirnetX (VHC) from 1 to 41+ and can Vringo ( VRNG) does the same thing?!!!</Title><Username>hblodgett500</Username><Timestamp>1343459470620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 03:11:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To LEARN a GOOD lesson, VRNG BOD and Management can STUDY the following RELATIONs as they're getting ready for October 2012 court date. Even if those involved might have "legal" case among themselves, but keep in mid that even with that kind of the case its a FEW million dollars, arguments among those "old" friends, AGAINST billions of dollars in VRGN case. Is the other real of just DIVERTING ATTENTION is UP to VRNG legal team to educate themselves and it's just a thoulght not even argument in my side. Google takes over ON2 and Motorola at some point, here are those directly or indirectly INVOLVED in the "stealth" process to make those transactions to happen: May 2007: ON2 &amp; Hantro deal and Rumor related to Adobe; Hambrecht, T. Armstrong, M. Cuban and talk about UFL Oct 9, 2007 Google to Put YouTube Videos on Its Ad Network Oct. 21, 2007 NBC Yanks YouTube Channel? Nov 1, 2007 Hambrecht: ON2 and Hantro deal was completed on Nov 1, 2007 Nov 6, 2007 Pete Wendell: Sierra Ventures, exixtng investor in Verisilicon, joined VeriSilicon Holdings Co. to raise more money for chip design technology: Nov 12, 2007 Eric Schmidt: Android was released on Nov 12, 2007 Nov 30, 2007 Carl Icahn: Started pushing Motrola for Split on Nov 30, 2007 April 07, 2008 Carl Icahn today announced that they have reached an agreement under which William R. Hambrecht, founder, chairman and chief executive officer of WR Hambrecht + Co. and co-founder of Hambrecht &amp; Quist, and Keith Meister, ..., will be nominated for election to Motorola's Board of Directors at the 2008 Annual Meeting of Shareholders and included in the Company's 2008 proxy statement. ---- LionsGate: Icahn and M. Cuban and LGF stock handling after LionsGate BOD and Management making Icahn to intent to sell his stocks in LGF???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1343492692592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 12:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>