<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353753508245-1</Id><Title>Why It’s Time For Local SMBs To Get On Board With Mobile And Why Launch for Local from Local Corp will have Big Future</Title><Msg>Oct 15, 2012 at 10:25am ET by Stephanie Hobbs While attending BIA/Kelsey’s SMB Digital Marketing 2012 Conference in Chicago last month, I was surprised by the results of a recent LCM study, which showed that only 20 percent of local businesses said they have experience with mobile marketing. Small businesses today operate in a time when smartphone adoption is growing rapidly (eMarketer predicts there will be 116 million U.S. smartphone users, representing 37% of the population, by the end of this year.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753508245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:38:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353753708278-2</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Time For Local SMBs To Get On Board With Mobile And Why Launch for Local from Local Corp will have Big Future</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753508245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:38:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get Going Fast with the Propel package for $249! • No contracts or setup fees • More affordable than the competition • Up and running in 7-10 business days – guaranteed You Get It All • Websites • Mobile • Social • Business listings • Banner advertising • Content</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753708278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:41:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353753839996-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Time For Local SMBs To Get On Board With Mobile And Why Launch for Local from Local Corp will have Big Future</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753508245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:38:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arizona Business Gazette Mobile marketing success for local business Sept. 13, 2012 07:11 AM Use of mobile devices continues to grow by leaps and bounds, and local business owners should be taking notice now more than ever. A new "Mobile Path to Purchase" study conducted by Nielsen tracked what consumers are doing with their mobile devices. According to the study, consumers show a strong preference for finding information related to local contact and purchases, such as looking up a business location, accessing map and driving directions and calling a business. Depending on the category and device used, as many as 73 percent of mobile users report looking for a business phone number and subsequently calling the business. In addition, up to 84 percent of mobile searchers report looking up a business location and accessing driving directions. Those, quite simply, are huge numbers that are driving a great deal of activity and leads for local businesses. For business owners, of course, the implications are clear: You need to be visible in mobile search, and your ads or listings should always include a phone number and directions Read more: Arizona Business Gazette</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753839996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:43:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353759509445-4</Id><Topic><Title>Why It’s Time For Local SMBs To Get On Board With Mobile And Why Launch for Local from Local Corp will have Big Future</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353753508245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 05:38:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think about it; 50% is a massive number. Fully half of all search queries coming from smartphones have local intent. That translates into many billions of local searches from mobile devices in 2012 (well over 20 billion). In addition to browser-based local search there’s a huge volume of local queries coming through apps, where mobile consumers spend roughly 80% of their time (Nielsen). Nobody is tracking local queries in apps. It could be billions more annually. The following comScore-Localeze-15Miles survey reflects that half of smartphone owners (Q1 2012) use apps for local search. Despite this huge volume of local queries in mobile, a majority of SMBs and brands still don’t have mobile-optimized websites (or RWD sites). It’s not only amazing, it’s “marketing malpractice.” Source: Greg Sterling on Screenwork, where you can read the complete article.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1353759509445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:18:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353764091884-5</Id><Title>got it bing!</Title><Msg>have you google fanbois tried bing?</Msg><Username>genexcess</Username><Timestamp>1353764091884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:34:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353771675310-6</Id><Title>Nexus</Title><Msg>Bought my brother one for his birthday. It broke in less then 2 weeks</Msg><Username>lotto1717</Username><Timestamp>1353771675310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:41:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786237906-7</Id><Topic><Title>Soros added 190,000 shares of GOOG</Title><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1353520175903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 12:49:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure "what's up", but I saw on my Think or Swim news info, posted at around market close on Friday, that the CEO of Morgan Stanley and some Trust Fund, also associated with MS, filed with the SEC to sell a combined total of 207k+ shares of Google. The CEO was 200k+, and the Trust was 7k+.</Msg><Username>schwan987</Username><Timestamp>1353786237906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:43:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353795764948-8</Id><Topic><Title>SAPX</Title><Username>angry_negro</Username><Timestamp>1335793646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-04-30 09:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you're angry because you bought SAPX too high. Buying in April yee-ouch!</Msg><Username>dollar_dividend</Username><Timestamp>1353795764948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:22:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>