<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347876917154-1</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney to outline how he would govern By KASIE HUNT and KEN THOMAS | Associated Press – 2 hrs 25 mins ago WASHINGTON (AP) — Mitt Romney will seek this week to explain more about what he would do as president, a strategy shift intended to change the trajectory of a race that President Barack Obama appears to be winning. With the new push, Romney is looking to put behind him a turbulent week that saw him stumbling to respond to an ongoing crisis in the Middle East. And he's spent hours preparing for debates, mindful that they may be his last best hope of overtaking Obama. Romney advisers spent the weekend in Boston hashing out a plan to right his struggling campaign. On Monday, top advisers planned to explain how the campaign would change tact as the candidate himself began a major push to Hispanic voters.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347876917154</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:15:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347877029939-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sep 17, 2012 Romney to outline how he would govern By KASIE HUNT and KEN THOMAS WASHINGTON (AP) — Mitt Romney will seek this week to explain more about what he would do as president, a strategy shift intended to change the trajectory of a race that President Barack Obama appears to be winning. With the new push, Romney is looking to put behind him a turbulent week that saw him stumbling to respond to an ongoing crisis in the Middle East. And he's spent hours preparing for debates, mindful that they may be his last best hope of overtaking Obama. Romney advisers spent the weekend in Boston hashing out a plan to right his struggling campaign.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347877029939</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347877089895-3</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sep 17, 2012 Romney to outline how he would govern By KASIE HUNT and KEN THOMAS WASHINGTON (AP) — Mitt Romney will seek this week to explain more about what he would do as president, a strategy shift intended to change the trajectory of a race that President Barack Obama appears to be winning. With the new push, Romney is looking to put behind him a turbulent week that saw him stumbling to respond to an ongoing crisis in the Middle East.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347877089895</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347877274116-4</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!!! After a few tries posting the same message with different part of the article Yahoo Admin was FORCED to unlock the 1st message posted insted of the last. WOW!!!!! Who does Yahoo support: Republican or Democrats, and why they are using PUBLIC scrach Board to take side???? WOWWW:</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347877274116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:21:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347879413996-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2009 McLaughlin will report to Aneesh Chopra, recently named as the nation’s chief technology officer. As a peripheral note, McLaughlin will be the third high-level Google veteran to join the Obama administration since it took command of the executive branch, according to a New York Times story. Katie Stanton (a veteran of Google’s new business development team, named as White House director of citizen participation) and Sonal Shah (previously a member of Google’s philanthropy division, named to the transition team) were the other former Google employees tapped for the Obama team Google's Global Policy Head Said to Join Obama Administration By Bloomberg June 3, 2009 Andrew McLaughlin is leaving his post as head of Google's global public policy division to become deputy technology officer for the Obama administration. McLaughlin, who worked from 1999 to 2002 to help found ICANN, was Google's first public policy executive. In his new position, McLaughlin will be working with Obama's chief technology officer, Aneesh Chopra, the former Virginia secretary of technology. 000000000000000 Google CEO to endorse Obama: WSJ (AFP) – Oct 20, 2008 WASHINGTON (AFP) — Google chief executive Eric Schmidt plans to endorse Barack Obama this week and campaign for the Democratic presidential candidate, The Wall Street Journal reported Monday. "I'm doing this personally," Schmidt told the newspaper in an interview, adding that the Mountain View, California-based Internet search giant was "officially neutral" in the November 4 presidential election.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347879413996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 06:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347879642185-6</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Latest Obama stage prop: Retired mega-Dem donor/former Google asks prez to raise his taxes By Michelle Malkin • September 26, 2011 At a LinkedIn town hall/campaign rally forum with President Obama today, a questioner picked “randomly” from the audience just happened to beg the president to raise his taxes: The questioner is one Doug Edwards, an early Google employee who is retired and who has given gobs and gobs of cash to the Democratic party via Tim Carney: It seems relevant to point out that this rich liberal is Doug Edwards from the Obama-friendly and regulation-friendly Google. Edwards has given $300,000 to politicians since 2000 — every single dime to Democrats. He specifically said he wanted his higher taxes to cover Pell Grants. That’s about 60 Pell Grants he could have provided.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347879642185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347879785288-7</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Owen Thomas Dec 27, 2008 Google Execs Pay $150,000 for Obama Bash It's Google's presidency. We're just watching it. Six Google executives, including CEO Eric Schmidt and cofounder Larry Page, have donated $25,000 apiece to fund President Barack Obama's swearing-in party. Taken as a whole, the Googlers' cash is one of the largest corporate donations to Obama's inaugural committee. Marissa Mayer, an early Google employee who now oversees its search engine, and David Drummond, the company's top lawyer, also donated, as did YouTube cofounder Chad Hurley and Dick Costolo, the former CEO of FeedBurner, an advertising startup acquired by Google last year, Unlike election spending, donations to cover the expenses of an inauguration are relatively unlimited. Obama's committee has capped donations at $50,000. It's a time-honored way to win influence.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347879785288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347880155151-8</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I consider the recent video clip as free Ad to support Obama by Google in 2012 USA Presidential election year!!!! casp321 Google Denies Early Ad Deal for Obama Campaign By Judson Berger Published June 16, 2011 A Google spokesman vehemently denied Thursday that President Obama's 2012 campaign got early access to a new advertising program, claiming a sales rep who suggested as much was just plain wrong.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347880155151</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347880198669-9</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The technology in question, called "cost-per-lead," charges clients for every time a piece of personal information is collected from users. A staff member at the National Republican Senatorial Committee thought he was looking at an early version of the program after he saw an Obama ad on the site RealClearPolitics last month and emailed Google about the possibility of getting in on the action.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347880198669</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:09:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347880632124-10</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'World News' Political Insights: Mitt Romney's Own Empty-Chair Challenge By Rick Klein | ABC OTUS News – 10 hrs ago. ANALYSIS Things haven't been going Mitt Romney's way since roughly the moment that Clint Eastwood dressed down that empty chair. It isn't simply that the stunt distracted from an otherwise solid Republican National Convention, overshadowing a big introductory moment for the Romney campaign. It's that Romney has struggled to fill the leadership chair himself, despite several high-profile opportunities handed to him by national and international events. Yes, President Obama got a convention bump. Yes, the fact that this race has a frontrunner for the first time basically since it began can change just as quickly in the other direction. But a static campaign is suddenly on the move. That movement is throwing Romney off his main campaign message; a candidate who has long calculated that the only issue that matters is the economy is chasing headlines, with varying degrees of success. The questionable timing of Romney's response to anti-American unrest in the Middle East - violence that would include the death of four Americans, including the U.S. ambassador to Libya - constituted a missed opportunity for the Republican nominee. The campaign seems conflicted at times on what other opportunities to pursue in taking on Obama. Recent Romney messaging has focused on welfare policy, the administration's stance toward China, and even mentions of "God" on U.S. currency, to mention just a sampling. Romney's laser-like focus on the economy was supposed to take advantage of all that. But just seven weeks before the election, that strategy doesn't seem to be working.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347880632124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347885259950-11</Id><Title>Facebook $FB up in Pre-Hours Last: 22.45 Change: +0.450 (+2.05%)</Title><Msg>FB up in Pre-Hours Last: 22.45 Change: +0.450 (+2.05%)</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347885259950</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890151403-12</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL: Yahoo BLOCKING any word starting with "I" and continueing with "s" and Google Youtube runners, who might also be Iranian descent and possibly his relative, possibly worked for Savak and turtored Iranian political prisoners under the Shah, do not want to block a video clip which is disturbing to people religious believe??? This why It seems Google trumping Republican Plan to help Obama to be re-elected as USA president in 2012. This is for Republic supprt and might be anothe "october-surprise" for you: Sep 16, 2012 Iran on brink of nuclear bomb in six-seven months: Netan... By Matt Spetalnick and Dan Williams The unusually public dispute between close allies - coupled with Obama's decision not to meet with [Netan] later this month - has exposed a gaping U.S.-[sIrae] divide and stepped up pressure on the U.S. leader in the final stretch of a tight presidential election campaign. ------------- Re: When will be Google turn? By casp321.6 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . You need just to DECODE what they mean. Was/is it NOT? This is HOW they make it kosher and halal at the SAME "BakerHouse" and "sell" it as kosher OR halal, depending who their AUDIENCE might be!!!!! ----- "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. ----- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday. ----- Sen. Jim Demint offers blunt words on Iran Thursday, 16 July 2009 11:37 Rabbi Hillel Goldberg I lead into the American side of the equation with this question: What does Iran think when it hears, “We will not take the military option off the table”? ----- US Sens question Halliburton Selling Nuclear Technology to Iran neverknwo / LiveLeak | May 26, 2007 Halliburton VP, Sherry Williams testifies at a Senate hearing about the company's dealings with Iran-- Halliburton is charged with selling nuclear technology to Iran. Halliburton, the notorious U.S. energy company, sold key nuclear-reactor components to a private Iranian oil company called Oriental Oil Kish as recently as 2005, using offshore subsidiaries to circumvent U.S. sanctions. The story is particularly juicy because [VP Chen?y], who now claims to want to stop Iran from getting nukes, was president of Halliburton in the mid-1990s, at which time he may have advocated business dealings with Iran, in violation of U.S. law. Source: "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. -------------- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday. -------------- Sen. Jim Demint offers blunt words on Iran Thursday, 16 July 2009 11:37 Rabbi Hillel Goldberg He’s clear on what the US must do to counter Iran’s pursuit of a nuclear weapon, and on what [sIrael] will do. He’s very blunt about both. I lead into the American side of the equation with this question: What does Iran think when it hears, “We will not take the military option off the table”?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347890151403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890794670-13</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1) Salar Kamangar, CEO of YouTube Google dispatched one of its longtime employees, Salar Kamangar, to help Hurley [Youtube CEO at the time] steer YouTube in 2008. 2) Amin Zoufonoun, director of corporate development at Google, has been hired away by Facebook to lead its mergers and acquisitions team, Amin Zoufonoun work included leading some of these deals in the U.S. and internationally, including On2, ... Amin Zoufonoun's Summary: Corporate Development, primarily strategic initiatives and partnerships, and the evaluation, negotiation and execution of mergers, acquisitions and investments 3) Mike Jazayeri, Google's director of product management for WebM 4) Afsaneh Naimollah, BOD of On2 Technologies, Inc. Ms. Naimollah has been the Managing Partner of Chela Capital Partners, a mergers and acquisition advisory firm that she founded. 5) Homa Zaryouni in New York ??? FT Reporter: "An Adobe takeover of On2 has been speculation for some time, the insider said. “We do from time to time hear from third parties that a company is interested in On2,” the insider added." 6) Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development Mar. 18, 2009 Woodside will be VP-Americas Operations, reporting to Omid Kordestani, SVP-Global Sales &amp; Business Development. May 22, 2012 Google, which made the deal to gain access to Motorola's vast trove of technology patents, said on Tuesday that Motorola Chief Executive Sanjay Jha has stepped down and has been succeeded by Dennis Woodside, former president of Google's Americas region. 7) Mob of "mobs" is the "bridge" but not like a chess game even if its Page might be the same while it's "flashing" under this "digit" is NOT as pretending to be part of a WHOLE after all the HOLE might be part of it but still is NOT uniform any how! 8) Mani Aliabadi Mani Aliabadi General Counsel, Widevine Technologies, Inc Mani Aliabadi serves as General Counsel of Widevine Technologies Inc. Mr. Aliabadi joined Widevine in March 2005 as the head of Widevine's legal department focused on corporate and intellectual property law. At Widevine, Mr. Aliabadi leads a legal group responsible for the management and oversight of corporate governance, mergers/acquisitions, business development activities, intellectual property protection and licensing, regulatory compliance, risk and litigation management.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347890794670</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347892122166-14</Id><Title>FB has more than 900 Million Users!!</Title><Msg>FB has more than 900 Million Users!!</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347892122166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347893191614-15</Id><Title>S&amp;P 1550-1600</Title><Msg>How high would GOOG go then ? Alos does Election brings traffic to Internet ?</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1347893191614</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347894331776-16</Id><Title>900 million children on facebook</Title><Msg>Go down</Msg><Username>fonsvanhoof</Username><Timestamp>1347894331776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:05:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347895579424-17</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Top Romney Staffer Denies Campaign Disarray By David Muir | ABC OTUS News – 4 hrs ago Stuart Stevens has been one of Romney's closest advisers and is the person - besides Romney - most responsible for many aspects of the campaign's direction and message. "Listen, I think Clint Eastwood, having Eastwood on your side and what he said about the president is incredibly powerful. He came out and gave a strong stance, and I think it was great," Stevens said, "We're talking about this when the Democrats had a floor fight over God? Give me a break."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347895579424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347897305324-18</Id><Topic><Title>900 million children on facebook</Title><Username>fonsvanhoof</Username><Timestamp>1347894331776</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:05:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RIGHT! LOL.</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1347897305324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347898294668-19</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for your valuable information</Msg><Username>kkojxcjxkn</Username><Timestamp>1347898294668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347898309176-20</Id><Title>this comes back strong as the spy goes up this afternoon</Title><Msg>Lets see</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347898309176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:11:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347898820469-21</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Iran Human Rights Memorial Human rights violations in this case One person's story Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar (Kamali) About Age — Nationality Iran Religion Presumed Muslim Civil status — Education university diploma Occupation armed/security forces Rank/Position — Affiliation armed forces Case Date of execution June 9, 1980 Location Evin Prison, Tehran, Iran Mode of execution shooting Charges Collaborating with the political police SAVAK About this Case The execution of Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar was reported in the Jomhuri Eslami daily (June 10, 1980). Arrest and detention Based on the report, Mr. Kamangar was arrested by Revolutionary Guards towards the end of the year 1979 in Evin Prison, where he allegedly had gone to receive his salary. Trial The report mentioned that the defendant was tried at the First Branch of the Islamic Revolutionary Tribunal “a while ago.” The final verdict, however, was issued on the morning before the sentences were carried out. Charges Regarding Mr. Kamangar’s charges, the report reads as follows: “Seifollah Faraji Kamangir, the torturer and SAVAK interrogator also known as Dr. Kamali, joined the hated SAVAK since its very founding in 1335 [1957]. During the years of his service at SAVAK he tortured many revolutionary combatants in the most savagely brutal ways so that many of them, including Rezayi, Khalil Tabatabai, Moqayadi, Dibaj and others, were martyred.” ------------- Re: Wonder how much is a drone? By casp321.3 months ago.Permalink . 11. Re: Top Secret: You people are the USA Government&amp;&amp;39;s ENEMY ...One person's story Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar (Kamali) Case Date of execution June 9... Regarding Mr. Kamangar’s charges, the report ... --------- THE NEW YORK TIMES, MONDAY, JUNE 11, 1979 Torture’s Teachers By A.J. Langguth LOS ANGELES – A few months ago, I received some clippings of interviews with a former Federal Intelligence agency official. That operative, Jesse Leaf, had been involved with the agency’s activities in Iran, and well into the stories Mr. Leaf made some damning accusations. He said that the C.I.A. sent an operative to teach interrogation methods to SAVAK, the Shah’s secret police, that the training included instructions in torture, and the techniques were copied from the Nazis. ---------- SAVAK From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia SAVAK operated from 1957 to 1979, when the Pahlavi dynasty was overthrown. SAVAK has been described as Iran's "most hated and feared institution" prior to the revolution of 1979 because of its practice of torturing and executing opponents of the Pahlavi regime.[2][3] At its peak, the organization had as many as 60,000 agents serving in its ranks according to one source</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347898820469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:20:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347902554348-22</Id><Title>Facebooks Improving Ad Performance Can Spell Trouble For Google = GO FB</Title><Msg>.............</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347902554348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347902619965-23</Id><Title>Facebook nasdaq FB bounce!!</Title><Msg>imho</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347902619965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347904921555-24</Id><Title>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google it 10 X's the money @ current .19 pps</Title><Msg>Google them ( Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) ) and get on board for the ride back up.</Msg><Username>serenityloveh69</Username><Timestamp>1347904921555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:02:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905455099-25</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Riots are spreading. This isnt good.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1347905455099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905565869-26</Id><Topic><Title>Page, Brin, Insider purchases (PACB) (SONS) (ACAD)</Title><Username>mgmwynns</Username><Timestamp>1347632134289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>symbol: ANX Phase 3 trial approved. $3.00 soon.</Msg><Username>mgmwynns</Username><Timestamp>1347905565869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347906304812-27</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone catch the ride on here</Msg><Username>kkojxcjxkn</Username><Timestamp>1347906304812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347906305317-28</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone catch the ride on here</Msg><Username>kkojxcjxkn</Username><Timestamp>1347906305317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347908348814-29</Id><Title>With GOOG at $710 AAPL should be $800 by now!</Title><Msg>Much better holding than Google for pete's sakes!</Msg><Username>cramerstrophywife</Username><Timestamp>1347908348814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:59:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347908349444-30</Id><Title>Grover Norquist</Title><Msg>is not interested in what is good for USA. He is only interested in defeating Obama. Republicans care nothing about women, country, healthcare for anyone, poverty. He is only interested in representing the elite. America was not founded upon protecting the elite. They have the ability to protect themselves. How about protecting those who were born with health problems, birth defects, and those who never had an even start in life to begin with. Suzanne Blanchard</Msg><Username>ewblanchard</Username><Timestamp>1347908349444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347908939973-31</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the sudden drop ?...You're not keeping up with the News, Hezbollah and Iran said, those responsible for the making of the offending film will pay.</Msg><Username>lucky_me2010</Username><Timestamp>1347908939973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347915720014-32</Id><Title>GLENN BECK BACK ON CABLE T.V.! (DISH CH. 212)</Title><Msg>He has his own 24-hour news and information cable channel called THE BLAZE (Dish Ch . 212).    Tell your friends.  Also you can read THE BLAZE website.  It's exceptional.  It's the real news - the true news with streaming videos.  Last month on THE BLAZE website's one-year anniversary for the month of August, it announced a record 9 million unique viewers (the one time log ins) and 75 million (the multiple log ins.)  Other exceptional true news Internet websites are:  DRUDGEREPORT, BREITBART, DAILYCALLER and of course Fox News has its own website.</Msg><Username>martin_barret</Username><Timestamp>1347915720014</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347916087469-33</Id><Title>TWO DAYS AND STILL AT $710</Title><Msg>pathetic</Msg><Username>airstockman</Username><Timestamp>1347916087469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347924568000-34</Id><Title>GOOG stock, this is a must see, what do you guys think.</Title><Msg>The information provided at VIP is very compelling and it has assisted me in the decision making process and it has also created a better base for me to understand stock GOOG, visit it at, vippennystocksite dotcom</Msg><Username>jamesbrown1847</Username><Timestamp>1347924568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347925096681-35</Id><Title>Think you could see 720 but out of my long today at 712</Title><Msg>Think you could see 720 but out of my long today at 712; great stock could go higher maybe much more than 720 but the down side is much bigger than the up at this point. Good luck to all (long and short)</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347925096681</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347928401357-36</Id><Topic><Title>TWO DAYS AND STILL AT $710</Title><Username>airstockman</Username><Timestamp>1347916087469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:08:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That means nothing apple is selling alot of phones so this will continue to go up: That makes sense!</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1347928401357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>