<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347698639047-1</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Wonder how much is a drone? By casp321 3 months ago Was it a "bug" or feature? Ask silberman, secord, hakim, ghorbanifar, kangarlou, mousavi, bush, north, robert gate, poindexter, ... casey, buckley, shackley to let you know how their "creation" in beirut related to hostage-crisis in 1979-1981 and 1984-1984: Made in the SAME "BakerHouse" and distributed as Kosher and/or Halal, depending who the audience might be Re: Wonder how much is a drone? By casp321 3 months ago What they use to REMOTELY CONTROL their FRIENDs, NOT "enemy" as their Paid Media paint for, ACTIVITIEs turns into FIERCE fight to CONTROL the "White House" as it took place in 1979-1981. Search for Silberman, North, Secord, Hakim, Ghorbanifar, Kangarlu, MacFarlane, Poindexter, Robert Gsate, Bush ACTIVITIES during 1980 dealing with Iran "hostage-crisis"??? That's why Republican crying about Iran-leak these days. "Cyber-az" just another #$%$ and CAMPAGIN for 2012 USA Presidential-election, the same as "attack" of the country, yahoo does NOT let post the name for OBVIOUS reasons, to help Republican in the Election. Kangarku [and Buckley in beirut], Mosavi's deputy; and as Mosavi had said once to North or those on Reagan side, "we let you get-rid of Democrats as USA president" during the time of Hostge "crisis" in 1979-1981? Republicans renew attacks on Obama administration over leaks By Christopher Wilson and Paul Eckert | Reuters – 9 hrs ago WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Republicans on Sunday renewed their attacks on the Obama administration over suspected leaks of classified security information, with one influential senator saying the Justice Department should appoint a special prosecutor to investigate. Among the government secrets leaked to the media in recent months were reports on U.S. cyber warfare against Iran, Re: Another October, is it "Surprise"?? By casp321 9 months ago It is alleged that President Reagan sent Silberman in the fall of 1980 to make sure the Iranians weren’t planning to give up the US hostages taken at the American embassy, thus creating an "October surprise" that would help reelect Jimmy Carter. Silberman was rewarded for his role in Iran with the judgeship that later allowed him to overturn the conviction of Oliver North for his role in the Iran-Contra affair. ----------- Viet D. Dinh, Born in Saigon, in the former South Vietnam, he was the chief architect of the USA PATRIOT Act. After graduating from law school, Dinh served as a law clerk to Judge Laurence H. Silberman of the U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit After 9/11, Dinh conducted a comprehensive review of DOJ priorities, policies and practices, and played a key role in developing the USA PATRIOT Act and revising the Attorney General's Guidelines, which govern federal law enforcement activities and national security investigations</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347698639047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 04:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347699239236-2</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sep 14, 2012 Media for Christ, a nonprofit that raised more than $1 million last year "to glow Jesus' light" to the world, was listed as the production company for the film....Most of "Innocence of Muslims" was shot in about two weeks inside a squat warehouse that serves as the offices of Media for Christ, And Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, who authorities say has used multiple names and was convicted of bank fraud, says he managed logistics for the film. Anger for Islam ties players behind prophet film By MICHAEL R. BLOOD | Associated Press – 33 mins ago DUARTE, Calif. (AP) — The shared belief that radical Islam threatens the world brought together an ex-convict, an insurance salesman and a Christian charity in production of a crudely crafted film that ridicules Muslims and the Prophet Muhammad and has incited violent protests across the Middle East. Media for Christ, a nonprofit that raised more than $1 million last year "to glow Jesus' light" to the world, was listed as the production company for the film. Steve Klein, a California insurance salesman and Vietnam War veteran who has spent years protesting at mosques and espousing hatred of radical Muslims, acted as the film's promoter. And Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, who authorities say has used multiple names and was convicted of bank fraud, says he managed logistics for the film. Federal authorities have identified Nakoula as the key figure behind the film. A federal law enforcement official told The Associated Press on Thursday that authorities had connected Nakoula to a man using the pseudonym of Sam Bacile who claimed earlier to be writer and director of the film. Most of "Innocence of Muslims" was shot in about two weeks inside a squat warehouse that serves as the offices of Media for Christ, according to Eric Moers, who served as chief electrician for the production.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347699239236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 04:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347699707147-3</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anger for Islam ties players behind prophet film By MICHAEL R. BLOOD The permit, issued by Film LA, could have cost under $1,000 though details aren't known because the document has been sealed at the request of federal law enforcement officials. Moers said the film took 15 to 16 days to shoot and 90 percent of the work was done at the Media for Christ studios. He said one day was spent at a movie ranch in Santa Clarita, and one day was spent filming at the home of the man he knew as Bacile. ------------ About Us FilmL.A. is a private, 501(c)4 not-for-profit organization established for the public benefit. We coordinate and process permits for on-location motion picture, television and commercial production under contract to an ever-increasing roster of public-sector clients in the Los Angeles region. All permits are issued by the authority of and in accordance with the policies of each client jurisdiction. We function differently than the typical film office or film commission. Most such entities are publicly-funded government agencies focused on promoting their regions to the film industry. FilmL.A. was created when the City and County of Los Angeles decided to privatize their film permit offices, allowing more flexibility in providing services to production companies and local communities. Although FilmL.A. is funded primarily by permit coordination fees paid by production companies, ongoing community relations is a key component of the service we provide. We work to strike a balance between the needs and interests of the entertainment industry and the neighborhoods affected by on-location production.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347699707147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347700368291-4</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Ex-Agent: CIA Seed Money Helped Launch Google By casp321 2 years 3 months ago -----Moreover, the source said the CIA’s Office of Research and Development “has been giving [Google] additional money and guidance and requirements.” The source said “at least one US intelligence agency” (presumably the CIA) worked to “leverage Google’s [user] data monitoring” capability as part of an effort by the intelligence community to glean from this data information of “national security intelligence interest” in the war on terror, in other words the war on the American people (or more specifically those in opposition to the government). Moreover, the source said the CIA’s Office of Research and Development “has been giving [Google] additional money and guidance and requirements.”</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347700368291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347700435964-5</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sep 14, 2012 Google rejects White House request to pull Mohammad film clip By Gerry Shih SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Google Inc rejected a request by the White House on Friday to reconsider its decision to keep online a controversial YouTube movie clip that has ignited anti-American protests in the Middle East. ------------- Ex-Agent: CIA Seed Money Helped Launch Google By casp321 2 years 3 months agok Ex-Agent: CIA Seed Money Helped Launch Google Steele goes further than before in detailing ties, names Google's CIA liaison Paul Joseph Watson Prison Planet Wednesday, December 6, 2006 Is Google's quest to manage the world's information leading straight to the CIA? Former CIA clandestine case officer Robert David Steele made some very hot comments on his appearance on the Alex Jones radio show. Steele cites his contacts within the agency with the information that Google and the CIA are involved with one another.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347700435964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347700809300-6</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monday, March 31, 2008 CIA and Google Team Up Again For More Spying Search engine company has long been in bed with intelligence network "We are a very small group, and even a lot of people in the federal government don't know that we exist," said Mike Bradshaw, who leads Google's federal government sales team and its 18 employees, yesterday to the San Francisco Chronicle. ----- Re: Ex-Agent: CIA Seed Money Helped Launch Google By casp321 2 years 3 months ago CIA and Google Team Up Again For More Spying Search engine company has long been in bed with intelligence network Steve Watson [Infowars] Monday, March 31, 2008 Google is supplying the software, hardware and tech support to US intelligence agencies who are in the process of creating a vast closed source database for global spy networks to share information. Google is selling storage and data searching equipment to the CIA, the FBI, the National Security Agency, and other intelligence agencies, who have come together to build a huge internal government intranet.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347700809300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:20:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347700931767-7</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monday, March 31, 2008 CIA and Google Team Up Again For More Spying Search engine company has long been in bed with intelligence network "We are a very small group, and even a lot of people in the federal government don't know that we exist," said Mike Bradshaw, who leads Google's federal government sales team and its 18 employees, yesterday to the San Francisco Chronicle.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347700931767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347701305108-8</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>July 30, 2010 Bob Jacobson Google and CIA Invest in a Minority Report-Like Technology That May Make Our World a Less Certain Place</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347701305108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347701390891-9</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The investment arms of the CIA and Google are both backing a company that monitors the web in real time -- and says it uses that information to predict the future.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347701390891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347701428138-10</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The idea is to figure out for each incident who was involved, where it happened and when it might go down. Recorded Future then plots that chatter, showing online "momentum" for any given event. "The cool thing is, you can actually predict the curve, in many cases," says company CEO Christopher Ahlberg, a former Swedish Army Ranger with a PhD in computer science.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347701428138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347701597575-11</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The current even is the INDICATION of WHY Yahoo changed the format to BLOCK to post the links related to articles being posted on SCRATCH Yahoo Board because we are EXPOSING their CRIMINAL intents and their relastion with INTELLIGENCE agencies even though they are a public companies with real regular investors!!!!!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347701597575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 05:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347712549262-12</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Google promoting Violence in different part of world PROMOTING insult to their believes and this is WHY Google STOLE ON2 Video codec and Hantro from its shareholders to use CIA propaganda: Terry Jones, 'Sam Bacile': The men behind the movie? Terry Jones is an extremist pastor who is promoting 'Innocence of Muslims,' the controversial film that may have been produced by someone using the name 'Sam Bacile.' Talia RalphSeptember 12, 2012 Terry Jones and a man going by the name Sam Bacile have been said to be behind "Innocence of Muslims," the controversial, low-budget film behind the protests at US Embassies in Cairo and Benghazi. Amid the protests in Benghazi, US officials suspect a planned attack killed US Ambassador Christopher Stevens and three others. Separately, the Associated Press reported it had tracked down the manager for the company that produced "Innocence of Muslims," a California Coptic Christian convicted of financial crimes named Nakoula Basseley Nakoula. An address traced to Nakoula's cell phone, as well as an alias listed in federal court papers suggested that Nakoula and Bacile may be the same person, the AP reported. In an interview with the AP outside Los Angeles, Nakoula denied that he directed the film and said he knew Bacile, who supported the concerns of Christian Copts about their treatment by Muslims.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347712549262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347712609214-13</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>from Christianpost site: By Paul Stanley, Christian Post Reporter September 14, 2012 Who Is Sam Bacile; What Is Terry Jones' Role in the Middle East Attacks? U.S. intelligence officials are still trying to piece together the tragic events of the past few days that led to the unrest in Egypt and Libya and at least four murders. But behind the scenes is Gainesville, Fla., Dove World Outreach Center pastor Terry Jones and a man federal authorities have now identified as a Southern California Coptic Christian by the name of Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, 55, who adopted the persona of Sam Bacile, the man who produced the amateur film titled "Innocence of Muslims" that Muslim extremists say sparked Tuesday's violence that killed Stevens and three others.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347712609214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347712736700-14</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sep 15, 2012 California man linked to anti-Islam film taken in for questioning By Alex Dobuzinskis LOS ANGELES (Reuters) - A California man convicted of bank fraud was taken in for questioning on Saturday by officers investigating possible probation violations stemming from the making of an anti-Islam film that triggered violent protests in the Muslim world. Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, 55, voluntarily left his home in the early hours of Saturday morning for the meeting in a sheriff's station in the Los Angeles suburb of Cerritos, Los Angeles County Sheriff's spokesman Steve Whitmore said. "He will be interviewed by federal probation officers," Whitmore said. He said Nakoula had not been placed under arrest but would not be returning home immediately. "He was never put in handcuffs... It was all voluntary." Nakoula, who has denied involvement in the film in a phone call to his Coptic Christian bishop, was ushered out of his home and into a waiting car by several sheriff's deputies, his face shielded by a scarf, hat and sunglasses. The crudely made 13-minute English-language film, filmed in California and circulated on the Internet under several titles including "Innocence of Muslims", mocks the Prophet Mohammad.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347712736700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347712812472-15</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BANK FRAUD CONVICTION Nakoula, whose name has been widely linked to the film in media reports, pleaded guilty to bank fraud in 2010 and was sentenced to 21 months in prison, to be followed by five years on supervised probation, court documents showed. He was accused of fraudulently opening bank and credit card accounts using Social Security numbers that did not match the names on the applications, a criminal complaint showed. He was released in June 2011, and at least some production on the video was done later that summer.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347712812472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 08:40:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347717554232-16</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 SI and 3 pdf docs: They can NOT say they did NOT know!!!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1306070069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-05-22 09:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KKR, Blackstone Deal-Rig Antitrust Suit Expanded by Judge By Sophia Pearson - Sep 9, 2011 Plaintiffs in a case accusing 11 firms, including KKR &amp; Co. and Blackstone Group LP (BX), of conspiring to rig the market for leveraged buyout deals can expand their investigation, a federal judge ruled. The plaintiffs, including a Detroit police and fire pension fund, can seek information on 10 additional deals, U.S. District Judge Edward F. Harrington said in a ruling Sept. 7. He didn’t identify the transactions, which are described in a proposed fifth amended complaint to be filed under seal. The firms argued that adding the deals would be “unduly burdensome and prejudicial,” according to court papers. The lawsuit, initially filed in 2007, claims the firms conspired to drive down prices in the largest leveraged buyout deals in violation of federal antitrust laws. The case previously was limited to 17 transactions. Harrington gave the plaintiffs until April 17 to seek the information. Among the deals in question is Neiman Marcus Group Inc.’s $5.1 billion buyout by Warburg Pincus LLC and TPG Capital Inc., SunGard Data Systems Inc.’s $11.3 billion takeover by seven private-equity firms and Aramark Corp.’s roughly $8.3 billion purchase in January 2007. Three plaintiffs are also shareholders of Freescale Semiconductor Inc., which was taken private by a group including Blackstone and Carlyle Group. TPG and Carlyle are also defendants in the suit. ‘Bidding Clubs’ The firms allegedly formed “bidding clubs,” referred to in the private-equity industry as “consortia” or “teams” to rig the bidding, according to a redacted fourth amended complaint made public yesterday. Use of the clubs limited the number of bidders, depressing prices at target companies, the plaintiffs said. ‘Sham Bids’ The conspiracy began in at least 2003, plaintiffs said in court papers. The so-called bidding clubs would orchestrate competing bids and knowingly submit “inferior sham bids,” according to the complaint. The average premiums paid to shareholders in bids involving club deals were significantly less than those paid in either sole-sponsor LBOs or acquisitions by strategic bidders, the plaintiffs said. The defendant firms were enriched through the conspiracy as debt financing shields the income they pull out of target companies from taxes. The annualized net returns to the firms are 20 percent to 30 percent, according to the complaint. The case was filed after the U.S. Justice Department began probing bidding practices among private equity firms in October 2006. No actions were ever brought by the government. Dealmaking effectively stopped in 2008 as the global financial crisis, triggered by subprime mortgage defaults and the collapse of Lehman Brothers Holdings Inc., dried up financing for new transactions. Private-equity purchases have returned at a diminished level. Managers have announced $278.5 billion in transactions so far this year, less than half of the $682.8 billion during the same period in 2007, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. The reduced numbers of deals and smaller purchase prices have made buyouts by groups of firms less prevalent. The case is Dahl v. Bain Capital Partners LLC, 07-12388, U.S. District Court, District of Massachusetts (Boston).</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347717554232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 09:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347718294247-17</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG attains in One Trades for NasdaqNM shoppers</Title><Username>ralden86</Username><Timestamp>1324747495000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2011-12-24 12:24:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**** this share has a Bright future......</Msg><Username>coffeyg74</Username><Timestamp>1347718294247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:11:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347718664638-18</Id><Topic><Title>ON2's Video technlogies flying in the CHINESE CLOUD???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1303221042000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-04-19 09:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why in the Europe and NOT in the USA they had to SCAM ON2 shareholders? Who was Jill Joll, ON2 CEO in 2007 contact that "promised" or made oral deal for two or three deals with about $300K but DENIED them later on? Was BJ lieing or it was part of a BROADER SCAM? Why did they let BJ land a CEO positition at a Homeland Security related company after FALSIFYING ON2 financial reports in 2007? Here I have some answer for you. It's FBI and DOJ jobs to get to the bottom of the SCAM, all I can do is bringing you to the DOORSTEPs of those might have involved in ON2 SCAM and trying to get away from the backdoor. I'm taking you to the front door: Re: This is why yahoo and google getting away with ... By casp321.21 days ago.PermalinkGo to topic . No wonder why ON2 robbery is too complicated and ON2 shareholders had break too many "codes" to simplify it, Housing Obama for "party" Who are also familiar to ON2 shareholder through camany named Google dealing with ON2, Amazon, Zencoder, Salesforce, September 19th, 2011 Obama Hits Up Silicon Valley One More Time at Google exec Marissa Mayer’s Palo Alto house [on October 22, 2010] --Google CEO Eric Schmidt --and attended an exclusive meetup in February [2011?] at Kleiner Perkins VC John Doerr’s house --Obama also hung out at Salesforce CEO Marc Benioff’s house in April [2011?].</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347718664638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347722619463-19</Id><Title>GOOG or FB or Znga</Title><Msg>Facebook, Inc. operates as a social networking company worldwide. The company builds tools that enable users to connect, share, discover, and communicate with each other; enables developers to build social applications on Facebook or to integrate their Websites with Facebook; and offers products that enable advertisers and marketers to engage with its users. As of February 2, 2012, it had 845 million monthly users and 443 million daily users. The company was founded in 2004 and is headquartered in Menlo Park, California. Zynga Inc. develops, markets, and operates online social games as live services on the Internet, social networking sites, and mobile platforms. The company offers its online social games under the CityVille, Zynga Poker, FarmVille, CastleVille, FrontierVille, Mafia Wars, Word with Friends, Hidden Chronicles, Zynga Bingo, Scramble With Friends, Slingo, and Dream Heights names. Its games are available on various platforms, including Facebook and other social networks, as well as mobile platforms, such as Apple iOS and Google Android worldwide. The company was formerly known as Zynga Game Network Inc. and changed its name to Zynga Inc. in November 2010. Zynga Inc. was founded in 2007 and is headquartered in San Francisco, California.</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347722619463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347724431827-20</Id><Topic><Title>REE: Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347661985041</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:33:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just wonder if Democrats trumping Republican by the way Google PROMOTING violence in the Middle east by BROADCASTING what cause distubance in believe of those in that region. That's why they had to STEAL ON2 with Hantro and its TrueMotion video codecs and survilance and Security system to serve USA "intelligence" system better tham MS, FB, Yahoo or all the other USA companies tracing/tracking individual activities in the USA??? Google a PUBLIC for Democrat to be ELECTED as USA president in Nov 2012?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347724431827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 11:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347725399890-21</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1291298875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-02 09:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's interesting Yahoo blocks any reference to Sirael but then they PROMOTE vilence in the Middle East and other regions of the world by INSULTING their believes, what a CRIMINAL intends and what a CRIMINMAL people those promoting VIOLENCE in the name of "free"?? myaz!!!!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347725399890</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347727430604-22</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprised me too, why Google didn't block that offending youtube video earlier, especially in the Middle East ?. It's one of their subsidiary. Does Google think it wasn't offensive enough to Muslims ????</Msg><Username>lucky_me2010</Username><Timestamp>1347727430604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347727808586-23</Id><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Msg>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!!! taking hostage what the people believes instead of ... ON2 Video codecs technology and taking HOSTAGE what people believe instead of doing what they played Iran-Hostage-1979-81 SCAM and lebonan 1984-1985 hostage SCAM. Check Ghorbanifar, Secord, Hakim, Bush, Silberman, BUCKLEY, Casey, Shackley, Robert Gate, North, Pondexter, McFarlane, ...Ghotbzadeh, Mousavi, Kangarlou, Rafsanjani, Karobi, Nabavi, who were involved in 1979 and 1984 hostage scam by even sending to death their very own???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347728245524-24</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would not be surprised to see Republican coming out with their own version of HOSTAGE taking, either the "old-way" as they did in 1979-81 in Iran and 1984-85 in Lebonan or new way that Google is PROMOTING remotely for Democrat to elect Obama as USA president in Nov 2012. Would NOT be surprided!!!!!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347728245524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347728388686-25</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CRIMINALs at work until Nov 2012, different time different TACTIC, but possible the CORE of the SAME shadowy government that was involved in 1979 and 1984???</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347728388686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347734084877-26</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please, don't censor the free expression of speech. No matter how inane. It wasn't an easy freedom to secure, it's just as difficult to defend. Don't make it easy for our enemies.</Msg><Username>crossroadsva</Username><Timestamp>1347734084877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347734936274-27</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their SEMSELESS Propaganda against their FRIENDly Government By casp321.7 months ago.Permalink . The people are their enemy NOT the government, which is their friend, they call their "enemy". Check this out: June 09, 2004 Donate Remembering the Dead: Reagan Armed Iraq and Iran in 1980s War That Killed Over 1 Million We look at the policies of the Reagan administration in the Middle East, specifically during the Iran-Iraq war, one of the bloodiest conflicts in modern times in which more than a million people were killed. Chemical weapons were used and two of the most ancient societies on earth were devastated. We speak with Iranian human rights lawyer and 2003 Nobel Peace Prize winner Shirin Ebadi and journalist Alan Friedman about how the Reagan administration armed Iran and normalized relations with Iraq, selling weapons to both sides of the conflict. Re: Congress WASHING USA BLOODY hands in Iraq/Iran in 1980s War That Killed Over 1 Million By casp321.7 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . For EIGHT years USA and its INTELLIGENCE agencies HELPED Iranian Government in Iran/Iraq war to SUPPRESS Iranian people. Now their agencies and Congress trying to WASH their BLOODY hand because of UNCERTAINLY about the FUTURE of IRANIAN Government. That's what they are working" to mAINTAIN their FRIENDLTY Government NOT to d"destry" as they are PAINTY it. They are FRIENDs NOT enemy. There is NO secret about it. Their talk about secrecy is #$%$ PLAIN and sIMPLE!!!!!!!!! Re: Congress WASHING USA BLOODY hands in Iraq/Iran in 1980s War That Killed Over 1 Million By casp321.7 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Why would Yahoo provide hundreds of Iranian Yahoo accounts to Iran Government? Were those Yahoo BOD and chairman RESIGNATION because of Yahoo working for CIA and Investors were NOT happy about it? It's about MARCH in March. With #$%$ PROPAGANDA, they are trying to "gain" your support in SUPPORING their FRIEND as they PAINT it their "enemy to HIDE the real relationship. They NEED your support for their CRIMINAL activities. With their PROPAGANDA, they are TRYING to mobilizing those, on both sides, who do NOT care what one side or the other might be doing, to justify their CRIMINAL activities and the on going EXECUTIONs in Iran. One side is trying to PRO-LONG their FRIENDs, NOT "enemy"s as they paint, "power" even if the PEOPLE of Iran might TURN the system upside down. Search for Secord involvement in Iran in 1970s and 1980s then you would know what a SHAM and FABRICATED Show USA Congress had in 1980s about the USA involvement in Iran, that they are calling "Iran-contra" to Hide the REAL relationds among USA, IRAN, Irsael. They are FRIENDs NOT enemy. What they say is just #$%$ to HIDE their cRIMINAL activities against Iranian people. That simle even if they SPEND BILLIONs of dollars to HIDE their relationship. One should ask a simple question: Why Yahoo just removed the informations, links related to Secord and NOT Bush or Saudi or drone? Because that ACTIVITIES is still LIVE and ON-GOING. Secord is one of the few INVOLVED in bringing Iranian government to power by USA that still alive, most are DEAD, either EXECUTED in Iran, got Heat attack, Cancer or had airplain crash or blown up in "their own" ...</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347734936274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 14:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347747131298-28</Id><Topic><Title>casp321 remember bill joll thought you like to know</Title><Username>wmhjr99</Username><Timestamp>1337952121000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-25 09:22:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In his recent webcast it turns out Mr Joll forgot to mention that they didn't acquire any of the appliances in those pictures and they just have to hope that whoever buys the hardware from Bivio (it's up for sale as well) will continue to sell it to ISC8 and considering their financial status that seems unlikely so they really wound up with virtually nothing other than another debt and the ability to issue more shares of stock diluting the rest of us even further.</Msg><Username>jarred.randolph</Username><Timestamp>1347747131298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 18:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347752306319-29</Id><Topic><Title>censor the offending video, Google!!!</Title><Username>mjh194353</Username><Timestamp>1347660335079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's the problem, innocent People are dying for your free speech. How about going out there yourself and kill your enemy. Fight your own battle !</Msg><Username>lucky_me2010</Username><Timestamp>1347752306319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 19:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>