<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346478824265-1</Id><Title>Arpiao kick Obamanure butt</Title><Msg>"It is a miscarriage of justice that the federal government is dropping its case against Sheriff Arpaio and to make such an announcement on the Friday night before the Democratic National Convention can only be politically motivated to shield the administration from criticism," Pablo Alvarado, director of the National Day Laborer Organizing Network, said in a statement. Maybe those illegals can't vote for you Bamanure.</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346478824265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 01:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346485782258-2</Id><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Msg>Check it out on Youtube! Wow!!</Msg><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346485782258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 03:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346487579187-3</Id><Topic><Title>*** GOOG Insiders Unloading GOOG.. ***</Title><Username>dean2222</Username><Timestamp>1346458368449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:12:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, insiders think the current GOOG stock price is worth selling. Put yourself in their shoes. If you think your currently own stock has upside ahead, would you sell? You will sell if you think the stock is fairly valued and the upside is limited!</Msg><Username>dean2222</Username><Timestamp>1346487579187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346487746818-4</Id><Title>VRNG</Title><Msg>Should we be worried about the Vringo patent suit?</Msg><Username>frankomd</Username><Timestamp>1346487746818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346489985196-5</Id><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Msg>A real man. Full of class and character. Discipline and dignity. Just like the late Charles Bronson or Chuck Norris who were and are incorruptible by the Hollywood PIGS. Compare these folk to the filth of the likes of the unkempt michael moore who escaped from the group home one day and never returned. The Republican Convention was a blessing of encouragement and true hope to change the big mistake made in '08.</Msg><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489985196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346504917527-6</Id><Title>Why Is GOOG CEO Playing SoftBall With Apple? Is He Helping Apple OR Shareholders?</Title><Msg>Google pays 12.5 Billion for Motorola's Patents and CEO Does Not use that patent power against Apple. Motorola has won in court over Apple infringing on their patents but now that Google owns those patents, nothing is going on in this one sided war, Apple against Google. How many Apple shares are being held by the board at Google? The future of Android depends on what Google does with the patent power from Motorola. Google should be flooding the U.S. patent office with claims of prior art against Apple's broad patents and invalidate those patents. Google shareholders want to see a Google vs Apple on the first page of the news and not a Motorola vs Apple on page 200. The future of Google is in Android and those like Samsung that make Android products,,, Google must show more support for Samsung and others who built Android to what it is today. To the Google Board, sell all your Apple shares and buy more Google, the time is now.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1346504917527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346506747880-7</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG</Title><Username>frankomd</Username><Timestamp>1346487746818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Mark Cuban is HEDGING by investment in VRNG because he saw the trouble and also might've been interested in looking at the inside of the "darkroom" to see how's everything in the Vringo's "house." How deep an investor can get into the inside beats me. But, ON2 had a lot of Shorts having access to INSIDE info, otherwise how could Shorts be able to cover from Oct 2008 to August 2009 while keeping ON2 PPS under $0.40 and taking SI volume from 2+ million to under 500K by the end of July 2009? How could it be possible? here is why: Breaking the codes or breaking the links of the connection chains: ---Hambrecht was AOL and Motorola BOD ---Hambrecht &amp; Armstrong: Tim Armstrong was Google EXECs in 2007 and , while at Motorola, he became William/Bill Hambrecht's BUSINESS PARTNER with UFL ----- Hambrecht was AOL BOD for sometime but resigned in 2011? ---Hambrecht and Icahn: Icahn forced Motorola to have Hambrecht as one of its BOD ----- Hambrecht became Motorola BOD but resigned a few days after Motorola and Google announced the buy-out on August 15 2011? ---Icahn and Cuban ----- Ichan and Cuban were investors in Lionsgate, which Cuban sold his shares in LGF to Icahn. Later on Icahn sold all of his shares in Lionsgate without getting his way around? ---Hambrect and Armstrong and M. Cuban, and P.P, husband of congresswoman Nancy ----- Hambrecht and Armstrong, while Armstrong was still Google EXEC, became partners in UFL and M. Cuban became one of UFL "investors". Interestingly enough Armstrong was moved to AOL as CEO and much later time Cuban sued Hambrecht in relation to UFL "investment" But what is the REAL deal behind the scene is not really clear too me??? ---Hambrecht and Schmidt and Google ---Hambrect and ON2 Hambrecht became ON2 "advisor", at the end of 2006 in acquiring Hantro, a Finish company. ON2 acquired Hantro on Nov 1, 2007. Iterestingly enough Google TRADEMARKED Hantro logo on April 2, 2008, about a month prior to ON2 and Sun Microsystem making deal on May 7, 2008 Aug 17, 2011 [ 2 days after Google announced acquiring Motorola Mobility] “I want to thank Bill for his valuable service and guidance to Motorola and to Motorola Mobility,” said Sanjay Jha, chairman and chief executive officer, Motorola Mobility. “Bill played an instrumental role in the separation of Motorola into two independent publicly-traded companies, as well as in our recent milestone transaction with Google. On behalf of the entire Board of Directors, I wish Bill only the best.” Wed Aug 17, 2011 Icahn nominee Hambrecht leaves Motorola board Motorola Mobility Holdings Inc MMI.N said on Wednesday that William R. Hambrecht is leaving its board of directors immediately. It did not explain why.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346506747880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346507687742-8</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG</Title><Username>frankomd</Username><Timestamp>1346487746818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thursday, August 30, 2012 Magistrate Update VRNG there will indeed be a hearing of sorts regarding the Discovery sanctions (telephone conference) on September 6th [2012] with Judge Stillman (recent update on court schedules). The fact that this is listed as a telephone conference and not a motion hearing is very interesting. Perhaps this is an initial settlement conference? -------- Aug 30, 2012 Vringo Issues Investor Update Press Release: Vringo, Inc. Current Litigation: I/P Engine v. AOL, Google et al. --Fact discovery in the case closes on September 4, 2012. --Expert discovery closes on September 11, 2012. --Pre-trial disclosures are scheduled to be exchanged between the parties on September 19, 2012 and --any objections exchanged on September 26, 2012. --An attorney conference with the Court is scheduled for September 28, 2012. --A final draft pretrial order will be proposed on October 3, 2012 and --a final pretrial conference with the Court will be conducted on October 5, 2012. --Proposed voir dire and jury instructions will be submitted to the Court on or before October 9, 2012. --Trial will commence on October 16, 2012 at 10:00 AM. --------------- Don Stout and H. Van Sinclair own VRNG share and are counsel and members of Vringo's legal team knowing inside/out ad no need for waiting for any leak! The trading plans are designed to align the interests of directors and officers with the Company's investors FORM 8-K On August 31, 2012, Vringo, Inc. The trading plans are designed to align the interests of directors and officers with the Company’s investors by allowing them to monetize a portion of their equity positions when the market prices of the Company's common stock are between $4.25 and $30.00 per share, in a systematic, nondiscretionary manner with the goal of minimal market impact, and compliance with federal securities laws and regulations adopted by the Securities and Exchange Commission. ------- FORM 8-K Dated: August 29, 2012 On August 25, 2012, the board of directors (the “Board”) of Vringo, Inc. (the “Company”) approved, at the recommendation of the Compensation Committee of the Board, an increase in the base salary of Ellen Cohl, the Company’s Chief Financial Officer,...In addition, the Board approved the acceleration of certain of Ms. Cohl’s unvested stock option grants with exercise prices between $0.01 and $5.50 which will become fully vested immediately.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346507687742</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346507988762-9</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG</Title><Username>frankomd</Username><Timestamp>1346487746818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I found these examples regarding "telephone conference", but there might be different reasons for vringo's conference call: Telephone Calls. With the exception of scheduled telephonic conferences, and as provided at section V.B below, telephone calls to chambers are permitted only for matters such as scheduling and calendaring. Court personnel are prohibited from giving legal advice or discussing the merits of a case. Following telephonic contact with chambers, counsel will be required to file an ex parte or Joint Motion, as appropriate, which will be granted only upon good cause shown. D. Telephone Conferences Judge Robreno may hold telephone conferences to resolve scheduling matters or discovery disputes. Counsel will be notified of the date and time for the telephone conference. It will be the responsibility of counsel for the moving party to initiate the telephone conference and to contact Judge Robreno through his secretary after all parties are present on the call. Once a motion to compel is filed, Judge Robreno will schedule a telephone or in-person conference to resolve the dispute within ten (10) days. [...] Judge Robreno permits telephone conferences to resolve discovery disputes during depositions in cases where the deposition would otherwise have to be adjourned. Judge Robreno generally will hold a telephone scheduling conference with counsel in criminal cases shortly after arraignment. At the conclusion of the conference, Judge Robreno will issue a Scheduling Order governing speedy trial issues, discovery, time for filing motions, and the trial date. --------- TELEPHONE CONFERENCES Judge Padova sometimes uses telephone conferences for non-complex pretrial conferences, scheduling, discovery disputes, settlement conferences and other like matters. Telephone conferences should be arranged through the Deputy. Judge Padova expects counsel to bring matters to his attention only after they have been discussed with opposing counsel. All parties must be represented on any telephone conference with Judge Padova. Counsel have the responsibility to initiate telephone conferences and to contact Judge Padova through his Deputy after all other parties are present on the call.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346507988762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346512303934-10</Id><Title>SPLITTING...</Title><Msg>anyone know when this baby is splitting??</Msg><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1346512303934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346512470986-11</Id><Title>Mitt Romney is liar from a cult , no beer , wine or spirits ( very strange dude)</Title><Msg>one sick puppy</Msg><Username>grouponnewbie</Username><Timestamp>1346512470986</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346520565883-12</Id><Title>Obama's America - which dream</Title><Msg>About 2016: Obama’s America 2016 Obama's America takes audiences on a gripping visual journey into the heart of the world’s most powerful office to reveal the struggle of whether one man's past will redefine America over the next four years. The film examines the question, "If Obama wins a second term, where will we be in 2016?" Across the globe and in America, people in 2008 hungered for a leader who would unite and lift us from economic turmoil and war. True to America’s ideals, they invested their hope in a new kind of president, Barack Obama. What they didn't know is that Obama is a man with a past, and in powerful ways that past defines him--who he is, how he thinks, and where he intends to take America and the world. Immersed in exotic locales across four continents, best selling author Dinesh D’Souza races against time to find answers to Obama’s past and reveal where America will be in 2016. During this journey he discovers how Hope and Change became radically misunderstood, and identifies new flashpoints for hot wars in mankind’s greatest struggle. The journey moves quickly over the arc of the old colonial empires, into America’s empire of liberty, and we see the unfolding realignment of nations and the shape of the global future. Emotionally engaging, 2016 Obama’s America will make you confounded and cheer as you discover the mysteries and answers to your greatest aspirations and worst fears.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346520565883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346520719492-13</Id><Title>End wars 'responsibly'? Excuse me Mr.Obama</Title><Msg>Fox just showed clips of Obama at Ft. Bliss yesterday trying spin for upcoming convention to cover his earlier comments stating 'we have a long tough fight ahead of us in Afghanistan' by stating 'we must end these wars responsibly.' HA! Where the heck is Cindy Shehan and the Code Pinkies? What this truly indicates is exactly what most of us in the know knew all along and that is the Military Command makes such decisions and any Commander in Chief with any brains will listen because afterall that is what they do for a living KILL FOLKS! So I give Obama that much credit that he listens to the Military Command as did Bush (who got Congressional approval for Iraq on top ot it unlike Obama and most dems signed on including Hilary Billary and John Kerry.) The problem I have is the dumb USA citizens that bought all the Obama hype and seated this complete inept child prodigy community orgaznizer as POTUS and are not showing their disdain for all his campaign LIES at all. This alone shows the truth and that is dems vote dem regardless of ANYTHING. Hopefully 11/2012 they will clearly show they've had enough of this inexperienced child divider and if not then you indeed will DESERVE the SKYROCKTING utility bills Obama promised you must be passed along to you under his plan and the ever escalating price of gas now at $3.85 average compared to $1.87 when GW Bush left office. It's dispicable however the complete pass voters and the Lame Stream MSM give Obama as he is now out there openly preparing for his convention collection of upcoming lies telling us to 'gear up for a long tough fight' in Afghanistan and no outrage at all. That same Lame Stream MSM gave Cindy Sheehan and her 20 Code Pink protesters round the clock coverage daily/weekly outside the Bush Crawford ranch yet completely backs Obama as he tells the nation that he bascally lied and now must follow the Military Command. I agree he has very little choice as indeed the Military Command is a strong force established now for over 240 years and surely they would never allow a Chicago community organzizer to step in and start dictating how they will fight. Folks that believe such non-sense are indeed nonsensical and naive to the max. Just as Bush did not decide to open the battle in Iraq but rather the Military Command the same holds today as indeed our fighting machine is not finished in Afghanistan or the Middle East overall at all but for Obama to be out there now spinning it in such manner as he is in complete control with ZERO media or dem constituency outrage shows just how corrupt this dem machine is. . .. .. . . We are in the process of testing our new message boards. Please provide your feedback</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346520719492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346521136180-14</Id><Title>Mormon or Obamamuslimist?</Title><Msg>Good point and add to that what Huckabee said at the convention: 'what is more disingenous a President claiming to be Christian (Obama) yet supporting partial birth abortion, infanticide and $716 billion cut to Medicaid or a Morman not only prolife but on the record for endless charity behind the scenes when no cameras were there for the now infamous Obama endless photo ops.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346521136180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528454031-15</Id><Topic><Title>VRNG</Title><Username>frankomd</Username><Timestamp>1346487746818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:22:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To be honest, I don't think anyone(SHAREHOLDERS)have any idea of the damage this lawsuit will bring to GOOGLE. They will be blindsided when the verdict comes in for VRNG. They think of themselves as a GOLIATH and cannot be damaged, but a $1,000,000,000 loss in this trial will hurt bad.$680 down to $400 PPS.by end of OCT. Oct. 16 trial begins!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346528454031</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528859950-16</Id><Topic><Title>SPLITTING...</Title><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1346512303934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will anounce next week for sure. that's why we are on a terror. 6 for 1.......... All the hedge funds have been aware for a month now. You will be surprised next week sir</Msg><Username>northofheaven2000005</Username><Timestamp>1346528859950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528928548-17</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489985196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot mr jack-ie off-ie</Msg><Username>northofhell200333333</Username><Timestamp>1346528928548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346529109075-18</Id><Title>$1,000,000,000 Loss Coming</Title><Msg>All I have to say is VRNG</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346529109075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346529328671-19</Id><Topic><Title>SPLITTING...</Title><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1346512303934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will be splitting when VRNG takes half of it's net worth.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346529328671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346531227963-20</Id><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Msg>interesting.</Msg><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346532755198-21</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489985196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for all your support Mr. You sound like Clint is that you Eastwood?</Msg><Username>northofhell200333333</Username><Timestamp>1346532755198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535097788-22</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the VRNG ruling will sting at the end of October. 32 trading days till Oct. 16.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346535097788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535511051-23</Id><Topic><Title>CLINT EASTWOOD was ACES!</Title><Username>briggrunner</Username><Timestamp>1346489985196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:59:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about all th big MISTAKES made from '00 to '08 that led to this. Your idea is to try it again. Face it, it didn't work!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1346535511051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346536010377-24</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it hurts android and its ecosystem. it hurts goog presence and delivering of goog service in mobile space thru android. why pay for goog when it cant grow in mobile space? lol...</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346536010377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346536181225-25</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in next couple to a year, people like who are looking mobile device probably will only look at window 8 or apple OS mobile device (tablet, phone, blabla..)</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346536181225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346536596554-26</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is GOOG CEO Playing SoftBall With Apple? Is He Helping Apple OR Shareholders?</Title><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1346504917527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:08:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The future of Google is in Android and those like Samsung that make Android products" you absolutely nailed. before android is pronounced DEAD. dead to vendors and users. before users start thinking about non-android device. before they search and view video on non-google service. lol, apple already forbidden youtubing on its next gen iphone. do you need more indication of google's space in mobile space - yeah ZERO...</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1346536596554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346544890053-27</Id><Title>What about all th big MISTAKES made from '00 to '08 that led to this. ????</Title><Msg>You dems is nuts!! Never do you mention 100 years of primary dem party control handing us EVERY failed system and entitlement of today. Just check the charts to KNOW the last 100 years and you will see all 'dem BLUE' years for primary control. You are so tiny minded to keep chiming the dem mantra about Bush and the last decades when in FACT dems have controlled most over the last 100 years and as that IDIOT Mr. Alan 'Andrea Mitchell dem' Greenspan said in 2009 'we are ending a 100 year business cycle.' My question then and now 'why did they end it 9/2008 if not to ensure crowning Obamadungdufus?' Folks must be on guard now for another such 9/12 or 10/12 surprise by the dems as the FILTHY RICH SOROS and other one world government types try to again sieze the moment with more fake 'financial recovery show' that all one must do is look at the current debt of $16 Trillion and know any talk of financial reform by dems is 1,000% OXYMORON and emphasize the MORONS! Obama and the dem Pelosi Congress piled on $5.6 TRILLION new debt more increase than all prior Presidents combined with the MASSIVE HEALTHCARE WELFARE BILL "TAX" yet to kick in 2014. One thing is certain dems signed the Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE into law 1913 using another trick move just like the trick 51 vote Budget Reconciliation they used to ram through the MASSIVE HEALTHCARE WELFARE BILL "TAX" for one reason only 'to feed their Fed CREATURE bank debt upon which it functions. Open them thar eyes dems you've been SMOODGED but have taken us wiser folks with you all these 'dem BLUE' failed years. Time for some real change. ANYONE but Obama 2012 then continued House cleaning ridding RINOS and backseating Dingy Harry the Body Reid and the do nothing Senate. As the Roberts ruling continues to be analyzed I believe his words say it all: 1. It is a tax just as we all surmised from the beginning and 2; most importantly the court cannot protect the citizens from the consequences of an election. So you see, just as I and many said, Obama has indeed changed the country forever in a very bad way. We indeed will now have the UK failed system of socialized medicine, to replace our very outstanding previously profit driven capitalistic form of medicine that being the very factor that made it so great. What this is truly about is 100 years of primary democrat party failed control for which their chickens indeed have come home to roost and they spent all our money (SS/Medicare, income taxes etc..) on welfare to lock in democrat votes moving forward. 1913 dem Wilson Federal Reserve Bank CREATURE that has debt leveraged our currency to zero intrinsic value, 1933 dem FDR failed SS Ponzi that was only to cost $.03 per pay, 1964 dem LBJ failed Medicare Ponzi now completely broke necessitating socialized medicine with the death panels to preclude costly care for the boomers now retiring in mass and being told all the money taken from them was squandered on welfare, and now Obama under dem Pelosi Congress more debt increase than all prior Presidents combined in less than 3.6 years. Yes Justice Roberts is correct that the court cannot be responsible for the consequences of an election, indeed Obama Care is a huge cost and most importantly this decision will cost many more jobs and the USA as once known is now finished. Hopefully Romney can stand on the 10th Amendment which is correct asserting that healthcare in MA was a states issue and this Federal mandate is not but repealing it now will be tough and impossible without Repubs taking House, Senate and POTUS. Without Harry Reid gone nothing will ever be accomplished.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1346544890053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346548214198-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>win8 is DOA</Msg><Username>ipud_deity</Username><Timestamp>1346548214198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549730398-29</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Samsung ruling did hurt Google. The wimps at Google came out to side with Apple and say it was the changes that Samsung made to the Android system that got them in trouble. Nice to see the people at Google don't even support a partner like Samsung in a one sided trial. The wimps at Google, the Google CEO should get their butts to the U.S. Patent office and invalidate some claims in those broad Apple patents. My vote is to get rid of everyone on the board if they don't. Use those Motorola patents and come down on Apple fast and hard.</Msg><Username>fireundersmoke</Username><Timestamp>1346549730398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:35:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346553275908-30</Id><Topic><Title>The Samsung ruling didn't hurt GOOG one bit</Title><Username>woelfelinc</Username><Timestamp>1346531227963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't help AAPL one bit either, they are back to where they were before the ruling.</Msg><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1346553275908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>