<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347528360350-1</Id><Topic><Title>Google in Deep Doo Doo! VRNG!</Title><Username>letitgrowknows</Username><Timestamp>1347495568601</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:19:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"With an Apple acquisition of Vringo" Wow! Vringo bagholders are really getting desperate</Msg><Username>andresfandom</Username><Timestamp>1347528360350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 05:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347532805147-2</Id><Title>Ever Notice?</Title><Msg>Ever notice how dems just pick up on whatever the Lame Stream MSM spin of the day is? Check dem posts and you will see they always chime in with the MSM talking points whatever they are for the day. Now we have, in JAMMY CARTER remnants, another Ambassador murdered on foreign soil and immediately Lame Stream MSM attacks Romney for speaking out in a much stronger fashion by the way than Obama. But then Obama is having his way with removal of Mubarak and Gaddafi being replaced by the very USA hating Muslim Brotherhood. Just watch though and it will be easy to perceive how naive dem Obama worshippers are as they instantly attach to whatever the Lame Stream MSM co-arm of the dem party tells them to do. Romney has the 1st Amendment right to say whatever he so pleases then add to that the fact that he is running for President at this most horrific juncture in our history and I say it's refreshing to hear such leader stand up for the USA and not continue the apologies so inhererent with Obama and his Brotherhood laden regime. I dread that tonight they will again torture us with Obamadungdufus the empty suit addressing the nation with more of his teleprompter non sense IMAGE ONLY #$%$ that landed us here in the first place. Thank God the NFL will again be upstaging him and his accomplices. Romney is correct in his assertion these are very dangerous times for the USA and I firmly believe Obamadundufus is the ENEMY WITHIN and have felt that from day one. He is positioning the USA for destruction if not from within but also from without. Now come on dems wait for your daily talking points then tell us all about it. HA! Imbeciles in mass! You could not see Russia from Moscow!!!</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1347532805147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:40:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347537984955-3</Id><Topic><Title>on2 lawsuit</Title><Username>msj21464</Username><Timestamp>1287610350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-10-20 17:32:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Acer cancels smartphone launch with Alibaba at last minute SHANGHAI, Sept 13 | Thu Sep 13, 2012 SHANGHAI, Sept 13 | Thu Sep 13, 2012 7:12am EDT SHANGHAI, Sept 13 (Reuters) - A planned launch of a smartphone between Acer Inc and a unit of Alibaba Group, China's biggest e-commerce firm, was canceled on Thursday due to what Alibaba said was pressure from Google Inc on the Taiwanese group. Acer and Alibaba's cloud computing unit had planned to launch the Acer CloudMobile A800 smartphone, using Alibaba's mobile operating system, Aliyun, in Shanghai on Thursday afternoon. But when journalists showed up for the event they were not allowed to enter the venue and an Alibaba Cloud Computing official said the launch had been canceled due to internal reasons. Later, Alibaba's unit released a statement saying Acer had faced pressure from Google and pulled out of the launch event. "Our partner received notification from Google that if the new product launch with Aliyun went ahead, Google would terminate Android product cooperation and related technical authorization with Acer," Alibaba Cloud Computing said in a statement.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347537984955</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347539939832-4</Id><Title>GOOGLE may get desperate(VRNG)</Title><Msg>VP of Google admitted fault with patents they are using from VRNG. The trial OCT.16 is a slam dunk for VRNG,Google may have to pay similar to Samsung ruling!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347539939832</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347540032233-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Wonder how much is a drone? By casp321.2 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . What you need is just trying to figure out the RELATION of how those group in Beirut were created and run by Shackley, Buckley, Kangarlu and what were Ghorbanifar, North, Secord, Kangarlu, Mousavi relation and roles in those underground operations, then you 'll see NO secret as they try to make them secret and keep HIDING the ORIGINATOR from you: All from the same "BakerHouse: Kosher and Halal:</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347540032233</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347540304383-6</Id><Topic><Title>Ever Notice?</Title><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1347532805147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 06:40:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And MONDAY MORNING quarterback ROMNEY would have done things differrently,republicans are so desparate ther're trying to elect the only DOLT available. How sad they look!</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347540304383</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347540549599-7</Id><Title>OBAMA-LINCOLN (SAME)</Title><Msg>For all people, not just one class(rich)</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347540549599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541739149-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am loving what I have been reading on this company</Msg><Username>penningtonroberta</Username><Timestamp>1347541739149</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347541880859-9</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wait till VRNG decision for decline</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347541880859</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542168995-10</Id><Topic><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...GUIDES FOR 40% 2013 REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE NET INCOME. NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347291878048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A cloud play growing profitably exponentially and trading at 5 PE? You've got to be kidding me right? That customer list is very impressive too. Their chart looks pretty good too...Thanks!!</Msg><Username>anny.sakana</Username><Timestamp>1347542168995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347542794261-11</Id><Topic><Title>Westinghouse Solar, Inc. (WEST) Google it</Title><Username>serenityloveh69</Username><Timestamp>1346849607980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 08:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patients are worth at least $4.00 a share</Msg><Username>serenityloveh69</Username><Timestamp>1347542794261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542835058-12</Id><Title>NObama (the APOLOGIZER in chief) loves poor people so much...he keeps creating more of them!</Title><Msg>Vote NObama out in Nov.!!!</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347542835058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542855195-13</Id><Title>GOOGLE does not want trial with VRNG</Title><Msg>OCT. 16 trial will damage Google not only in PPS, but in not being able to use the technology they are using illegally now. Google has to settle before, or risk a similar SAMSUNG loss. Shareholders, if you're smart, you have to take this trial serius.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347542855195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543012974-14</Id><Topic><Title>Who is ORDERING Yahoo to Delay the TIMESTAMPPED messages ALREADY posted?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1327147898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-01-21 07:11:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mohsen Kangarlou was one of them that worked for Behzad Nabavi and Mousavi’s</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347543012974</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347543097747-15</Id><Topic><Title>NObama (the APOLOGIZER in chief) loves poor people so much...he keeps creating more of them!</Title><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347542835058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now who' s the minority(rich), that's why Republicans have no chance, Romney represents only upper class, that's his downfall.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347543097747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347544032345-16</Id><Title>jamesgreaves555-full time UNEMPLOYABLE?</Title><Msg>can u at least try for a regular job? oh I forgot, posting here is ur full-time job!</Msg><Username>hypocritrepublican</Username><Timestamp>1347544032345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347544655637-17</Id><Topic><Title>jamesgreaves555-full time UNEMPLOYABLE?</Title><Username>hypocritrepublican</Username><Timestamp>1347544032345</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow,Touched a nerve, or the truth hurts.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347544655637</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347545853608-18</Id><Title>Huge Insider buy</Title><Msg>NS director bought 25 MILLION shares and it pays 8%!!!!</Msg><Username>chessnotcheckersed</Username><Timestamp>1347545853608</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347546440914-19</Id><Title>NTWK $5.7 UP 32C .....BREAKING OUT!!!....ANALYST TARGET $16....3M SHARE FLOAT....PROFITABLE CLOUD PLAY</Title><Msg>$10 Short term target.....easy double. Look at technicals and fundamentals coming together.......rally just getting started Huge profitable growth per guidance (40% revenue growth and 300% net income growth to $1/share in 2013) Forward PE only 5.5....trading at 20% sector average</Msg><Username>kellyjessica50</Username><Timestamp>1347546440914</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:27:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347546741644-20</Id><Title>Hypocritrepub-Quite a portfolio you have(Several Pages)</Title><Msg>If anyone needs a job, it points to you, check your record, it speaks for itself, you really are a hypocrite as your name pertains.By the way I am employed and work 50 hours a week.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347546741644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547267145-21</Id><Title>LOL: VRNG PPS INCREASED from $3.15 on 8-31-2012 to $3.52 on 9-12-2012</Title><Msg>LOL: VRNG PPS INCREASED from $3.15 on 8-31-2012 to $3.52 on 9-12-2012 While Short desperately tried to keep PPS down in August: VRNG Short Interest Settlement Date: 8/31/2012 Short Interest: 6,423,289 Settlement Date: 8/15/2012 Short Interest:4,031,566</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347547267145</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:41:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347549766885-22</Id><Title>U.S. Ambassador DEAD, thanks to 0bama for supporting the Arab Spring.</Title><Msg>...</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347549766885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347549809841-23</Id><Title>Why did obama put enemies of America in power in Egypt &amp; Libya? Why would he do such a thing?</Title><Msg>...</Msg><Username>stockguru7</Username><Timestamp>1347549809841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347551809435-24</Id><Topic><Title>NObama (the APOLOGIZER in chief) loves poor people so much...he keeps creating more of them!</Title><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347542835058</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:27:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frankly, I'm not that fond of Romney either, but at this point anyone is better than that #$%$ loser APOLOGIZER IN CHIEF NObama!</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347551809435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347552075442-25</Id><Title>Wont matter whether we get QE3, 4, or 5... The $ will tank, prices will rise on FOOD &amp; GAS...</Title><Msg>And markets will TANK! Just ask your local retiree, savers, the unemployed and under employed if they're better off today with NObama's &amp; Bernanke's policies?</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1347552075442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:01:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347554578804-26</Id><Topic><Title>Congress WASHING USA BLOODY hands in Iraq/Iran in 1980s War That Killed Over 1 Million</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1328014445000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-31 07:54:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Congress WASHING USA BLOODY hands in Iraq/Iran in 1980s War That Killed Over 1 Million By casp321.2 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Why would Media comparing Ghotbzadeh "destiny" to those involved in current Egypt??? Ghotbzadeh was EXECUTED in 1982 even though he was one who were on the FIRST line to work with CIA/NSA to bring current Iranian regime to power:</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347554578804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347554764533-27</Id><Topic><Title>A SHAM election in Iran and a SHAM "bluffing" from the USA</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1330781794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-03-03 08:36:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are one of the reasons Yahoo is introducing "new format": Re: A SHAM election in Iran and a SHAM "bluffing" from the USA By casp321.6 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Interestingly enough, to SAVE one of their own SKIN in Iran, like Mousavi or kahrobi BUT NOT Ghotbzadeh, they "EXPOSE" the ones that they want to be saved and before losing their HEADs in the power struggle in Iran. It seems the Media in the USA are trying to Save Mousavi since he helped Republican to become president in 1980 but in 1982, having Republican president in USA not only did NOT save Ghotbzadeh they ORDERED for his ELIMINATION as soon as possible so he could NOT talk about Safari-Club, Secord, Shackley, .... ------------- Of course some of the DATEs are NOT accurate for obvious reasons.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347554764533</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347555606897-28</Id><Title>and here isyour chance to UNLOAD it all before</Title><Msg>others wise up. no reason in world to not want to sell into this of all stocks</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1347555606897</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347559231718-29</Id><Title>German court backs Apple in patent fight with Motorola</Title><Msg>FRANKFURT | Thu Sep 13, 2012 6:04pm BST (Reuters) - A court in Munich ruled on Thursday that Motorola Mobility, owned by Google Inc, had infringed an Apple Inc patent and ordered that all tablets and smartphones containing the technology be recalled. Judge Peter Guntz said Motorola had infringed Apple's "overscroll bounce" technology, which enables users to move documents over the screen of their device and let them bounce back to the centre after releasing their fingers. A spokeswoman for the court said the ruling was not likely to have an immediate impact as Apple would have to specifically request a ban on the product and Motorola could also appeal against the ruling. FREE GUIDES AND REPORTS FROM DIANOMIADVERTISEMENT Market Outlook What does the rest of 2012 hold for stocks? Download Free Report Apple and Google did not immediately reply to requests for a comment on the ruling. Google bought loss-making Motorola Mobility for $12.5 billion (7.7 billion pounds) last year, in its largest acquisition ever, aiming to use the company's patents to fend off legal attacks on its Android mobile platform and expand beyond its software business. Other technology companies have also invested billions of dollars in buying up patent portfolios that they can use against rivals and have also ploughed money into litigation in the United States and Europe. Last month Apple scored a landmark legal victory over Samsung Electronics Co Ltd when a U.S. jury found the Korean company had copied critical features of the iPhone and iPad and awarded Apple $1.05 billion in damages. Germany has become a major battleground in the global patent war between makers of mobile phones, tablet computer devices and their operating software, as court actions there have proved to be relatively cheap and speedier than in other jurisdictions. (Reporting by Harro ten Wolde; Editing by David Holmes)</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1347559231718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347565299809-30</Id><Title>what's with the $0.50 spreads on the 9/14 705c's?</Title><Msg>that crap!</Msg><Username>daddybigstick1028</Username><Timestamp>1347565299809</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566756959-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why yahoo blokes the posts? Are they EXPECTING COORDINATED scam announcement from different corners??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1345773491431</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 21:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need just to DECODE what they mean. Was/is it NOT? This is HOW they make it kosher and halal at the SAME "BakerHouse" and "sell" it as kosher OR halal, depending who their AUDIENCE might be!!!!! ----- "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. ----- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347566756959</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347567145210-32</Id><Title>TOMORROW - 688 OPEN 696 CLOSE</Title><Msg>GIDDY UP!</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1347567145210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347567305444-33</Id><Topic><Title>TOMORROW - 688 OPEN 696 CLOSE</Title><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1347567145210</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL THAT IS!</Msg><Username>bigghowie</Username><Timestamp>1347567305444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568467157-34</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: Yahoo Admin BLOCKING TIMESTAMPPED Messages</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1332511369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-03-23 10:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“The Safari Club needed a network of banks to finance its intelligence operations. With the official blessing of George H.W. Bush as the head of the CIA,” Saudi intelligence chief, Kamal Adham, “transformed a small Pakistani merchant bank, the Bank of Credit and Commerce International (BCCI), into a world-wide money-laundering machine, buying banks around the world to create the biggest clandestine money network in history.”[2] As CIA director, George H.W. Bush “cemented strong relations with the intelligence services of both Saudi Arabia and the shah of Iran. He worked closely with Kamal Adham, the head of Saudi intelligence, brother-in-law of King Faisal and an early BCCI insider.” Adham had previously acted as a “channel between [Henry] Kissinger and [Egyptian President] Anwar Sadat” in 1972.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347568467157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568506715-35</Id><Topic><Title>Another October, is it "Surprise"??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1318597393000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-10-14 09:03:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Safari Club – An Alternate Super Intelligence Agency Alexandre de Marenches The Safari Club- An Alternate Super Intelligence Agency. In September 1 1976, a group of countries got together and established a newly formed secret cabal of intelligence agencies called the Safari Club. It included France, Egypt, Saudi Arabia, Morocco, and Iran [Secret service during the Shah called SAVAK]. The club was a brain child of Alexandre de Marenches, head of the French external intelligence service SDECE.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347568506715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568525963-36</Id><Title>tomorow open 707$ close 712$</Title><Msg>goo goog</Msg><Username>fonsvanhoof</Username><Timestamp>1347568525963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568543327-37</Id><Topic><Title>USA "Plot" SCAMs and Saudi Involvement?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1318506584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-10-13 07:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Safari Club – An Alternate Super Intelligence Agency It stops at almost nothing to further the bank’s aims the world over.”Saudi Prince Mohammed al-Faisal also set up Faisal Islamic Bank of Egypt (FIBE) as part of the banking empire. The “Blind Sheikh,” Sheikh Omar Abdul-Rahman was one of its founding members. Growth of Islamic banking would directly help the growth of the Islamist movements, and allow the Saudis to pressure poorer Islamic nations, like Egypt, to shift their policies to the right. FIBE worked closely with BCCI. Investigators would later find that BCCI held $589 million in “unrecorded deposits,” $245 million of which were placed with FIBE! BCCI at a later stage was also ‘discovered’ to be deeply implicated in illegal arms and narcotics trade .But all this was to happen way in the future, when CIA wanted to get back into the driving seat!</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347568543327</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568590885-38</Id><Topic><Title>USA "Plot" SCAMs and Saudi Involvement?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1318506584000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-10-13 07:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is not clear when the Safari Club disbands, but it existence was exposed not long after the shah was deposed in Iran in 1979, and it seems to have disappeared by the time de Marenches stepped down from being head of French intelligence in 1982. September 1, 1976-Early 1980s: Secret Intelligence Cabal Works with Rogue CIA Elements to Influence Middle East and Africa The Safari Club included France, Egypt, Saudi Arabia, Morocco, and Iran.” [Scott, 2007, pp. 62] An Egyptian reporter digging through Iranian government archives will later discover that the Safari Club was officially founded on September 1, 1976. Alexandre de Marenches, head of the French external intelligence service SDECE, was the chief instigator of the group. Author Joe Trento will later allege that the Safari Club, and especially the Saudi intelligence agency led by Kamal Adham and then his nephew Prince Turki from 1979 onwards, fund off-the-books covert operations for the CIA. But rather than working with the CIA as it is being reformed during the Carter administration, this group prefers to work with a private CIA made up of fired agents close to ex-CIA Director George Bush Sr. and Theodore Shackley, who Trento alleges is at the center of a “private, shadow spy organization within” the CIA until he is fired in 1979.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347568590885</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347568739706-39</Id><Topic><Title>Who is pulling the "WAGON"???</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1318606428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2011-10-14 11:33:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>November 22, 2002: More Defendants Added to 9/11 Lawsuit Against Saudis 9/11 victims’ relatives add nearly 50 defendants to their $1 trillion lawsuit against mostly Saudi citizens and organizations Saudi Interior Minister Prince Nayef. The suit claims he was engaged in payoffs to al-Qaeda. Additionally, as interior minister he controls the activities of numerous Islamic charities said to help finance al-Qaeda. Super Intelligence Agency Alexandre de Marenches The Safari Club- An Alternate Super Intelligence Agency. In September 1 1976, a group of countries got together and established a newly formed secret cabal of intelligence agencies called the Safari Club. It included France, Egypt, Saudi Arabia, Morocco, and Iran. The club was a brain child of Alexandre de Marenches, head of the French external intelligence service SDECE. It was likely formed with the connivance of CIA to compensate for it’s paralysis after Watergate – as a means of circumventing US Congress which had tied down the CIA! Acutely conscious of the Soviet threat these countries had decided that if the US could not do anything to counter it, they would. Alexandre de Marenches, head of the French external intelligence service SDECE, was the chief instigator of the group. Millions are spent to create staff, offices, communications, and operational capability. Periodic secret conferences are held in Saudi Arabia, France, and Egypt. This group plays a secret role in political intrigues in many countries, mostly in Africa and the Middle East. For instance, a rebellion in Zaire is put down by Moroccan and Egyptian troops, using French air support. Author Joe Trento will later allege that the Safari Club, and especially the Saudi intelligence agency led by Kamal Adham and then his nephew Prince Turki from 1979 onwards, fund off-the-books covert operations for the CIA. But rather than working with the CIA as it is being reformed during the Carter administration, this group prefers to work with a private CIA made up of fired agents close to ex-CIA Director George Bush Sr. and Theodore Shackley, who Trento alleges is at the center of a “private, shadow spy organization within” the CIA until he is fired in 1979. The Safari Club and rogue CIA will play a major role in supporting the mujaheddin in Afghanistan. [Scott, 2007, pp. 63-64, 111] It is not clear when the Safari Club disbands, but it existence was exposed not long after the shah was deposed in Iran in 1979, and it seems to have disappeared by the time de Marenches stepped down from being head of French intelligence in 1982.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347568739706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568798952-40</Id><Title>adwords payment glitch</Title><Msg>down all day, anyone who make a daily payments cannot do so.</Msg><Username>robgolden1986</Username><Timestamp>1347568798952</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347569801269-41</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1331259440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-03-08 21:17:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mohsen Kangarlou was one of them that worked for Behzad Nabavi and Mousavi’s ------- November 27, 1988 In fact, Mr. Ghorbanifar later claimed that Mr. Kengarlou had arranged Mr. Buckley's capture. ------- Indeed, Buckley had had to approve CIA assassinations undertaken by the Shackley organizations. -------------- Re: When will be Google turn? 17-Feb-12 11:17 pm Secord still possibly OPERATINg with Iran's SECRET agencies. Search for Secord activiies in Iran in 1970s under the shah and 1979 and 1980s under CURRENT Iranian regime</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347569801269</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:56:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347571300037-42</Id><Title>Will short this tomorrow likes its 1999</Title><Msg>Money money money money, MONEY Some people got to have it Hey, Hey, Hey - some people really need it Hey, listen to me, y'all do thangs, do thangs, do thangs - bad thangs with it Well, you wanna do thangs, do thangs, do thangs - good thangs with it - yeah Un Huh, talkin' bout cash money, money Talkin' bout cash money - dollar bills y'all - come on, now LOL!!</Msg><Username>pharrisa</Username><Timestamp>1347571300037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347576200724-43</Id><Title>AAPL WINS PATENT VS MOTOROLA IN GERMANY, WIN VS SAMSUNG=GOOG IN BIG SIHT</Title><Msg>Goog anti trust competitive android, samsung and motorola losing===== goog in big trouble</Msg><Username>tamermou</Username><Timestamp>1347576200724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347576300635-44</Id><Title>Uncle Ben Bernanke doing all he can to assist Obama</Title><Msg>Today dem loyal Uncle Ben Bernanke (acclaiming non partisanship) avowed dems will again feed their FED RESERVE CREATURE BANK MORE DEBT to the tune of $40 billion per month until after the election. Now don't you just love that timing. Bernanke acclaims this should create many jobs. What a lack of concern for the true state of our nation by adding more debt to the already monstrous $16 TRILLION (one third under Obama.) Hopefully businesses won't fall for the ploy and not hire. It's all smoking mirrors with that outragious debt burden hanging over our heads. One thing is certain when there is fire you don't throw gasoline upon it.</Msg><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1347576300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347579233473-45</Id><Topic><Title>Uncle Ben Bernanke doing all he can to assist Obama</Title><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1347576300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ummm...that would be "smoke and mirrors"....... Also, Ben didn"t say "untill after the election", he said until employment picture improves, also, Ben is a Republican held over from the Bush yrs.</Msg><Username>styro90</Username><Timestamp>1347579233473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347579831334-46</Id><Title>Facebook Outperforming Google in Ads From Browsing $FB $GOOG</Title><Msg>Facebook Outperforming Google in Ads From Browsing $FB $GOOG</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347579831334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347582365083-47</Id><Title>Ben Bernanke-Appointed. by Mr. BUSH</Title><Msg>So do we blame the REPUBLICANS for this decision? They're the one's doing all the complaining too.The REPUBLICANS seem to be confused.</Msg><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347582365083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347585738218-48</Id><Title>Ambassador sodomized before being murdered</Title><Msg>Just reported that Ambassador Christopher Stevens was raped and sodomized before being murdered yesterday. Obama's naivety will get us all killed. As Governor Romney correctly asserted 'we are living in very dangerous times.' Obama must go!</Msg><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1347585738218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347585953397-49</Id><Topic><Title>Ben Bernanke-Appointed. by Mr. BUSH</Title><Username>jamesgreaves555</Username><Timestamp>1347582365083</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:26:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And reappointed by NObama, beside the 'real' question is would W have reappointed him after seeing what an F'turd he turned out to be? Also GreenSPAM was appointed originally by papa Bush and then reappointed countless times by "I Did Not Have Sexual Relations With That Woman..." Slick Willie. So, seriously what's your point? Because other than your selective memory and obvious partisan wrangling I really see no value in your lower than whale s#it IQ level comment. So do us all a favor and go crawl back under that rock your daddy #$%$ on and you sprang out from. Would you please?</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347585953397</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347586375917-50</Id><Topic><Title>Ambassador sodomized before being murdered</Title><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1347585738218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:22:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe it, after all NObama and his lackeys (i.e., Bernanke) have been doing the same to this once proud country the last 4 years as well. Still my condolence to the Steven's family.</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347586375917</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347586715223-51</Id><Title>The most in-depth information available on GOOG stock</Title><Msg>The team at Thepennystockgeek has performed some wonderful analysis and through this they have provided some compelling insight, which has assisted me in the decision making process and now I have a better understanding of GOOG, check it out at, thepennystockgeek dotcom</Msg><Username>bateman5842</Username><Timestamp>1347586715223</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347587460124-52</Id><Topic><Title>Uncle Ben Bernanke doing all he can to assist Obama</Title><Username>obamadungdufus</Username><Timestamp>1347576300635</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:45:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ben is a deranged Keynesian who wants to keep his million $$$ salary job and see his picture all over TV 24/7 and that's not going to happen if Romney gets elected especially after he said he wants him fired, right? Beside how many jobs has 4 years of QE and 4 trillion further in debt gotten us? Care to guess. I'll tell you how many, nada, zilch, zip, zero...not even one flipping burgers! S#it Bernanke has spent over 1.6 million on every adult in this country so far and hasn't even created ONE F'n Walmart greeter job. Now that's F'd up to say the least. Yes people NObama and his Keynesian lackey likes poor people so much they keep creating more of them. So, I say let's send him back to the WH so he can complete the job of converting this once proud and prosperous country into another sewage trap like all those other rich, democratic and above all peaceful #ell holes countries of the Middle East. What do you say?</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1347587460124</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347591683369-53</Id><Title>Would this market rally have legs?</Title><Msg>1. Fiscal cliff looming 2. Unemployment still a big issue 3. Corporate earnings would be hit and miss 4. NASDAQ at the highest point since 2000 (that's 12 years) Thoughts?</Msg><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347591683369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592114216-54</Id><Topic><Title>Will short this tomorrow likes its 1999</Title><Username>pharrisa</Username><Timestamp>1347571300037</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 17:21:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would this market rally have legs? 1. Fiscal cliff looming 2. Unemployment still a big issue 3. Corporate earnings would be hit and miss 4. NASDAQ at the highest point since 2000 (that's 12 years) Thoughts?</Msg><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347592114216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:08:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347592319680-55</Id><Topic><Title>Would this market rally have legs?</Title><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347591683369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Couple of more things: 1. Europe still not out of the woods 2. China growth is stalling Thoughts?</Msg><Username>pricelinelong</Username><Timestamp>1347592319680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 23:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>