<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348481788035-1</Id><Title>Romney to cut taxes in Reagan fashion</Title><Msg>I hope folks are out of ‘Obama Image Mode’ 11/2012 and heard the 60 Minutes 1 hour dialogue with Romney and Obama. Romney will lower all tax rates (top 35% back down to 28% just as Reagan) and across the board for all. This will again spur jobs and the economy just as it did when the Gipper brought us out of the Jimmy Carter nightmare (until Obama the worst on record since the 1929 Great Depression.) Obama now holds that record (not Bush!!!) What we must be on guard about now is the Lame Stream MSM co-arm of the dem party spinning it as class warfare (the ole Karl Marx platform at its max.) Romney went on to clarify he will severely cut loopholes for rich at the top but that 28% rate will still send the job rate soaring again as all small business (S-Corps/LLC’s filing as Corps.) who’s business taxes flow through their personal taxes as a conduit, will again see profit a strong potential for growth!!! 2012 must be about anyone but Obama first and foremost.</Msg><Username>foretherun</Username><Timestamp>1348481788035</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348484046903-2</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>06/19/12 Google exec: technology wave leaving many behind Google executive warns that technology revolution is leaving many behind Schmidt was in [sIrael] to attend an annual conference sponsored by President Shimon Peres. Despite his concerns, Schmidt delivered an optimistic message, saying that the tremendous growth of smartphones can quickly reduce the gaps between haves and have-nots. Netanyahu's office said the two men [Eric Schmidt ...]also discussed cooperation in medicine, science and defense against cyber-attacks.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348484046903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 06:54:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348485668067-3</Id><Title>2007: Here Comes The Google Mafia</Title><Msg>Here Comes The Google Mafia Erick Schonfeld Friday, December 28th, 2007 As Googlers get long in the tooth and their stock options fully vest, some are hanging up their employee badges and giving up the free food at the Google cafeteria to try their hand as venture capitalists and angel investors. (That is, if Facebook doesn’t nab them first). Just like the Paypal Mafia before them (Peter Thiel, Elon Musk, Reid Hoffman, Max Levchin, Chad Hurley and Steve Chen, Jeremy Stoppelman, David O. Sacks, etc), these rich alums are setting out to use their Google money as seed capital for a new round of startups. So who are these people? The growing Google Mafia includes Chris Sacca, Aydin Senkut, Paul Buchheit, Georges Harik, Satya Patel, Salman Ullah, Sean Dempsey, and Andrea Zurek. Sacca just left his post as head of Google’s bid for wireless spectrum and WiFi initiatives to become a full-time angel investor. Already while at Google, he invested in Twitter and PhotoBucket. Zurek, a former manager for AdWords, is also an angel. Patel, another former Google adverising exec, now works for Battery Ventures. Former deal-makers Ullah and Dempsey are reportedly raising money for their own venture fund. -------- Re: For Former On2 Shareholders By casp321 9 months ago Here is an EXAMPLE: "Chris Sacca knows success. As former Head of Special Initiatives for Google, he was privy to all projects in development and served as Google's leadership spokesperson." What this says is that Google and ON2 did NOT "know" the VALUE of ON2's FlixCloud but Google ex-EXEC found it out in the "first meeting." And NOW, the question is when that MEETING took place? They paid their "special" AGENTs through back door by giving away for "free" to Zencoder FIRST then DISTORTING Zncoder ORIGINATION date/history and then "INVITNG" those AGENTs to INVEST what was given away for "free" from ON2 shaeholders "pocket" ---It took me one meeting to know I wanted to work with Zencoder," said Chris Sacca, former Google executive, ---Chris Sacca knows success. As former Head of Special Initiatives for Google, he was privy to all projects in development and served as Google's leadership spokesperson. And, Sacca knows Twitter. Re: ON2's "lead" "plaintiffs" and ON2 defendants? By casp321 1 year 5 months ago What Our [Zencoder] Investors Say.... ---Chris Sacca, former Google executive, founder and managing director of Lowercase Capital ---- "It took me [Chris Sacca] one meeting to know I wanted to work with Zencoder" 04/12/11 "A team of the video realm's smartest hackers beating the pants off all competitors in a space that is growing exponentially? It took me one meeting to know I wanted to work with Zencoder," said Chris Sacca, former Google executive, founder and managing director of Lowercase Capital.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348485668067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 07:21:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348490027981-4</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG, Biggest Price Decliner! What Goes Up Must Come Down! Why The Sudden Drop?</Title><Username>lester.knowles19</Username><Timestamp>1328792509000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-02-09 08:01:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This will be one of my best trades ever</Msg><Username>lewisthurman250</Username><Timestamp>1348490027981</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348490835792-5</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>adding to the list. Wonder how I missed this: November 3, 2009 YouTube Video Dealmaker Jordan Hoffner Leaves Company YouTube executive Jordan Hoffner, who helped forge deals with Time Warner Inc. and Walt Disney Co. as director of content partnerships, is leaving the company. Re: on2 lawsuit By casp321 1 year 11 months ago 1) ON2 shareholders Sue Google in mid August 2009. 2) Google China President, Kai-Fu Lee, resigned in September 2009?? 3) Google head of global communications and public affairs at YouTube resigned in Sep 2009?? AND ON2 shareholders case is STILL on "TRACK" AND 4) Hurley Steps Down as YouTube CEO on OCTOBER 29, 2010</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348490835792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348490879686-6</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YouTube Video Dealmaker Jordan Hoffner Leaves Company (Update2) By Brian Womack - November 3, 2009 16:21 EST Nov. 3 (Bloomberg) -- YouTube executive Jordan Hoffner, who helped forge deals with Time Warner Inc. and Walt Disney Co. as director of content partnerships, is leaving the company. Hoffner will be replaced by Chris Maxcy, who has worked on agreements with record labels, said Aaron Zamost, a spokesman for YouTube, a division of Google Inc.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348490879686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348491533616-7</Id><Title>NTWK $6.7 .......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Up every day since record earnings......Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target......In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues…..Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average......Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions</Title><Msg>Short-term Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart. In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348491533616</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348491712698-8</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!!! How did I miss this: Nov 3, 2009 - 9:30AM YouTube’s Content Head Jordan Hoffner Leaving [Google/Youtube]To Join Ben Silverman’s New Venture Jordan Hoffner, the head of content partnerships for YouTube, is leaving the company, and joining Ben Silverman’s new content venture at IAC (NSDQ: IACI), we have learned. The move from YouTube was announced internally today. This is the second senior digital exec to join Silverman’s venture, after we first reported on Drew Buckley also joining it last month. Hoffner joined YouTube in 2006, right after Google (NSDQ: GOOG) bought it. He came from NBC, where he was the VP of digital running the NBCU digital studios. Prior to that at NBCU, he and Mike Steib, also now a Googler, conceived and launched NBC Weather Plus, a 24-hour digitally broadcast weather-news service.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348491712698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348492339395-9</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jordan Hoffner: Transformed by Television YouTube's Jordan Hoffner was captivated early on by the medium's power By Joel Topcik -- Broadcasting &amp; Cable, 12/30/2007 7:00:00 PM Jordan Hoffner knew early on that he wanted to pursue a career in television. The son of Larry Hoffner, a longtime ad-sales chief for NBC,</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348492339395</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348492781089-10</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jordan Hoffner: Transformed by Television YouTube's Jordan Hoffner was captivated early on by the medium's power By Joel Topcik -- Broadcasting &amp; Cable, 12/30/2007 After a year and a half, Hoffner returned to NBC as a researcher on the Today show under then Executive Producer Jeff Zucker. That enthusiasm led Hoffner to join NBC, where he spent more than a decade rising from news producer to digital programmer. And it also led him to leave the network behind for the next frontier in television: broadband video. For the past year, Hoffner has been something of a network president for YouTube, the online-video site owned by search giant Google. As head of content partnerships, he has forged ties with networks, station groups and other media companies to bring their content to YouTube's passionate audience. Hoffner began his career at NBC as an intern for CNBC while attending Vassar College in New York, and managed to parlay that into a gig as an NBC Sports runner at the 1992 Barcelona Olympics. But in the fall of 1992, he headed to Los Angeles, where he worked as an assistant to talent agent Marty Hurwitz in hopes of breaking into entertainment. After a year and a half, Hoffner returned to NBC as a researcher on the Today show under then Executive Producer Jeff Zucker. He moved up to associate producer, and in 1997 jumped to primetime as a producer for MSNBC's Big Show With Keith Olbermann. When the Monica Lewinsky scandal broke, he went to Washington, D.C., to produce reports for Olbermann and CNBC's The News With Brian Williams. Hoffner says he draws on his years at NBC to "speak both languages: the Internet for people out here, and the media language for people out there." His old boss Zucker, now president/CEO of NBC Universal, has taken note: “I've always had great respect for YouTube and what they do,” he says. "And I think Jordan has brought a great sense of professionalism and knowledge of the more traditional media companies to how they interact with the larger world."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348492781089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493179693-11</Id><Topic><Title>2009: Stanford professor mentored Google founders apparently drowned in his pool</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1346793412063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:16:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google’s SEC filing reveals YouTube investors are big winners after $1.65 billion sale February 9th, 2007 Sequoia Capital XI, the Sequoia fund that invested close to $11.5 million in YouTube from November 2005 to April 2006, was listed as having 941,027 shares, which are valued at more than $442 million.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348493179693</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348494117877-12</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jordan Hoffner, President of Digital Media, Electus Wednesday, April 28, 2010 8:15 to 9:30 am Paley Center Los Angeles THIS MEDIA COUNCIL EVENT IS INVITE-ONLY. Jordan Hoffner is the president of digital media for Electus, LLC, a subsidiary of the Interactive Corporation. He is a founding member of Electus and is responsible for all content development, programming, distribution and monetization across all digital platforms. Jordan came to Electus after spending over three years as the director of content partnerships at YouTube. He is responsible for establishing and managing content partnerships across all content verticals, specifically focusing on the entertainment, sports, film, television and broadcast sectors in the US, Canada and Latin America. Jordan transferred to the YouTube team shortly after the company was acquired by Google to help drive new partnerships for the next generation video platform. At Google, Jordan led the premium, archival and information video content efforts, focusing on cable television, music, and university videos. Prior to joining Google, Jordan was vice president of NBC Universal Digital Studios and led the Digital Studios team in producing and acquiring original broadband content. Jordan began his career at NBC in 1992. During his tenure there, he served as a production assistant, producer for "Today", senior producer for MSNBC's "The News with Brian Williams", director of NBC Corporate Development, and vice president and general manager of NBC Weather Plus.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348494117877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348495215321-13</Id><Topic><Title>Get better for GOOG lively authority. Discover in under wraps the Google Inc.</Title><Username>w_maynard</Username><Timestamp>1334750612000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-04-18 08:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>crawford.carlo90</Username><Timestamp>1348495215321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348496481805-14</Id><Topic><Title>goog will see 800 dollars</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1348336583895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:56:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was thinking they would hit $800 when it was just at $650 about a month ago. Now it looks pretty certain...Fundamental-wise and chart-wise it's looking very good!</Msg><Username>kupi23</Username><Timestamp>1348496481805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:21:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348496792115-15</Id><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Msg>Should be a reversal at any moment now....</Msg><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348498450926-16</Id><Title>Shorting GOOG here @$740-$742, Bad mgmt, stockholders unfriendly company, a sure-win short long term</Title><Msg>This is a sure-win short bet for a long term! Very bad mgmt, they issue shares reckless to anyone within the company with no voting right, and yet they're holding very little shares which control the company,and yet 2 of the founders have cashed out billions. Bad mgmts are always trying to screw shareholders and the company pays no dividend to its owners but keep diluting quarters after quarters. The company has been growing from 40%-50% a few years back to 10%-20% recently and sooner or later it will have 1%-5% growth. Remember they are shareholders unfriendly and pays nothing to its shareholders but keeping issuing more shares, this trick will soon be running out of hot air and all nonsense will kick in, ie, very bad mgmts, no dividends, keep diluting your ownership while they still control the company while cashing out, this is a sure-win bet in a long term, anything above $700 a share is a free money for anyone shorted it but of course it may take a bit longer people finally give up on this POS, I have plenty of margin left to wait a lot longer, this is a long term short bet. I am shorting here for good...</Msg><Username>lagrammy01</Username><Timestamp>1348498450926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348498595667-17</Id><Title>GOOG's all time high of 747.24 set November 7, 2007</Title><Msg>Close to being broken! Can it do it today?</Msg><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1348498595667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348498854959-18</Id><Title>Goog just killed facebook.</Title><Msg>any questions?</Msg><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1348498854959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348499075558-19</Id><Title>Wow, goog break out since last month. See you at $800.</Title><Msg>Break all time high of 5 years ago. Good sign!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>dslmantl</Username><Timestamp>1348499075558</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499078452-20</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG's all time high of 747.24 set November 7, 2007</Title><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1348498595667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Done, by 4 pennies.</Msg><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1348499078452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499327631-21</Id><Topic><Title>Goog just killed facebook.</Title><Username>osulinn</Username><Timestamp>1348498854959</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:00:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who cares???</Msg><Username>estanczyk</Username><Timestamp>1348499327631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499408187-22</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG's all time high of 747.24 set November 7, 2007</Title><Username>the_stock_warrior</Username><Timestamp>1348498595667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:56:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>many expecting the promised 3-1 split...around the corner?? booyah</Msg><Username>estanczyk</Username><Timestamp>1348499408187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:10:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499747834-23</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just entered the $750 weekly puts here at $8 + Lets see what happens next 2 days....</Msg><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348499747834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348499993294-24</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stocks massively overvalued vs what it has been delivering</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1348499993294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500261626-25</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong week to play with puts especially afte AAPL's perceived disappointiment. GOOG is priced for perfection by any technical measure but lagging funds will chase it right up to earnings announcement. Would wait another week or until it's well above 750 then take a shot that earnings disappoints or a "sell the news" happens.</Msg><Username>robynrokn</Username><Timestamp>1348500261626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348500437491-26</Id><Title>GOOG stock not doing a thing in 5 years</Title><Msg>GOOG stock not doing a thing in 5 years Just barely touch 747 that was the price in November, 2007</Msg><Username>ashok4598</Username><Timestamp>1348500437491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500465258-27</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh and btw, not that it really means much but look at GOOG, holy moly it's like 100 pts plus above its' 50 DMA.</Msg><Username>robynrokn</Username><Timestamp>1348500465258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500836163-28</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good point this trends higher all week, 780, 790? Think of it as a 7.90 stock and it was at 5.50 a few months ago; the move up makes sense. 7.45 to 7.9 is not a huge move</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348500836163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348501027659-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG stock not doing a thing in 5 years</Title><Username>ashok4598</Username><Timestamp>1348500437491</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:27:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the point? You can't go back 5 yrs and it sure has done a helluva lot in 5 weeks.</Msg><Username>robynrokn</Username><Timestamp>1348501027659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348501549827-30</Id><Title>These keeps trending up into earnings</Title><Msg>Wish I had my shares that I sold at 710; so be it. Another strong close and I buying some 760 calls monthly</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348501549827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348501823448-31</Id><Title>ask yourself why this would go down</Title><Msg>FB is not threat, apple sales are down and Android is being adopted, they have TONS of add revenue.</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348501823448</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348503672790-32</Id><Title>right on CUE the PUMP by maheny as they all now start dumping</Title><Msg>at the highs</Msg><Username>cwtripps</Username><Timestamp>1348503672790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:21:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348504340506-33</Id><Title>Google breaks all time high today!</Title><Msg>Google broke its all time high of $747.24 set back on November 7 2007.That was back before Obama. Cuffs</Msg><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1348504340506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348504929223-34</Id><Title>Selling Puts</Title><Msg>I am selling puts, will close over 750 on Friday. Have been selling puts since 640.</Msg><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348504929223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505275371-35</Id><Topic><Title>From Shams, who transformed Rumi from a learned religious teacher into the world’s greatest poet of mystical love</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348146529548</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When someone is full, hundred thousand prophets can't empty him." From Shams, who transformed Rumi from a learned religious teacher into the world’s greatest poet of mystical love. Some believe that Shams was killed by the angry Rumi's disciples.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348505275371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505316098-36</Id><Topic><Title>Google breaks all time high today!</Title><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1348504340506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:32:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG AT ALL ATME HIGHS!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>mattbarnes747</Username><Timestamp>1348505316098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505330278-37</Id><Topic><Title>American idioms: give voice to (something)</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1340848217583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-27 21:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When someone is full, hundred thousand prophets can't empty him." From Shams, who transformed Rumi from a learned religious teacher into the world’s greatest poet of mystical love. Some believe that Shams was killed by the angry Rumi's disciples.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348505330278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:48:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505370883-38</Id><Topic><Title>American idioms: give voice to (something)</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1340848217583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-27 21:50:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jul 19, 2012 - 3:41PM PT Both Google — and CEO Page — still quiet on mobile ad specifics By Jeff John Roberts In response to a question about the state of CEO Larry Page’s health, an executive said “Larry has lost his voice and can’t do any public speaking .. but he continues to run the company.” Page has missed several Google events in recent weeks, after the company disclosed that he has been unable to speak.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348505370883</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348505472657-39</Id><Title>GOOG TRADES AT ALL TIME HIGH!!!</Title><Msg>NOT SELLING ANY OF MY SHARES.</Msg><Username>mattbarnes747</Username><Timestamp>1348505472657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505560902-40</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!! By casp321.5 hours ago.Permalink . 06/19/12 Google exec: technology wave leaving many behind Google executive warns that technology revolution is leaving many behind Schmidt was in [sIrael] to attend an annual conference sponsored by President Shimon Peres. Despite his concerns, Schmidt delivered an optimistic message, saying that the tremendous growth of smartphones can quickly reduce the gaps between haves and have-nots. Netanyahu's office said the two men [Eric Schmidt ...]also discussed cooperation in medicine, science and defense against cyber-attacks. ???????????????? Re: ONT: Did Judge Gray Ever Comment On The Heist? By casp321.1 year 11 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Google is Flying a Quadcopter Surveillance Robot, Says Drone Maker By Clay Dillow Posted 08.09.2010 A German drone maker claims Google is trialing one of its drones, a battery-powered surveillance quadcopter previously used by UK police and special forces. What the search giant and alleged Wi-Fi data collector plans to do with the drone is unclear, but it seems likely that this isn't going to sit well with privacy advocates.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348505560902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348505939877-41</Id><Title>Should close up 20+ today</Title><Msg>$850 is what analysts are looking at.</Msg><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348505939877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506161338-42</Id><Topic><Title>Selling Puts</Title><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348504929223</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:42:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may close under 720 by Friday - you have no idea!!!</Msg><Username>eichenwaldamy</Username><Timestamp>1348506161338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506190538-43</Id><Topic><Title>Should close up 20+ today</Title><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348505939877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:58:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>protip: analysts always pick some arbitrary number higher than the stock's current price.</Msg><Username>exqotile</Username><Timestamp>1348506190538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506356974-44</Id><Topic><Title>Get better for GOOG lively authority. Discover in under wraps the Google Inc.</Title><Username>w_maynard</Username><Timestamp>1334750612000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-04-18 08:03:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds interesting. Let me try this.</Msg><Username>farrell.carmen97</Username><Timestamp>1348506356974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348506438736-45</Id><Title>only a matter of when they slam this down like apple</Title><Msg>keep thinking you are safe. apple is infinitley better company too</Msg><Username>notoriousbono</Username><Timestamp>1348506438736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506731366-46</Id><Topic><Title>Should close up 20+ today</Title><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348505939877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:58:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am long GOOG but that is a 12 month target not a one day. GO GOOG!</Msg><Username>workoutbuddy11</Username><Timestamp>1348506731366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506731510-47</Id><Topic><Title>only a matter of when they slam this down like apple</Title><Username>notoriousbono</Username><Timestamp>1348506438736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:07:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would this deserve to be slammed down?</Msg><Username>kupi23</Username><Timestamp>1348506731510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506826624-48</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will take a partial position of puts at an even round number of $750</Msg><Username>hugsforfree00</Username><Timestamp>1348506826624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348507844572-49</Id><Title>TiVo settles lawsuit against Verizon for $250.4M</Title><Msg>TiVo settles lawsuit against Verizon for $250.4M TiVo settles patent lawsuit vs Verizon for $250.4M; Verizon will license TiVo DVR technology By The Associated Press | Associated Press – 16 minutes ago Verizon will pay Tivo Inc. at least $250.4 million to license its digital video recording technology and settle a patent lawsuit.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348507844572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508055000-50</Id><Topic><Title>TiVo settles lawsuit against Verizon for $250.4M</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348507844572</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same month ON2 "merger" scam started: Aug 26, 2009 - 3:49PM PT TiVo Sues AT&amp;T and Verizon for DVR Patent Infringement By Chris Albrecht TiVo has filed lawsuits against AT&amp;T and Verizon over DVR patent infringements. From TiVo’s earnings press release: Additionally, today we filed complaints in the United States District Court, Eastern District of Texas against AT&amp;T Inc. and Verizon Communications Inc. for infringement of three TiVo patents, including the Time Warp patent. The complaints seek damages for past infringement and a permanent injunction, similar to the one issued by the United States District Court, Eastern District of Texas against DISH/EchoStar. “We will continue to pursue enforcement where necessary to stop infringement of our intellectual property,” [TiVo CEO Tom] Rogers stated.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348508055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508120537-51</Id><Topic><Title>ON2's IPs, Customers, and Targetted Markets</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1260980385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2009-12-16 11:19:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tivo IP dispute about $400 mil &amp; ON2's IPs for about $27 mil??? LOL!!!! They sold ON2 for just $1.8 for one position and another three "high" ranking ON2 Tech getting position "secured" with Google for a few mil!!! TiVo won its trial in 2006 that claimed Dish infringed its patent for so-called “time warp” technology that lets users record a TV program and play it back at the same time.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348508120537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508171635-52</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: What If ...?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1311508382000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-07-24 07:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: ON2: What If ...? By casp321.1 year 1 month ago.PermalinkGo to topic . ---- April 15th, 2008 ----- MONSOON licensed Hantro™ 4100 and 2600 for HAVA live TV/DVD/TiVo ----Monsoon Licenses [Hantro/]On2’s Mobile Decoders Monsoon Volcano Combines TiVo, Slingbox, Roku, Remote DVR and Smartphone Streaming An all-in-one convergence device that makes everything less expensive</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348508171635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508262596-53</Id><Topic><Title>Hantro+VPx or VP6/7/8??????</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1268182202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-03-09 19:50:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Hantro+VPx or VP6/7/8?????? By casp321.1 year 11 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Why would they want to HIDE this post with one-star?? TiVo and Google partner to measure Google TV Ads Dianna Dilworth November 24, 2009 TiVo has teamed up with Google to measure the audience reach of Google TV Ads. Terms of the deal, announced November 24, were not disclosed</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348508262596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348508445620-54</Id><Title>folks - a stock that takes 5 years of consolidation to hit new highs is super bullish</Title><Msg>i see this doubling within 12 months. this is a real company, unlike that PIG apple which exploits children.</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1348508445620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:40:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508672105-55</Id><Topic><Title>folks - a stock that takes 5 years of consolidation to hit new highs is super bullish</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1348508445620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple isn't a real company?</Msg><Username>xxyb737</Username><Timestamp>1348508672105</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348509462225-56</Id><Title>$850 before earnings</Title><Msg>is possible and then, with blowout earning, it will trade flat because it was priced in.</Msg><Username>high_tech_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348509462225</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509583114-57</Id><Topic><Title>folks - a stock that takes 5 years of consolidation to hit new highs is super bullish</Title><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1348508445620</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:40:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apple is all hype. 1 trick pony that is on its last legs.</Msg><Username>keepshorting</Username><Timestamp>1348509583114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348509607008-58</Id><Topic><Title>Finally, GOOG is moving</Title><Username>i_am_mothra_stewart</Username><Timestamp>1344969901088</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aaaand... I win again. GOOG at new all time highs. mothra</Msg><Username>i_am_mothra_stewart</Username><Timestamp>1348509607008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348509611203-59</Id><Title>Cheapest oil stock on NYSE, TXS is ....</Title><Msg>CHEAPEST OIL STOCK, highest risk reward is LPR..... currently 1.63, NAV of more then $9 risk reward of 500% Evi Resource Opportunity Overlooked: We feel the focus on Q1 operational issues and near term guidance changes has masked progress on drilling density at Evi. Operated activity was focused on the northern block of Evi during Q1, where LPR drilled eight wells in a single section. All eight wells are now on stream and initial rates indicate no signs of interference between wells. LPR has regulatory approval for up to 16 wells per section in certain sections at Evi and has plans to initiate a pilot of up to 12 wells per section in H2. Notwithstanding certain step-out wells that did not perform as expected, we believe LPR ultimately has the opportunity to double its current 500 well location inventory and surface up to ~$9/share. As well managements guidance For second half of 2012 was for 90$ wit with a differential of 12 meaning they only expected to receive 78$ a barrel for oil vs. The 100$ we are getting today. Wti at 92 Edmonton par wit premium of 7.50$ That is a big deal especially when oil accounts for 70% of rev. At current cap ex and prices we will be fc positive in q3 with 1 rig in evi, I suspect we will add back the second one and ramp up into 2013.....and if we sell off some ng acreage, then add more evi......look out ....this stock came public at the wrong time and forest shouldn't have dividended out the ownership....there is no short interest, no interest, completely unknown which is great for us in at these vast discounts. Time will reprice. The oil is flowing. Liquidity secure with over a 100 million available and that to will expand as banks use higher price decks. No worries on a possible winfall tax from US govt should and when oils spikes. Land in NWT more productive then Barnett Shale, once Ng recoveries LPR is a ATM, spitting out cash. See my research on board. :o)</Msg><Username>jimjones62</Username><Timestamp>1348509611203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:00:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510295626-60</Id><Title>conx, cheapist at health care.</Title><Msg>FDA approved........</Msg><Username>charlesinter</Username><Timestamp>1348510295626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510333750-61</Id><Title>Now is the GOOG pump</Title><Msg>AAPL no more the favorite stock now is GOOG.</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1348510333750</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348510376087-62</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK? By casp321.1 year 10 months ago.Permalink . ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK?? Why Google "gave" VP8 to Ceva, which has RESEARCH center in Israel, as was posted on Google/Yahoo/Message Board, and Why ON2/MF/Google PRESENTED ON2 in Feb 2010 in Barcelona Show under a SHADOW of Israeli Companies??? This is NOT about ON2's Chinese, Asian, European, or ON2's SHAREHOLDERs with DIFFERENT religions, it is ABOUT ON2's Shareholders being ROBBED by Google under the SHADOW of Israeli companies!!! Why did MF present ON2 "G1" under SHADOW of Israeli Company in Barcelona in Feb 2010</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348510376087</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348510658298-63</Id><Title>All they did is sold AAPL and got in long GOOG</Title><Msg>keep the profits growing Moving money around</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1348510658298</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:17:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348511476883-64</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1291298875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-12-02 09:07:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK? By casp321.1 year 10 months ago.Permalink . ON2: Why ROBBING American Shareholders under SHADOW of Israeli Companies is OK?? Why Google "gave" VP8 to Ceva, which has RESEARCH center in Israel, as was posted on Google/Yahoo/Message Board, and Why ON2/MF/Google PRESENTED ON2 in Feb 2010 in Barcelona Show under a SHADOW of Israeli Companies??? This is NOT about ON2's Chinese, Asian, European, or ON2's SHAREHOLDERs with DIFFERENT religions, it is ABOUT ON2's Shareholders being ROBBED by Google under the SHADOW of Israeli companies!!! Why did MF present ON2 "G1" under SHADOW of Israeli Company in Barcelona in Feb 2010?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348511476883</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348511672998-65</Id><Title>NTWK $6.8 Up 2%.......Hottest NASDAQ stock….Price and Volume up every day......Short-term Target: $10++…...Fundamentals can support $16 per analysts with $21 max target. …..Strong 2013 guidance calls for over 30% revenue growth and $1/share net income due to strong global demand for its Legacy and Cloud software solutions…….Cloud Division is growing exponentially.....Only 6 PE and 1 times sales is 30% of sector average...... In 2010 it went from $8 to $24 in 4 weeks with 50% lower revenues</Title><Msg>Analyst Target: $16 per Upgrade………Take a look at incredible NTWK chart.....3M share float In 2010 NTWK went from $8 to $24 in a few weeks. Today NTWK is a much stronger company with far more revenue sources including new Cloud Divisions. Unlike 2010, NTWK today has the flexibility to deliver reliable software products and services not only from Pakistan but also from excellence centers located in Bangkok, Beijing, the US, and the UK. The float today is 1/10 of what it was then and 2013 revenues are expected to breakaway into the mid $40 million for the first time in company history. During 2010 (and 2007) NTWK's market cap reached over $100 million on 50% lower revenues of what is projected for 2013. During the September 4Q CC NTWK officials stated that revenues are expected to reach $100 Million in 2015 up significantly from the $38 Million reported in 2012. They also expect margins to continue to go up as the high-margin Cloud divisions keep continuing exponentially to revenues. MUST READ ……This Week’s Analysts Comments on Upgrade: We project 13% annual growth to FY14 from FY10 reflecting 80 significant NFS legacy customers in FY14, up from 52, 37, and 28 in FY12, FY11, and FY10, respectively. The new Vroozi Cloud Division contributed $1.3 million in FY12. We expect at least $4 million in FY13 and $6 million to FY14 Our price target is based on the average forward 2013 P/E multiple of 13.2X (up from 12.8X in August 2012). NTWK is trading at 6.4X our FY13 projections. We are forecasting EPS of $0.85 per share. We applied an 11X multiple to our FY13 EPS forecast. We anticipate a richer multiple as earnings momentum builds in FY13. The company guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013. NTWK is entering FY13 with a $25 million backlog and approximately $100 million in qualified leads. One quarter of the backlog is from four new NFS platform customer implementations that began in 4Q12. In August 2011, NetSol launched its Cloud Vroozi Division, an e-procurement search tool for SAP supplier relationship management (SRM) users. SAP AG is a global vendor of enterprise management systems that has the largest market share (24%) based on a worldwide Gartner survey. Vroozi should provide sales diversification and a higher margin recurring revenue stream. The Vroozi division contributed $1.3 million in FY12 sales and is expected to grow to $4 million in revenues in 2013 NTWK announced its 2nd Cloud Division last week offering an array of products and services to capture a greater % of the cloud applications in North America. The company is implementing this division using their significant software development capabilities and infrastructure. === MORE NTWWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Company projects Doubling/Tripling revenues and net income by 2015 - Significant Institutional investor ownership and growing - Insiders bought over 5% of the Outstanding shares the last 2 years and never sold a single share - Total share count is only 7.5 million shares. The float is only 3 million shares - Trading at forward PE of 5 - Strong balance sheet with $1.5/share cash - Has global agreement with Mercedes Benz - Already 7 countries with NTWK software for leasing and financing Mercedes Benz/Daimler including China, India, Japan, and others…and a few more coming in quarters/years ahead. - No.1 in China and APAC in leasing/financing software products and services. NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Volvo, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. About NTWK: NetSol Technologies, Inc. ((NASDAQ: NTWK) is a worldwide provider of global IT and enterprise application solutions that include credit and finance portfolio management systems, SAP consulting and services, custom development, systems integration, and technical services for the global Financial, Leasing, Insurance, Energy, and Technology markets. Headquartered in Calabasas, Calif., NetSol's product and services offerings have achieved ISO 9001, ISO 20000, ISO 27001, and SEI (Software Engineering Institute) CMMI (Capability Maturity Model) Maturity Level 5 assessments, a distinction shared by only 178 companies worldwide. The company's clients include Fortune 500 manufacturers, global automakers, financial institutions, utilities, technology providers, and government agencies. NetSol has delivery and support locations in San Francisco, London, Beijing, Bangkok, Lahore, Adelaide, Rio de Janeiro, and Riyadh</Msg><Username>d.malkkey</Username><Timestamp>1348511672998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348511967150-66</Id><Title>NYSE: MOH - Molina Healthcare is flying $24.87 +0.36!!!! goog aumy</Title><Msg>........</Msg><Username>wworld933</Username><Timestamp>1348511967150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348512085250-67</Id><Title>GOOG WILL SEE 755 CLOSE</Title><Msg>Buy goog,will hit 900 soon, 755 be close price,it s all right ,no big deal.</Msg><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1348512085250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348512446612-68</Id><Title>Looks to us that GOOG going another 10% higher</Title><Msg>short term They want $800+</Msg><Username>jgiled</Username><Timestamp>1348512446612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348512579576-69</Id><Topic><Title>ON2, Weiner, Universal videostreaming??</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1342873324004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 08:22:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny Yahoo admin started TIMESTAMPPING and DELAYING again. Whatch for "air &amp; water SHOW" with their friend as they call "enemy" it on GOING and that's when Yahoo DELAYS the timestampped messages to let the CRIMINAL show fool as many people as they think they can? By casp321 1 year 11 months ago 1) ON2 shareholders Sue Google in mid August 2009. 2) Google China President, Kai-Fu Lee, resigned in September 2009?? 3) Google head of global communications and public affairs at YouTube resigned in Sep 2009?? AND ON2 shareholders case is STILL on "TRACK" AND 4) Hurley Steps Down as YouTube CEO on OCTOBER 29, 2010 5) YouTube Video Dealmaker Jordan Hoffner Leaves Company reported on November 3, 2009 YouTube executive Jordan Hoffner, who helped forge deals with Time Warner Inc. and Walt Disney Co. as director of content partnerships, is leaving the company. 6) Ben Smith Google does not seen announced his departure but : employees; GOOG; Internet industry September 2003 – October 2009 (6 years 2 months) Created and developed top strategic partnerships including NBC Universal, Disney, Fox, and other major film and television studios</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348512579576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348513247488-70</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG WILL SEE 755 CLOSE</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1348512085250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 14:41:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know about today's close, but tomorrow's open will be $760. Money is being reallocated from AAPL to GOOG over the maps faisco, isn't it obvious?</Msg><Username>speakwithlove</Username><Timestamp>1348513247488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348514086963-71</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many days in a row has GOOG been up? 11, 12? and when was the last time it's been up this many days non-stop? VERY.. VERY long time ago!</Msg><Username>dberhe</Username><Timestamp>1348514086963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348514960769-72</Id><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Msg>I don't know why GOOG is so strong. I've seen no big upgrades and nothing to suggest that their earnings and the economy are growing. It must be the Bernanke effect and the Fed and banks buying the S&amp;P and Dow 30 stocks. I wish I was in deeper. (Hey! That's what my girlfriend says!)</Msg><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348515874599-73</Id><Title>Future Foolish Bagholders!</Title><Msg>Who are the fools buying Google at these absurd levels! Kiss your money goodbye! Who are you?</Msg><Username>boyt1961</Username><Timestamp>1348515874599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516115530-74</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surging volume suggests Hedge Funds buying heavy... For what reason, I haven't the slightest idea why. Still technicals suggest she might even see 760 this week if she closes above 746 today.</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1348516115530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348516482937-75</Id><Topic><Title>Future Foolish Bagholders!</Title><Username>boyt1961</Username><Timestamp>1348515874599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please let the board know who you are and the reasoning you bought Google at such a foolish price. I would like to know your reasoning for your insanity????????</Msg><Username>boyt1961</Username><Timestamp>1348516482937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348516710291-76</Id><Title>Someone call 911...Shorts getting a## r@ped again.</Title><Msg>HAHAHAHAHAHAAAAAAAAAAAAA....</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1348516710291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517021937-77</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just go back and look at chart or prices since Jul 12th....up almost 200 pts since end of June on steady incline , tracking against upper trend line. Don't want to short until the channel is broke.</Msg><Username>robynrokn</Username><Timestamp>1348517021937</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517530114-78</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She'll test the 760s easily tomorrow. As you pointed out hedge funds are chasing it... Also, stock is set to split 2-for-1 sometime later this month. I would definitely restraint from shorting or buying puts until at least that's out of the way. I think the funds want this priced somewhere around the 380 - 400 range following the split... Or in other words, 760 - 800 pre split.</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1348517530114</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348517810307-79</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>today is day 8 up. last time it made it this many up days in a row was october last year after it bottomed out. it managed 9 up days in a row.</Msg><Username>exqotile</Username><Timestamp>1348517810307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:16:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348520354837-80</Id><Title>GOOG WILL BE 755 OR 760</Title><Msg>DREAM COMES TRUE.</Msg><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1348520354837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348521056149-81</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funds simply don't know what to do with all the free Bernack Crack and are chasing only large breakout stories. It's like the 1999 echo-bubble except it's only S&amp;P500 Wall Street Darling stocks that are getting the momo love from Bernanke's latest and largest Free Money Bubble.</Msg><Username>jjjinglehimersmith</Username><Timestamp>1348521056149</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348521373207-82</Id><Title>Congratulations Google...it Only....</Title><Msg>took 5 years to make a new high....but ya did it finally.......all that Android stuff and ya finally jumped above that $747 Nov 2007 high......to me that is a lot of years of nothing....if you are investing for the long.......still Congratulations</Msg><Username>ottoman272000</Username><Timestamp>1348521373207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348521717850-83</Id><Title>$750.11 all time high reached today!</Title><Msg>$770.00 before christmas eve day as I predicted for weeks.cuffs</Msg><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1348521717850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522116757-84</Id><Topic><Title>....anybody DARE to look at buying Puts ???</Title><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348496792115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>didnt realize a split-date HOW SOON ??</Msg><Username>allisonwvl</Username><Timestamp>1348522116757</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348522239041-85</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are trading a stock and don't understand why it's up or down, you shouldn't be trading it. That is truely spinning a roulette wheel. Google android software in phones is dominating all phones other than I-phones on this plannet. You tube is making strides in monetizing that segment (making $). Their advertising on smart phones is making $ (something facebook can't figure out - that's why they will go down to $17 again). This is in addition to their bread and butter aspect of search. Add that info along with if Apple is worth $650 billion, then Google should be worth more than the $200B they were bouncing around the last couple of years. They also have $45B cash and can sock away $10-$15B each quarter. YTD Google even after this run-up is only up 16% for this year. They actually beat earnings for the last quarter reported and that is not one of their stonger quarters for reporting. Additionally mutual fund managers want to show winner stocks on their quarterly statements which ends at the end of this week. Lastly look at a five year/max year chart for Google and see the breakout. It's called a rising wedge...</Msg><Username>kupi23</Username><Timestamp>1348522239041</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525504274-86</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG will probably continue to run up heading into Q3 earnings which should be released around 10/10--so 11 trading days from today. In fact, barring any major market pull back between now and then, I wouldn't be surprised to see GOOG trading close the 780 range by then.</Msg><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348525504274</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525573326-87</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hedge fund hotel now...anyone buying up here is absolteyly NUTS. one of the most overbought stocks with NO good fundies, i have ever seen google is a hihgly cyclical business</Msg><Username>notoriousbono</Username><Timestamp>1348525573326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348525687428-88</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOGLE is a failed, OLD stodgy big cap tech. its nothing to do with their actual businesses. its desparate hedgies and fidelities of the world who have bid this up without regard for RISK for MONTHS now google is busy laying off people..they bought a joke of a company mot..and its not working out</Msg><Username>notoriousbono</Username><Timestamp>1348525687428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348526021632-89</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG WILL BE 755 OR 760</Title><Username>dkatakmo</Username><Timestamp>1348520354837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:59:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already up another $1.20 to $750.58 in after-hours trading, which leads me to suspect we'll easily see 754-755 tomorrow at the open barring any unforeseen negative market driving events later this evening or tomorrow morning. Furthermore, watch out for the mother of all short squeezes tomorrow if GOOG breaks above 760 tomorrow. If that happens it could probably gap up another 20 points within a blink of an eye.</Msg><Username>moniapp293</Username><Timestamp>1348526021632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348526156074-90</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Such an angry and clueless noob...no wonder you're getting azZr@ped piker.</Msg><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1348526156074</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:35:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348527071244-91</Id><Title>Up another $2 in after-hours trading... (+17 for the day).</Title><Msg>Which probably means she'll open around 755 tomorrow if this keeps up.</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1348527071244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348527084964-92</Id><Title>Up another $2 in after-hours trading... (+17 for the day).</Title><Msg>Which probably means she'll open around 755 tomorrow if this keeps up.</Msg><Username>margincalll</Username><Timestamp>1348527084964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348527433855-93</Id><Topic><Title>Someone call 911...Shorts getting a## r@ped again.</Title><Username>funnimone67</Username><Timestamp>1348516710291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:58:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok here we go 911</Msg><Username>jai_hakim</Username><Timestamp>1348527433855</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:57:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348527454733-94</Id><Topic><Title>ON2: What If ...?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1311508382000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2011-07-24 07:53:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who did provide these reporters with Rumor ? From what CIRCLE was it? 5) Homa Zaryouni in New York ??? FT Reporter: "An Adobe takeover of On2 has been speculation for some time, the insider said. “We do from time to time hear from third parties that a company is interested in On2,” the insider added."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348527454733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348528700903-95</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and Romney calling them "bump", "spring", and I see them as "Google Bump" and "Facebook Spring"but again the question is who is making them Kosher and Halal considering who's made Google and FB? Usually Yahoo Admin TIMESTAMPs the messages around these kind of activities or SHOW, I call, and DELAY posting them becvause of the millions of dollars they've spent on the SHOW to deceive those who can nOT see that all these are made at the "BakerHouse" by the SAME cooks/crooks.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348528700903</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348528899111-96</Id><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Msg>So now GooG is a sell, me out</Msg><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529003547-97</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good Bye Goog Investors see you when war is over.</Msg><Username>onebuckoneshare</Username><Timestamp>1348529003547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529119317-98</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google is a very strong SELL until iran and Israel are peaceful again,</Msg><Username>samtrader80</Username><Timestamp>1348529119317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529237221-99</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>me happy I took me profits of 277K today. Me no likes war at all.</Msg><Username>humptypuredumpty</Username><Timestamp>1348529237221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529354306-100</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just sold after market shares. good luck all!!!</Msg><Username>cashoutcowgirl</Username><Timestamp>1348529354306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529451427-101</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Israel vs. Iran not good for google or thee stock market, me out</Msg><Username>cashoutcowgirl</Username><Timestamp>1348529451427</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348529601233-102</Id><Title>Google a strong sell until world is safer Iran &amp; Israel War not good</Title><Msg>time to say good bye until world is safe again.</Msg><Username>cashoutcowgirl</Username><Timestamp>1348529601233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529736378-103</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am with you signing out until these are better in this crazy world.</Msg><Username>sellupdump</Username><Timestamp>1348529736378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529777996-104</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CIA using Google Youtube or small video clips and .... the judge saysd he can not order the removal of it. LOL!!! Was alreay planned that way: Google and Yahoo provided to Iranian secret agents hundreds of thousands Iranian Google and Yahoo accounts. How many of them by now are being inprisoned, totured or even being killed is beyiond imagination. That's how they make it kosher and halal at the same "Bakerhouse" and sell it to differentr audiences to deceive them: Re: ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account By casp321.3 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . The "olympic game" in Iran they are talking might be Ahmadinejhad and current Iranian Government on one side and Mosavi, Kahrobi, Kangarlu, on the other side. The first have Democrat from USA as their Coach and the laler Republica from USA their coach too Re: The Smoking Gun: Plot by Fossil Fuel Giant to Further Corrupt Aussie Media Exposed By casp321.3 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Mousavi then became Iran Prime-minister for 8 years running the Gun-barrel war with Iragq during that time: in the October Surprise deal of 1980. Ben-Menashe quoted Mousavi as saying, “we did everything you guys wanted. We got rid of the Democrats. We did everything we could, but the Americans aren’t delivering [and] they are dealing with the Iraqis.” Re: The Smoking Gun: Plot by Fossil Fuel Giant to Further Corrupt Aussie Media Exposed By casp321.6 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . in the October Surprise deal of 1980. Ben-Menashe quoted Mousavi as saying, “we did everything you guys wanted. We got rid of the Democrats. We did everything we could, but the Americans aren’t delivering [and] they are dealing with the Iraqis.” ------ October 1980: Osama’s Oldest Brother Allegedly Involved in ‘October Surprise’ Salem bin Laden, Osama’s oldest brother, described by a French secret intelligence report as one of two closest friends of Saudi Arabia’s King Fahd who often performs important missions for Saudi Arabia, is involved in secret Paris meetings between US and Iranian emissaries this month, according to a French report. Re: ON2: And COMPROMISING Iranian Yahoo &amp; Google Account By casp321.6 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . Interesting to see if those in POER-STRUGGLE, supporting Republican in the USA, will check the background of those got the 300,000+ Iranian Google accounts holders and 200,000 Yahoo accounts holders to see who in the CIA/NSA they are communicating with? Are "hackers" in Iran interested in Republican President or Democrat President Election in Nov 2012? Those in power-struggle know who is who but the one taking orders from them would depend. What will happen to Mousavi, Karrobi, Nabavi, Supporters of Republican in Iran and Ahmadinejad and others SUPPORTING Democrat and would be able to stay in Power should Obama win in Nov 2012 but might not only lose the power should Republican win 2012 Presidency but also some might loose their HEAD to silence those might EXPOSE the others connected to CIA/NSA. By casp321 3 months ago Was it a "bug" or feature? Ask silberman, secord, hakim, ghorbanifar, kangarlou, mousavi, bush, north, robert gate, poindexter, ... casey, buckley, shackley to let you know how their "creation" in beirut related to hostage-crisis in 1979-1981 and 1984-1984: Made in the SAME "BakerHouse" and distributed as Kosher and/or Halal, depending who the audience might be Re: Another October, is it "Surprise"?? By casp321.11 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . "As a former Reagan advisor, Mr Silberman took part in a meeting between top Republicans and Iranian government representatives during the 1980 election campaign, when the Carter administration was trying to negotiate the release of American hostages in Tehran. Judge Silberman and two aides who took part in the meeting later claimed they had rejected the Iranian offer of a deal and did not even remember the name of the Iranian representative. But the meeting was never reported to the state department, at a time of high tension in the US-Iranian relations."[6] According to the February 7, 2004, edition of the New York Times[7] "Judge Silberman, 68, works part-time on the United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, where he was appointed by President Ronald Reagan, and is one of three judges who sit on the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court of Review, a body that hears appeals in matters of intelligence gathering. Considered a stalwart conservative, he was senior foreign policy and intelligence advisor to the 1980 Reagan-Bush campaign, playing a role in a meeting with an Iranian emissary in an effort to have 52 American hostages released a month before the election."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348529777996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348529888442-105</Id><Topic><Title>Google a strong sell until world is safer Iran &amp; Israel War not good</Title><Username>cashoutcowgirl</Username><Timestamp>1348529601233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:33:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sergey Brin and Larry Page hold 5 billion in cash each as I write - Smart Boys, the Google Kids. War is not good for anyone.</Msg><Username>sellupdump</Username><Timestamp>1348529888442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530083100-106</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why someone from Google talk to foreign country about DEFENCE, .... Google after all is a PUBLIC company with REAL investors NOT a gevernment agent, at least on the surface of it: 06/19/12 Google exec: technology wave leaving many behind Google executive warns that technology revolution is leaving many behind JERUSALEM (AP) ' Google's executive chairman Eric Schmidt on Tuesday warned that vast numbers of the world's population are missing out on the advantages brought by the Internet. Schmidt said that about 2 billion people, less than a third of the world's population, have Internet access, and 1 billion have smartphones. "The World Wide Web has yet to live up to its name," he said. "Technology does not produce miracles, but connectivity, even in modest amounts, changes lives Schmidt served as Google's chief executive from 2001 to 2011, leading it through its initial public offering and transforming it into one of the world's largest and most influential companies. He stepped down as CEO last year and has been executive chairman since then. Google turned into a huge company "with its goal of making information accessible to the masses," he said. Schmidt was in [sIrael] to attend an annual conference sponsored by President Shimon Peres. Despite his concerns, Schmidt delivered an optimistic message, saying that the tremendous growth of smartphones can quickly reduce the gaps between haves and have-nots. Netanyahu's office said the two men [Eric Schmidt ...]also discussed cooperation in medicine, science and defense against cyber-attacks.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348530083100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530148751-107</Id><Topic><Title>ON2 Video technologies changing the way they are taking HOSTAGEs remotely!!</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1347727808586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 12:50:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Date of execution June 9, 1980 Location Evin Prison, Tehran, Iran Mode of execution shooting Charges Collaborating with the political police SAVAK About this Case The execution of Mr. Farajollah Seifi Kamangar was reported in the Jomhuri Eslami daily (June 10, 1980). Arrest and detention Based on the report, Mr. Kamangar was arrested by Revolutionary Guards towards the end of the year 1979 in Evin Prison, where he allegedly had gone to receive his salary.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348530148751</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348530261160-108</Id><Title>Up $200 in 3 months. Lol</Title><Msg>Yeah completely normal action. No bubble there. Nope none at all.</Msg><Username>charts_say_sell_u_dumb_azz</Username><Timestamp>1348530261160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530315970-109</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google no 850 dollars anytime soon - A STRONG SELL UNTIL IRAN IS NO NUCLEAR Fair market now? down she goes Tuesday.</Msg><Username>fairmarketmaker</Username><Timestamp>1348530315970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348530415956-110</Id><Title>Israel &amp; Iran Do They Know War is Hell, Nukes are Risky Business.</Title><Msg>Nukes are risky biz in this troubled world.</Msg><Username>fairmarketmaker</Username><Timestamp>1348530415956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530541326-111</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"When someone is full, hundred thousand prophets can't empty him." From Shams, who transformed Rumi from a learned religious teacher into the world’s greatest poet of mystical love. Some believe that Shams was killed by the angry Rumi's disciples.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348530541326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530589513-112</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A strong stock market sell all in order Tuesday.</Msg><Username>purepimpdaddy2</Username><Timestamp>1348530589513</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348530724031-113</Id><Title>My World Ho's Time To Jump Ship Sell It all - Dow Fall</Title><Msg>my bro and sisters not a good buy in stock in these harder and dangerous time - Obama Sucks!!!</Msg><Username>purepimpdaddy2</Username><Timestamp>1348530724031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:52:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530850148-114</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems Google trumping Republican Plan to help Obama to be re-elected as USA president in 2012. This is for Republic supprt and might be anothe "october-surprise" for you: Sep 16, 2012 Iran on brink of nuclear bomb in six-seven months: Netan... By Matt Spetalnick and Dan Williams The unusually public dispute between close allies - coupled with Obama's decision not to meet with [Netan] later this month - has exposed a gaping U.S.-[sIrae] divide and stepped up pressure on the U.S. leader in the final stretch of a tight presidential election campaign. ------------- Re: When will be Google turn? By casp321.6 months ago.PermalinkGo to topic . You need just to DECODE what they mean. Was/is it NOT? This is HOW they make it kosher and halal at the SAME "BakerHouse" and "sell" it as kosher OR halal, depending who their AUDIENCE might be!!!!! ----- "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. ----- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday. ----- Sen. Jim Demint offers blunt words on Iran Thursday, 16 July 2009 11:37 Rabbi Hillel Goldberg I lead into the American side of the equation with this question: What does Iran think when it hears, “We will not take the military option off the table”? ----- US Sens question Halliburton Selling Nuclear Technology to Iran neverknwo / LiveLeak | May 26, 2007 Halliburton VP, Sherry Williams testifies at a Senate hearing about the company's dealings with Iran-- Halliburton is charged with selling nuclear technology to Iran. Halliburton, the notorious U.S. energy company, sold key nuclear-reactor components to a private Iranian oil company called Oriental Oil Kish as recently as 2005, using offshore subsidiaries to circumvent U.S. sanctions. The story is particularly juicy because [VP Chen?y], who now claims to want to stop Iran from getting nukes, was president of Halliburton in the mid-1990s, at which time he may have advocated business dealings with Iran, in violation of U.S. law. Source: "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. -------------- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday. -------------- Sen. Jim Demint offers blunt words on Iran Thursday, 16 July 2009 11:37 Rabbi Hillel Goldberg He’s clear on what the US must do to counter Iran’s pursuit of a nuclear weapon, and on what [sIrael] will do. He’s very blunt about both. I lead into the American side of the equation with this question: What does Iran think when it hears, “We will not take the military option off the table”?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348530850148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530874993-115</Id><Topic><Title>Israel &amp; Iran Do They Know War is Hell, Nukes are Risky Business.</Title><Username>fairmarketmaker</Username><Timestamp>1348530415956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nukes indeed are very risky biz. Me a Sell Out Tuesday.</Msg><Username>shingles101educator</Username><Timestamp>1348530874993</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348530937284-116</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Message Board - Imminent Israel vs. Iran War a Stock Market Game Changer?</Title><Username>traderjoecash</Username><Timestamp>1348528899111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:21:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need just to DECODE what they mean. Was/is it NOT? This is HOW they make it kosher and halal at the SAME "BakerHouse" and "sell" it as kosher OR halal, depending who their AUDIENCE might be!!!!! ----- "Halliburton Secretly Doing Business with Key Member of Iran's Nuclear Team," Jason Leopold, GlobalResearch.ca, Aug. 5, 2005. ----- May 1, 2007 Halliburton defends its dealings with Iran No Republican subcommittee members showed up for Monday's session, unusual for a congressional hearing. A spokesman for the ranking Republican on the subcommittee, Sen. Jim DeMint of South Carolina, did not return calls Monday.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348530937284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348531003033-117</Id><Topic><Title>Israel &amp; Iran Do They Know War is Hell, Nukes are Risky Business.</Title><Username>fairmarketmaker</Username><Timestamp>1348530415956</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:46:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you enlist rather than sitting there blogging like a little coward.</Msg><Username>solomangrundie</Username><Timestamp>1348531003033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348531030897-118</Id><Title>Shingles and Wars are PainFul</Title><Msg>can we all just get along? Fot this reason the whole market is a huge sell Tuesday.</Msg><Username>shingles101educator</Username><Timestamp>1348531030897</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 19:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348535843932-119</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally.... someone who thinks like me... For everyone here asking why Google is going up on no new news... why don't you instead 1. Read up in Google yourself and realize what a FANTASTIC stock it is to own or 2. read the shortened version that kupi23 offered you. I know most of you will read the shortned version as you have no intention on taking anytime to really learn about what stocks to buy and instead asking random people on the message boards. If you did your homework a few months ago.. you would have realized how undervauled Google was then.. and still is now. Its a money making machine even without any "new news"! If you want to trade a stock on NEWS... then you are not investing wisely. For those of you who do not want to do your homework and just go by what people write on the boards... i will say it one more time... BUY GOOGLE NOW and when its trading over 1,000 you can come back and thnak me then.... feel free to go back and read my previous posts over the last 4 months... how i was saying to buy it at 600.. 620..650... 680.. 700.... and i am still saying to buy it now....</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1348535843932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:17:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348535857444-120</Id><Title>ON2 Lawsuits in August 2009 and Google/Youtube EXECs departures from August to Dec 2009</Title><Msg>By casp321 1) ON2 shareholders Sue Google in mid August 2009. On or about August 10, 2009, On2 Technologies, Inc. (the "Company") was served with two purported class action complaints, one filed in the Court of Chancery of the State of Delaware and another filed in the Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of Queens. Both complaints generally allege, among other things, that the members of the Company's board of directors breached their fiduciary duties to the stockholders of the Company in connection with negotiating and entering into the previously disclosed merger agreement with Google Inc. ("Google"), and that Google and the Company aided and abetted in such alleged breaches of the directors' duties. 2) Google China President, Kai-Fu Lee, resigned in September 2009?? President of Google China to Resign. September 4, 2009 President of Google China, Kai-Fu Lee is resigning. 3) Google head of global communications and public affairs at YouTube resigned in Sep 2009?? Tuesday, September 1, 2009 Google executive Ricardo Reyes will join Tesla Motors as vice president for communications, starting in mid-September. Reyes, 35, is head of global communications and public affairs at YouTube, one of the premier destinations online and a subsidiary of Google. He previously handled litigation, competition and policy communications for the online search, services and products company. 5) YouTube Video Dealmaker Jordan Hoffner Leaves Company reported on November 3, 2009 YouTube executive Jordan Hoffner, who helped forge deals with Time Warner Inc. and Walt Disney Co. as director of content partnerships, is leaving the company. 6) Ben Smith. October 2009 Google does not seen announced his departure but : employees; GOOG; Internet industry September 2003 – October 2009 (6 years 2 months) Created and developed top strategic partnerships including NBC Universal, Disney, Fox, and other major film and television studios 4) Hurley Steps Down as YouTube CEO on OCTOBER 29, 2010</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1348535857444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348536092964-121</Id><Title>780 calls tomorrow</Title><Msg>this has a nice 10-20 point move a day to 800.</Msg><Username>lincolnsummers123</Username><Timestamp>1348536092964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348536281963-122</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen Mr. Chillen2307...</Msg><Username>kupi23</Username><Timestamp>1348536281963</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348537131370-123</Id><Topic><Title>Why is GOOG so strong?</Title><Username>no_pricetag_on_fun</Username><Timestamp>1348514960769</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hallelujah!</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1348537131370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348537327148-124</Id><Title>GOOG Stock, this is interesting about it's big moves your thoughts</Title><Msg>The team at VIP has performed some wonderful analysis and through this they have provided some compelling insight, which has assisted me in the decision making process and now I have a better understanding of GOOG, check it out at, vippennystocksite dotcom</Msg><Username>levy1847</Username><Timestamp>1348537327148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:42:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348537723392-125</Id><Title>I'm slowly starting to unload</Title><Msg>Profit taking is always beneficial. I'll be back next month once market corrected.</Msg><Username>eloysalcedo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348537723392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348537893595-126</Id><Title>It scares me when analysts start recommending a strong buy after a bull run!</Title><Msg>To me it means they are unloading positions.</Msg><Username>eloysalcedo2003</Username><Timestamp>1348537893595</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348537916730-127</Id><Title>SHORT GOOG ..HERE IS WHY..</Title><Msg>Soon the angry muslim countries and its people all over the world will cut all advertising with google over the prophet mohammed film shown on youtube, specially if you look to countries like saudi a arabia , dubai a.r.e and asia ,i heard that all the arab business men in the u.s.a. Will cut all ads with google . Give it a time .. Remember you hear it here first.. I don't have any position in the stock.. Just a thought..</Msg><Username>oshtomoom</Username><Timestamp>1348537916730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539118345-128</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG Stock, this is interesting about it's big moves your thoughts</Title><Username>levy1847</Username><Timestamp>1348537327148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:42:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM!!! Thee is a Trojan virus on this jerks web sight!</Msg><Username>obamasuxcockwithnegrolips</Username><Timestamp>1348539118345</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348539763113-129</Id><Title>Biggest manipulation by machines ever, why 750 sharp?</Title><Msg>#$%$!!!</Msg><Username>wallstreetskimmer</Username><Timestamp>1348539763113</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348541101929-130</Id><Topic><Title>Future Foolish Bagholders!</Title><Username>boyt1961</Username><Timestamp>1348515874599</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>inertia . It's physics. Once it got going there was no stopping it. Should hit 1000 my March 2013</Msg><Username>jkrull43</Username><Timestamp>1348541101929</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>