<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348978462692-1</Id><Title>Split?</Title><Msg>Split is supposed to occur after earnings in October, correct?</Msg><Username>rmkm2204</Username><Timestamp>1348978462692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:14:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348985675148-2</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the current valuations, Google is expensive as compared to its competitors, but it is trading below its industry P/E average. I buy the stock, because Google is correctly priced at present. Upcoming events, which could affect the stock price, include next month's earning release, and the launch of Microsoft 's Surface tablet.</Msg><Username>tomson.antony</Username><Timestamp>1348985675148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 02:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349009940050-3</Id><Title>Dems setting up debates</Title><Msg>Democrats are out in force on Lame Stream MSM co-arm of dem party attempting to set the tone for Wednesday’s debate. Candy Crowley just acclaimed on CNN that Romney has the most to lose since he is behind in the polls. HA! One could only imagine the USA becoming so dumb as to allow for such nonsensical point of view with the economy ready to absolutely FALL, 23% unemployment and the Mid East worst than it’s ever been with Obama removing the two dictators most capable of the hard handed rule to keep the populace in check and replacing them with Obama’s Muslim brothers the ‘Brotherhood.’ And what does the Lame Stream MSM co-arm of the dem party tell us ‘IMAGE ONLY MUST AGAIN RULE.’ Open your eyes folks and know it’s IMAGE ONLY that landed us here with this most failed Obama regime of all time. Now takes the prize from Carter as worst ever. Romney should win hands down regardless of the gaffs the corrupt MSM will find (i.e. Palin did not know Paul Revere ripped a F__A___R____T on the way to town. In reality however Palin was corrupt in her assertions about Paul Revere and Chris Matthews and Lame Stream wrong. Of course they never pointed that out once the damage was done.</Msg><Username>foretherun</Username><Timestamp>1349009940050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349011678252-4</Id><Title>Return to 690</Title><Msg>this week prior to earnings, so when earnings come out, it will pop back to 750 or above.</Msg><Username>missmarket30</Username><Timestamp>1349011678252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349019567100-5</Id><Topic><Title>Billionaires Love these 5 stocks</Title><Username>rightdon53</Username><Timestamp>1348905484509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now it is a good time to BUY GOOG on dips, GOOG bandwagon is inevitably destined for a trip up.</Msg><Username>lindontomson</Username><Timestamp>1349019567100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349040252099-6</Id><Title>S3 is killing the iphone..</Title><Msg>android market is insane...iphone should have flooded the market with phones, since there are none out, it makes it easier to switch. The iphone is the same phone as the 4s essentially. I suspect aapl will miss huge on next earnings. this will be 800 before aapl.</Msg><Username>alsteele_88</Username><Timestamp>1349040252099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349043103332-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why Goog stock will see 600 in October'2012</Title><Username>election00</Username><Timestamp>1348973059128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you right... except you forget to mention.... that it will be after the stock split that google will see 600 again..... i assume thats what you meant.... because for google to see 600 again any other way is rediculous!</Msg><Username>chillen2307</Username><Timestamp>1349043103332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349046493087-8</Id><Title>Obama King of debt and King of Executive Orders</Title><Msg>EXECUTIVE ORDERS ISSUED… Teddy Roosevelt 3 Between Teddy to FDR NONE FDR 11 in 16 years Truman 5 in 7 years Ike 2 in 8 years Kennedy 4 in 3 years LBJ 4 in 5 years Nixon 1 in 6 years Ford 3 in 2 years Carter 3 in 4 years Reagan 5 in 8 years Bush 3 in 4 years Clinton 15 in 8 years George W. Bush 62 in 8 years Obama 923 in 3 1/2 years!</Msg><Username>omni1tsd</Username><Timestamp>1349046493087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349049892129-9</Id><Topic><Title>FB Facebook OVERSOLD and UNDERVALUED Techincal BOUNCE coming!!! Watch ZNGA PCFG too</Title><Username>wworld933</Username><Timestamp>1347973089748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 08:58:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Thursday, the social-media giant launched a new service called Gifts. As the name suggests, it enables users to buy, give and ship real gifts to friends directly through Facebook. Gifts can be given from the birthday reminders news feed, or from a person’s timeline. The gift giving process can be completed on Facebook’s website or on Android (NASDAQ:GOOG) mobile phones, with Apple (NASDAQ:AAPL) iPhone and iPad versions rolling out soon. The service is currently offered to only a small amount of users, but will expand in the United States over the coming months.</Msg><Username>limitedspacecadet</Username><Timestamp>1349049892129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:04:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349054983167-10</Id><Title>Barrons says Google has more upside in this weekend's edition</Title><Msg>Barrons says Google has more upside in this weekend's edition</Msg><Username>jeffreysauctions</Username><Timestamp>1349054983167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 21:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349063860666-11</Id><Title>Quite a Rally in the Face of Stage One of AAPL's Thermonuclear War.</Title><Msg>First GOOG gets cut out of the AAPL ecosystem. And, anyone with a brain knows that it is only a matter of time before AAPL overtakes Andriod's market share in smartphones. AAPL is expected to sell 250 million iphone 5's. The future of search is mobile and GOOG has #$%$ of the 800 pound gorilla in smart phones. Stage two of thermonuclear war will be really cool. AAPL will build a relational data base as good if not better than GOOG's. As a matter of fact they have probably been working on it since before Jobs died. They will control all those precious little eye balls. GOOG will be screwed. I hope #$%$ in AAPL's sandbox with Andriod was worth it. Now AAPL will take a big lumpy dump in GOOG's sandbox! I hope all that imaginary money that GOOG is making on Andriod was worth the massive damage is will cause to the future of GOOG.</Msg><Username>alphashort</Username><Timestamp>1349063860666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>