<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358332014444-1</Id><Title>Google has 172,771,973 Monthly Unique Visitors against the 22,738,205 Unique Visitors of Local Corp - that is the 7.6-fold of Local Corp, but Google has the 4,861-fold market-cap of Local Corp with 238,210 million against the idiotic low 49 million of Local Corp</Title><Msg>That is a divergence of the factor 640, if you divide 4,861 through 7.6 - the biggest divergence on Nasdaq I ever had seen. Source: Siteanallytics</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1358332014444</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 05:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358336933657-2</Id><Title>Website on the move</Title><Msg>freestockwizard</Msg><Username>stocks2cheap</Username><Timestamp>1358336933657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 06:48:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358339982620-3</Id><Title>GOOG to make offer for DELL !</Title><Msg>It seems an unnamed informed source close to the negotiations is reporting Google is considering throwing their hat into the ring and bid for DELL. That would be interesting.</Msg><Username>marketsagame</Username><Timestamp>1358339982620</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 07:39:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358342149675-4</Id><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Msg>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358342395486-5</Id><Topic><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“He was killed by the government, and MIT betrayed all of its basic principles,” he [his father Robert Swartz] said.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342395486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:19:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358343093876-6</Id><Title>Hacker Marius Milner secretly intercepted WiFi data as the firm’s Street View</Title><Msg>Hacker Marius Milner identified as Google’s personal data cropping engineer May 1, 2012 Google Street View is a service highlighted in Google Maps and Google Earth that offers panoramic views of streets. It launched in 2007 in the United States and has expanded to many cities and rural areas worldwide. The project ambitiously maps the world’s streets with photographs while accumulating data about local wireless networks to bulk location-based searches.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358343093876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:31:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358343183537-7</Id><Topic><Title>Hacker Marius Milner secretly intercepted WiFi data as the firm’s Street View</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358343093876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold casp321 by casp321 . Jun 13, 2012 Denials Over Google Street View By EDWARD WYATT | New York Times – Google has long prided itself on not being a conventional company. But there is one characteristic it apparently shares with the most sclerotic bureaucracy: the willingness of its employees to say, “Not my job.” The company on Tuesday released a trove of documents related to a federal investigation of its Street View mapping project. Although the project was intended to photograph the world’s streets, from 2007 to 2010 Google gathered unencrypted Internet data from wireless networks, including the content of private communications, as its specially equipped cars passed through neighborhoods. Among the documents released Tuesday are sworn declarations by nine people — their names and titles redacted but most of whom appear to be Google engineers — who said they were not aware of the data collection either because it was not part of their job or they did not review the project documentation, even when it was provided to them.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358343183537</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:33:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358343293861-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hacker Marius Milner secretly intercepted WiFi data as the firm’s Street View</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358343093876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:31:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Google, Street View, Marius, and MORE! casp321 by casp321 . Jan 13, 2013 8:51 AM . Permalink Re: As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold casp321 by casp32... Re: As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold casp321 by casp321 . May 6, 2012 10:32 AM Wayne Slavin July 19, 2004 What is NetStumbler? [Wayne Slavin] NetStumbler is a wireless tool that allows you to detect wireless networks. It was written by my friend Marius Milner. Wayne Slavin July 19, 2004 [Q] Your site describes NetStumbler as "beggarware." What does that mean? [A by Wayne Slavin] It means you don't have to pay for a license to use it. The program contains information about the (software) drivers for many wireless cards. That information was obtained under nondisclosure agreements with the manufacturers. As part of those agreements, NetStumbler cannot be resold. Sun 1 Feb 2004 Source Code Posted in FAQ by mariusm # Q: Can I see the NetStumbler source code? Is it open source? A: NetStumbler is not open source. Indeed it contains a lot of code that was developed under Non-Disclosure Agreements, and the source cannot be released to the general public - if I do so then several teams of lawyers will show up on my doorstep.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358343293861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:34:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358344137074-9</Id><Topic><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Congressional Backlash Over Aaron Swartz's Suicide Has Begun Adam Clark Estes 586 ViewsJan 15, 2013 As lawmakers decry the Justice Department's treatment of Aaron Swartz, House Oversight Committee Chairman Darrell Issa says he's launching an investigation into the matter. Swartz, a 26-year-old computer savant who killed himself last Friday in the face of hacking charges, would've been a hero if he'd had a different profession, said the congressman. "I'm not condoning his hacking, but he’s certainly someone who worked very hard," Issa told The Huffington Post on Monday night. "Had he been a journalist and taken that same material that he gained from MIT, he would have been praised for it. It would have been like the Pentagon Papers." Instead, Swartz was looking at 35 years in jail and $1 million in fines. "It does seem like it was an awful lot," said Issa. "But again, we're in the business of finding for sure." -------------- Re: Re: Rumi: If you are irritated by every rub, how will you be polished? casp321 by casp321 . Dec 29, 2012 12:45 PM LOL: Marius described himself as a “hacker”... [while] Milner is listed as an inventor on a Google patent filed in 2007 for technology to protect against “hackers" 5/01/2012 @ 11:20AM |4,558 views Wi-Spy Google Engineer Outed As 'Hacker' 'God' Marius Milner</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358344137074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:48:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358345205762-10</Id><Topic><Title>What kind of CLEARANCE Google Street View handlers had while driving around USA Lawmakers' Home</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1278723207000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2010-07-09 20:53:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What kind of CLEARANCE GoogleStreet View handlers had while driving around USA Lawmakers' Home</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358345205762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:06:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358345304928-11</Id><Topic><Title>As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1336052694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-03 09:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This fellow is being called “Engineer Doe” by the FCC but has been discovered this week as being a software engineer by the name of Marius Milner by the New York Times.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358345304928</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:08:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358345332705-12</Id><Topic><Title>As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1336052694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-03 09:44:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kashmir Hill, Forbes Staff Honestly, I’m a little shocked it took this long to identify Milner. As Google well knows, information like this likes to be found.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358345332705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:08:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358345352621-13</Id><Topic><Title>Google is spying: 72 passwords &amp; 774 distinct emails....</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1336132996000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-05-04 08:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lawyers Claim Google Wi-Fi Sniffing ‘Is Not an Accident’ By David Kravets Email Author June 3, 2010</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358345352621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:09:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358346086602-14</Id><Topic><Title>Google gets sued again .. now by Spain</Title><Username>chkprof</Username><Timestamp>1282104664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2010-08-18 00:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what, google would say: 1) What did those AGs do with their "investigation" in 2010? 07/21/10 Google Faces 38 States in Expanding Privacy Investigation 2) What the AGs really mean this time? February 22, 2012 In a letter sent earlier today, 37 state attorneys generals (or their equivalents) wrote to Larry Page, Google's CEO, "to express our strong concerns with the new privacy policy that Google announced it will be adopting for all of its consumer products." --AGs cite potential increase in identity theft risk</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358346086602</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 09:21:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358350510587-15</Id><Title>Goog's falling cost per click and Galaxy S3's Sudden Death Syndrome</Title><Msg>Goog's cost per click has fallen 4 straight quarters in a row, and the current quarter will be no different because the world is transitioning away from goog's cash cow sponsored ads on traditional desktop pc's to the mobile Internet, where Goog makes far less money even with Android's 72% market share on generally large-screen Android devices. Ironically, goog makes 4 times more on iOS devices than on Android, because Android users (who still mostly use 3 year old Android 2.3 Gingerbread, whose phones still today outsell Android Jellybean phones 2-to-1) simply are too poor and not interested in clicking on goog's mobile ads and buying anything online. Goog's cost per click will continue to dive the more popular Android gets and the more traditional PC sales fall year over year as is happening now. Goog gets 96% of its revenues from the traditional desktop and its mobile revenues are 4-to-1 tied to iOS than Android. Meanwhile, Samsung STILL hasn't fixed the sudden death syndrome problem that's causing Samsung Galaxy S3's worldwide to fail after only 6-8 months of ownership. Samsung's customer service is typically #$%$, they're only interested in getting you to buy the entirely new phones like the galaxy s4 since the previous S3 is apparently just designed to fail on you anyway. The "Ultimate GS3 Sudden Death Thread" is almost 400 pages long now at the XDA developers site, the main Android developers site in the world.</Msg><Username>adonis9000</Username><Timestamp>1358350510587</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 10:35:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358353860732-16</Id><Title>Kapersky Lab: 99% of new mobile malware targets Android</Title><Msg>Android is full of vulnerabilities because it's based on Java, and if you havent't heard Java should be turned off immediately on any computer because you're just making yourself a target for malware attacks. Kapersky Labs just reported the other day they're finding 6,300 different malware EVERY MONTH now targeting Android devices (including on the Google Play store), and these Android phones were already buggy, laggy, and eventually need to be re-booted or have their batteries taken out every day just to remain barely functional or experience Sudden Death Syndrome outright.</Msg><Username>adonis9000</Username><Timestamp>1358353860732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:31:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358353939659-17</Id><Title>Easy money! GOOG can trip to 630</Title><Msg>inflection with high 'slop' is approaching</Msg><Username>dad_bargarow</Username><Timestamp>1358353939659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:32:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358354051973-18</Id><Title>GREEEDINESSS MADE ME LOOOK STUPPIDD!</Title><Msg>AND YOU???</Msg><Username>rddr2022</Username><Timestamp>1358354051973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:34:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358354861241-19</Id><Topic><Title>8000% on KROGER and (ATTD) deal, Phase III Recover drink ATTD's product will now be sold in KROGER</Title><Username>greatpennies</Username><Timestamp>1354049588326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow ATTD just inked massive sales agreement with a 33 billion dollar company, which is one of the nations largest sales distributor</Msg><Username>hugedoubler</Username><Timestamp>1358354861241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 11:47:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358356708463-20</Id><Title>Every search made on FACEBOOK will be one less made on GOOGLE...</Title><Msg>this is bad news anyway you slice it. Wouldn't be surprised to see a major flash crash type sell off in google.</Msg><Username>jzandmebuddies</Username><Timestamp>1358356708463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 12:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358359429206-21</Id><Title>people selling GOOG and buying RIMM &amp; AAPL.</Title><Msg>glad i'm not long GOOG</Msg><Username>charts_say_sell_u_dumb_azz</Username><Timestamp>1358359429206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358360240276-22</Id><Topic><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as some can pay "blood-money" they can get away with anything but why calling one "felone" and another "hero"??? casp321 casp321 by casp321 . Dec 29, 2012 12:45 PM LOL: Marius described himself as a “hacker”... [while] Milner is listed as an inventor on a Google patent filed in 2007 for technology to protect against “hackers" 5/01/2012 @ 11:20AM |4,558 views Wi-Spy Google Engineer Outed As 'Hacker' 'God' Marius Milner -------------- Department of Justice Office of Public Affairs FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE Wednesday, August 24, 2011 Google Forfeits $500 Million Generated by Online Ads &amp; Prescription Drug Sales by Canadian Online Pharmacies Internet Search Engine Accepted Advertisements from Online Canadian Pharmacies that Targeted U.S. Consumers and Illegally Imported Controlled and Non-Controlled Prescription Drugs into the United States PROVIDENCE, R.I. – Online search engine Google Inc. has agreed to forfeit $500 million for allowing online Canadian pharmacies to place advertisements through its AdWords program targeting consumers in the United States, resulting in the unlawful importation of controlled and non-controlled prescription drugs into the United States, announced Deputy Attorney General James M. Cole; Peter F. Neronha, U.S. Attorney for the District of Rhode Island; and Kathleen Martin-Weis, Acting Director of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration’s Office of Criminal Investigations (FDA/OCI). The forfeiture, one of the largest ever in the United States, represents the gross revenue received by Google as a result of Canadian pharmacies advertising through Google’s AdWords program, plus gross revenue made by Canadian pharmacies from their sales to U.S. consumers. -------------- Re: Re: Hacker Marius Milner secretly intercepted WiFi data as the firm’s Street View casp321 by casp321 . Jan 16, 2013 8:34 AM Re: As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold casp321 by casp321 . May 6, 2012 10:32 AM Wayne Slavin July 19, 2004 What is NetStumbler? [Wayne Slavin] NetStumbler is a wireless tool that allows you to detect wireless networks. It was written by my friend Marius Milner. Wayne Slavin July 19, 2004 [Q] Your site describes NetStumbler as "beggarware." What does that mean? [A by Wayne Slavin] It means you don't have to pay for a license to use it. The program contains information about the (software) drivers for many wireless cards. That information was obtained under nondisclosure agreements with the manufacturers. As part of those agreements, NetStumbler cannot be resold. ----------------- Re: Hacker Marius Milner secretly intercepted WiFi data as the firm’s Street View casp321 by casp321 . Jan 16, 2013 8:33 AM Re: As part of nondisclosure agreements, NetStumbler could not be resold casp321 by casp321 . Jun 13, 2012 Denials Over Google Street View By EDWARD WYATT | New York Times – Google has long prided itself on not being a conventional company. But there is one characteristic it apparently shares with the most sclerotic bureaucracy: the willingness of its employees to say, “Not my job.” The company on Tuesday released a trove of documents related to a federal investigation of its Street View mapping project. Although the project was intended to photograph the world’s streets, from 2007 to 2010 Google gathered unencrypted Internet data from wireless networks, including the content of private communications, as its specially equipped cars passed through neighborhoods. Among the documents released Tuesday are sworn declarations by nine people — their names and titles redacted but most of whom appear to be Google engineers — who said they were not aware of the data collection either because it was not part of their job or they did not review the project documentation, even when it was provided to them.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358360240276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358360994294-23</Id><Topic><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sad and funny yahoo blocks this public news? Google, Conn. AG Agree That Google Sniffed Wi-Fi Data By Mark Hachman January 28, 2011 The attorney general's office of Connecticut and Google reached an agreement Friday that will allow the state's investigation of Google's Wi-Fi snooping to proceed. According to a statement released by George Jepsen, Connecticut's attorney general, Google has admitted to collecting "URLs of requested Web pages, partial or complete e-mail communications or other information, including confidential and private information" that was transmitted over the air as its Street View cars were within range between 2008 and Sept. 2009. The announcement was made on the day that several groups tried unofficially to dub Data Privacy Day. In a separate statement, Jepsen urged consumers to secure their wireless networks to prevent wireless data from leaking beyond their property. The agreement, referred to as a "stipulation," means that Connecticut and the 40-state coalition it is leading can resolve the matter without the necessity of a court case, Jepsen said. That came as a result of a Civil Investigative Demand that the state filed earlier. In collecting photos used for its Street View feature of Google Maps, the cars used to photograph street-level scenes also "sniffed" unsecured personal and business data that was broadcasting at the time, via routers built into the vehicles. That data collection has become a significant black eye for Google, with South Korea becoming the latest country to investigate the breach.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358360994294</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358361349190-24</Id><Topic><Title>Internet activist Aaron Swartz's father tells funeral his son was 'killed by the government'</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358342149675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 08:15:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Connecticut Won't Press for Google WiSpy Data, Looks to Settle January 28, 2011 John Paczkowski “Verifying Google’s data snare is crucial to assessing a penalty and assuring no repeat. Consumers and businesses expect and deserve a full explanation, as well as measures shielding them from future spying. We will scrupulously safeguard the confidentiality of information we review. “We will fight to compel Google to come clean–granting my office access to improperly collected materials and protecting confidentiality, as the company has done in Canada and elsewhere.” – Connecticut Attorney General Richard Blumenthal Dec. 10, 2010</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358361349190</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:35:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358361418353-25</Id><Title>FB is developing fullblown seasrch</Title><Msg>Do you really think they spend all the money to search for people?</Msg><Username>truetrader100</Username><Timestamp>1358361418353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:36:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358364382679-26</Id><Title>Time to buy the king of search..</Title><Msg>Oversold.....</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1358364382679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:26:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358364733262-27</Id><Title>Is there some sort of wall at $715 ...</Title><Msg>which only opened long enough for me to buy.</Msg><Username>xmsr_to_100_soon</Username><Timestamp>1358364733262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:32:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358365131919-28</Id><Title>Sell GOOG</Title><Msg>Buy AAPL...Long and strong AAPL</Msg><Username>ny_nyyankee</Username><Timestamp>1358365131919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:38:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358367515158-29</Id><Topic><Title>Time to buy the king of search..</Title><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1358364382679</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:26:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buy when they all look at AAPL..FB also tries to go to hod...</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1358367515158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:18:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358369837170-30</Id><Topic><Title>Sell GOOG</Title><Username>ny_nyyankee</Username><Timestamp>1358365131919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 14:38:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are they mutually exclusive? Or are you just saying now it's AAPL's turn?</Msg><Username>myronblender</Username><Timestamp>1358369837170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:57:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358369905026-31</Id><Title>Will GOOG open higher tomorrow?</Title><Msg>Or will we start low and have to claw back?</Msg><Username>myronblender</Username><Timestamp>1358369905026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 15:58:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358370019078-32</Id><Title>Donkey Killers</Title><Msg>Why would anyone run over a Donkey with a camera truck, take pictures of it, and then post it online. Ok, I suppose you would for the right price but what's the right price? Surely a little in ad sales and some street Cree is not enough. Maybe you would for a sneak peak at apples next iPhone. Please don't run over anymore Donkeys with your camera truck. So uncool.</Msg><Username>A Yahoo! User</Username><Timestamp>1358370019078</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 16:00:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358376880820-33</Id><Title>BOYS WILL TAKE HER DOWN LIKE APPLE</Title><Msg>Buy put protection. wish i did at 775 if you own 100 shares buy the feb 700 put for protection.....paid if it flys up after earnings and protects on downside under 700</Msg><Username>bmpthegreat</Username><Timestamp>1358376880820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 17:54:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358380231654-34</Id><Topic><Title>FB is developing fullblown seasrch</Title><Username>truetrader100</Username><Timestamp>1358361418353</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:36:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of Apple developing fullblown maps. Little to gain and 35% share drop to lose. Seems crazy to me.</Msg><Username>myronblender</Username><Timestamp>1358380231654</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 18:50:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358382905301-35</Id><Title>WHERE IN JESUS IS THE STOCK SPLIT.</Title><Msg>Never saw a company announce a 2-1 stock split, and never give it.</Msg><Username>steveo23jack</Username><Timestamp>1358382905301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 19:35:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358389586886-36</Id><Title>So a $20 stock is going o take down GOOG??</Title><Msg>Help me understand how this product has the least little to do with impacting GOOG's business model. I own both stocks, but FB fell on its face after the news was let. GOOG back up tomorrow. This is silly,</Msg><Username>jdelgado7723</Username><Timestamp>1358389586886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:26:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358389921817-37</Id><Topic><Title>people selling GOOG and buying RIMM &amp; AAPL.</Title><Username>charts_say_sell_u_dumb_azz</Username><Timestamp>1358359429206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 13:03:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every trade has a seller and buyer, volume has been low, so no real selling is going on. The tone is light do to buzz from less than interesting news. Sit tight, GOOG will climb the rest of the week. Dell is over, FB is over and RIMM is topped. Money flow at the end of today was good. More will move in tomorrow.</Msg><Username>jdelgado7723</Username><Timestamp>1358389921817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:32:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358391060807-38</Id><Title>This board is barren for a very large cap company. It means it's mostly funds holding it.</Title><Msg>manipulation by the funds.</Msg><Username>theytookallthegoodloginnames</Username><Timestamp>1358391060807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358396114979-39</Id><Topic><Title>Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" $$$ECRET$$$---What THEY don't want YOU to find out??????????</Title><Username>disgracedpublicist757</Username><Timestamp>1356210989988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 16:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kristen is not a big fan of Lindsay</Msg><Username>disgracedpublicist757</Username><Timestamp>1358396114979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:15:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358396188918-40</Id><Title>sell before goog misses estimate again.</Title><Msg>this time it will drop 10%.</Msg><Username>theytookallthegoodloginnames</Username><Timestamp>1358396188918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 23:16:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>