<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367080618611-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mozilla HTML5 mobile OS new ecosystem.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366982590982</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:23:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI...............</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1367080618611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 12:36:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367084230438-2</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Schmidt criticizes Google's Glass device.</Title><Username>strong_iiiii</Username><Timestamp>1366983390159</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These problems are minor points. A good high tech developer aims at the future and not the present. Back when Microsoft was competently run (pre Balmer) their products were constantly demanding better hardware than existed at the time project development began, but were well suited for new hardware that later came out (around release date). As with self driving car, laws need to evolve to match technology. Focus should be does it make sense to wear while driving?, not status under current rules. Initial rules for children prudent--eventually will probably fall away--Early internet and cell phones were not for children either.. Expensive is a hardware issue. Electronics component prices come down over time. On any long cycle development project, it is a serious mistake to develop based on current component costs. Battery issues: Common to all mobile electronics. Enough at stake and feasibility of better power technologies imply this will eventually be solved. Version 1.0 will be bleeding edge technology, but the general concept has a future. In the high tech field, if you stand still you fade away. Apple did not get to where it is today by making PC clones. HP and Dell are the result of "me to" products and not reaching for the future. Android was the response to the threat from Phone companies and Apple of a closed search market as mobile search emerged. If Google does not continue to explore future interfaces, it could lose its position in search when the next technology comes along.</Msg><Username>anonymouswizard</Username><Timestamp>1367084230438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 13:37:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367120459563-3</Id><Title>Time to tread carefully</Title><Msg>The results have done the stock good, and it is now moving towards the 50 DMA of $807. This level is likely to provide minor resistance. After that the obvious level will be the 52 week high which is likely to provide slightly stronger resistance. After that the territories are unchartered. A look at the valuations, on an absolute basis, it is trading at the 5 times its sales and 3.54 times its book value. The P/E (ttm) is 24 which is getting a little uncomfortable. All hopes are based on the ability of Google to bring out and succeed with newer and more innovative products. Hopes from Glass are already very high, and the self-driven cars etc. are also attracting interest. Then there is the Fiber. All these things put together ultimately seem to be factoring in a high probability of success of all Google ventures. There is not much competition in the search engine space, and the brand strength is amazing. Still the hopes and expectations are not always easy to meet. Latest case being Apple (AAPL) which did so well that it was punished when it slowed down. Anyway, for Google, there are other issues like unintended patent violations which can cost the company a lot of money. Recently, patent monetization has become big business and all are trying to enforce violations. MGT Capital Investments (MGT) recently filed a $4.5 billion dollar lawsuit against casino gaming companies. The Markman hearing is expected in second half of this year and MGT is already buzzing with activity. What is more important for Google is to clear the issues related to its privacy policy and allegations of “dominance”. With several lawsuits in EU, UK etc., a lot of PR work has to be done. All this put together, it seems that the immediate trigger, apart from result of the lawsuits, will be success (or failure) of Glass. One has to tread carefully and always remember that sentiments can change quickly.</Msg><Username>investora2z</Username><Timestamp>1367120459563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 23:40:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>