<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358694538725-1</Id><Title>MMRF partner of GOOGLE in PHR'S</Title><Msg>Rules go into effect on March 26th,New HIPAA Omnibus Rules Certainly Encourage the Use of a Personal Health Record for Patients With Getting Copies of Their Medical Records.Buy 500K of MMRF and Retire early folks.Do some DD on it.MMRF got plenty of Monopoly-Patents...like VRNG.</Msg><Username>wyn.moore</Username><Timestamp>1358694538725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 10:08:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358698282483-2</Id><Topic><Title>GOOG's cost per click down 4 quarters in a row due to mobile (iOS, Android)</Title><Username>adonis9000</Username><Timestamp>1358490499569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 01:28:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goog tanked $80 in one day after the last earnings report after its cost per click fell 15% due to mobile and it missed its EPS estimate by 17%. Go back and read about goog's last earnings report and the 15% decline in cost per click. Goog's cost per click started to decline 4 quarters ago and has fallen every quarter since. It's nonsense to suggest goog makes as much from mobile ads as traditional desktop ads. Goog makes anywhere from 60-85% less depending on which mobile device is displaying the ads. Mobile devices's screens are just smaller than PC screens. As for any money goog does make on mobile, it came out during the trial they only made $500 mil. so far total profit on mobile ads after investing $30 bil. on developing Android and related services. As for that $500 mil., iOS revenues exceed Android revenues 4-to-1. Android is a money hole. The main beneficiary is Samsung whose market cap has risen 6-fold while goog's price is the same as it was 5 years ago. Samsung's market cap will exceed goog's this year, by the way. Goog's jealous so it will come out with the x-phone and x-tablet later this year and not give Samsung the latest Android updates. Samsung will retaliate by bringing out Tizen phones this year. Samsung Galaxy S3's and Note II's are dying off due to Sudden Death Syndrome just in time. Samsung and Goog both want to be like Apple, control both hardware and software, but they will both fail.</Msg><Username>adonis9000</Username><Timestamp>1358698282483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 11:11:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358701207202-3</Id><Title>Qihu confirms cooperation with Google</Title><Msg>Qihoo 360 confirmed cooperation with Google, says Jefferies Jefferies says that during recent meetings, Qihoo 360 (QIHU) management confirmed cooperation with Google (GOOG), with Google's ad system accessing into Qihoo search. Management also expects no meaningful impact from Baidu's (BIDU) investment in Kingsoft, according to Jefferies. The firm raised its price target for Qihoo 360 shares to $38 from $35 and reiterates a Buy rating on the stock.</Msg><Username>britslc</Username><Timestamp>1358701207202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 12:00:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708881571-4</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the info timh1951; have used it multiple times this morning!</Msg><Username>fire_1_on_ice</Username><Timestamp>1358708881571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:08:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358708936311-5</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Got it merenkov; thanks for the tip!</Msg><Username>fire_1_on_ice</Username><Timestamp>1358708936311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 14:08:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358724513981-6</Id><Title>Friday Blurb causing a stir....</Title><Msg>Reading an article about some leak on Friday indicating that the Motorola Mobility losses are really slamming Google's numbers. Scary, I KNEW MMI was a money pit.</Msg><Username>fattymcbutterpants2001</Username><Timestamp>1358724513981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726219366-7</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go to that board and search under "newest" for the terms "Demark", "Gore", etc. My co managing partner has been sharing many insights known only in the let's call it esoteric hedge fund research circles. We are positioned for our view that AAPL is going to blow out the quarter Wednesday. Though FB and others are stuggling to figure out sustainable mobile revenues from their posturing, we think GOOG has a big role to play forward due to its quality maps and search tie ins... Still scratching our heads on the Friday news. Strange IR effort to say ~ hey street, your numbers are too high and figure out the mobility sale already. IR does not mix well with novel approaches and IR. We are very long (combined over 10% of aum) in GOOG and AAPL, the two clear long term winners, but we only trade Faceplant aka Fakebook. Observationally, it is interesting that FB has gone from college cool to middle school girls texting each other and grandparents sharing pictures of their grandkids and vacations. FB's corporate penetration is bizarre too. Companies are increasingly involved on FB, but if you click to many saying "visit us on FB", you'll see the FB page is typically a mission statement, business overview and inks to their corporate websites. It is hard to see how much any corporation would be willing to pay for that for more than a novelty period.</Msg><Username>jlbhgb</Username><Timestamp>1358726219366</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:56:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358726330350-8</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same... "squeezetracker" has actively shared many worthwhile posts going into this Q's earnings report though.</Msg><Username>jlbhgb</Username><Timestamp>1358726330350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 18:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358728160434-9</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can still ignore on the AAPL board. Just click the down arrow next to the reply button.</Msg><Username>darrell_d_b</Username><Timestamp>1358728160434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:29:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358729356900-10</Id><Topic><Title>Why are there no profits from Android?</Title><Username>dogeater20088</Username><Timestamp>1358565768446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-18 22:22:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm Maybe because Android is given away for Free to all phone makers. Now Google/Motorola compete with the same phone makers they give android to for free. Where would Android be without Samsung? What happens if the linux based operating system Samsung is testing and plans to use in its phones becomes favored over Android in Asian markets? A lot of questions for Google going forward. Free Android phones given away to people with lower income do not bother with mobile ads and find them mostly annoying.</Msg><Username>ottoman8255</Username><Timestamp>1358729356900</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 19:49:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358732647399-11</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Believe it or not the Ignore User is an option under Reply. Why? Who knows! I have successfully ignored dozens of idiots and continue to do so.</Msg><Username>buymoreapple</Username><Timestamp>1358732647399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 20:44:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736322553-12</Id><Topic><Title>Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" $$$ECRET$$$---What THEY don't want YOU to find out??????????</Title><Username>disgracedpublicist757</Username><Timestamp>1356210989988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 16:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Makes The Da Vinci Code look like nuthin but a pile a boooossssittt.......The New York Times"</Msg><Username>crookedhedgefundmanager</Username><Timestamp>1358736322553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:45:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358736664824-13</Id><Topic><Title>Johnny Dirtbag "Movie Star" $$$ECRET$$$---What THEY don't want YOU to find out??????????</Title><Username>disgracedpublicist757</Username><Timestamp>1356210989988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-22 16:16:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This novel is a bad influence on the public at large; and will require further analysis to arrive at a competent review.....The New York Times"----</Msg><Username>crookedhedgefundmanager</Username><Timestamp>1358736664824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-20 21:51:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>