<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358429137882-1</Id><Title>EARNINGS Question....</Title><Msg>what is the current estimate for jan 21st??....$8.63 or $10.5 per share...thanks for clarification</Msg><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358429137882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 08:25:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358431937778-2</Id><Topic><Title>Great point of view, see what we think</Title><Username>travelpeople00</Username><Timestamp>1161808945000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2006-10-25 16:42:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LONG TREND !! $1000 soon</Msg><Username>luizimonti</Username><Timestamp>1358431937778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 09:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358435700419-3</Id><Title>High of day</Title><Msg>Going higher...yesterday I said buy the king of search....</Msg><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1358435700419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:15:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358437270285-4</Id><Topic><Title>High of day</Title><Username>cybercash28</Username><Timestamp>1358435700419</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:15:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do NOT believe GOOG will miss this time.</Msg><Username>actionspread</Username><Timestamp>1358437270285</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:41:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358438106976-5</Id><Title>what is the earnings estimate this coming earnings call??</Title><Msg>thanks</Msg><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358438106976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 10:55:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358439511601-6</Id><Topic><Title>8000% on KROGER and (ATTD) deal, Phase III Recover drink ATTD's product will now be sold in KROGER</Title><Username>greatpennies</Username><Timestamp>1354049588326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-27 15:53:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New baby millionaires will be made here on or before 2nd quarter.</Msg><Username>overlookedpennies</Username><Timestamp>1358439511601</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:18:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358441480035-7</Id><Topic><Title>EARNINGS Question....</Title><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358429137882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 08:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Im seeing 10.61 as the 8.63 is the low estimate for earnings. Average forecasts of the analysts</Msg><Username>riley200834</Username><Timestamp>1358441480035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 11:51:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358442015444-8</Id><Topic><Title>Google was trying to buy daily-deals</Title><Username>lorriemarencojaashjy3803</Username><Timestamp>1303916937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-04-27 11:08:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One more thing luke.</Msg><Username>robinhenry612</Username><Timestamp>1358442015444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:00:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358442152072-9</Id><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Msg>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google? Re: Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Jan 17, 2013 9:10 AM ############ Hambrecht, Paul husband of Nancy congresswoman, ... Google should not be accused of "unfair" acts: lawmakers Reuters – Mon, Nov 19, 2012 WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Two lawmakers urged the Federal Trade Commission on Monday to steer clear of expanding its authority as it investigates allegations search engine company Google violated antitrust law. The two California Democrats in the House of Representatives, who count Google as a major campaign contributor, asked the FTC not to accuse the company of "unfair" acts if it believes it broke antitrust law. Anna Eshoo, on the Energy and Commerce Committee, and Zoe Lofgren, who is on the Judiciary Committee, said there were reports to suggest the FTC planned to use the unfair standard to avoid proving some elements required in an antitrust claim. ?????????? Want a voice in Washington? Invest in a politician December 12, 2010 | Modified: March 19, 2012 Finally, Paul Pelosi Jr., Nancy's only son, works for Bill Hambrecht at WR Hambrecht. Pelosi's office didn't return a phone call, but Hambrecht did. I asked him if his ties to Pelosi earned him the hearing. He said Pelosi was motivated only by "genuine desire to find a private-sector solution" to unemployment. Hambrecht added that Democratic Rep. Anna Eshoo, whose Silicon Valley district includes many start-ups, was the real prime mover. ############ 0 users liked this posts 0 users disliked this posts Reply Report Abuse Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too?casp321 by casp321 . Jan 17, 2013 9:03 AM . Permalink Why would Hambrecht ===================== Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Jan 17, 2013 9:03 AM Why would Hambrecht "direct money o other causes" and what are those "causes"? How did ON2 come up with CREATING ON2 UK limited PRIVATE account? Not a lawyer would know much about funneling money with that SOPHISTICATION? by casp321 . Jan 7, 2013 10:20 AM Hambrecht &amp; Pelosi was publicly reported in 2004: William or Bill Hambrecht has been a major source of financial backing for Pelosi's career, which includes ... and directing money to other causes ... Pelosi identifies as critical. ============== Re: Re: Re: Re: Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Jan 9, 2013 3:05 PM . Permalink After posting ON2 UK account with $50 million on December 10, 2012, Google TRANSFERRED the... After posting ON2 UK account with $50 million on December 10, 2012, Google TRANSFERRED the money from that account to unknown account by December 13, 2012???? by casp321 . Dec 11, 2012 10:21 AM About $50 million reported to be in ON2 UK account as of jan 2012. Bill Jill, as they called Bill Joll in UK, was ON2 UK director before his term was terminated sometime in 2008??? --------- Android and AXI based SoC Platform for Custom Silicon Solutions VeriSilicon 2010.11 VeriSilicon Has Been Selected As Channel Partner for WebM ▼ G-series 1 is the only HW decoder in the market supporting all On2 VP codecs ▲ VP6 –Adobe Flash, JavaFX ▲ VP7 –Skype, Move Media Player, ABC and Fox streaming ▲ VP8 –the new free open source internet video format used in the WebM ▼ VeriSilicon has been selected by Google as the first channel partner to distribute to all chip companies other than a few strategic 8 partners of Google. ▼ VeriSilicon has been granted modification rights. ▼ VeriSilicon has been distributing Hantro/On2 products before Google acquirsition. ▼ VeriSilicon has released ZSP based VP6/7/8 (WebM) decoders.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358442324407-10</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumi: If you are irritated by every rub, how will you be polished? casp321 by casp321 . Dec 27, 2012 10:14 PM If you are irritated by every rub, how will you be polished? ~Rumi Why Google in less than three days, from December 10, 2012 to December 13, 2012, EMPTIED ON2 account in ON2 UK after being EXPOSED on scratch Yahoo GOOG/VRNG Board? casp321 $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ Official Legal documents for ON2 TECHNOLOGIES (UK) LIMITED Legal Information Financial Year End: 30 Jun Capital:£1.00 on 13 Dec 2012 ??????????????? Official Legal documents for ON2 TECHNOLOGIES (UK) LIMITED Legal Information Capital:£30,079,102.71 on 5 Jan 2012 $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ ============= Re: Re: Re: ON2 UK Limited, Salary or Dividend: Guide Running a limited company casp321 by casp321 . Jan 9, 2013 10:59 PM ON2 TECHNOLOGIES, INC. - FORM 10-Q - November 5, 2009 Asset Impairment. During the quarter ended September 30, 2008, the global economy had dramatically weakened, which, among other factors, contributed to the continued underperformance of our Hantro business and resulted in a decline in our overall market value. Based on those circumstances, at September 30, 2008, the Company performed an impairment review of its goodwill and intangible assets related to its On2 Finland business. The Company engaged an outside valuation specialist to perform the evaluation, utilizing management’s inputs and assumptions, by analyzing the expected future cash flows of the business. Based on the results of the evaluation, the Company determined that goodwill and other intangibles were impaired. Accordingly, the Company recorded an impairment charge during the quarter ended September 30, 2008, totaling $20,265,000 (goodwill) and $5,980,000 (intangible assets) to reduce their carrying value to an amount that is expected to be recoverable. As of September 30, 2009, based on management’s analysis, the valuation and adjustments made through December 31, 2008 do not require further adjustment for additional impairment resulting from any events or changes in circumstances.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442324407</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:05:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358442707706-11</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ON2 CEO, called Bill Joll in the USA and Bill Jill in UK falsified ON2 earning in 2007 and was ON2 UK Limited Director in 2008 and 2009, which shows termination, as was reported? Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Jan 17, 2013 9:03 AM Why would Hambrecht "direct money o other causes" and what are those "causes"? How did ON2 come up with CREATING ON2 UK limited PRIVATE account? Not a lawyer would know much about funneling money with that SOPHISTICATION? by casp321 . Jan 7, 2013 10:20 AM Hambrecht &amp; Pelosi was publicly reported in 2004: William or Bill Hambrecht has been a major source of financial backing for Pelosi's career, which includes ... and directing money to other causes ... Pelosi identifies as critical. ----------- One scenario created by casp321 not real history: ON2 shorting: Was it ‘detective work’ or "impermissible insider trading" casp321 by casp321 . Sep 19, 2011 7:00 PM ON2 shorting: Was it ‘detective work’ or "impermissible insider trading" ON2's CEO in 2007, Bill Joll, gave AUTHORITY to his friend's, Mike O'Hare, financial institution, Opeenheimer, to do rob ON2 shreholders by Shorting/Tossting/Covering and giving information to who ever they pleased. This is how one can write a scenario for it: ------------- Joll to O'Hare, "Go ahead ROB, or Short/toss/cover, ON2 shareholders." O'Hare to Joll, "What about our fiends and Bill Hambrecht friends?" Joll to O'Hare, "Your friend is my friend and give the information to any of your friends you think would want to make money while watching video on Youtube or having videocoferencing on Skype or playing Online videogames through Chinese Netease." O'Hare to Joll, "What if ON2's shareholders Interest and PPS gets 'shorter' and Short Interest grow bigger and ON2 shareholders find out about it?" Joll to O'Hare, "Tell them your BILL is our BILL." O'Hare to Joll, "If ON2 shareholders catches us red-handed what we should do?" Joll to O'Hare, "Tell them our BILL is your BILL and the Judge knows it too." ------------- Here it is: "On2 has agreed to indemnify Oppenheimer for certain liabilities that might arise out of the engagement, including the rendering of the opinion." ------------------------ Re: Born in the USA???? casp321 by casp321 . Sep 13, 2011 11:31 AM . Permalink When you need to understand what these,‘detective work’ and "impermissible insider trading," it's NOT what it really means, it's HOW you play their game and you MUST have PROVE to be part of their CIRCLE, which might not have that much link and leak, because everything is on the RUN: they MOVE/REMOVE/HIDE/DESTROY-HISTORY/...??? ---Prosecutors are seeking a sentence of 19 1/2 to 24 1/2 years at his sentencing on Sept. 27. “In my own mind, the line between permissible ‘detective work’ and impermissible insider trading was not always clear, especially with regard to companies broadly covered by the news media as to which there was a wealth of publicly available information, including frequent leaks, rumors and speculation about corporate transactions and other important developments,” Rajaratnam told the probation officer, according to prosecutors.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442707706</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:11:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358442854302-12</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings were $8.08 a share</Title><Username>darcycalicojbqwcq7588</Username><Timestamp>1303749094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-04-25 12:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be expecting for more news.</Msg><Username>robinhenry612</Username><Timestamp>1358442854302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:14:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358442978856-13</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are they related: Judge Tommy E. Miller &amp; Dan, sun of George Miller? casp321 by casp321 . Jan 8, 2013 8:26 AM --Dan Miller was ON2 CTO, CEO until 2003 --George Miller thought "ins and out of Congress" to congresswoman Nancy Pelosi --Vringo vs Google Case Reassigned to Magistrate Judge Tommy E. Miller as directed. Magistrate Judge Douglas E. Miller no longer assigned to the case. (ecav, ) (Entered: 10/11/2012) .</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442978856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:16:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358443415949-14</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Verisilicon documents: "VeriSilicon has been distributing Hantro/On2 products before Google acquirsition."</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358443415949</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:23:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358443985026-15</Id><Topic><Title>Earnings were $8.08 a share</Title><Username>darcycalicojbqwcq7588</Username><Timestamp>1303749094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-04-25 12:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this with us.</Msg><Username>robinhenry612</Username><Timestamp>1358443985026</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444272409-16</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was about $50 milllion deposited in ON2 UK Limited account until December 13, 2012, from ON2's products or Google's Admoerds or from BOTH? Google trademarked ON2 and Hantro in 2007 and 2008, respectively. Google TERMINATED Hatro trademark on Nov 12, 2012 while Vringo lawsuit against Google was going on and Veringo counsels were asking damages from Google earnings? Google subsidiary in nethearlan released Google account in Irland on Nov 21, 2012, one day after Verigo got the favourit rulling in the case? Re: Re: ON2 UK Limited, Salary or Dividend: Guide Running a limited company casp321 by casp321 . Jan 9, 2013 10:29 PM ON2 UK Limited account went down from Capital:£30,079,102.71 on 5 Jan 2012 to £1.00 on December 2012??? casp321 --------- "Guide Strike off your limited company from the Companies Register Business assets Part 2: Directors' responsibilities Before applying to strike off your limited company, you must make sure you’ve closed it down legally. You should make sure that any business assets are shared among the shareholders before the company is struck off. Anything that’s left will go to the Crown - you’ll have to restore the company to get anything back." -------------------------- Re: Re: ON2 UK Limited, Salary or Dividend: Guide Running a limited company casp321 by casp321 . Jan 9, 2013 9:15 PM As a Director of Limited company "You can ask other people to manage some of these things day-to-day. For example, an accountant can manage your accounts for you - but you’re still legally responsible for them." Guide Running a limited company Part 1: Directors' responsibilities As a director of a limited company, the law says you must: try to make the company a success, using your skills, experience and judgment follow the company’s rules, shown in its articles of association make decisions for the benefit of the company, not yourself tell other shareholders if you might personally benefit from a transaction the company makes keep company records and report changes to Companies House and HM Revenue &amp; Customs make sure the company’s accounts are a ‘true and fair view’ of the business’ finances register for Self Assessment and send a personal Self Assessment tax return every year if you get an income from the company You can ask other people to manage some of these things day-to-day. For example, an accountant can manage your accounts for you - but you’re still legally responsible for them. ---------------- As of December 10, 2012: Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Dec 10, 2012 More information about company ON2 TECHNOLOGIES (UK) LIMITED Adding contact information Company Status Active Company Type Private Limited Company Incorporation Date 24/12/1991 Board members of ON2 TECHNOLOGIES (UK) LIMITED All board members PAUL GORDON WILKINS - Director JOHN KENT WALKER - Director GRAHAM LAW - Director DONALD STEWART HARRISON - Director -------------- Re: Re: Re: ON2 shareholders EXPOSING Google criminal intention, Vringo counsel can take a note of t too? casp321 by casp321 . Dec 10, 2012 11:54 PM So, they had hidden ACCOUNTs in UK in the expenses of ON2 shareholders while ON2's Interim, MF, was calling quit while ON2 UK had different accounts on its own? WOW???? Legal Information Capital:£30,079,102.71 on 5 Jan 2012 Filed on: 22 Feb 2012 Form: TM01 - Ending appointment as Director APPOINTMENT TERMINATED, DIRECTOR JOHN WALKER Filed on: 16 Feb 2012 Form: AP01 - Appointment of Director DIRECTOR APPOINTED DONALD STEWART HARRISON ------------------------------- How many shareholders ON2 UK Limited as PRIVATE company had? Who from ON2 USA knew about ON2 UK Limited existance? How many beside Bill Jill, Paul Wilkin and MF? Re: Re: ON2 UK Limited, Salary or Dividend: Guide Running a limited company casp321 by casp321 . Jan 10, 2013 11:03 AM Complain to the Insolvency Service You can complain to the Insolvency Service if you have reasonable grounds to suspect a company of: causing significant harm to customers, suppliers etc breaking the law, eg fraud serious misconduct having a significant irregularity in its affairs You can also report someone who’s disqualified as a director, but is taking part in the management of a company. What happens next If the Insolvency Service decides that your complaint is serious enough, they will either carry out a confidential investigation pass your complaint on to another public body, if appropriate - tell them if you don’t want them to do this If they find anything wrong and have enough evidence, they may ask a court to: close the company down disqualify the company’s directors If they find an offence may have been committed, they’ll send a report to the appropriate authority, who will decide whether to carry out a criminal investigation. -------------------------- Re: ON2 UK Limited, Salary or Dividend: Guide Running a limited company casp321 by casp321 . Jan 10, 2013 10:58 AM UK Limited: Quick answer Complain about a limited company Not what you're looking for? ↓ You can complain to the Insolvency Service, Companies House or the Serious Fraud Office if you suspect a limited company or its directors of fraud or serious misconduct. How to complain Get more information or report misconduct using the Insolvency Service’s investigations hotline. You can also write to them: Intelligence Hub Investigations and Enforcement Services Insolvency Service 3rd Floor Cannon House 18 Priory Queensway Birmingham B4 6FD Give as much information as you can when you complain. Serious and complex fraud If your complaint relates to a serious and complex fraud involving more than £1 million, check the Serious Fraud Office’s criteria for taking on cases to see if you should report it to them.</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358444272409</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444343865-17</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was about $50 milllion deposited in ON2 UK Limited account until December 13, 2012, from ON2's products or Google's Adwords or from BOTH?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358444343865</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:39:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444496191-18</Id><Topic><Title>EARNINGS Question....</Title><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358429137882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 08:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thanks for the info...the wallstret cheat sheet had $8.63 and yahoo finance had $10.53 ..just confused at what the analysts r looking for....</Msg><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358444496191</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:41:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444660243-19</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is it possible for ON2 shareholders to PROVIDE the activities in ON2 UK Limited account as PRIVATE to the current judge sitting on ON2 OPT-OUT and not sending the final reasults out yet. Woulsd it make any difference. I believe ON2 might have had a lot of ACTIVITIES funneling money IN and OUT of ON2 UK for long without even UK government know about DETAILs of them. Can anyone bring this to current judge ATTENTION and show how much she's screwed by not listening to OBJECTORs and letting ON2-plaintiff-with-100-ONT-share "settle" the case?</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358444660243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:44:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444752459-20</Id><Topic><Title>Short GOOG and going Long MSFT--anti Cramer trade</Title><Username>profitprophetgold</Username><Timestamp>1357313520794</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 10:32:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Winning!</Msg><Username>profitprophetgold</Username><Timestamp>1358444752459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358444975361-21</Id><Topic><Title>Still a Bull</Title><Username>evieluongo364</Username><Timestamp>1322459829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-28 00:57:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great trading tool</Msg><Username>robinhenry612</Username><Timestamp>1358444975361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:49:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358445366554-22</Id><Title>Facebook search is awesome...</Title><Msg>and although zuck says it isn't internet search...searching facebook is the same thing... every company has a facebook page... this is going to hurt Google tremendously.</Msg><Username>jzandmebuddies</Username><Timestamp>1358445366554</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:56:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358446535465-23</Id><Topic><Title>Millions of $ in ON2 UK Limited account, Hantro, China, Verisilicon &amp; Google?</Title><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358442152072</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 12:02:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's interesting to see, at least for now, is if Chinese Government, British Government in UK, USA Government will INVESTIGATE Dai dynasy from Verisilicon, Vivante and Marvell and Erich Schmidt from Google and Pete Wendell from Siera Venture invested in Verisilicon and had "friendship" with Eric Schmidt at Stanford teaching courses together??</Msg><Username>casp321</Username><Timestamp>1358446535465</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:15:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358448040355-24</Id><Title>GooG n Grasso</Title><Msg>not a leader,, not at 52 highs pumpers got it wrong,, Apple will fly and google will go nowhere for a while</Msg><Username>tj_shanks</Username><Timestamp>1358448040355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:40:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358448208943-25</Id><Title>APPLE CANCELLING PARTS DUE TO POOR SALES ---- WILL TRANSLATE INTO POOR</Title><Msg>Guidance on e-day next week, unless the books are "cooked" :)</Msg><Username>hcl815</Username><Timestamp>1358448208943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:43:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358448297136-26</Id><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Msg>I'm a fan of both Google and Apple, each innovators in their own way. But have any of you ever visited the AAPL message board here at yahoo? While the GOOG board may have 15 or 20 posts in a day, the AAPL board will have thousands, mostly crude, illiterate, juvenile trash-talking, essentially rendering that board unusable. Here it seems like there is just occasional thoughtful discussion. Can anyone explain this discrepancy?</Msg><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358450820195-27</Id><Title>When does the pre earnings pump start?</Title><Msg>Tomorrow? Let's light this candle into Tuesday.</Msg><Username>salvatoregovernale</Username><Timestamp>1358450820195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 14:27:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358450859541-28</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here ever visit the AAPL board?</Title><Username>merenkov</Username><Timestamp>1358448297136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:44:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It speaks to the quality of the company and "the company they keep." Google would be the group I would want to hang around-- owners and shareholders. I have a Andr phone and love it-- I can live without the hype of apple products and the kind of people that race after them "blindly" .............an opinion</Msg><Username>thebigpitcher17</Username><Timestamp>1358450859541</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 14:27:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358452655197-29</Id><Topic><Title>APPLE CANCELLING PARTS DUE TO POOR SALES ---- WILL TRANSLATE INTO POOR</Title><Username>hcl815</Username><Timestamp>1358448208943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:43:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Old news.If you do some research you'll find that Apple is changing displays. Google has much far to fall than Apple. Ad spending was very soft in last qtr and Google makes more money off IOS than Andriod.</Msg><Username>genesis_gekko</Username><Timestamp>1358452655197</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 14:57:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358462744990-30</Id><Topic><Title>GooG n Grasso</Title><Username>tj_shanks</Username><Timestamp>1358448040355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 13:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grasso is a pump and dump artist. Be careful.</Msg><Username>dreamscaper33</Username><Timestamp>1358462744990</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 17:45:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358466201510-31</Id><Title>Here is why goog dropping</Title><Msg>Once upon a time a man told a small village, “I will buy monkeys for $10 each.” Since there were many monkeys in the forest, the villagers caught them and sold them to the man. As the supply of monkeys diminished, the villagers’ efforts slowed, so the man offered them $20 each. They renewed their efforts but the supply of monkeys diminished further, so he increased his price to $25. Soon no one could even find a monkey in the forest. The man increased his price to $50, but announced, “Since I must go to the city on business, I authorize my assistant to buy monkeys on my behalf.” As soon as his boss was gone, the assistant told the villagers, “My boss has collected lots of monkeys. I’ll sell them to you for $35 and then, when he returns, you can sell them to him for $50.” The villagers rounded up all the money they could and bought as many monkeys as possible. Then they had monkeys everywhere… … but they never saw the man or his assistant again. And now you understand the workings of the stock market!</Msg><Username>maluk658</Username><Timestamp>1358466201510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467076799-32</Id><Topic><Title>Here is why goog dropping</Title><Username>maluk658</Username><Timestamp>1358466201510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:43:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOOG is holding up better then any tech stock out there buddy. It's not about one day. Go look at AAPL if you want to see a stock that's past it's prime and in a long term downtrend spiral.</Msg><Username>dreamscaper33</Username><Timestamp>1358467076799</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 18:57:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358467951276-33</Id><Topic><Title>EARNINGS Question....</Title><Username>h08859</Username><Timestamp>1358429137882</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 08:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whisper # they have to beat is $11</Msg><Username>dreamscaper33</Username><Timestamp>1358467951276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358469385641-34</Id><Title>O.K. Lets everyone settle down and look at the PE and stock outstanding for GOOG and APPL</Title><Msg>IMHO there is a great deal to understand. GOOG search is #1 for anything you want or need to know. EVERTHING!! APPL is the #1 at selling their products to the world. The world want's the best and don't want second best. So who should you invest in? Both IMHO.</Msg><Username>laylow1991</Username><Timestamp>1358469385641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 19:36:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358476104466-35</Id><Title>GOOGLE blows away earnings, $800+ into next week. Trending in EPS: one miss, then BIG blow out.</Title><Msg>Google, has a tendency to miss one, and then next EPS is a blow out. This Quarter should be a blowout. Look at the trend for past 8-10 EPS reports. They like to keep increasing thier Earnings and cash, and make new investments in between. Goggle whould have new targets of $900 to $950 coming, where today some are at $850. Long google.</Msg><Username>earningsalert321</Username><Timestamp>1358476104466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 21:28:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358482500786-36</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE blows away earnings, $800+ into next week. Trending in EPS: one miss, then BIG blow out.</Title><Username>earningsalert321</Username><Timestamp>1358476104466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 21:28:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the reason?: I'll lend one. Starting October 2012, Google started charging for previously free "product listing" ads. Just in time for holiday shopping. This is going to be a revenue spike that is not really being talked about.</Msg><Username>belladonnatello2000</Username><Timestamp>1358482500786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:15:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358482713297-37</Id><Title>Insider selling</Title><Msg>According to the insider transaction, there seems to be a lot of selling going on. If you don't believe take a look at the insider roster.</Msg><Username>nthn.cchrn</Username><Timestamp>1358482713297</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:18:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358483392670-38</Id><Topic><Title>GOOGLE blows away earnings, $800+ into next week. Trending in EPS: one miss, then BIG blow out.</Title><Username>earningsalert321</Username><Timestamp>1358476104466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 21:28:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While I certainly wish you are right I just noticed GOOG hasn't avoided a post earnings selloff since October 2011. Harsh.</Msg><Username>salvatoregovernale</Username><Timestamp>1358483392670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:29:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358484156504-39</Id><Title>WARNING---SELL0FF..SELL0FF...SELL0FF---WARNING!!!</Title><Msg>DID YOU SELL YET?</Msg><Username>mlg4044</Username><Timestamp>1358484156504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 23:42:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>