<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366432149056-1</Id><Topic><Title>options exp...did not make 800</Title><Username>jpnmqrtn</Username><Timestamp>1366402214311</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:10:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you bought calls this morning you made a ton of money if you sold this afternoon.</Msg><Username>elrrambu</Username><Timestamp>1366432149056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 00:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366439029881-2</Id><Topic><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366371214572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does not matter what you think. It is more important to see how the big money reacts to earnings and what they see ahead. I think more traders were expecting a bigger miss on revenues and the tax rate was already a known factor. The stock reacted violently positive on triple normal volume and it was a bullish engulfing candle. The dumb money sold or did not buy. It is obvious this stock is headed much higher. Believe what you want but it doesn't matter to anyone except yourself. Feel good you are either short or don't own the stock and watch it march much higher. Apple is going to have declining revenues over the next year or two and GOOGLE will be growing over 20% year over year and maybe even more. AAPL was a 5-6 year flash because of iphone and ipad but that lead is gone. GOOG has more interessting future for sure. I'ts my bet for the first $1000 tech stock</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1366439029881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:23:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366449676521-3</Id><Title>Innovation is the key to rapid growth</Title><Msg>Numbers apart, the focus of the earnings release remained on innovation. Page said that incremental improvement is guaranteed to be obsolete over time.. The eagerly awaited Glass and other projects like self driven cars were mentioned. In its quest to innovate &amp; grow, Google has to always remain alive to unintended patent infringements and disturbing the privacy sentiments across cultures. Patent &amp; privacy suits are increasing and spoiling the image of the company. Even Facebook (FB) and LinkedIn (LNKD) are facing lawsuits filed by a subsidiary of Document Security System (NYSE:DSS) which is an innovator in document security solutions. Apple (AAPL) has crashed mainly because of lack of innovation. Meanwhile, the Q1'13 went okay with a revenue of $13.97 billion (a 31% rise on a YoY basis). The Traffic Acquisition Cost (TAC) was $2.96 billion (25% of ad revenues, same percentage as Q1'12). The operating margins appear to have reduced with the figure for operating income in Q1'13 being $3.48 billion which is 25% of revenues compared with $3.39 billion (32% of revenues) last year. The GAAP net income increased from $2.89 billion to $3.35 billion during the same period. The GAAP EPS increased from $8.75 to $9.94. Ad Revenues comprised 93% of the total showing a growth of 22%. Site reveneus were 67% of the total, network revenues 25%, and other revenues 8%. Out of these, the network revenue showed the slowest growth of 12%, and the other revenues grew by 150% on a small base of $420 million to $1.05 billion. Geographically, international revenues were 55% of the total compared with 54% in Q1'12. Paid clicks increased 20% on a YoY basis and 3% sequentially. The Cost-Per-Click decreased by around 4% on YoY and sequential basis. Motorola revenues were $1.02 billion in Q1'13. Other Cost of Revenues was 21% of revenues compared with 12% of revenues in Q1'12, which put pressure in the operating margins.</Msg><Username>investora2z</Username><Timestamp>1366449676521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366453752530-4</Id><Topic><Title>Pepsi has been on the move up lately</Title><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1366412437119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 19:00:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that you Jimmy? Hey Cramer go BUY BUY BUY some AAPL @ 700... Boooyah!!!</Msg><Username>chic_getthedoor</Username><Timestamp>1366453752530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366453914465-5</Id><Topic><Title>Undervalued Google worth $1,100.00 a share!</Title><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1365715436546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your call on APPL BUY BUY BUY @ $700 was a failure too Jimbo.... BooYah!!</Msg><Username>chic_getthedoor</Username><Timestamp>1366453914465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366455333957-6</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought the Apr 26 805 calls @ 2.35 and had plan on holding until Monday but they went over 7.00 and sold at 6.30. Remember these calls were over seven prior to earnings announcement and GOOG had to go up 34 points before it got back to 7.00 after earnings. It is a tough game and it takes a lot guts or stupidity to play. Some days you eat the bear and other days the bear eats you. Yesterday some of us ate the bear and others gotten eaten. Jusy my observation.</Msg><Username>elrrambu</Username><Timestamp>1366455333957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 06:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366467802894-7</Id><Title>The beginning of the end for Goog?</Title><Msg>So, Goog just reported earnings for the most recent quarter, and "missed" on rev's, generally considered the most important guide of the quality and consistency of the earnings. They handily beat on the eps, but after a quick look it's easy to see why... The eps beat on a mysterious charge that is typically spread out over the full year and in this case it was pulled forward to take the entire amount in the most recent quarter, strange. They had a crazy low tax rate that is likely to be higher in the current quarter. They benefitted globally from the weak dollar, but in a race to devalue currency that could become a head-wind in the current quarter as all other nations are now playing the game in a race to the bottom. Finally, cost cutting helped. Like any big bank or multi-national these days the goog cut costs and improved the eps, great. The cost per click (CPC) stays on it's trend down, margins continue to shrink, and Motorolla remains an anchor around the neck of the company there are a few things to be worried about. The move to mobile is going to sap much of the money from ads that goog currently receives as the effectiveness of those ads is dramatically worse than traditonal online ads. The only thing making money for goog is the search, and it's an amazing, incredible, marvelous, and wonderful cash cow. It does make a ton of money, but it's making less and less each year on a CPC basis and margins will continue to be squeezed. At this point there is no innovation of any kind coming from goog (or apple) so there really is no propellant to drive the pps higher. Google glass and the drivers less car are more gimmicks than the future of innovation. Without the 'next big thing' on the horizon and with numbers that are eroding it's hardly time to pile into this bloated stock. Perhaps we run to 900, heck, we might even sniff $1000 as several analysts have suggested? The law of big numbers will catch goog like others before it... G/L trading~</Msg><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467802894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366467909632-8</Id><Topic><Title>Undervalued Google worth $1,100.00 a share!</Title><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1365715436546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might run, but down it will go... analysts just talking their book to make a buck. Law of big numbers drags it down eventually, not to mention the lack of innovation and no more "one time charges" to prop up the eps.</Msg><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467909632</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468070598-9</Id><Topic><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366371214572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, "nothing matters" when it's negative. Keep your head in the sand and you will lose it all. That's a funny reply. Stock may pop, but once they see that the emperor has no clothes on this pig will dive (again).</Msg><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366468070598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468292134-10</Id><Topic><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366371214572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree 100% with points above. They miss on the most improtant metrics and analysts "upgrade" the stock to make a buck. Nothing on the horizon to keep this stock going up. The most recent quarter was basically a lot of fuzzy math and accounting tricks to "dress up the numbers" and for the most part the people fell for it. My expectation is that they bomb the next quarter and the stock collapses back down (again). It might be from a $1000 starting point, and this isn't Enron, but it's a lot of smoke and mirrors right now for (still) being a 1 trick pony, with a pony that's getting tired of doing this dance for all these years. Mobile will kill google earnings just like so many other companies...</Msg><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366468292134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366468599755-11</Id><Topic><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366371214572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 07:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you say "apple is going to have declining revs over the next year or two and goog will be growing over 20% yoy and maybe more"</Msg><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366468599755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366469054696-12</Id><Topic><Title>The beginning of the end for Goog?</Title><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467802894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, Google is seeking mobile growth more then pc</Msg><Username>tyler.fetty</Username><Timestamp>1366469054696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366474866848-13</Id><Topic><Title>Google has the brightest future of any company. (Android, Search ads, etc.). $1,000 very soon</Title><Username>biobum</Username><Timestamp>1366379693678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:54:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exciting week ahead!</Msg><Username>biobum</Username><Timestamp>1366474866848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:21:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366474966642-14</Id><Topic><Title>Undervalued Google worth $1,100.00 a share!</Title><Username>kingcuffs</Username><Timestamp>1365715436546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:23:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe higher...</Msg><Username>biobum</Username><Timestamp>1366474966642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366476629448-15</Id><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Msg>- Miss on the revenue. - Miss on cost per click (fell 4%). - Miss on Motorola Mobility revenue ($1B vs $1.51B last quarter). - Tax paid only 8% compared to 18% in previous quarter.</Msg><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366476629448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366481562299-16</Id><Topic><Title>4 main negative factors in recent earning.</Title><Username>europe_and_usa</Username><Timestamp>1366476629448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:50:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like the market disagrees. Up nicely yesterday.</Msg><Username>valueinvestor66</Username><Timestamp>1366481562299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 14:12:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366486978594-17</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i bought 790 @ 2 and closed at 10.50.....but those were lot cheaper than 2 ....</Msg><Username>tendulrocks</Username><Timestamp>1366486978594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366487080705-18</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep...i rode those calls ...check my aapl MB posts on that day</Msg><Username>tendulrocks</Username><Timestamp>1366487080705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366488077950-19</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you followed goog u knew 800 was minimum for friday...</Msg><Username>tendulrocks</Username><Timestamp>1366488077950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 16:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493248332-20</Id><Topic><Title>The beginning of the end for Goog?</Title><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467802894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How could earnings beat if they took an entire amount of a charge that should be spread over the entire year. That does not make sense and would decrease earnings. I really don't agree with much of what you said other than to say that at some point the law of large numbers comes into play. Dollar is moving up not down. Innovation at google is probably better than most companies in the space. Monetizing most of it has not been as good as it should. But highly likely if they do hit something big it will be a money maker. Look at the driverless car. If that is patented that could be a major game changer. I could see big things from google glass.</Msg><Username>pricewowens</Username><Timestamp>1366493248332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493417455-21</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just figured out how to capture options from .02 to $7! LMAO!!!!!</Msg><Username>ttran906</Username><Timestamp>1366493417455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366500257286-22</Id><Topic><Title>795 calls trades as low as .02 today, now almost 7.00</Title><Username>demsarewhack</Username><Timestamp>1366397612110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:53:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those options were very expensive before earnings. I learned my lesson with OTMs, have decimated my account trading them. Sticking to ATMs from now on, that's if I have guts or get stupid once again. I'll watch action on NFLX and AAPL next week, just watching</Msg><Username>zbc407</Username><Timestamp>1366500257286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:24:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366505260447-23</Id><Title>Next week predictions?? I think it is headed towards all time high's</Title><Msg>Results are pretty awesome and WallStreet seems to like all their gigantic bets.. Even one clicks..google to stratosphere...</Msg><Username>happyorcl</Username><Timestamp>1366505260447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 20:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366510137362-24</Id><Topic><Title>The beginning of the end for Goog?</Title><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467802894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in terms of point of sales, mobile is better. in terms of view frequency of Ad, laptops and iPads are better place to dig. so, how to compromise these two attributes in marketing, impression or action? a product must impress a cosnumer for action. here is a little hint how to link these two together, if you stare a web page for one minute, related product info is sent to your cell phone and ready for action. Cupons, stores, driving directions, WEB site, and deal comparisons are at your hand. This shows a move from imou onepression to action. Every phone call you made is analyzed for certain mechaindise and goods to be adertised in your bigger screen possession, say pswowo c or laptop. Your wife might need a pair of shoes. Your daughter might need airplane ticket for a volleyball tournament in west coast. These two events show how Ad flow from small device to the bigger one for details and comarisons.</Msg><Username>after8before12</Username><Timestamp>1366510137362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366510321064-25</Id><Topic><Title>The beginning of the end for Goog?</Title><Username>soonersof_ou</Username><Timestamp>1366467802894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:23:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(continued) of cause, we are not there yet. but this is the killer app.</Msg><Username>after8before12</Username><Timestamp>1366510321064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 22:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>