<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-31"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343708451000-1</Id><Title>How would romney try to run(ruin) the country?</Title><Msg>I believe in capitalism and have no problem with people acquiring wealth but I object to how some of them acquire their wealth. Romney's job at Bain was to increase the wealth of his already wealthy investors. But he achieved that by loading divisions with debt, selling bonds to outside investors (including state pension funds), bankrupting the debt burdened division and sending jobs offshore. Money from bond sales and borrowed money was paid to the wealthy Bain investors as dividends. They walked away with millions while workers lost jobs, pensions, and benefits. State pension funds are still suffering today because of those bond purchases - not because of union contracts! Creditors were left with unpaid invoices for goods and services so they lost a bundle, maybe some of those businesses failed as a result. But Romney succeeded in making money for Bain investors. He cannot do that with the U.S. government. He can't load Virginia with debt and then close it down and divide the remaining money among the rest of the nation. If a hurricane devastates North Carolina, Romney can't fire them and tell them we can't invest any more money in the state. That's how he succeeded at creating wealth. How will he run the country?</Msg><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343708451000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343735429000-2</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what I thought you'd say. It's the typical DemocRAT response when they've been called out. Good luck to ya.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343735429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 07:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343740984000-3</Id><Title>Red - Premarket</Title><Msg>Does not bode well for ebay. For any tech coming for that matter. Overpriced, and these managers know it. October is just around the corner, and this year, people will really be cautious about being in this market. Too many manipulators out there.</Msg><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1343740984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343744297000-4</Id><Title>Good Morning Fellow Ebayers</Title><Msg>Ebay has lost thier mind! We closed our store and are doing more Craigslist less Ebay That's what Ebay wants that's what Ebay gets Besides Ebay owns part of Craigslist and the ZERO fees I pay them Ebay gets 25% of ~ ROTLMAO</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343744297000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343745018000-5</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! You are calling me out? GEE! Thanks. "Rafalca, the Romney's Olympics-bound dressage horse, nets the family a $77,000 tax credit, $2,000 of which, according to Current's calculations, is for what they spent on health care for the horse. The average American family only spends $1,557 a year on health care." Read the provided link or get a DEMOCRAT to read it for you. http://scientopia.org/blogs/drugmonkey/2012/07/12/wait-full-stop-ann-romneys-horse-nets-them-a-77000-tax-credit/</Msg><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343745018000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343745257000-6</Id><Title>Was there a downgrade this AM?</Title><Msg>very very weak today</Msg><Username>robtri2</Username><Timestamp>1343745257000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343745434000-7</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dribbles, you and Middy don't see eye to eye when it comes to politics ~ LOL I would rather DIE then vote for Obama! ! ! The $77,000 horse could do a better job than Obama has. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343745434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343745847000-8</Id><Title>EBAY continues to plunge - no bid</Title><Msg>Someone is getting out...</Msg><Username>robtri2</Username><Timestamp>1343745847000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343746204000-9</Id><Title>EBAY---Getting Creamed</Title><Msg>if trend continues and any bad news we could see Ebay at $ 39-$40 in days paypal being challenged?????? by apple</Msg><Username>oldpalos</Username><Timestamp>1343746204000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343746443000-10</Id><Title>Crash on AAPL news</Title><Msg>AAPL taking over EBAY biz with new site.</Msg><Username>robtri2</Username><Timestamp>1343746443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343746558000-11</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>johns_joint, "I would rather DIE then vote for Obama! ! !" You sound potentially dangerous. It appears you would definitely be a candidate for the "crackometer" as soon as romneys people get it perfected. Have you bought a bunch of guns &amp; ammo recently??</Msg><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343746558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343746810000-12</Id><Topic><Title>I saw this on CNBC</Title><Username>kelcismp990</Username><Timestamp>1343742649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SPAM SPAM SPAM SPAM</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343746810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:00:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343746866000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Is eBay about to plunge? I think I have figured it out</Title><Username>georgiannawisnoski</Username><Timestamp>1343741060000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:24:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DAILY SPAMMER - MALWARE LINKS</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343746866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343747034000-14</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Have you bought a bunch of guns &amp; ammo recently??" Just the opposite! I gave away all my guns except for a few 22's and gave away over 5000 rounds of ammunition of which most of it was .308, .223 &amp; 12 ga. #8 lead shotgun shells. I have no need for firearms where I'm at. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343747034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343747417000-15</Id><Title>If Apple had Amazons P/E it would be valued at $12,000 a Share</Title><Msg>If we gave Apple a P/E of 286 it's stock price would be over $12,000 a share and have a market cap of $10 Trillion Dollars</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343747417000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343747504000-16</Id><Title>UP IN THE PM</Title><Msg>putt says...</Msg><Username>forputt</Username><Timestamp>1343747504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343747974000-17</Id><Title>Buy on the dip!!!!</Title><Msg>Buy on the dip!!!! All smart investers do.</Msg><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343747974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343748744000-18</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, dear. I see you need more schooling. Let me see if I can put this in terms you might understand. 1. In order to claim a DEDUCTION (refer to my original response regarding the difference between a deduction and a credit which you keep calling it) on a business you must own a business to begin with. 2. The Romney's did not run a horse business (or hobby). In other words, the Romney's did not make any money nor did they attempt to make any money on that horse in 2010 (the year you claim they received a 77G tax "credit". 3. Q1: How can you receive a tax "credit" (or deduction for that matter) on something you never used to make money in the first place? 4. Q2: If you don't have a business do you think the fed. gov. is going to give you a $77G tax credit on the loss of said nonexistent business? 5. Q3: I agree Obama's policies are absurd but how f'in stupid do you think he allows the IRS to be? 6. The Romney's did not attempt to make any money on that hobby horse therefore did not qualify for nor receive a tax "credit" (or deduction). 7. If the Romney's ever decide to use the horse for business income they will then qualify for a tax deduction on any losses or pay taxes on any profit from the venture. Profit - Expenses = profit or loss. See how that works? 8. I have no intention of clicking on your DemocRATic links for the twisted version of the facts. It's not necessary.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343748744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343749094000-19</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Psssssst Johnie Osborne, that isn't the Man you are always so g@yly and sickly obsessed over! Do try to contain yourself and do try to die. The world, this board, and obviously your ignored heroin craving baby momma daughter and neglected Grand baby Dime Bag sure don't need you.</Msg><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343749094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343749261000-20</Id><Topic><Title>I would hate to be short on Ebay Tuesday</Title><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343676775000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:32:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes pumper, I sure do hate being short today but somebody besides ebay insider management needs to stuff the lost value of this company's "stock" into its pocket where it will do the world some better good. Anyways, I see you've been a very busy busy busy little pumper. Do you even get paid a penny a post? I bet not, you just pump because you're a loser who melts in your other many many IDs.</Msg><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343749261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343749761000-21</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ms Midnite, Love ya and I always will, and understand the differences you explain in the tax code, thank you, and I'm not that other ID but you're still arguing on the wrong side of history, as the vast majority of most Americans don't have a 77K horse, and the vast majority of Americans don't get a 77K tax credit on anything, and frankly the vast majority of Americans don't even make 77k a year period. And the vast majority of Americans don't make their money speculating with government loans to bankrupt businesses, fire workers and park their investment profits in overseas tax shelters while they ride a fine horse. I may not be your favorite cup of tea as I am a radical socialist and dislike the Dems for going along with RepubliCON fascism, and upping the use of preditor drones (even on US soil) and bailing out banks that should have failed. Other than that, keep your good posts going and keep your powder dry. The tree of liberty is mighty thirsty right now. Mighty thirsty.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343749761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343749974000-22</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey sharpeyed Dribbles! Middy knows a Texas democrat when see reads one! Can't hide behind that. . . PS: He's YOUR Obama, your people voted him in!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343749974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343750461000-23</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has been a likable President but has only served the bankersters and the out of control War On Terror myth. But everyone can clearly see you, John Osborne, are an idiot's idiot, a grandfather child playing at talking to adults when you're simply trapped in your "everyone is all one poster" nonsense. I am a democrat, or from Texas, the way you're a successful father and grand father. Old idiots need to crawl away. The world needs intelligence like never before. Why bark and let the world see you're a loser's loser? An idiot's idiot. A failure in all ways.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343750461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343750548000-24</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I cannot find a copy of the only tax return Romney had the temerity to release, but it appears from reports he claimed deductions for the business of whatever in the amount of $77,000. The loss could be challenged as a hobby as you imply and then it would be up to the Romney's to demonstrate a profit motive. Going to the Olympics is not a profit motive in itself, but selling an Olympic horse might be their ultimate payoff and excuse for a profit motive. Such an argument could be made, but I do not know if it would play well among the public. You are right that the loss is a deduction and not a credit and at Romney's tax bracket may have only saved him 12 to 20 thousand dollars. Still, that is one heckuva loss to claim and it insults the majority of American people who can only look in awe at what is spent on that horse. The link you didn't want to follow is probably one of the ones that compares what the average American spends on health care and transportation and finds it less than Horse Romney.</Msg><Username>flyktning_alltid</Username><Timestamp>1343750548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343752028000-25</Id><Topic><Title>-Video Update</Title><Username>randolphhuw621</Username><Timestamp>1343745431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's awesome.</Msg><Username>griswoldyeo372</Username><Timestamp>1343752028000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343752973000-26</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;&lt;"The link you didn't want to follow is probably one of the ones that compares what the average American spends on health care and transportation and finds it less than Horse Romney."&gt;&gt;&gt; Romney apologizes for being wealthy and taking full advantage of any tax breaks he is privy to. According to Obama that is a crime in this country. (The Obama's AGI the year before he took office was $3 Mill. shhhh) On a final note, I just want to give a shout out to whoever it was that built my business. I can't thank you enough whoever you are!</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343752973000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343754074000-27</Id><Topic><Title>-Video Update</Title><Username>randolphhuw621</Username><Timestamp>1343745431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great move</Msg><Username>ddeneeim205</Username><Timestamp>1343754074000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343754871000-28</Id><Topic><Title>-Video Update</Title><Username>randolphhuw621</Username><Timestamp>1343745431000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UGLY SPAM MALWARE LINKS - IGNORE</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343754871000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343755016000-29</Id><Topic><Title>eBay is showing historic technical movement</Title><Username>kalliehumbel</Username><Timestamp>1343749646000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:47:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UGLY SPAM MALWARE LINKS -IGNORE</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343755016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343757356000-30</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ms Midnite, again, love ya even though we're on opposite political teams. Overall thanks for trying to keep the intelligent discourse (or as one of our most clever posters put it "intelligent disc horse") going inspite of the trailer park boys, but please stick to the facts as your team is most sadly in need of that. First, Romney hasn't apoligised for his wealth, there are a slew of quotes where he and his wife rub peoples faces in it. And any apology is not going to get those folk their jobs, companies and towns back. Obama is not saying that's a crime. Obama is a Wall Street lapdop and is not trying to criminalize wealth. Even if he rolls back some of the obscene tax breaks the rich get (which he really does not have the heart for) even ill gotten wealth like the Romney's won't be criminalized. Personally, I'd like to see people who bankrupt companies and fire workers and the rich who say they need wealth to create jobs (only in china) and offshore their casino winnings be treated like drug lords and mobsters. Everything seized for the good of a sinking nation. And finally, those who watch more than Fox "News" know Obama's entire quote was (to paraphase) 'if you have a successful business, you didn't build it by yourself, there were your parents, the folks who built the roads and bridges, the government that built the internet' and we pay our taxes to pay that back, and pay it forward. He forgot to say 'and the Indians we stole the land from' and our children to our great granchildren we stole the resources from', but you get the idea. Successful business men did not create their wealth simply by being smart or working hard, especially in the new guilded age of vulture capitalism, preditory lending and offshoring everything. Neither candidate is truly addressing the gross inequalities, but the whole "trickle down" theory has long been discredited as it all (the jobs, the businesses, the schools and services 'trickled down' to China, Guam and other now successful economies. Personally if I ripped off my community and hid the money in the Cayman's they'd seize it and jail me. Most people just want the laws enforced equally.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343757356000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:55:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343757752000-31</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"(or as one of our most clever posters put it "intelligent disc horse")" Patting yourself on the back again! ~ LOL Tell us, if you don't vote for Romney or Obama who should one vote for? enlighten us. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343757752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343757763000-32</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! It looks like John Osborne z50com (5000 rounds of ammo) is a danger to herself and the community, and making anti-Obama statements. Maybe Cypress dodged a Batman killer of their own here, and I bet the game is over and The Joker is still wild. What an unfortunately revealing post there John Osborne. And seriously, a horse as President? Only a horse's hind parts would say something that ignorant in public. Why does your Fox News types hate our President so badly?</Msg><Username>aig.elike</Username><Timestamp>1343757763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343757878000-33</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I kept my powder dry, and I had lots of it. But now days I need no more than a few hundred rounds of 22's Your the one Homeland Security is WATCHING ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343757878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343757996000-34</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't have other IDs to pat on the back, and don't need your ignorant opinions. I don't need to discuss matters of importance with a grand father child, a 12 year daily board troll and a danger to the community at large. Bye. Sweat your ignorance is silence because your words only reveal it publicly.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343757996000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343758521000-35</Id><Title>Major Support at $ 43.44</Title><Msg>if $ 43.44 broken then Ebay will test $ 42.00 or less and if this market gets crapped on---EBAY could be $ 40.78</Msg><Username>b.coogan</Username><Timestamp>1343758521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:15:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343758893000-36</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Homeland Security isn't worried about me moron. You lies will always remain just that: lies. But you are being monitored by federal, state and private entities as a 12 year melting daily board troll, obsessing on a chat board while destroying his own family, stockpiling 5000 rounds while hating Obama may do anything. Anything!</Msg><Username>aig.elike</Username><Timestamp>1343758893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343761384000-37</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>midnite.oas..., typical GREEDY republiCON lip service. IF you have a business &amp; IF it is successful which I doubt because you spend too much time on these message boards but for the sake of debate we will play like you do so KEEP ALL YOUR BS LIP SERVICE AND GIVE THE EMPLOYEE'S A RAISE SO THEY CAN AT LEAST AFFORD THE BASIC NECESSITIES OF LIVING.</Msg><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343761384000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343761890000-38</Id><Title>Where is the buyback???</Title><Msg>What are they going to do with all the bond sales if they said they are not buying any company?</Msg><Username>ilovefed</Username><Timestamp>1343761890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343765127000-39</Id><Title>EBAY move is over folks</Title><Msg>This one is dead money. You need to be out. it's over.</Msg><Username>robtri2</Username><Timestamp>1343765127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343765434000-40</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can understand a liberal viewpoint, I hold some liberal viewpoints, but your slobbering love affair with the green brained communist president is pure idiocy. The despised MadBozo would be a better president. Your statement is a joke and far removed from brainy discourse -- hey idiot, GUAM is part of the United States. "Neither candidate is truly addressing the gross inequalities, but the whole "trickle down" theory has long been discredited as it all (the jobs, the businesses, the schools and services 'trickled down' to China, Guam and other now successful economies." GUAM -- LMFAO!!! What an idiot! You are one of those clueless idiots Jay Leno interviews on JayWalking.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343765434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343770400000-41</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As much as I agree with you Sharpey, up to this post, your point can be made with a better attitude, being less personally derogatory, and being less emotional. Let the fact speak for themselves as I dount you'll convert many true believers. Just my opinion.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343770400000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343770864000-42</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY move is over folks</Title><Username>robtri2</Username><Timestamp>1343765127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just had a blow out quarter, has had upgrades with more to come, paypal is killing it, auction site not far behind. You don't have clue. Do your homework.</Msg><Username>retirewithsiri</Username><Timestamp>1343770864000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343771093000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Major Support at $ 43.44</Title><Username>b.coogan</Username><Timestamp>1343758521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And out of nowhere come the bears just because there was some profit taking. Meanwhile ebay is still making new highs. Calling all investors, don't pay any attention to trading junkies. GLTA Investors</Msg><Username>retirewithsiri</Username><Timestamp>1343771093000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343771323000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Buy on the dip!!!!</Title><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343747974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally, a smart guy on this board. Attention all: Ebay is up almost 50% this year... Long and Strong is the only way to make money on this stock. GLTA Investors</Msg><Username>retirewithsiri</Username><Timestamp>1343771323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343771407000-45</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agqut, I contend that you can't read and have no reading comprehension skills if you think I have much love, much less slobbering love for the current preditor-drone-in-chief, but I've never really considered you part of the 'intelligent discourse' crowd. And Obama is as much a communist as you are a mentally well balanced nice polite guy, but at least we both can agree that Professor Madbezos would be a great President. The 'trickle down' theory has long been completely discredited in every way shape and form. Even when the banksters failed, they did not ask the rich benficiaries of their failed investment strategies to kick in, they did ask their massively rich CEOs to be responsible for the failures they caused, they did not let the supposed 'free market' decide, they had to have 'trickle up' and stole their losses from the American taxpayer. And PS: Guam is part of America only for the reason to stamp "Made in USA" on their sweat shop slavery made items. That was a Newt Gingrich fiasco. There a millions of jobless Americans that would like to make something and stamp 'Made in USA; on it but Newt, Romney, and frankly, Obama, are pretty much silent on that. Who knew "Go west young man" meant to China? This nation's leaders gave it away. Gave it all away.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343771407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343772515000-46</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So sad. -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1343772515000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343772552000-47</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why so many ids? -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1343772552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343772606000-48</Id><Title>Now more than ever buy aapl. Split soon?</Title><Msg>aapl remains the only safe haven. -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1343772606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343773520000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Major Support at $ 43.44</Title><Username>b.coogan</Username><Timestamp>1343758521000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:15:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not a short--I have held since Ebay was 36.78, and made some nice money after earnings released BUT this stock is TOTALLY manipulated and profits you thought you had can be erased in minutes with MM"S so looking at the charts is important and if the news is bad wednesday or thursday---EBay will get creamed</Msg><Username>oldpalos</Username><Timestamp>1343773520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343773633000-50</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad we can talk about this freely &amp; openly. :) I was being sarcastic when I said Romney apologizes for being wealthy. Sarcasm is my second language and I need to be more aware of how it can be taken literally. My belief is wealth is nothing to be ashamed of or apologize for. That is unless the wealth is obtained by shady means. I don't know how all those offshore dealings work so I can't comment on that but I don't condone tax evasion if that's what it comes down to. Below is the precise Obama quote on business. Here is the YouTube video to listen to as you read along. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YKjPI6no5ng "If you were successful, somebody along the line gave you some help. There was a great teacher somewhere in your life. Somebody helped to create this unbelievable American system that we have that allowed you to thrive. Somebody invested in roads and bridges. If you've got a business, you didn't build that. Somebody else made that happen. The Internet didn't get invented on its own. Government research created the Internet so that all the companies could make money off the Internet." Was Obama talking about teachers? roads &amp; bridges? the internet? or was he talking about businesses? Obama now claims he was saying businesses didn't build roads and bridges. LOL It's pretty clear to me that he said it exactly as he meant it. He was talking about and discrediting American businesses (he always has) and I take issue with that. By the way the government didn't build the internet. Another Obama lie is his claim that the borders have never been more secure when the opposite is true according to border officials. Have you heard about this. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xb2_3R6oHSQ If you or I did what that alien did we'd be thrown in jail. Boarder officials have been told they will lose their job if they don't let in the democrats...er...I mean "dreamers".</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343773633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343773744000-51</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I rest my case -- you are truly an idiot! "And PS: Guam is part of America only for the reason to stamp "Made in USA" on their sweat shop slavery made items. That was a Newt Gingrich fiasco." You dummass, Guam is a territory of the United States, the people of Guam are United States citizens. Jay Leno needs you clueless dumb basstards to make fun of, and you proudly strut your ignorance here. Hey, where is your hero Keith Olberman?</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343773744000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343774786000-52</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor 'tard who thinks Sully rules anything! You see what you want to see. You'll never be part of the intelligent discussions. Pumping Apple when you can't even afford am apple to eat! Priceless!</Msg><Username>aig.elike</Username><Timestamp>1343774786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343775449000-53</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;&lt;"KEEP ALL YOUR BS LIP SERVICE AND GIVE THE EMPLOYEE'S A RAISE SO THEY CAN AT LEAST AFFORD THE BASIC NECESSITIES OF LIVING"&gt;&gt;&gt; Shut up and Pay, is that it? Spoken like a true DemocRAT. Gimme, gimme, gimme. I'll let whoever it was that built my business give out the raises. LOL.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343775449000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343775487000-54</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I don't agree with you but at least this is intelligent "disc horse" LOL! I've seen the speech and know what he meant. Fox "News" veiwers got the edited line and thus the tizz was thrown. But none of us got here on our own. The present day rich want to break the social contract. It's been shown they don't re-invest in America and create jobs. It's even been proven they're holding off and sitting on cash 'til after the election so the economy will be worse for Obama. They are sick he's black but he's only half black, so they should be only half sick, and what should really anger them is preditors (a wussy way to fight) and preditors over the US. I do not agree that Obama is an alien either, neither foreign or space alien. But I know Fox "News" crowd does. And it's funny they call him a communist when he's given the military and banksters everything they ever want. I do agree the borders aren't secure but technically our nation's enemies are in seats of power. The families that sneak over here seem to be pretty nice and stable on a personal level. This is a nation of immigrants after all. Anyways, I don't have easy solutions, but would like to see almost every politician thrown out, and replaced with regular people who pledged to ignore lobbyists, and I'd like to see corporations declared non-persons again and the Supreme Court along with them. We were supposed to be a nation of checks and balances, but criminals are cashing huge checks while undoing any balance.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343775487000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343775657000-55</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have to "rest your case" because you don't have facts and only get personally angry when your foolishness is shown. If we have any strawmen needing attacked with hateful innuendo and slander we'll have Jay Leno call you Agqut.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343775657000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343775740000-56</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 'green on the brain' president is the most depressing president ever, and we all thought Jimmy Carter's malaise mantra was depressing. Jug Ears is a downer of a president, he makes feel guilty because I breath in oxygen and breath out toxic earth destroying carbon dioxide. He makes me feel guilty for using his roads to haul my crops to market, guilty for drilling a hole in the ground to extract his water so I can live, guilty for dumping my waste into a septic system, guilty because my cows pass gas into the air and defecate indifferently upon Jug Ear's soil, guilty when I cash my Marcellus Shale royalty check ..... Then there is my neighbor on welfare, free cars(ostensibly to find work), free cell phones, exemption from property taxes(as long as family continue to live on the property), free cell phones (which assisted their friends to steal $2000.00 worth of scrap steel from me), free air conditioning (ostensibly for medical reasons), free on home delivery of medical services (try getting your medical supplies delivered to your door in a private company white van), liberal food stamps which buy some high class food(how do I know? because their trash blows onto my property), free sewage disposal(bad septic system which overflows onto my property), electric service assistance, heating assistance (yes I notice their windows open in cold weather). Yet these are the people Jug Ears Community Organizer loves and respects while despising those that employ intelligence, hard work, tenacity and take a huge personal risk to succeed building a business. There is no doubt where Green Brain Jug Ears is coming from, he sees himself as a king and all things belong to him, your existence depends on his benevolence. Biggest downer president ever, Jug Ears is depressing the whole country.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343775740000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343778088000-57</Id><Title>Obama Best President Ever</Title><Msg>If not for Obama I wouldn't have lost my home of 14 years and been able to buy a BIGGER nicer home in a better neighborhood. I'm on top of the world LIFE IS GOOD pssst: No need to vote for him his job is over. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343778088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343781190000-58</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By the way the government didn't build the internet." The genesis of the internet is attributed to the Defense Department which provided the funds for researchers to invent a technology for large main frame computers at university and defense research centers to communicate with each other. http://www.computermuseum.li/Testpage/99HISTORYCD-ARPA-History.HTM You are technically correct the government didn't actually build out the internet as we know it today, but the Defense Department's research efforts established the technology. If you can show me where I am wrong, I'd be pleased to be corrected.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343781190000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343783088000-59</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought it was a group at UCLA.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343783088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343784681000-60</Id><Topic><Title>I saw this on CNBC</Title><Username>kelcismp990</Username><Timestamp>1343742649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Logical Thinking</Msg><Username>bonexqm278</Username><Timestamp>1343784681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:31:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343786091000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Best President Ever</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343778088000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:41:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're going to blame Obama because your were a daily 247 board troll for 12 long years? Seriously? Wasn't Bush the blame through most of that time? No need to listen to your lies and idiocy, your life is over.</Msg><Username>aig.elike</Username><Timestamp>1343786091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343787888000-62</Id><Topic><Title>TBOW</Title><Username>cane5</Username><Timestamp>1343408276000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 12:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump,,,,,</Msg><Username>doccjcj</Username><Timestamp>1343787888000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:24:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343788373000-63</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we democrats are most definitely the "fair &amp; balanced" party. We stand for working AMERICAN families being paid a living wage so they can afford such luxuries as education, health insurance, medications, food, shelter, clothing, decent transportation, utility service's, a pension and OH yes! a vacation every now &amp; then! Now we are not asking for a "gubment" hand out like corporate welfare recipients such as the romney's get to pay for a HORSE, we just want the basic's. Don't you want to join us??</Msg><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343788373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343788787000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Buy on the dip!!!!</Title><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343747974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:19:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How low is the dip? $10??</Msg><Username>m13monkeys</Username><Timestamp>1343788787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343788977000-65</Id><Title>The only way to make $$ on Ebay is.....</Title><Msg>SHORT!</Msg><Username>m13monkeys</Username><Timestamp>1343788977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343789708000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay removed negative feedbacks for crooked sellers</Title><Username>m13monkeys</Username><Timestamp>1320647151000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-11-07 01:25:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ebay did it again. Removed all of the negative feedbacks I gave to crooked sellers in last couple months.</Msg><Username>m13monkeys</Username><Timestamp>1343789708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>