<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346391161000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Maybe $40 Wouild Be A Level Ebay Could Keep?</Title><Username>id.dejour</Username><Timestamp>1346344511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you care as much as I do? 15% haircut, very, very unlikely.</Msg><Username>facts_are_facts_are</Username><Timestamp>1346391161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 01:32:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346391208000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Read this new report on eBay</Title><Username>joanrohl</Username><Timestamp>1346338711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing of interest.</Msg><Username>facts_are_facts_are</Username><Timestamp>1346391208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 01:33:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346418840000-3</Id><Title>ALERT: Watch Video Now!</Title><Msg>I am thrilled! It clearly shows they understand the technical aspects of the stock market and are accurate in predicting its future direction. There videos is clear, to the point, straight forward, and NO hype. I came upon this site and decided to give it a try. They have a terrific service. Being able to make money again is certainly a great feeling. Watch there free video. WWW.TECHNICALINVESTOR.INFO</Msg><Username>crystolrobin319</Username><Timestamp>1346418840000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 09:14:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346423763806-4</Id><Title>EBAY MF #$%$</Title><Msg>Look at these fund managers pump this POS up, just to get their options filled. Really Criminal. How do they allow this???</Msg><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1346423763806</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346424177000-5</Id><Title>Good Morning Ebay Investors</Title><Msg>You are being rewarded for being patient. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346424177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:42:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346424293978-6</Id><Title>Yahoo you are SCCCCCCUMMMMM</Title><Msg>A person can't even write out the word SCCCCCUMMMMMM without these idiots changing it to non-readable. What a pathetic attempt at censorship. Not to mention, your new boards SUUUUCCCCCKKKKKKK</Msg><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1346424293978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425140656-7</Id><Title>Break Out day---could touch $ 48 plus</Title><Msg>about time to see breakout--this is a winner--with discover deal this stock could be $ 60 plus</Msg><Username>oldpalos</Username><Timestamp>1346425140656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:59:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425230144-8</Id><Title>See You At $60</Title><Msg>Told you so.</Msg><Username>actor904</Username><Timestamp>1346425230144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425283000-9</Id><Title>Isn't Ebay Just Giving Back Yesterday's Dollar?</Title><Msg>Can you say P U M P? This isn't growth, it's a wildly fluctuating tumor. See this and plan for the D U M P.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346425283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346425446000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't Ebay Just Giving Back Yesterday's Dollar?</Title><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346425283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "dump" to $FIFTY$ is coming sooner than later. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346425446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346425581079-11</Id><Title>Buying For NO reason</Title><Msg>Rigged market, rigged, rigged, rigged. Wallstreet #$%$mm manipulating this just to get their options filled. Everyone knows this is top heavy and ready for a crash. Enjoy Sept you idiottssssss</Msg><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1346425581079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346426876000-12</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry Aghate, Flyktning lost no credibility, nor do I, because we, unlike you and the Rethuglicon party deal in facts, not in outright lies, thinly veiled racism and unsubstantiated opinion based on far right illogical talking points. It's fact: Rethugs, and many Demoncrats, are completely in the pocket of Big Pharma companies. That's why health care (Obamacare, actually a copy of Romneycare) can't get passed (even when single payer or any actually helpful idea is removed from the bill). That's why a certain number of Americans have always been sacrificed anytime Big Pharma has a lame idea, or feels their massive profits about to be checked. America has turned into a backwoods country, which is fine with you and some rednecks, but other countries like Canada, France, Germany, The Netherlands and more, take care of their people. They keep costs down by cutting Big Pharma out, just like we would keep jobs in the US by cutting Tomb Raiders predator capitalists like Romney out of destroying companies for his own short term gain. Romney killed that guy's wife. How many other wives are we going to let him kill? Romney will gut America, sell its assets and lay off and offshore every part of our government to China, because THAT is his only business experience. Ryan is going to put our seniors on the street in boxes (many are already there) while giving us the dopey eyes and telling us he's a Gen X rocker. It's all a giant canard. It's all the Rethugs have this time. They are as empty of ideas ad their hearts are empty of compassion for anyone but themselves. A party too crazed by racism for facts anymore. They will only sucker the rubes. Why do we allow the Rethugs a national spotlight to breed falsehoods and racism like a toxin on the public discourse? You'll vote for neither? I bet you'd vote for a mental patient if it were white. Meanwhile, any thinking person can look at all the speeches at the Rethug Con and tell it's lies, BS, and racism. Why do people who lie and claim they have the country's best interests at heart only do so if the President is white? It's beyond obvious the Rethugs are a party of old haters. on their why out, and it's too bad their isn't a party with a spine to take over and fix things, for the average person, not just thinking of helping the richest all the time. Guess what? After 30 years of "trickle down" it's only trickled into the rich's private offshore accounts. That's a fact. PS: Your nickname for me shows you lost the debate and are spent of ideas and logic. I bet you came up with that as it simply reflects your personal hillbilly hobby.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346426876000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427148000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't Ebay Just Giving Back Yesterday's Dollar?</Title><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346425283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone knows you're not an investor. You're too broke to even raise your children, pay your taxes, or be a contributing member of anything but drug society. Ebay could be at $50 and you still wouldn't make $49 and 99 cents nor the extra penny. You're just a lying pumper who gets off thinking someone out their believes his teenage brained nonsense. Maybe if Romney gets elected he'll bring back work camps for your lazy ilk.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346427148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427150000-14</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"are completely in the pocket of Big Pharma" I have NO heath insurance and I don't buy medicine, I GROW IT. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346427150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427354000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't Ebay Just Giving Back Yesterday's Dollar?</Title><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346425283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least Romney believes in the US Constitution, something Obama threw in the trash. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346427354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427435000-16</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try treating a car wreck victim with your "medicine". Oh wow dude bro'. Rupub or Dem, the Feds are coming for your pot. We can't have anything Big Pharma doesn't provide to alleviate post 911 America's pain. No one would want to smoke anything grown by a daughter neglecting fool anyways. I know pot makes people dumb but you take the cake.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346427435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427513000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't Ebay Just Giving Back Yesterday's Dollar?</Title><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346425283000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean something George W. Bush destroyed and called "A useless piece of paper" and Obama just waltzed in as new corrupt manager and said cool.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346427513000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:38:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427632000-18</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Rupub or Dem, the Feds are coming for your pot" For every plant they take growers plant 10 more. 60% of Americans approve of Medical Marijuana It seems the Fed could care less what the majority in this country want. They know what's good for me &amp; you! ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346427632000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427778000-19</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"but you take the cake" I'll take the layered one Angels Food and Devils Food. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346427778000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:42:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346427877000-20</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you're Devil's food. Just wait and see. You'll see. Eternally.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346427877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:44:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346428143000-21</Id><Title>Read this new report on eBay</Title><Msg>I cant believe what this analyst just told me about eBay. Check it out! http://STOCKCHARTINGSOFTWAREFREE.INFO</Msg><Username>rosamondthetford</Username><Timestamp>1346428143000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429290259-22</Id><Topic><Title>See You At $60</Title><Username>actor904</Username><Timestamp>1346425230144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When did it hit $60? I predicted $50, and haven't seen it hit that yet. Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass</Username><Timestamp>1346429290259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346429401318-23</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo you are SCCCCCCUMMMMM</Title><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1346424293978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:44:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I commend Yahoo on attempting to clean up the language people use on their message boards. Now if they would only ban posters like DRIBBLES from doing so, then this board will be much better place.</Msg><Username>sullyinmass</Username><Timestamp>1346429401318</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:10:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346430189000-24</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"JUG EARS is depressing the spirit off [sic] this country, 4 more years of his idiocy the USA may never recover." Poor babies. People still have to get off their butts and work. I thought that was what you were all about. Funny. "Where you lose credibility is blaming it solely on the republicans." The Democrats could have passed something; most Democrats wanted the US government to be in a stronger position when negotiating its own bill payments. "Your first love JUG EARS could have addressed the cost of drugs in the "Affordable"(facetious context) Care Act -- HE DIDN'T." You are correct and that is one of the many flaws in the bill. He needed to not have the medical establishment in his face or nothing would have passed. The problem with the Republicans is that they were satisfied with health care just the way it was. They didn't see it as perfect, but they didn't have problems getting or keeping insurance and self-interest ruled out any major changes. "I remain pessimistic, I believe this country has to impact the financial concrete wall at a 1000 mile per hour to show people there was actually a financial crisis." You may be right. I think the financial markets have unfinished business with the failing of financial institutions and the drain of legacy programs we can no longer afford. We are likely to have a crisis no matter who is president.</Msg><Username>flyktning_alltid</Username><Timestamp>1346430189000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:23:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346430972000-25</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Your nickname for me shows you lost the debate" -------------- This what you missed it in your communist ravings. I am not debating you, I am demonstrating my contempt for the infantile idiot you are. Matter of fact no one is debating you, you may have started the threads, but no one is engaging in meaningful debate with you. You come off as a girly-man, someone that has never been in the military, someone who's father was a homosexual that married and had children to stay in the closet, someone that is uncomfortable around real men. The handle alphamale is also a cover up for your own homosexuality. Now grab your Astroglide and go pack fudge.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346430972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:36:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346431873758-26</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo you are SCCCCCCUMMMMM</Title><Username>basicknowledge</Username><Timestamp>1346424293978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:44:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It the way of a Socialist future in America... How's that change working out?</Msg><Username>hereislarry</Username><Timestamp>1346431873758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 12:51:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346435980000-27</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor angry Aghate, I agree that the intelligence around here, outside of Flyktning, and frankly sometimes ewven you, is much to be desired but you're clearly destroying every bit of pretty much already damaged credibility by describing yourself at the bottom of your posts, and admitting how you became the world's angriest old redneck. I'm betting you're just a clip and a bad day away, or a lost election, from shooting up some place. Wish I were there to stop you. Maybe another Alpha will. We are legion. You'll see.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346435980000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 13:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440446000-28</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Poor angry Aghate, I agree that the intelligence around here, outside of Flyktning, and frankly sometimes ewven you, is much to be desired but you're clearly destroying every bit of pretty much already damaged credibility by describing yourself at the bottom of your posts, and admitting how you became the world's angriest old redneck. I'm betting you're just a clip and a bad day away, or a lost election, from shooting up some place. Wish I were there to stop you. Maybe another Alpha will. We are legion. You'll see." ---------------------- With every post you add more evidence that you are a functional idiot. And, it becomes more obvious you are a fudge-packing phaggot. Hey I found your Craigslist ad: http://newyork.craigslist.org/mnh/m4m/3228499581.html</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346440446000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346440960000-29</Id><Topic><Title>RNC "We Built This" With 62% Of Public Funds</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346089627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:47:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke angry Aghate, cruising your Craigs g@y pages trying to make your failed straw dog point only shows you're a hound with no bone. Ever. Just chasing your own tail. Look son, you can't build anything with hate, although your GOP tries and tries. But thanks for showing I'm right! That's why I'm the intelligent Alpha and you're some angry Agqut, crusing your g@y pages. Find a pal. Get happy. Just don't ask and don't tell, the way the other board clowns here give themsleves away. Literally and figuratively.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346440960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346442307184-30</Id><Topic><Title>See You At $60</Title><Username>actor904</Username><Timestamp>1346425230144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 11:00:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I Think it is going to $52 after earnings. It will hit $60 in January if not before that.</Msg><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1346442307184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346444296000-31</Id><Title>3rd Party Sellers on Walmart</Title><Msg>I went to walmarts web site looking for an electric smoker. I was surprised to see so many models available only to discover that they were being offered by a third party. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346444296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346444884000-32</Id><Title>FUNcTIONAL IDIOT ANALMALE GETS TOTALLY GAPED!!!</Title><Msg>Yikes. The TRUTH really hurts, eh?!!!!! John whipping and wiping IT up. Good. Now, back to aapl and TEAM WEALTH. -Sully Rules Ebay nearing 50!!!!!! Poor paper trader.</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1346444884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:28:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346445045000-33</Id><Title>John, here is a great pin.</Title><Msg>http://www.amazon.com/Hot-Properties-Get-A-Bong/dp/B005JSZ64S/ref=wl_it_dp_o_pC_S_nC?ie=UTF8&amp;colid=9YIN6URR0PVQ&amp;coliid=I125TO92OT9Q41</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1346445045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346445246000-34</Id><Title>L@@K at ANALMALE all gaped out up here! Gross.</Title><Msg>We don't swing that way over here. Now go gape your Labor Day weekend away! YOU WILL. Always have. Foul. -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1346445246000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:34:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346452984000-35</Id><Title>Incredible H@m@ Over Reactions Show Facts Trump Emotion</Title><Msg>Nothing more needed to be. Agquts very public loss and life long hillbilly humiliation comes through loud and qu**r in his Sully homo ID. Some people lose graciously, not these clowns. I will simply continue on the intelligent discussion high road. True intelligence always trumps evil. Always. Fact.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346452984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>25</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346453633000-36</Id><Title>We Are Writing The Epilogue To The World We Knew</Title><Msg>We Are Writing the Epilogue to the World We Knew by John Atcheson "...While politicians fiddle, the world burns..." Let’s look at the facts: Arctic sea ice hits lowest extent ever measured (and it’s still melting) – check. Hottest winter, spring, summer, year, decade ever measured – check. Most extensive drought in 50 fifty years, and getting worse – check. Worst floods in recorded history – check. Hottest seas in eons – check. Most acidic oceans ever measured – check. Most greenhouse gasses released in a single year – check. Highest sea levels since Pleistocene – check. Most permafrost melted (with record releases of methane) ever measured – check. Massive crop failures and record high food prices – check. Most severe weather events ever recorded – check. Week after week of record heat and drought brought nary a mention of global warming. It was as if people were dropping dead from bullets, but no one mentioned guns – oh wait. Bad analogy. That's actually happening..." "But here’s the thing. We are writing the story, but our children and their children’s children will inhabit..." "Imagine a world where vast regions of an acidic ocean are dominated by jellyfish. A world where tuna, salmon, halibut swordfish, crabs, shellfish, shrimp and the rest of the seafood we take for granted – the primary source of protein for more than a billion people – is virtually gone. Oh, and that might come with a side of oxygen depletion. You know, the stuff we breathe..." "The land? An unending series of drought, flood, fire and famine. Throw in some disease, a little social chaos – with as many as billion climate change refugees desperately swarming the planet by 2050..." "The coasts will be their own special blend of hell on earth. Ports will have to be abandoned. The richer countries might get away with extraordinarily expensive dikes, levies, and pumps for a while, but eventually even they’ll have to be abandoned. Wicked storms will be routine. International trade will become difficult and unreliable. That is, assuming anyone has the social cohesion and political capacity to engage in global trade. This is the epilogue we are writing. It is all but inevitable at this point. What Bill McKibben called, global warming’s terrifying new math. But as terrifying as McKibben’s math is, it doesn’t even consider the increasingly likely horror of methane releases from permafrost and clathrates. Methane just happens to be 72 times as strong a greenhouse gas as carbon dioxide in the short term, and 25 times as strong over the long term. And there are 1.5 trillion tons of carbon trapped in perma-frost and about the same amount in clathrates..." "So yeah, Hell is coming, but it’s coming a lot faster than any predictions you’ve see so far from the scientific community. Now, as we’re closing the book on civilization as we know it, yes, let’s talk about how we can increase the production and use fossil fuels; let’s serve up divisiveness, hate and fear at a time when unity and courage are needed; let’s get guns into the hands of every possible frightened and hate-filled person so we can up the ante on the chaos to come; let’s talk about gutting government – the only force capable of mounting a coherent response to this unfolding tragedy. That’s the real Republican platform. Democrats? They don’t even have a platform. To the extent they do, it seems to be “We’re not quite as bad as them.” And the press? They’re busy hammering away at the Epiloge" www.commondreams.org/view/2012/08/31</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346453633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:53:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>25</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346455039000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Incredible H@m@ Over Reactions Show Facts Trump Emotion</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346452984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will simply continue on the intelligent discussion high road." When you travel down this road would it be possible to do it in a Maserati under your "marketendgaming" ID?</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346455039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346455232000-38</Id><Topic><Title>We Are Writing The Epilogue To The World We Knew</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346453633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been talking to Al Gore again haven't you? Global warming, you think you or me can stop it? ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346455232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346459939000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Incredible H@m@ Over Reactions Show Facts Trump Emotion</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346452984000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:43:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor John Osborne, ebay's failing z50com. No matter what, any time intelligent discourse tries to get started up here, you blather "everyone is all one poster" while you and your pals go publicly hom 0. No wonder you and your pals are failures at everything in life.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1346459939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346461050000-40</Id><Topic><Title>We Are Writing The Epilogue To The World We Knew</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346453633000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 18:53:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John, took your recommendation and saw the movie 2016. Learned that JUG EARS' mentor was the communist Frederick Davis. Davis a card carrying communist party member was considered so dangerous to the USA that he was on the FBI's instant incarceration list in case of national emergency. It was through Davis that JUG EARS received funds from the communist party to attend the prestigious Ivy League Universities. The communist party essentially funded JUG EARS life until he wrote his books and became a millionaire. The other thing is how JUG EARS learned how to employ white guilt to get one over on the country. They talked to JUG EARS brother who was articulate, brother George stated Kenya would be better off today if they hadn't driven out the whites. Reminded me of Rhodesia, the richest country in Africa til they drove out the whites, now Rhodesia is the poorest country in Africa, something ANANMALE would love to see happen to the USA. The only thing ANALMALE isn't considering is that he is white and is being played like a fiddle. The movie presented the conclusion that JUG EARS mission is to diminish the USA. Well you got to give JUG EARS accolades for being successful in wrecking the USA. 4 more years of JUG EARS and the USA will be well on its way to emulating the squalor and poverty of Kenya, he!! we might even see a few million bloated dead white people floating down the Mississippi reminiscent of the genocide that polluted Lake Victoria.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346461050000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>