<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345372701000-1</Id><Title>Zeekrewards Shut Down</Title><Msg>Ponzi Scheme: http://youtu.be/ut9phGrDi3g</Msg><Username>ebayislost</Username><Timestamp>1345372701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 06:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345382168000-2</Id><Topic><Title>"Gone are the days........</Title><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1345301011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:43:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sully does rule. MY ID SAYS IT ALL</Msg><Username>sully_rules</Username><Timestamp>1345382168000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 09:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388225000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"....when it comes the fact of global climate change only being "debate-able" basically because the Koch brothers spend billions for their own "scientists" and Fow "news" is paid to spread their nonsense." ------------------------ A FACT you wish to ignore: Whether global warming is fact or fiction the global warming zealots diminished their case by the emails that surfaced that PROVED (your) scientists openly admitted to fudging the data. Also Al Gore is probably the very worst spokesman for the cause, Gore has a carbon footprint 50 times that of the average American and Gore (and Jugs Ears too) were all set to make billions trading carbon credits. All the while the global warming cultists suck in the bullschit climate change rhetoric, buy their homo lattes in a paper cup and beat themselves on the chest for being the ideal greenie weenie. As usual the truth lies somewhere in between. Personally I believe there is some validity to the global warming issue. The fact that CO2 is at the highest level in 100's of thousands of years is indicative humans may be impacting the climate. What to do about it? In the past century we have burned 1/2 of the worlds supply of fossil fuels, the next 1/2 will be burnt in the next 50 years -- all gone. Burn 'em up , yes there will be an additional impact, but nothing that won't be reversible. Another fact: We will never get China and the emerging third world countries to stop burning so essentially the USA unilaterally stopping burning has zero effect on the inevitable outcome. Yes climate change exists, but it is idiots like you analphabeticmale that go into hyper-zealot mode and close yourself off to debate that cause reasonable people to suspect your motives. I am open to debate on the issue, but you (and your Nancy Pelosi like mind) would be the last person I would consider engaging in a debate. You are the very embodiment of an idiot because you are not a thinker but a cult worshiper of goofy peoples(i.e. Al Gore) idiocy.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345388225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345389423000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention that Al's mode of transportation during his Global Warming tour was via private jet. One has to ponder what caused the last global warming cycle....perhaps dinosaur farts? LOL</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345389423000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:17:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345389708000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A super volcano eruption would release more CO2 than mankind has in all of his history. The planet would warm even if mankind was not present. I do beleave mankind is assisting in this process but not on the scale that most people think. Heck, if the sun farted we could all be burned to a crisp. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345389708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393014000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"perhaps dinosaur farts? LOL" Your attempt at humor missed its mark by a mile. Don't give up your day job. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1345393014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345396628000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make sound points in the middle of your post Agqut, and often in almoist every one of your posts, but you clearly come from the school of "let's get all hateful and denigrate our opponent with personal non-facts and spurious BS remarks" school of debate. I have as much to do with Nancy Pelosi as you do non-emotional, non-hate filled intelligent discourse. PS: Anyone who thinks our world hasn't been irrevokably changed by buring fossil fuel and won't be almost unliveable to even a tiny handful of humans afterwards (and we are beginning that decline already) has no0t been paying attention and thought this pending crisis through. All our energy in this world has been entropy based and that's not all the energy there is but our society's world view is as cut off from actual science as we are civility and manners. People are savage and frankly too many of them are willfully ignorant. Perhaps the experiment needs to fail.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345396628000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345400819000-8</Id><Topic><Title>chart analysis</Title><Username>myronbmb685</Username><Timestamp>1345390336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great analysis!</Msg><Username>leicesterkqd333</Username><Timestamp>1345400819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345403094000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"PS: Anyone who thinks our world hasn't been irrevokably changed by buring fossil fuel" Massive forest fires started by lightning has put more pollution in the air than mankind has since he's been on the face of the Earth. Man will become extinct like every other species has in the past. PS: Enjoy your short stay here ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345403094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426525000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Man will become extinct like every other species has in the past.) We will become extinct! If we do not find other places /planets to live on. Earth is a ticking time bomb on the evolutionary calender. Whether it be a celestial collision, a major volcanic eruption or the human element??? One of those scenarios is going to do us in. Religion might save you....but it won't save the planet. Something to think about, as some of the smartest men on earth are now exploring the Red Planet. Go NASA!</Msg><Username>gewizmeto</Username><Timestamp>1345426525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345428838000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen this documentary before? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o-zM8IQHVzI</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345428838000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>