<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-02"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346597350000-1</Id><Title>Why did Obama Lie about Bin Laden?</Title><Msg>Why would the President lie? http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/08/29/navy-seal-book-raises-questions-about-bin-laden-death-report-says/</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346597350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603136565-2</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo, is this new and improved?</Title><Username>gewizmeto</Username><Timestamp>1346511420185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll bet the genius behind all of this is COLLEGE EDUCATED ~ LOL Maybe even went to Temple U. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346603136565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346603357000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Obama Lie about Bin Laden?</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346597350000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 10:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Why would the President lie?" ---------------------- JUG EARS himself is a lie, a fraud, simply a front nan puppet of his Chicago communist handlers. "Bissonnette also writes disparagingly that NONE of the SEALs were fans of President Barack Obama" -- More importantly, (and I mean extremely importantly) even though the military is comprised of a large percentage of blacks the officer hierarchy despises JUG EARS. That is IMPORTANT because should a national crisis arise and JUG EARS attempts to seize power (like Hitler did) the American military will stop him in a heartbeat. I worried about the power seizing scenario from before JUG EARS election, the man has a sinister quality to him. On JUG EARS visit to West Point shortly after his election any observer could plainly see the polite coldness the Army officers demonstrated. The polite coldness JUG EARS received relieved any concerns of a unfortuitous rise to absolute power. JUG EARS campaign crowds are only 50% of what they were in 2008, there is a palpable lack of enthusiasm for JUG EARS. Only the most shrill whackjobs (i.e. pee down his leg Chris Matthews) of the news media are enthusiastically beating the drums for his reelection. The average Americans are beginning to see JUG EARS sinister quality, while they may not view it in that exact context, they sense there is something very disturbing about JUG EARS. Thank God and the collective common sense of the American people JUG EARS will live out his life in obscure infamy worse than that of Jimmy Carter. Romney is a 100% buffoon(he trained Meg Whitman), but at least he's a patriot and take it to the bank, Romney won't sellout the USA. Read more: http://www.foxnews.com/us/2012/08/29/navy-seal-book-raises-questions-about-bin-laden-death-report-says/#ixzz25KNFPHkz</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346603357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 12:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346607171316-4</Id><Title>eBay's new search page is absolutely awful!</Title><Msg>Just went to eBay's site to list some items for sale and I saw that since last week they updated their search page. To keep it short, the updates are absolutely terrible! They removed sorting functionality and created additional hoops to jump through just to limit a search. Bad move eBay!!</Msg><Username>bergermeister99</Username><Timestamp>1346607171316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 13:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346608882000-5</Id><Title>Auctionbytes Readers are Uninformed</Title><Msg>Here's a real winner http://www.ecommercebytes.com/C/letters/blog.pl?/comments/2012/9/1346556148.html#comments I just typed "Western Union Sign" into ebays search and got results. In the text of these ads have "Western Union" in them. Doesn't Ina verify this stuff before she posts it? ? ?</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346608882000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346609833000-6</Id><Title>EASTWOOD/CHAIR 2012! You Feel Lucky Punks?</Title><Msg>Well do ya? Hven't laughed this hard since Reagan fell asleep wetting himself on TV back in 1984! Eastwood was totally off ther reservation and outed exactly how denile and out to touch the Repubs are these days! They'll say and do anything. Anything! To try to keep a black man from being re-elected yet everything they do just makes their game worse. Convention delayed over Katrina like hurricaine? Check. Massive amounts of money from gambling BS'er Adelstein? Check. No mention of the ongoing endless wars Repubs started with their lies back in the Bush Jr era? Check. No mention or sight of Bush/Cheney whatsoever? Check. Eastwood blaming Obama for Bush Jr's Afgan invasion? Check. Ryans endless lies and Romnney's endless smirks? Check. No policy plan from a guy who guts businesses? Check. But I'd vote for Eastwood and an emprty chair just to have some laughs while The Myans sort this whole mess out! Priceless! Utterly priceless!</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346609833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>37</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346610381000-7</Id><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Msg>Ever since Jimmy Carter helped arm the Taliban against Russia, to Reagan and Ollie North trading weapons to terrorists to arm the Contras (more terrorists) to the fictions of Bush 1, Bill Clinton and especially Bush Junior, and topping it off with Obama's BS about killing a guy who was probably already dead back in 2000, Osama, our former ally, has been demonized and the blame for an attack he couldn't possibly have done: Sept 11. There is no way a guy in cave on a cell phone could get the entire US defense to stand down and let those attacks happen. There are 1000s of architects, engineers and scientists who demand an actual investigation beyond the BS cover story the US government cooked up, so they could have endlessly profitable invasions everywhere. Since almost no truths about Obama have been said why wouldn't there be lies and serious questions about his so called killing? I'm sure Osama will come out with yey another tape explaining his own death properly when they decide which of his 4 different pictures will hold the most traction with the dumbed down American voters. PS: Why are we paying the Taliban to let our supply convoys through? Why are we now helping Al Q in Syria? Hard questions that seem to never get asked by the soft minded.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>30</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346612793000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"has been demonized and the blame for an attack he couldn't possibly have done: Sept 11." Why is it so hard for you to believe Osama organized the Sept. 11th attacks? A single rogue pilot of a small plane could crash it into a baseball stadium during a game and could kill more people than in the twin towers. How could anyone stop that? Answer: They can't. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346612793000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:06:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346615926000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any basic reading from multiple intelligent sites will show what happened that day was not the result of a few people who lived in caves, nor supposedly devout martyrs who did lines of of coke off topless dancer's bellies the nights previous to their attacks. I don't see any need to debate this with someone who won't do their homework and will quickly devolve into fart jokes or "all one poster" nonsense.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346615926000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 15:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>25</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346617334000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're just one of many WACKOS that thing GWB ordered the attack. PURE SILLINESS And those terrorists did not come from caves, they came out of suburban rentals like you live in. . . PS: YOU are all "one poster" a BIG one at that ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346617334000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 16:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346622829000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes you certainly know out Tool Fool! She fake recced your post down 35 times trying to wreck your free speech. If only she'd worked that hard to raise her neglected daughter! ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1346622829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623187000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why am I only seeing 31 recs on that post? Better LOOK into some reading glasses. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346623187000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 17:59:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623360000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You went just like I predicted, thanks for making my point! I drew no conclusion as to who did it, is guilt making you a bit psycho? A real investigation will get to the bottom of why 5 to 7 terror drills were going on that day, several of which involved hijacked planes crashing into the WTC. Odd huh? Those terror drills were known yet Rice said "no one would've imagined that" (Operation Northwoods). Why Bush said he say the first plane hit the tower in TV. Why Bush wasn't hustled to safety when it looked like he may be a target. (read Secret Service protocol). And why defense aircraft were sent over the Atlantic. And why the suspects were almost instantly named on TV heralding a war in Afganistan that had already been prepared for. Facts may make you uncomfortable but they are toxic to a nation and this nation's toxicity has spread world wide. Only a fool would think or good or sustainable. PS, thanks for all the fake recs! LOL!</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346623360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346623911000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you admit to only 31 fake recs? I see well enough to see a Mrs. McGoo melting her day away. LOL! ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1346623911000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625045000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've gone over the deep end. But we've all know this since your first post as CRWATCH2002 Next you'll be telling us the Earth is warming due to mans burning of fossile fuels ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346625045000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625087000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1 star means I hit the target dead on!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346625087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625225000-17</Id><Topic><Title>EASTWOOD/CHAIR 2012! You Feel Lucky Punks?</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346609833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am definitely down shifting and stopping my fine @ss car long enough to vote for Eastwood and The Chair for 2012! Not only will we get a Fistfull Of Dollars and A Few Dollars More, while all the Josie's wail, I know Bronco Billy won't let little shavers like Romney and Obama take away our guns and blondes! And I will sleep better at night knowing a sturdy chair is a heartbeat away from the Presidency. Well played sir. Well played.</Msg><Username>a_car_that_fine</Username><Timestamp>1346625225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625706000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>???? Your post makes no sense but thanks again for proving my point! All you can howl when you're overwhelmed is everyone is all one poster. You're a child. A baby. An infant.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346625706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346625937000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're 40 + negative fake recs shows I toppled your little towers at free fall speed. 'Oh your inhumanity'. LOL@</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346625937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626387000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're &lt;sic&gt; 40 + negative fake recs shows I toppled your little towers at free fall speed. 'Oh your inhumanity'. LOL@" ----------------------- Is that any worse than self-reccing your own posts? Ain't that many communists on this board to give 12 positive recs to everyone one of your Marxist posts within 15 minutes.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346626387000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346626670000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor angry Agqut. Everyones sees you and John fake recced those posts way down, but you can't run, you can't hide. LOL!@ You and John seem so Klan-ish. Was your Daddy black? ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1346626670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 18:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627139000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're a child. A baby. An infant." But smart enough to see YOU in all your ID's PS: Even when I'm stoned I'm smarter than you are ~ LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627139000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627182000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got 1 rec from me and it was 1 star (like always)</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346627288000-24</Id><Title>Hey John &amp; Agqut Free Speech Children</Title><Msg>Hey John and Agqut, my free speech poster children, are you using your free speech and 100s of IDs today to act childish and say you have the free speech right, nay the deep mental illness, to rob others of their free speech? Because Missies you would be wrong!</Msg><Username>flyktning_snitchin</Username><Timestamp>1346627288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627310000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's reccing down his own posts for some strange reason. I guess he thinks reverse psychology will work here somehow ~ Now that's FUNNY</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627310000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627475000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Was your Daddy black?" Chuck, FYI my family is originally from Birmingham and they sat in the FRONT of the bus. Hope that helps. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627478000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor John! "All one poster" is a mental disease, not insight! You're the dumbest person in any room, the pot isn't helping. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1346627478000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346627591000-28</Id><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Msg>Anyone with an IQ of more than 1 can see this Well, except for Charles Kelly aka "The Ebay NARU" Charles, maybe you can start a NARU club for Ebay failures. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346627664000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's still not my name. Let's not let your mental issues and heritage concerns distract from the point that all of the Presidents since '78 have lied about Osama. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1346627664000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346630102000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares about Osama? He got just what he ordered Ahmadinejad is next in line for an American whooping. . . That's if the israelis don't beat us to it.</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346630102000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346632887000-31</Id><Topic><Title>EASTWOOD/CHAIR 2012! You Feel Lucky Punks?</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346609833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Car :) Not only did your post Make My Day, I see it also brought out the Good, Bad and the Ugly! Every Which Way But Loose! Or shall I say “Lose”, which is what O-bama is going to do! You can take the man out of the ghetto, but you can’t take the ghetto out of the man! Beep beep, gotta go! Fox News is on! They hate him, I love it!</Msg><Username>a_car_this_fine</Username><Timestamp>1346632887000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346633309000-32</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy! Every time you get pinned to the mat and reamed publicly you go after that long long long gone poster that firsdt reamed you. So sad. Was your 12 years of daily melting worth me and Grand Baby Dime Bag's futures? All your melting down doesn't take one ounce of poo out of you and Baby Dime's britches. Pooh Wee!</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346633309000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346633444000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's "We" Kemosobbing? You don't set foreign policy! Mom says you're not even boss of the trailer! You're just the old guy in the corner going "all one poster all one poster" all day. Let's hope you get exactly what you ordered. Suck a snake g@y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy. Do the world a favor.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346633444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346633749000-34</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's my girl Charles Kelly You never seem to run out of ID's to pleasure yourself</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346633749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 20:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634535000-35</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy! Attacking that long gone man can't make you straight or a non-racist, or ever a grown up man. You will always be a loser. A sad broke loser.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346634535000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346634772000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Chuck, FYI my family is originally from Birmingham and they sat in the FRONT of the bus. Hope that helps. . ." -------------------- In the abstract Jim Crow racism was a terrible thing to inflict upon the blacks, but in reality the southerners knew blacks needed to be suppressed. Look to Africa for a frame of reference, despite a continent rich in natural resources blacks have failed to establish nothing but the worst form of civilization. Justice as practiced in northern Europe and the USA in nonexistent in Africa, the blacks have no conception of justice, even the American blacks. Pat Buchanan in his book postulates that by 2025 the USA be in the political control of minorities and it will be the exceptional nation the USA had been. Envision an African government here or a government like Mexico, you get the idea. Even the communist ANALMALE ain't going to like it. What Americans did to American blacks was inhuman, but necessary. As a kid in the 1920's our parents took us tt visit Washington DC. Being quite young I remember little except for sleeping on the mall near the Lincoln Memorial. Nobody even gave thought to anything bad happening to us. Today you wouldn't survive 2 minutes before some shine stuck a knife in you. I like Buchanan am convinced the USA is finished, if you've lived long enough in the USA your frame of reference tells you that the USA is going downhill in quickstep. Hopefully I'll be gone before the real bad s#it hits the fan and I am so sad for our grandchildren and great-grandchildren(several who are wild-eyed literals). There's really nothing I can do except vote against the JUG EARED idiots as the come on. Was watching Tony Brown's Journal about 40 years ago, there was heated racial argument between a white guest and a black woman guest. The black lady was outclassed and losing the debate, all of a sudden she shouted: "Only 10 percent of the world's population is Caucasian -- BLACK IS A DOMINANT GENE, it's just a matter time UNTIL WE BREED YOU OUT OF EXISTENCE." That black lady is dead on the money! My brother got it right when he stated: -- "We have lived in the very best times of the United States of America, we couldn't have been more fortunate" --</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1346634772000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346635624000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee Uncle Agqut, you and my g@y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy are so racist and g@y! You should play Twister together and learn to like colors!</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346635624000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636025000-38</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles, pretending to be a 22 year old girl fits your style to a T, kind of like "boyish rock star style" did. Thanks for giving all the readers a good laugh AGAIN</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346636025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636292000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles, your clueless. I grew up in Compton Ca. in the 60's &amp; 70's Look it up and learn something. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346636292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636656000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Only 10 percent of the world's population is Caucasian -- BLACK IS A DOMINANT GENE, it's just a matter time UNTIL WE BREED YOU OUT OF EXISTENCE." I remember Louis Farrakhan gaining momentum in the 80's saying to the blacks “Just Keep Having Those Babies”. It was the Black Power Movement. And its STILL moving - - - ½ on WELFARE! Where is “White Power” Where is “Miss White America” Where is “WET” Where is “White Sheen” Where is “Ivory” magazine Where is “White Pride” Blacks are the ones who are prejudice against WHITES. Maybe they have secretly always been, but even more so since Obama got elected, they walk around with a sense of ENTITLEMENT that they don’t deserve. I was not much prejudice before O’bama, but now, sorry, I can’t help it. PS: I did not rec anyone down, when I went to rec 5 stars, it turned to two.... Sorry.. Now I remember why I don't rec...</Msg><Username>angry_white_woman</Username><Timestamp>1346636656000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:44:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346636897000-41</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke fasiled Daddy failed Grand Daddy, that's not my name but it's funny how much that man owns you and to see you discredit yourself and get the world laughing at your g@yness on full public display.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346636897000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637023000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy Grand Daddy, do you think your public sickness about that long ago man has shown you to be an obsessed lying racist fool? Play naked Twister with Uncle Agqut and learn to like colors! Lordd knows you have nothing else to live for.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346637023000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637119000-43</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles, I've discovered your PROBLEM You were born a boy when you wanted to be a girl. You could always have a gender job done, it's never too late. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346637119000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637329000-44</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy failed Grsand Daddy. That's not my name but your every post obsessing on a long ago poster shows you were born worse than a girl, you're a g@y Tool Fool. Nothing worse than a retarded failed parent. Nothing worse. Have a sex change, marry Uncle Agqut and have a poo baby. Maybe you won't neglect that one.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346637329000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637330000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"and learn to like colors" Are you one of those "Blue Men" Green with envy or just a Yellow Fat Bellied Texan? PS: You live in a Red state. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346637330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637511000-46</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOLOL!@ Maybe John and Agqut could “Lather Up”!!!! Watch out Gewizmeto and Alpha!!!</Msg><Username>angry_white_woman</Username><Timestamp>1346637511000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 21:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346637658000-47</Id><Topic><Title>ALL ONE POSTER</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346627591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 19:13:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Charles, don't you have anything to do this evening? I myself am watching NASCAR</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346637658000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346638274000-48</Id><Title>She's All One Poster</Title><Msg>She's so easy to spot 4 or 5 red stars It's that simple</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346638274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346639308000-49</Id><Title>Muscular Distrophy Telethon</Title><Msg>It's really good music this year, although no Jerry Lewis (:. (Sad). But anyway, the music is way better. Check it out, and donate, if you can. Chanel 9, local, most locales....</Msg><Username>angry_white_woman</Username><Timestamp>1346639308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639361000-50</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy Grand Daddy. Still not my name there, nor where I live, but if you were 1/10 as clever as you think you are you would have a job, and a house, and a daughter, and a grand kid, and any self respect or credibility and not be fixated and obsessed over men from 2005. I make $35 an hour, take home, pricking you and laughing at how you bleed. How's your life alone in the trailer since Grand Ma rescued Mom? Why is z50com and your even sadder ebay site struggling so badly? Too much melt time?</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346639361000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346639562000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How's your life alone in the trailer" Buy a tool, get my new address and continue your stalking What else do you have in life?</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1346639562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:32:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346640544000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Every President Since 1978 Lied About Osama.</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1346610381000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 14:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy Grand Daddy. So 6 months ago.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1346640544000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 22:49:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>