<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353336811898-1</Id><Topic><Title>ebay, what the F!</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353199789593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most items carry a 9% final value fee per each.</Msg><Username>skirtt_chaser</Username><Timestamp>1353336811898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 09:53:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353342765965-2</Id><Topic><Title>ebay, what the F!</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353199789593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can a listing be .35 cents? I checked and with a store, a premium store, a anchor store and no store both auction and fixed price. NO .35 cent fee anywhere. Please explain, are you a ebay store owner and what type of listing? PS: skirtt_chaser, where are YOU seeing 9%? I see 7%, 10%, 11% &amp; 13% on Ebay's fee page!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1353342765965</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:32:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353342813699-3</Id><Title>There goes this piece of Garbage again</Title><Msg>AMZN is up well over 2.5% and This EBAY (Piece of GArbage) has lost over 1% of it's high this morning, while the market sits at its high of the day.</Msg><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1353342813699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:33:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353344218330-4</Id><Topic><Title>There goes this piece of Garbage again</Title><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1353342813699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:33:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon P/E of 2700 OMG! Where's the value? ? ? And look again, Ebay's heading back UP!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1353344218330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 11:56:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353348700411-5</Id><Title>Paypal impossible to get in touch with today!!!</Title><Msg>Freaking paypal is impossible to communicate with!!! #$%$??? My account payment method was changed and the computer says that it does not recognize my phone number. I called the number on my paypal cc and talked with someone in india who has no idea what is going on. This is over an hour on the damn phone. Is this the typical service these days?</Msg><Username>lotahype44</Username><Timestamp>1353348700411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:11:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353352226284-6</Id><Topic><Title>Paypal impossible to get in touch with today!!!</Title><Username>lotahype44</Username><Timestamp>1353348700411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I had no problem calling Paypal today. Was on hold for about 30 seconds Customer rep was able to help me with my problem of printing shipping labels She's my HERO for the day. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1353352226284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 14:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353357182200-7</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Mad,I heard You and Temple U had a very happy group of kids there !!!</Title><Username>cincyyyyy</Username><Timestamp>1353092422702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I am and even before that date,I havn't seen the display myself but we have freinds that work/live up in dayton and wright patt air base that are into aviation that are very impressed with the whole museum.BTW My grandson played two hockey game's against the Dayton Stealth team His team won both of them 4-2 and 4-1 very good games from both team's. The goaltender's made the difference.You from the Dayton/Cincy area ? Mad/CRLmelord still around ?GLTY</Msg><Username>cincyyyyy</Username><Timestamp>1353357182200</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:33:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353358130080-8</Id><Topic><Title>Paypal impossible to get in touch with today!!!</Title><Username>lotahype44</Username><Timestamp>1353348700411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 13:11:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad they were able to help someone! I am NOT going to use their credit card for anything except for Ebay and I have no intention of buying ANY product over $30 on ebay. I don't think it is legal to be so uncommunicative in the USA for a company that handles money.</Msg><Username>lotahype44</Username><Timestamp>1353358130080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 15:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353376468483-9</Id><Topic><Title>ebay, what the F!</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353199789593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When selling on eBay there are Final Value fees which are calculated differently for different caragories. You can go to ebays learning center and it will give you the break down for what your final value fees are. . $24 for 3 items that's about 8-9% final value fee as well as a shipping fee if you charge for shipping. Now I don't agree with that because most of us sellers only charge what USPS Calulates the shipping to be. I'll take you $24 to my $300 eBay fees but I sell high end items. Just type in fees in the eBay learning center also your fees are broke down under your seller account. Just click that and it will bring up your invoice or billing activity so you can see the breakdown. Good luck, I will say there aren't any better services out there, at least with eBay &amp; Paypal you can sell and be protected on the back end.</Msg><Username>whites1294</Username><Timestamp>1353376468483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 20:54:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353376870911-10</Id><Topic><Title>ebay, what the F!</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353199789593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have to have a store to sell, and the fees are different with each category. When their running the listing specials you can get insertion fees that low but your FVF will be different. It will be calculated according to item, item type and the category you listed it in. You can get the fee break down in the eBay learning center, all you have to do is type in Selling fees and it will bring the whole breakdown up. You can also see your selling breakdown under your selling account. I sometimes am billed the 9-10% and sometimes a lot more depending on the category, electronics is a high fee category. A lot of people don't understand when selling on eBay the sellers pay a lot to sell that's why it's important to calculate your fee into your price. That's why a lot of us sellers set reserves because we know what we need to make to cover everything and still make some profit. Hope this has helped.</Msg><Username>whites1294</Username><Timestamp>1353376870911</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 21:01:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>