<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349412881426-1</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY 1-866-540-3229 CUSTOMER SERVICE SUCKS</Title><Username>two_door32</Username><Timestamp>1349363659218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 11:14:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you trying to pay for and what method of payment are you using?</Msg><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349412881426</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 00:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349436555481-2</Id><Title>Ebay suck big time more and more !</Title><Msg>Ebay created monopoly acquiring Paypal clearly violation of antitrust laws. They are telling sellers what to sell, how to sell, how to pay, where to sell, where not to sell, lately they are charging sellers fees on shipping!! Their greed is amazing. They just send me notice of unpaid item IN SELLERS NAME !!! Cause I dared to pay by check, reason being they froze my Paypal acc for no reason. I used to have 4 accounts with ebay starting in 1998, Quit selling long time ago, only buying some times. I would never invest a penny in this stinking ebay rocket. But their time will come and shorts will make fortune shorting this pig all the way down.</Msg><Username>docpopov</Username><Timestamp>1349436555481</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 07:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349439370731-3</Id><Title>Wonder how analyst calculate abuse to sellers into price</Title><Msg>Traditional sellers are being cast off for Chinese flood. The abuse that is heaped upon traditional sellers is beyond belief. Excessive fees, forced returns, broken ratings systems are just the tip. The rules get changed regularly so that you can not set up a long term business model. Thankfully I've been able to move fully half of my sales to a competitor in the past six months. An excellent business has been turned into a trailer park.</Msg><Username>whoisjohngalt52</Username><Timestamp>1349439370731</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349445197759-4</Id><Title>ST JOKE OF THE DAY : 7.8 EMINPOLYMENT hahahahahahahahaha,,, is the game rigged Mr. President</Title><Msg>WALL-STREET KNOWS THESE NUMBERS ARE A LIE..........MR PRESIDENT YOU FOOOOOOOOOOOOLED ====NO-ONE======!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>flashywildwest</Username><Timestamp>1349445197759</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 09:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349450776497-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay Hits $50 Again</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1349362720243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 10:58:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and again today.</Msg><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1349450776497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349451905959-6</Id><Topic><Title>We Are Already Getting RETURNS Thanks To Ebay's New Policy</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1349403188929</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 22:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ebay been killing sellers for many years now. Wonder why remaining sellers are putting up with the greedy incompetent and downward stupid ebay management. This is one of the most overpriced stocks, if you made money on this pig, take your profits before is too late! I never owned this pig so I have no vested interest bashing it. Just from the former seller perspective.</Msg><Username>docpopov</Username><Timestamp>1349451905959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349455078907-7</Id><Title>"Leverage An Investment In Gold For A Few Cents"</Title><Msg>Bonanza Goldfields, BONZ, is a junior gold mining start-up company with tremendous potential. The new C.E.O. was a director at the U.S. Mint. Financing secured. Gold production will begin at the company's Tarantula site soon. Read the recent Yahoo news. "Penny stock today. Dollar stock tomorrow."</Msg><Username>wcoastguy2008</Username><Timestamp>1349455078907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 12:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349465313823-8</Id><Title>Ebay fees are getting really expensive.</Title><Msg>I'm moving some of my expensive items from ebay to ebid to move from paying a 9% fee to 0-3% fee. At least ebay lets you list for free so you can get enough money out of the buyer to cover your fees.</Msg><Username>chris96145</Username><Timestamp>1349465313823</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 15:28:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349481482849-9</Id><Title>I BEEN SELLING ON EBAY 12 YEARS,SALES HAVE COME TO A STALL, NO SALES WORST IN 10 YEARS</Title><Msg>I am a powerseller,and this sept and oct have been the worst in 12 years,i read it also on there message boards on ebay everyone having the same problem.im not sure why</Msg><Username>capecod245</Username><Timestamp>1349481482849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 19:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>