<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343902985000-1</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"BS, we do not need the "rich" 1/10th as much as they need the rest of us." -------- Wrong again my Ed Shultz polly parrot. The rich (AND MUCH OF THE PRODUCTIVE CLASS) have found ways in the global economy to bypass your beloved workers bees. Simply put you and your entitlement fixated workers have literally become relatively unproductive PITAs. If I (or you for that matter) had a business where I could get cut my labor cost by 80-90 percent, I (and you for that matter) would do it in a microsecond, a no brainer. I was one of your "worker bees" in the union construction trades and saw firsthand your beloved non-productive worker bees in action. In the union I was actually relegated mostly to the less than desirable work sites BECAUSE I WAS PRODUCTIVE! Eventually when it became common knowledge that I worked intelligently and productively whistle to whistle, the union hierarchy (mostly upper echelon Freemasons) used me and several other hard working members to do the grunt work for their buddies. I recall we were working five 8 hour days and we were call to a job 75 miles away to rebuild a 10,000 horsepower induced draft fan electric motor(yes a 10,000 horsepower electric motor). The union crony crew was working overtime seven 12 hour days doing absolutely nothing except acting. 4 of us grunts did all the actual work, the 10 cronies on the 7/12 crew slept, drank, hid or strutted their expertise. They made $6000.00 paychecks (this was in 1986) and we got $1600.00 checks. My point is that in the unions the productive are ostracized and those like the hard head me that refuse to be unproductive are punished. My father(an unpreductive type) retired in 1964 from USS Steel, he proudly made the statement that they (Steelworkers Union) had driven the company into the ground with ever increasing demands like 13 week vacations and highly restrictive work rules. Driven into the ground was dead on the money, steel making gradually moved out of Pittsburgh. Buy an I-beam today and you won't see USS, Bethelehem, Carnegie stamp on it, it will be Russian or Chinese. The US WORKER ENTITLEMENT ATTITUDE drove the steel industry out of the United States. China now produces more steel than the rest of the world combined. China puts a new coal generating power plant online about every two weeks. The US hasn't built a coal fired power plant since the seventies, WE DON'T NEED THEM because our industry is forced offshore by your self-serving idiotic demands. Think about your demand for health care, did you ever put a pencil to it? The US spends $10,000 --ANNUALLY-- FOR EVERY MAN WOMAN AND CHILD in America. How long can the PRODUCTIVE CAPACITY of the USA bear such a burden? You and your imbecilic Ed Shultz indoctrinated brain are the PROBLEM. I'll bet you are a highly unproductive person posting here on your employer's time, you use this board to screw off. I'm old enough to die off (hopefully before) this country impacts the financial wall, though I'd like to see you rioting in the streets like Greece for you beloved entitlements from someone else's money. Yes, I've seen you in society all too many times before, you beat your chest of how productive you are, but you are exactly like the union actors described above. You've actually got to a point where you believe you own BS.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343902985000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 06:23:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343912736000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Corrective Move Stepping in</Title><Username>robinmvv156</Username><Timestamp>1343909938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST SPAM SPAM SPAM</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343912736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343912977000-3</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT</Title><Username>darcieneg976</Username><Timestamp>1343836354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 11:52:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST SPAM MALWARE</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343912977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343913057000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Change In Trend Near?</Title><Username>trevjnw438</Username><Timestamp>1343822581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JUST SPAM MALWARE</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343913057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343914020000-5</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: update!!!</Title><Username>draksonrob58</Username><Timestamp>1343913666000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IGNORE - JUST STUPID SPAMMER</Msg><Username>killspam13</Username><Timestamp>1343914020000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343915038000-6</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make it sound like ALL the rich have offshore accounts and "fabricate" their taxes. You are also coming dangerously close to claiming Romney cheated on his taxes. That's a pretty serious accusation without any proof. (It's clear proof enough to you is the CBS newscasters opinions/take on the issues. LOL) Presidential candidates are only required to submit one tax return, which Romney did...just like many presidents before him, including DemocRATS. The only reason you're hearing so much about it during this campaign is because you DemocRATS will clutch at anything to win. You run your campaigns like kids that throw dirt in the other guys eyes then sucker punch him. Hell, you all even dug up some "news" that Romney was allegedly mean to a classmate in HIGH SCHOOL 40 some years ago. How desperate can Obama get? The reason for Obama's desperation is he knows he can't win based on his (failed) track record. You really need to stop listening to CBS news. They've got you all mixed up. You claim Romney gave .00000009 of his income in a positive way. That's because you didn't hear on CBS that Romney gave over 20% of his income (4M+) to charity last year. I'd say he's a pretty giving guy. Go see what single digit % Obama gave the year before he was elected....be sure to look to see who he gave it to also. (Hint: that white person hating church he went to for 20 years and the United Negro College Fund-pretty bias if you ask me.) Your liberal attitude is TWISTED. Saying things like this country doesn't need the rich and without the worker bee's there would be no colony. Wowsie, wowsie, woo, woo. Do you hear yourself? Without the rich there would be none of the hand outs you think you deserve Sherlock. You know, you sound extremely jealous. Why don't you quit your job if you despise working for someone that makes more money than you and start your own business. Then you can hire employees that you can pay as much as you pay yourself. Ever think of that?</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343915038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343917479000-7</Id><Title>Could be the best time to buy eBay</Title><Msg>Interesting insider activity on eBay http://COMPARESTOCKCHARTS.INFO</Msg><Username>ryannbrannin</Username><Timestamp>1343917479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343917967000-8</Id><Title>A lot of positive stories on EBAY.</Title><Msg>With this much positive spin, what institutions are looking to dump shares to retail longs?</Msg><Username>realtime879</Username><Timestamp>1343917967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343918678000-9</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The less education &amp; skills you have the more you'll rely on the government...just the way the DemocRATS want it." ---------------- John Kennedy proposed a seemingly wasteful goal of putting an American on the moon. I can remember in the 1950's reading in Popular Electronics about the invention of the microchip, of how engineers had amazingly put 13 transistors on a single chip. The article went on to say it was a nifty invention but there seemed little practical use for it. Kennedy's moon effort forced the miniaturization of electronic components which propelled the USA to leadership in electronics for the next fifty years. It also brought on our dominance of the computer and information wave. 100's of thousands of engineers were educated to meet the demand. The USA became more productive and stronger in the process. The USA through freedom and the innovative spirit freedom encourages has led the world from one productive endeavor to the next. Think of the agricultural revolution, we went from farming with horses in the 1940's to the highly productive farming of today. We led the world and improved agriculture worldwide. We led in steel, we led in petroleum, machine tools, heavy machinery, pharmaceuticals and in nearly every field of human endeavor. Most importantly we led in lifestyle improvement. What is the USA leading in today, what are we offering the world that they can't get somewhere else? Freedom (and absence of the heavy of government) is innovation's partner, we are losing the freedom to profit from are innovative spirit. Now the government focuses on college grants to educate those entering the ever expanding public sector. Private entrepreneurs are derided as greedy basstards to be ridiculed and taxed into poverty, even by president downer. It's always been this way to some extent, the productive class has never been appreciated, but today the productive are under an openly public sinister attack, president downer surely can't be this stupid. President downer essentially ended John Kennedy's space program and hasn't the VISION to institute a similar program that would lead to the immense national rewards gained from Kennedy's vision. President downer's vision is expanding the public sector and expanding entitlements in an effort to snuff out the independent innovative spirit of what Jug Ears considers a non-exceptional nation. (Non-exceptional nation -- don't get me started -- that empty suited downer rubs me raw -- pity for the men that suffered, bled and died to begin this country and to maintain it's freedom)</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343918678000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343919223000-10</Id><Title>Oh Momma get rid of Obama</Title><Msg>He's out to destroy the country I so love! But thank God he can only have 4 more years of rule at the most. I have to vote for Romney to rid myself of Obama. . . But on the bright side, I lost my overpriced home in the OC for a more conventional one here in the desert!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343919223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343920200000-11</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Brainy disc-ussion sprinkled with a little disc-function! Whodathunk? Very entertaining... Nice to see everyone getting along so well, LOL! Romney IS excruciatingly boring, especially in him mom jeans! Obama, every hommie in the hood is gonna be voting for him! Both awful! Crimelord for President :) If I could take a deduction for horse sh$$, I would!</Msg><Username>a_car_this_fine</Username><Timestamp>1343920200000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:10:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343920677000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Momma get rid of Obama</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343919223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:53:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lost your overpriced home, sold your over priced home for a profit, foreclosed, short sold, bidded it up, forced out. Lost, did you a favor, fancier neighborhood, better house, out in the desert, a more modest house, bought it, relatives gave it it to you... Oh poor z50com, the stories you make up need to get on the same page! Most fictional narratives do not meander so badly. Obama did not force you to live here 247 every day for 12 years neglecting your daughter and grand kid. Voting against your class interests for Romney will not get them back or heal you. I'm glad an Aurora type like you got rid of so much of your arsenal but remember Rudyard Kipling's sage advice about the last one.</Msg><Username>johnosborne.toolfool</Username><Timestamp>1343920677000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343921039000-13</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like you analogy about the workers and bees making a hive Sharpey, but the rich of the US and the poor do not have such a symbiotic relationship anymore. The word "class war" gets bandied about whenever such facts are mentioned, but the rich declared war on the poor years ago and are pretty much winning at the expense of the nation. Myself, I would not want to be rich in steaming cesspool ghetto of resentment, but the rich are able to buy media mouthpieces that blame the poor if they lash out at their future's being stolen for fancy baubles for the few. We need another New Deal and leaders with enough vision to bring it about before the place burns like Greece.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343921039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343921436000-14</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't agree with you Agqut but found your (probably true) story and your attempt at intelligent discourse so compelling I gave it a positive rec anyways. Unions are not the blame for this countries demise and offshoring. Are even 4% of the population even in a union anymore? This countries demise was started long ago, by buying into the FED (every dollar created starts as debt to a central European bank and the debt compounds from there) buying into Federalism (and no I am not a user of the term War Of Northern aggression, but the aggression never stopped from there) building an economy based on war, endless war, and allowing the rich to undo the basic safety nets of the New Deal. Blaming unions for the nation's demise is much like blaming the rape victim for the crime. That's not the greatest analogy but one that fits all the same. We've tried "trickle down", it failed. We should re-invent the IWW and try some "trickle up" for a change before we end up jealous of even third world nations.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343921436000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343923130000-15</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alpha :) I took me a while to read through this thread, didn’t see it right way, but thank you for the compliment, and your sterling political and diplomatic skills :)</Msg><Username>a_car_this_fine</Username><Timestamp>1343923130000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343923599000-16</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Again Ms Midnite, like you and your postings but disagree with you. The rich (all the rich) do cheat (I'm sure within mostly perfect legal lines) on their taxes and off shoring money is total cheating, though somehow legal. I'm willing to entertain the idea that Romney donated to charity (I'm sure in a tax deductable way) and will look into those facts, but there's also the fact of him not paying any income tax for his ten years at Bain. I'm sure he'll retro actively pay those. And as for his bully character, it is pertinent. We might as well elect one of our board trolls. Dollar for dollar, the rich receive far more benefits, entitlements and subsidies than the poor. The focus stays on the so called welfare cheats because the rich own the media that keeps that myth alive. It always boggles my logic why the (so called) conservatives support the very people who grew debt, the government and the endless wars that bankrupt the country the most, and assailed our freedoms the most, Reagan, Bush 1 and especially Bush 2, while lambasting Obama for basically following their failed path. Obama is basically watered down Bush 2 policies with smarter dialogue and more drones. I bet if we made a Preditor Drone dressage horse that could bomb Afgan weddings in the night, these two clowns would finally agree on something. Worst election ever! And it is at a most critical time. Vote early and vote often, but I think Mother Nature and Father Sun is about to cast the final vote.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343923599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343923746000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Momma get rid of Obama</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1343919223000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 10:53:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Johnosborne.toolfool makes a brutal bashing sound poetic! What relentless talent you effortlessly release on your enemy! Sorry John, but something about the way he writes makes you seem like Fifty Shades of Slave!!!</Msg><Username>a_car_this_fine</Username><Timestamp>1343923746000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343923804000-18</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aah shucks ma'am. Thanks for your great humor. May "Brainy Disc- Horse" live forever up here. I'd flirt with you but bet you (might be) taken.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1343923804000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343924348000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Corrective Move Stepping in</Title><Username>robinmvv156</Username><Timestamp>1343909938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>elsidhc636</Username><Timestamp>1343924348000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343924457000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Why Do Board Trolls Hate $45? $44? $43? $42? $41?? ??</Title><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343058624000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 11:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back to the top! Will I get to deduct 77K for my dressage board trolls? 'Natch!</Msg><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343924457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343925887000-21</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point was that a large portion of the American workforce is much too demanding, possesses an entitlement mindset and lacks a work ethic. Manufacturers who can substantially lower their labor costs by going to China (and anywhere else) also avoid all the environmental, social and litigious overburden of doing business in the USA. It is completely understandable. In regards to the rich, you have some valid points. What needs to be done is to separate the productive rich from the unproductive rich. Romney today is an example of the unproductive rich being able to live opulently forever off his financially questionable past(I can't quite rationalize if gambling in the hedge fund business is a productive endeavor). Romney and the rich living in perpetuity off past income perhaps should be taxed in a way that would force more of their income into productive enterprise. Your basic political naivete is all too apparent by swallowing liberal talking points hook line and sinker. The rich Democrats are as greedy as the Republicans, only the democrats are much more adept politically in that they can hide behind the social justice BS. A rich democrat will skin you just as quickly as as a republican. You have your political blinders on, just the thing the democrats want. You are no different than Shawn Hannity or Rush Lingbaugh. It is the independents that can't stand the ideological idiocy of either party that will control the election. Their choice sadly boils down to who to vote against. I can't recall voting for anyone in my life, always voted against someone, this time as last it will be Obama. The unfortunate outcome is though we independents control the election, those we cause to be elected have D's or R's behind their name and we that caused them to be elected are ignored. If you a dyed in the wool democrat you are an idiot. If you a dyed in the wool republican you are an idiot. I think of my republican brother-in-law that "pulled himself up by the bootstraps", that sent his kids to college on Pell Grants and never met a democratic giveaway program he couldn't take advantage of. Me? I never cashed the stimulus checks sent to me. Government money is borrowed unclean contaminated money and for me to spend it would make me as bad as the most corrupt recipient. I refused social security until it was forced on me at age 72, I use the money to buy sweet(molasses) grain chop for my beef brood cows, each one gets 7 pounds a day, you ought to see how nice they and their calves look, their coats shine like show cattle.. I won't use for my personal use a penny of government money, I'd rather see the cows have a treat..</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343925887000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343928011000-22</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alpha, I am taken. Taken aback! Sorry to disappoint you but I have the hots for Agqut. Agqut makes me hillbilly high! I always dreamed of endless biotching, a weathered picket fence, 2.5 sheep and a beautiful field of crab grass! Neighbors hide and blissful privacy is only a cornfield away! Somebody’s got to take care of the pet cemetery!!! Homemade Country Quencher is a proposal away! My dear friends on this here beloved board of mine, you are all invited!</Msg><Username>a_car_this_fine</Username><Timestamp>1343928011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 13:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343930397000-23</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think we lost Sharpey. LOL. If you think I love Romney you would be wrong. In fact, there hasn't been a presidential candidate I've wanted in office since Reagan. I was barely old enough to vote but loved his love of this country which couldn't have come at a better time after Carter. I've always considered my views to be somewhere in the middle leaning right but Obama has pushed me into right mode like no other. He is taking away our freedoms and leading this country into bankruptcy. He scares the carp out of me. He has spent 5 trillion dollars in 3 1/2 years and has nothing to show for it. (Unemployment is worse and the economy is no better. What happened to all that change?) That's what Bush spent in his entire 8 years in office which included one of the two most ridiculous wars of all time. I didn't appreciate Clinton until Bush came along. I'm going to post this now cause a thunderstorm is coming and it might shut down my computer. I'll finish later. Note to Sybil: I did not proof read.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343930397000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 13:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343930505000-24</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;&lt;" I didn't appreciate Clinton until Bush came along."&gt;&gt;&gt; Minus the cigar part.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343930505000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 14:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343933266000-25</Id><Topic><Title>romney deducted $77,000 for horse care in 2010</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1343532733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 23:32:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In fact, there hasn't been a presidential candidate I've wanted in office since Reagan." ------------------------- Respectfully, it was Reagan the began the modern era of borrowing. The US came out of World War Two a creditor nation until Reagan took office, under Reagan the US went from the world's largest creditor nation to the world's largest debtor nation. Read up on it, even Reagan himself described it as the biggest failing of his presidency. It was Reagan that started us on the journey to the 16 trillion national debt hanging like an albatross around our collective necks. Sorry, I know Reagan has this teflon like shield about his history, Nancy Reagan did a superb job "managing" Reagan's legacy. So good a job even Jug Ears believes it.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1343933266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 14:47:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343940769000-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bet you didnt know this about eBay</Title><Username>leighawyrick</Username><Timestamp>1343933786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 14:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IGNORE - SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343940769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 16:52:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343940810000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Did Hear The Forecast?&gt;</Title><Username>xavierharry2346</Username><Timestamp>1343920243000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 11:10:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CALLS FOR SPAM MORE SPAM - MALWARE LINKS</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343940810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 16:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343940863000-28</Id><Topic><Title>eBay could double based on this report</Title><Username>ashtongreder</Username><Timestamp>1343924648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 12:24:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEWARE SPAM MALWARE VIRUS LINKS</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343940863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 16:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343940908000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Corrective Move Stepping in</Title><Username>robinmvv156</Username><Timestamp>1343909938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 08:18:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PLAIN UGLY SPAM MALWARE</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343940908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 16:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343940975000-30</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT: update!!!</Title><Username>draksonrob58</Username><Timestamp>1343913666000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 09:21:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THANKS FOR FREE SPAM</Msg><Username>nw_ripper</Username><Timestamp>1343940975000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 16:56:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945094000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why Do Board Trolls Hate $45? $44? $43? $42? $41?? ??</Title><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343058624000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 11:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRIBBLES, You won't make any $$$ whatsoever. Since you previously admitted to not being a day trader. Better luck next time. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1343945094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:04:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343945548000-32</Id><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Msg>I just received this email. The timing is a little too ironic, don't cha think? To All My Valued Employees, There have been some rumblings around the office about the future of this company, and more specifically, your job. As you know, the economy has changed for the worse and presents many challenges. However, the good news is this: The economy doesn't pose a threat to your job. What does threaten your job however, is the changing political landscape in this country. Of course, as your employer, I am forbidden to tell you whom to vote for - it is against the law to discriminate based on political affiliation, race, creed, religion, etc. Please vote for who you think will serve your interests the best. However, let me tell you some little tidbits of fact which might help you decide what is in your best interest. First, while it is easy to spew rhetoric that casts employers against employees, you have to understand that for every business owner there is a back story.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945595000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This back story is often neglected and overshadowed by what you see and hear. Sure, you see me park my Mercedes outside. You saw my big home at last year’s Christmas party. I'm sure all these flashy icons of luxury conjure up some idealized thoughts about my life. However, what you don't see is the back story. I started this company 12 years ago. At that time, I lived in a 300 square foot studio apartment for 3 years. My entire living space was converted into an office so I could put forth 100% effort into building a company, which by the way, would eventually employ you. My diet consisted of Ramen Pride noodles because every dollar I spent went back into this company. I drove a rusty Toyota Corolla with a defective transmission. I didn't have time to date. Often times, I stayed home on weekends, while my friends went out drinking and partying. In fact, I was married to my business -- hard work, discipline, and sacrifice.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945595000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945639000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, my friends got jobs. They worked 40 hours a week and made a modest $50K a year and spent every dime they earned. They drove flashy cars and lived in expensive homes and wore fancy designer clothes. Instead of hitting Nordstrom's for the latest hot fashion item, I was trolling through the Goodwill store extracting any clothing item that didn't look like it was birthed in the 70's. My friends refinanced their mortgages and lived a life of luxury. I, however, did not. I put my time, my money, and my life into a business --- with a vision that eventually, some day, I too, will be able to afford these luxuries my friends supposedly had.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945676000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, while you physically arrive at the office at 9 am, mentally check in at about noon, and then leave at 5 pm, I don't. There is no "off" button for me. When you leave the office, you are done and you have a weekend all to yourself. I unfortunately do not have the freedom. I eat and breathe this company every minute of the day. There is no rest. There is no weekend. There is no happy hour. Every day this business is attached to me like a 1 day old baby. You, of course, only see the fruits of that garden -- the nice house, the Mercedes, the vacations... You never realize the back story and the sacrifices I've made. Now, the economy is falling apart and I, the guy that made all the right decisions and saved his money, have to bail out all the people who didn't.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945676000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945709000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people that overspent their paychecks suddenly feel entitled to the same luxuries that I earned and sacrificed a decade of my life for. Yes, business ownership has its benefits but the price I've paid is steep and not without wounds. Unfortunately, the cost of running this business, and employing you, is starting to eclipse the threshold of marginal benefit and let me tell you why: I am being taxed to death and the government thinks I don't pay enough. I have state taxes. Federal taxes. Property taxes. Sales and use taxes. Payroll taxes. Workers compensation taxes. Unemployment taxes. Taxes on taxes. I have to hire a tax man to manage all these taxes and then guess what? I have to pay taxes for employing him. Government mandates and regulations and all the accounting that goes with it, now occupy most of my time. On Oct 15th, I wrote a check to the US Treasury for $288,000 for quarterly taxes. You know what my "stimulus" check was? Zero. Nada. Zilch.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945709000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343945736000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The question I have is this: Who is stimulating the economy? Me, the guy who has provided 14 people good paying jobs and serves over 2,200,000 people per year with a flourishing business? Or, the single mother sitting at home pregnant with her fourth child waiting for her next welfare check? Obviously, government feels the latter is the economic stimulus of this country. The fact is, if I deducted (Read: Stole) 50% of your paycheck you'd quit and you wouldn't work here. I mean, why should you? That's nuts. Who wants to get rewarded only 50% of their hard work? Well, I agree which is why your job is in jeopardy. Here is what many of you don't understand .. to stimulate the economy you need to stimulate what runs the economy. Had suddenly government mandated to me that I didn't need to pay taxes, guess what? Instead of depositing that $288,000 into the Washington black-hole, I would have spent it, hired more employees, and generated substantial economic growth. My employees would have enjoyed the wealth of that tax cut in the form of promotions and better salaries. But you can forget it now. When you have a comatose man on the verge of death, you don't defibrillate and shock his thumb thinking that will bring him back to life, do you? Or, do you defibrillate his heart? Business is at the heart of America and always has been. To restart it, you must stimulate it, not kill it. Suddenly, the power brokers in Washington believe the mud of America are the essential drivers of the American economic engine. Nothing could be further from the truth and this is the type of change you can keep. So where am I going with all this? It's quite simple. If any new taxes are levied on me, or my company, my reaction will be swift and simple. I fire you. I fire your co-workers. You can then plead with the government to pay for your mortgage, your SUV, and your child's future. Frankly, it isn't my problem anymore. Then, I will close this company down, move to another country, and retire. You see, I'm done. I'm done with a country that penalizes the productive and gives to the unproductive. My motivation to work and to provide jobs will be destroyed, and with it, will be my citizenship. While tax cuts to 95% of America sounds great on paper, don't forget the back story: If there is no job, there is no income to tax. A tax cut on zero dollars is zero. So, when you make decision to vote, ask yourself, who understands the economics of business ownership and who doesn't? Whose policies will endanger your job? Answer those questions and you should know who might be the one capable of saving your job. While the media wants to tell you "It's the economy Stupid" I'm telling you it isn't. If you lose your job, it won't be at the hands of the economy; it will be at the hands of a political hurricane that swept through this country, steamrolled the Constitution, and will have changed its landscape forever. If that happens, you can find me in the South Caribbean sitting on a beach, retired, and with no employees to worry about. Signed, Your boss, Michael A. Crowley, PE Crowley, Crisp &amp; Associates, Inc. Professional Engineers 1906 South Main Street, Suite 122 Wake Forest, NC 27587</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343953836000-38</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.snopes.com/politics/business/valuedemployees.asp Interesting letter. -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1343953836000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 20:30:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343953873000-39</Id><Topic><Title>what I learned at ebay and paypal</Title><Username>poijadsfspfoij</Username><Timestamp>1341276988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-02 20:56:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good to know</Msg><Username>sdafiupiasjf</Username><Timestamp>1343953873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 20:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343955516000-40</Id><Topic><Title>what I learned at ebay and paypal</Title><Username>poijadsfspfoij</Username><Timestamp>1341276988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-02 20:56:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that a Vita Vega Matic, cause you got to add moonshine to make it work right, then I would agree. Now welcome to my ignore list.</Msg><Username>sr.cosa</Username><Timestamp>1343955516000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 20:58:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343955774000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snopes is the worlds greatest search engine.</Msg><Username>sr.cosa</Username><Timestamp>1343955774000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 21:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343957326000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Sharpey</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1343945548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 18:12:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The letter was pretty good. -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1343957326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 21:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343965051000-43</Id><Title>Sorry if I don't bid on your auctions!</Title><Msg>But ebay has the searches all messed up and out of order. Ending in 52 minutes comes before ending in 1 minute and comes towards the middle of the page. Who's the genius that came up with this idea? My buying has nearly dried up.</Msg><Username>mntndo67</Username><Timestamp>1343965051000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-02 23:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>