<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342960278000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Saturday Spam. Every DaY Melting. Board Is Finished.</Title><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342902977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 16:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have not been on this board for a loooog time but daaaaam" Perhaps not with this id, but you have been here 24/7 under your other ids. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1342960278000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 08:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342962711000-2</Id><Title>Bulls Are In The Ring</Title><Msg>I shorted two of there picks and went long on another, and all three are in the money for me! This is great! I'm probably a member for life, because I do not see anything else out there that I trust. That's what first attracted me to the site... it's just what I was looking for. Besides a very good track record, its simple and straightforward. They offer a free daily video also you can join. WWW.WINNINGSTOCKTRADES.INFO</Msg><Username>nathcrne89</Username><Timestamp>1342962711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342967820000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bulls Are In The Ring</Title><Username>nathcrne89</Username><Timestamp>1342962711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 09:11:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great move</Msg><Username>jeni.savor98</Username><Timestamp>1342967820000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 10:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342976934000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Saturday Spam. Every DaY Melting. Board Is Finished.</Title><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342902977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-21 16:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi, you'll have to excuse our Soiled Sullied "welcoming committee". Poor sick Soiled Sullied Sybil has bought into the "everyone is all one poster" lies harder than silly John Tool Fool Osborne z50com, with the similar daily troll behavior. They can't quite seem to find a real reason to live. They can't quite see that it's just their Gang Of Four Loser Board Trolls that melt. All the other posters here don't have the need to hang g@yly on anyone else's posts and trading decisions. These gurls never trade so they need the lameness of spotting typos and throwing 12 year old public poo to keep posting their utter uselessness 247 365 year after year after year.</Msg><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342976934000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:08:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342977161000-5</Id><Topic><Title>I had Charles talking to himself today</Title><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1342822607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-20 18:16:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I noticed that. You have Charles under your complete control. Keep up the great work! MY ID SAYS IT ALL</Msg><Username>sully_rules</Username><Timestamp>1342977161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1342977498000-6</Id><Title>Only Sullied Idiot Owned Slaves Melt On Long Ago Posters</Title><Msg>Poor broke Sullied Sybil and Sybil Sullied, yack with themselves and broke John Osborne z50com, g@yly obsessed over a long ago gone poster and think they see him everywhere, or accomplish anything by frittering their meth up here each and every day. No investors act like they do. Note their early morning and instant response posts and avoid those poor sick broke about to be very very unlucky board troll g@ys. Their ending will not be pretty, just like their daily lives. Not pretty aty all. Oh well! They keep begging and their Master will provide.</Msg><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342977498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342979333000-7</Id><Topic><Title>I had Charles talking to himself today</Title><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1342822607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-20 18:16:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the shout out. It really isn't that hard to keep Charles under control. He is very simple minded, so it doesn't take much effort. Did you notice how he posted within 5 minutes of your post? It just proves that Charles stalks this board 24/7. Pretty soon he is going to want to be you. He already wants to be me, as evidenced by all the fake Sully ids he has created in my honor. For some reason he hates himself, and wants to be others. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinma2009</Username><Timestamp>1342979333000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342980482000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Only Sullied Idiot Owned Slaves Melt On Long Ago Posters</Title><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342977498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone (but the sullied twins) can see the sullied twins instantly respond and chatter to themselves. Daily. Yearly. Accomplishing nothing. I appreciate the way you got these fools to wreck this board and out themselves for free! For free! Hilarious! Your ownership of them is very profound and priceless.</Msg><Username>id.dejour</Username><Timestamp>1342980482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1342980908000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Only Sullied Idiot Owned Slaves Melt On Long Ago Posters</Title><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342977498000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 13:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks, but I don't own them my friend. I just taunt them. It's funny to see not a day can go by, year after year, that they don't have to bleat g@yly for a poster who left in 2005. Now THAT's power! That Man owns every fiber of their bean, er being. They are just jabbering sacrificed pawns in a much much bigger game. A game they long long ago lost.</Msg><Username>sybil.dribble</Username><Timestamp>1342980908000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 14:15:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343009219000-10</Id><Topic><Title>overbought territory</Title><Username>bogdanmiltchev</Username><Timestamp>1342931034000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 00:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ebay will stand at $50 in a few weeks $$$$$$$</Msg><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343009219000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343009551000-11</Id><Title>will ebay hit $46.00 Monday?</Title><Msg>If the market is up Monday Ebay could close above $46.00. Ebay would closed above 46 Friday if it was a up market. Ebay is on a rocket to 50+</Msg><Username>acman40930</Username><Timestamp>1343009551000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-22 22:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>