<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356270433659-1</Id><Topic><Title>Did u hear?</Title><Username>caritadwn999</Username><Timestamp>1344265091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 10:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>jamesmac303</Username><Timestamp>1356270433659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 08:47:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356273697361-2</Id><Title>prepare for fiscal cliff as unemployment benefit and food stamp end next week</Title><Msg>prepare for fiscal cliff as unemployment benefit and food stamp end next week for many American. this will have financial and retail ripple effect. hold on your cash and dont spend on wasteful thing. tell your children and friends no present this year. Santa is dead...</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1356273697361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 09:41:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356273798443-3</Id><Topic><Title>prepare for fiscal cliff as unemployment benefit and food stamp end next week</Title><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1356273697361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 09:41:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no present this year cuz Santa program is gutted by GOP. just hold on cash cuz you will need it as fiscal cliff turn into REAL CLIFF for many American!!!!</Msg><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1356273798443</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 09:43:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356279853923-4</Id><Title>My Failed Daddy Failed Grand Daddy "Johns Joint" Tool Fool Is The Biggest idiot Spammer Here. Ever.</Title><Msg>My sad lonely broke failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy Johns Joint is the longest running spammer on this, or any board. Daily, 247 for 12 long wasted years he blathered his retarded dung across the net, while he trashed his very own daughter and grand kid, my baby Dime Bag. He has let down each and every person who ever counted on him, just so he could try to own a third rate chat board of a very manipulated 5th rate stock of a failed company that's dumped more Chinese made junk into this nation than Wallymart. Way to go Dad, you're a sullied 'tard. Always! How would any human ever be able to live with that as their life's legacy? Merry lonely Christmas in the cold desert loser.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1356279853923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 11:24:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356280630192-5</Id><Topic><Title>Where did all the REGULARS go?</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1355848436923</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-18 11:33:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g@y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy. YOU ran them all off by being a 247 board troll each and every day for 12 wasted years! Even your boyfriend Uncle Flyktning won't post to you and is busy rearranging his wife's paintings in his tiny little dusty lobby. Why don't you get your Fake Sullied IDs to give you a reach around for Christmas? It wouldn't be your first, but your first in a very very long lonely lonely Ripples time for you. Why did you have kids when you knew you were just going to trash them? How do you even keep from sinking in the sand out in your cold lonely snake infested desert?</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1356280630192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 11:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356285033017-6</Id><Title>CRAIGSLIST OUTAGE</Title><Msg>Since ebay owns 25% of craigslist, does anyone know anything about the current craigslist outage. It's been going on for more than 12 hours.</Msg><Username>moorelindaellen</Username><Timestamp>1356285033017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 12:50:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356290006369-7</Id><Topic><Title>prepare for fiscal cliff as unemployment benefit and food stamp end next week</Title><Username>pupu0495</Username><Timestamp>1356273697361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 09:41:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how is this related to your sell reconmend for ebay?</Msg><Username>growthcharlie</Username><Timestamp>1356290006369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:13:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356290341316-8</Id><Title>Wow! Check out Google Wallet! Forget Paypal!</Title><Msg>Since Ebay/paypal have become anti seller I've always been thinking of leaving ebay/paypal altogether but with recent dealing with ebay/paypal and their harsh service to me after I had just spend thousands on their site I figured enough is enough, I will take my money to ebid where I discovered Google Wallet. I know ebid isn't huge like ebay but with the money I spend it will help grow the site as sellers realize bigger sales and at a lower cost to them. I will ask these sellers to post certain items I am looking for. No more ebay/paypal for me, it's offically over.</Msg><Username>jupiterspinning</Username><Timestamp>1356290341316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:19:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356290569027-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay's Search Is The End Of Ebay</Title><Username>diehlr1</Username><Timestamp>1355235691340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 09:21:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem I had with ebay search is getting auctions that don't even have my keyword in the title.</Msg><Username>jupiterspinning</Username><Timestamp>1356290569027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 14:22:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356293068212-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay's Search Is The End Of Ebay</Title><Username>diehlr1</Username><Timestamp>1355235691340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 09:21:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you give an example I would like to try a search and see for myself</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1356293068212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-23 15:04:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>