<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345553732000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL.... now i know why the soap is on a rope!</Msg><Username>gewizmeto</Username><Timestamp>1345553732000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 08:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345555930000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agqut. Interesting post. My guess is that you are either approaching my age or are a very good student. People under the age of 30 usually don’t know many specifics of WW II and know little about Douglas MacArthur. BTW, I don’t know if you actually have any attachment to Pittsburgh (e.g. resident, former resident, etc.) I went to school in Pittsburgh. I love the city. It is again transforming itself.</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1345555930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 09:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345560494000-3</Id><Title>Paypal customer service is the worst</Title><Msg>I made a mistake of entering the wrong bank details by mistake. All I did was enter my checking account as a savings account. So I called them it was the worst experience ever. They said the transaction is pending and all I asked them to do was cancel it because it would never go through according to my bank representative. Paypal said the transaction was pending. Well no DUH. I asked if I could cancel it and he didn't even seem to know. What a nightmare now ill have to wait another few weeks I guess.</Msg><Username>poolplayer2k3ii</Username><Timestamp>1345560494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 10:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345561730000-4</Id><Title>Obama is too frickin funny!</Title><Msg>For the 3rd month in a row Obama has spent more in its campaign than it has raised. I literally LOL at the irony! He currently owes his campaign almost 3 mill. He does love to add to debt. He must think he can just go print some money for his personal use with the shrug of a shoulder. He raised 49 mill in July this year. This time 4 yrs ago he raised 746 mill. OUCH! It's no wonder his ads sound so desperate. He has to milk them for what they're worth (or more than they're worth). Meanwhile Romney has 186 mill on hand and that's with outspending him 2 to 1!!! Obama, start sending out those resumes for community leader positions and take Michele with you. Your luck has run out.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345561730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345564118000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is too frickin funny!</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345561730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep JUG EARS' chickens are coming home to roost. The ultra-liberal rag Newsweek obviously has seen no light at the end of JUG EARS' tunnel and done the first "progressive" hatchet job on the magnificent one. Newsweek's action may be just the beginning as the money was drying up for Newsweek(about a 100 years ago I actually subscribed to Newsweek). There are other liberal leaning "news" organizations that may be falling off or 'jumping off the back when no one is looking' of the JUG EARS bandwagon. The Newsweek piece was particularly interesting in that it took JUG EARS apart for an appalling lack of leadership because JUG EARS had abdicated his position as president to Nancy Pelosi and the dumbest man to ever be a US Senator, Harry Reid. When the JUGEARS-CARE legislation dust up was in full force JUG EARS' had to be asked to stop selling the legislation because his salesmanship was hurting chances of getting the legislation passed. Take JUG EARS off the Teleprompter and he convincingly demonstrates how truly inept and ineffective he actually is. If it ain't green JUG EARS doesn't give a schit about about it. The high functioning imbecile has squandered four years of the American people's time, somebody should have told the JUG EARED pretender that when you are getting deeper in a hole the smart thing is to stop digging.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345564118000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345564933000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is too frickin funny!</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345561730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are talking about JUG EARS campaign money. What I remember about his last campaign is how he took in about 300 million dollars from small credit card donations. It was alleged at the time that all that needed to donate by credit card to JUG EARS was only a valid credit card number, no name, no address, no phone number, NO VERIFICATION whatsoever. It was also alleged that the money for these donations was funneled through credit cards by the George Soros type donors. It would have been easy to do without leaving a trace. At the time there was talk of an investigation though nothing ever became of it, I suspect because possibly the GOP had dirtied their hands in the same manner. Deepthroat's advice "Follow the money" is applicable to JUG EARS, you're right, thank God JUG EARS has his community organizing skills to fall back on.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345564933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345568277000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is too frickin funny!</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345561730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;&lt;"The high functioning imbecile has squandered four years of the American people's time"&gt;&gt;&gt; Not just time but money! Money this country doesn't have. AND THERE'S NOTHING TO SHOW FOR IT except 2,000 pages of incomprehensible healthcare jargon that will soon be overturned. http://blogs.e-rockford.com/applesauce/files/2012/08/Newsweek-Truth.jpg Hit the road Barack don't you come back no more, no more, no more, no more! Hit the road Barack, don't you come back no more!</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345568277000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 12:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345568759000-8</Id><Topic><Title>todd akin, MO. on "legitimate rape"</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1345435552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good morning Sharpey, I see the angry angry Obama haters up here didn't want to touch this with any rethuglicons pole, but it ought to take the cake and cost them the election. No thinking woman should go near Romney/Ryan. I'm sure the rethuglicons want to avoid talk of rape, well the talk of some of them openly saying what they feel in secret with theie war on woman, because that will remind the people how they have raped the nation since Nixon every chance they got. Of course, few voters get pregnant with a rethuglicon's administration rape of the nation because "we have biological ways of stopping that": voting! I bet Romney is really scared having picked a Tea Bagger as his running mate since rethugs where already lukewarm to cold on him, and that side of the line has a lot of guns and don't mind shooting (Gifford and more) to get their way. Romney doesn't have a chance getting elected, but I bet the rabid wing already want Lyin' Ryan in there. I'm sure they wanbt to tell the voters "relax and enjoy it". I see ebay's in the red again and yet no one can see that the "markets" we have are not free and none of these pumped up values can be maintained by pouring endless amounts of fiat currancy at them. Get ready for a storm of beyond belief.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345568759000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569070000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like it that people want to run with my headlines and keep them alive but the low level of intelligent discourse here is saddening. So far in this thread we've "learned"" Lightning forest fires cause more pollution than the history of humans. Wrong. Talk of global climate change just yields a bunch of fart jokes. Laugh if you're not in a major drought, a wall of tornadoes, tsunamis, or other fun increasing mega storms. CO2 levels rising is no concern, but work hard to get to Mars. Not going to happen. Obama is the worse President. Wrong. Bush Junior will always be. Obama ran up all the debt. Wrong. Reagan started it. Bush Jr. sent it through the roof. And Romney creates jobs? Yeah, in China.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345569070000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569074000-10</Id><Topic><Title>todd akin, MO. on "legitimate rape"</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1345435552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"none of these pumped up values can be maintained" Are you talking about Amazon's SUPER high P/E of 294? Yes, it's been PUMPED like no other. . . As for Ebay it's a deal at it's current price with a P/E of only 16 Hope that helps :-)</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345569074000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569235000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since Obama's been in office housing prices have dropped over 50% Please re-elect Obama again. We're looking for a new house and have ALL CASH this time Obama's a shoe in for lower prices ~ hahahahaha I win either way!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345569235000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345569282000-12</Id><Topic><Title>todd akin, MO. on "legitimate rape"</Title><Username>sharpeyeddude</Username><Timestamp>1345435552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, your obsessive hatred of Amazon never helps when I'm talking about ebay raping its own long investors. I'm sure they'll "relax and enjoy it". Why be a pumper? You're not even a paid one!@</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345569282000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:14:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345569297000-13</Id><Title>ebayalphamale = NARU</Title><Msg>He's still in Beta mode on Ebay. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345569297000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570548000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Analfabeticmale, I remember talking to your parents. They told me if they had believed there was the very slightest chance you could have turned out right -- they would have fixed the rocks in your head.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345570548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345570974000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your insults can't touch me because everyone sees you're a grouchy old hateful thing that's far outlived its usefulness in this world. You just show you lost the debate since you can't argue to its merits, you only throw out idiocy and hate like "Joint".</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345570974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571057000-16</Id><Topic><Title>ebayalphamale = NARU</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345569297000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:14:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"He's still in Beta mode on Ebay. . . " ------------------- The best part of Analmale dripped off of his heroin addicted mother's anus hair.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345571057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571245000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analman -- So indicative of your emptiass personality, you can't even take a joke. I was certain a pussie like you was never in the military.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345571245000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345571373000-18</Id><Title>Johns_Joint=Endles Idiocy</Title><Msg>I guess we shouldn't expect much intelligent discussion to a loser who names himself after his wee willie and has lived on this board daily for a decade spam,ming, hating and disparaging everyone, but his 'catch phrases go like this: Whatever you say about ebay "yeah well what about Amazon" (a ten year old's debate style.) And when he still loses "you're a NARU" (when I never buy or sell on ebay, that's for losers, shysters and Chinese refurbs) And finally he'll probably rail about some guy who left in 2005. All this intelligent discourse come from a loser who pumps ebay for free and lived here so much he destroyed his own family and is wrecking his ebay z50com. Maybe a retard should be quieter and people would notice his retardedness less. Just saying.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345571373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571529000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of your insults touch me because your every remark shows I won the debate and you're hurrying to your cold lonely grave. Will your hate keep you warm there? Anyways, back to intelligent discourse for those who are intelligently capable of it.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345571529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571567000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Johns_Joint=Endles Idiocy</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345571373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analholeman, John is the the grand champion of bait and you dumb bassturd fell for it. SUCKER!</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345571567000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571834000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Why Do Board Trolls Hate $45? $44? $43? $42? $41?? ??</Title><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1343058624000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 11:50:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's talk about important things! Like why did the hateful board trolls dribble away $47 and $46 on their way to wrecking $45? Why ask why? Enjoy.</Msg><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1345571834000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:57:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345571894000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Johns_Joint=Endles Idiocy</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345571373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot the other step: that typo you gave them is going to sweat them for days! Days! Weeks!</Msg><Username>ebay.redchart</Username><Timestamp>1345571894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 13:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345576398000-23</Id><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Msg>We always hear about "welfare queens" and poor people gaming the system but don't forget the Mothers Of All Tax Payer Bottle Babies: The Rich. Hey American Sheeple, you're being fleeced. Royally fleeced. The New Robber Barons: How Taxpayers Subsidise CEOs' Multimillion Salaries A new report finds many top executives are taking home more than their corporations pay in taxes – at our expense by Pratap Chatterjee "...Dozens of US CEOs have cashed in on this major tax incentive at an estimated cost to US taxpayers of $9.7bn last year. Statistics provided by National Priorities Project suggest that the same amount of money could have paid for 142,625 elementary school teachers, or healthcare for 4.96 million low-income children. "At a time of austerity, it's beyond absurd that billions of our tax dollars are pouring into executive pockets," says Sarah Anderson, a report co-author. In 1980, the average US CEO was paid 42 times as much as the average worker when tax rates for the richest stood at 70%. Today, that ratio has widened to 380 times – exacerbated in part, no doubt, by the fact that CEOs are able to dramatically reduce their tax burdens by a reduction in top tax rates, as well as several new loopholes introduced in recent years. In fact, some companies paid their CEOs more money than they paid in taxes. Take Aubrey McClendon, CEO of Oklahoma-based Chesapeake Energy, who was paid $17.9m in 2011, while his company gave Uncle Sam just $13m on sales of $11.64bn..." "The Institute for Policy Studies found that 26 of the 100 highest-paid US CEOs took home more in pay than their companies paid in federal income taxes. On average, each of these company bosses was paid $20.4m last year. Another scam that CEOs pull on the taxpayer is called "deferred compensation". The way that works is simple – most taxpayers are expected to pay 35% of their income in taxes the year they earn it. But a CEO does not have to pay the tax until they claim the cash which can be earning interest in the mean time. Depending on how the money is invested, CEOs can engineer a substantial profit. This allowed Michael Duke, CEO of Walmart, to sock away $17,028,615 tax free in 2011, roughly 774 times more than one of his employees would have been allowed to do under normal tax rules. Yet the money these CEOs makes shrinks into insignificance compared to the money that hedge fund managers make. Take Raymond Dalio, who was paid an astronomical $3bn in 2011. This titan of Wall Street had to pay just 15% in taxes because the money was considered "capital gains", as opposed to the average citizen who would be required to pay 25% (in income tax). Cost to the taxpayer in 2011: $450m." http://www.commondreams.org/view/2012/08/20-7</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345580812000-24</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt; In fact, some companies paid their CEOs more money than they paid in taxes. Take Aubrey McClendon, CEO of Oklahoma-based Chesapeake Energy, who was paid $17.9m in 2011, while his company gave Uncle Sam just $13m on sales of $11.64bn..."&gt;&gt; Thanks for posting. These loony conservatives don’t realize that all money earned belongs to the government just like all profits from corporations belong to the government. The government, however, is benevolent and generally lets the wage earners keep some of the money before they hand the rest over to the government. Sometimes, however, sneaky executives and greedy corporations forget that it all belongs to Uncle Sam. They want Uncle Sam to let them keep more of the\Uncle Sam's money</Msg><Username>lrseab</Username><Timestamp>1345580812000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345582770000-25</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Render unto Ceasar what is Ceasar's.... In my business we give no more than is necessary or desirable. Laws taxing people are put there for a purpose, often not a good one, and laws granting deductions and exemptions are also there for a purpose good or not. This is representative government in action. Go ahead and vote for someone who makes you feel good about keeping your own money. If there are enough of you, things will change. If there are not, you will have to blame your countrymen, not the government. Government is simply the machinery of whoever holds the reins, however tenuously. EAM's article cites some pretty weak examples of loopholes, namely capital consumption allowances (which are incredibly generous in 2011) and deferred compensation. Capital consumption allowance benefits are a Republican idea which President Obama has adopted greatly. These benefits allow companies to write off the cost of certain capital acquisitions immediately or more quickly. Capital-intensive companies such as energy companies benefit tremendously from this program. Deferred compensation is simply somebody electing to be paid their pay in a later year, hardly a loophole in my opinion. JM$.02W</Msg><Username>flyktning</Username><Timestamp>1345582770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 16:59:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345583057000-26</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Respectfully Mr. Aholemale, You parade here as the most altruistic human on the planet, as do all your hyper liberal comrades. If you were in the same position as those CEO's you are griping about -- YOU WOULD DO EXACTLY THE SAME AS THEY. That's the problem with most liberals, they hide behind this do-gooder lyingBS to mask the nasty SOB's they really are. Have you ever noticed how nastiassed most of the liberals that appear on MSNBC really are? Dispositions just about a micrometer away from that of a junkyard dog. Break out your barf bag and watch MSNBC, pay particular attention the the women guests mouths, these are some vile SOB's.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345583057000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345583296000-27</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Render unto Ceasar what is Ceasar's...." Why don't you tell that to JUG EARS' treasury secretary tax cheat Timothy Geithner, the man that sets monetary policy in this country. SEE -- what hypocritical phony SOB's you truly are.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345583296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345584194000-28</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Another scam that CEOs pull on the taxpayer is called "deferred compensation". The way that works is simple – most taxpayers are expected to pay 35% of their income in taxes the year they earn it. But a CEO does not have to pay the tax until they claim the cash which can be earning interest in the mean time. Depending on how the money is invested, CEOs can engineer a substantial profit." Smart! Do you actually think ONLY CEO'do this?!! Well now, the big boys are also not immune to trying to dupe the IRS and save a nibble of the huge pie destined for the greedy government. Good. An interesting article which self-admittedly "suggests" valid points. Tax this! -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1345584194000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 17:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345586673000-29</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You won't believe this but I will tell you anyway. I have done peoples' taxes for 34 years and I know from experience that when it comes to cheating on taxes, there is absolutely no correlation between ideology and compliance. Liberals, conservatives, moderates and apoliticals are honest in equal percentages. Lefty doesn't want to buy bombs; righty doesn't want to pay bums. Cheaters always dress it up in some sociological good, but the bottom line is the bottom line. They want the money for themselves. So heap scorn on Timothy Geithner if you like and I will join you. He sets a horrible example and should have been fired for what he didn't do - render unto Ceasar.</Msg><Username>flyktning</Username><Timestamp>1345586673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345587682000-30</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, what these "loonies" don't understand is that ALL their profit comes from the workers, the production and creations of the workers below them. Workers who pay their taxes, to build roads, schools and all the other day to day infrastructure to make getting rich so possible. None of these CEOs are compensated for what they do, which is basically be the face of a corporation, and yammer catch phrases like 'off shoring' and 'golden parachutes'. The CEOs need to learn to pay their fair share and quit expecting society at large to carry their welfare lay about ways.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345587682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345587961000-31</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a family friend that was CEO of Baker/Hughes He worked his way up from the bottom. Worked for 30 years before becoming CEO. I would say he paid his dues and earned every million he made!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1345587961000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345588021000-32</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Agqut, the name calling debate loser. I am only the third most altruistic man on the planet at best, and I am in nearly the same position as people who can avoid taxes but I pay them, in the hopes hill people like you can drive on decent roads to go educate yourselves. And speaking of dispositions being nasty, how far might you be beyond a rabid junk yard dog? Have you ever cared once about anything besides your own hate and misery? Oh but I bet that's jug ears and the so called (corporate owned) liberal media's fault too.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345588021000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345588714000-33</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good points all. But also, this report wasn't simply about CEOs making obscene levels of compensation (far more in the US than other nations). It wasn't about them avoiding taxes and finding every loophole to do so (like Romney's 13%). It was about them getting taxpayer money. subsidies, to do all this. Taking money from all the downsized, likely to be laid off soon workers, too many without health care, too many who are having trouble making ends meet even WITH two jobs, it's always these folks on the hook when huge banks want paid back for their investement gambles and CEOs want obscene compensation. And these levels are obscene. If the nation wasn't going to h*ll in a handbasket I'd say painted Easter eggs for all, but this extreme level of shystering in a time of crisis is disgusting and immoral!</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345588714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 18:38:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345592048000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is too frickin funny!</Title><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345561730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't get the song Hit the Road Jack out of my head and almost referred to Obama as Jug Ears in a conversation today. Thanks.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1345592048000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345593172000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Extreme Right Wing Doubts On Ryan</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345130853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure em glad you were not correcting my sixth grade school work!</Msg><Username>gewizmeto</Username><Timestamp>1345593172000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 19:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345596370000-36</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"what these "loonies" don't understand is that ALL their profit comes from the workers" ---------------- Analmale, you are one naive infantile thinker. When I worked for an employer I was under no illusion that I had any vested interest in the employer's business. We (employees) used to refer to ourselves as whores because essentially the employer used us and dumped us when he was done with us. There was no history, no obligations, no sense of entitlement, we got paid for our hours work and that was the end of it. I once had 36 W2's in one year, I had worked for 36 different employers. The point is, only a communist thinks in the terms that the worker is the greatest member of a society. And you Analmale are a communist if you believe what you wrote above. Communism on paper is the ultimate form of government, the unfortunate fact is that everywhere communism has existed it always ends in disaster. "Workers who pay their taxes, to build roads, schools and all the other day to day infrastructure to make getting rich so possible." Sheer idiocy! Where did the worker get the money to pay taxes? That's right, from a business that made something and sold something. Analhole, when ever did a worker give anybody else a job. JUG EARS postulated the same idiot theory of "you didn't build that", in that one moment JUG EARS exposed the contempt he holds for the American entrepreneur. JUG EARS also espoused his view that the workers should have a stake in all American business like his rape of bond holders when he gave the UAW union a stake in General Motors(pure communism). General Motors is doomed to failure because business is tough enough without an outside interest interfering. Perhaps GM won't fail completely, if JUG EARS gets reelected GM can always get the blueprints for the Trabant to manufacture. If you don't know what t he Trabant car was, it was a communist government produced automobile infamous for horrible quality. It was a two cycle engine, gasoline and oil had to be mixed in the gas tank, the operator's manual said to shake the car to mix the gas before driving after a fill up. That's sounds just like the high functioning idiocy you are purveying here Analmale.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345596370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345597017000-37</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We have a family friend that was CEO of Baker/Hughes" ------------------ There is a greedy skunk on two fronts. JUG EARS hates greedy CEO's(but he took a lot of campaign cash last time from them, not this time ha ha) JUG EARS hates anyone associated with drilling holes in the ground to supply the USA with energy. Baker Hughes filthiest company on the planet, JUG EARS is saying wind and solar can supply the USA's energy requirements as the JUG EARED hypocrite flies along in Air Force One burning 3600 gallons per hour of petroleum fuel.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345597017000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345597150000-38</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" I am in nearly the same position as people who can avoid taxes but I pay them," ----------------- You're either a goddammed liar or a goddammed fool.</Msg><Username>agqut</Username><Timestamp>1345597150000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 20:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345599462000-39</Id><Topic><Title>New Report: CEOs Massive Salaries Subsidized By Your Taxes</Title><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345576398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 15:13:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor angry Agqut. You DO realize your extreme hate and name calling means you're hardly worth debating with, long ago lost, and it even detracts from the good point or two you actually do make. I am neither a fool nor a liar, and I'm certainly not god#%#%#%#ed. I'm bless baby, blessed. So I don't mind paying my taxes as a business success because I might need a road to drive on, a hospital to go to, I need schools for the rugrats so they do not grow up be illiterate animals that slaughter their elders, like the generation we seem to be raising, many of whom are angry for very good reason. I have no problem with being seen as a "Communist". I'm more like Woddy Guthrie said a "commonest". I'm of the Marx Engels original school, filtered through the Wobblies, the IWW, and has nothing to do with Stalinism. So I clearly know every bit of value in an item comes from nature, handled by the worker, the builder, the craftsman, the designer. CEOs and salesman help, but the world can do without them and probably be much better off. I suffer through the "corporatism" our country (USA) has morphed into, the socialism for only big banks and rich corporations at the expense of everyone else. It hasn't been "democracy" for a very very long time. Just because you think you get to vote for Tweedle Dumb or Tweedle Rich, does not mean this nation has democracy, or much of a future frankly. I manasge to make my living, and plan my future, in spite of that, and on the bones of that. And I'm fine with it. Again, understand only the weak say the things to me you do, and only the weak think they have any affect in doing so. I gather we'd have a far different style of talk in person. Please use the public transportation my tax dollars have created to ride the roads me, and others built, to go to the schools we funded and at least try to expose yourself to the basics of civil discourse. It may do wonders for your mood.</Msg><Username>ebayalphamale</Username><Timestamp>1345599462000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-21 21:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>