<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358948856621-1</Id><Topic><Title>This Garbage stock is now the same price prior to earnings</Title><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1358868430902</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-22 10:27:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PayPal's new scam of "forcing" ebayers to pay for items out of their checking accounts is causing an exodus from the site. people like to use their credit cards to gain reward points and have the security of the credit card company to help fight for your rights. buy buy ebay, U blew it this time !!!</Msg><Username>buy_sell_sell_buy</Username><Timestamp>1358948856621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 08:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358955064100-2</Id><Title>There goes EBAY again</Title><Msg>Markets are at their highs of the Day. And EBAY (piece of #$%$) is already 1% lower than the high of the day. WHAT A PIECE OF #$%$</Msg><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1358955064100</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 10:31:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358955079336-3</Id><Title>After listing several items for sale on Ebay some interisting info</Title><Msg>I just finished listing and selling several objects on ebay here is what I found. Very frustrating to list items as their photo uploaded would not upload the photos or only partial upload a number of photos, I had to try several times to get the photos uploaded time wasted 10 minutes. Shipping calculator just so frustrating not all options one time next time too many. Their listing helper was in one instance opened on the easy version, next listing opened in the advance mode, shipping was reset to some magical numbers that I never set. All in all it takes aprox. 30 minutes per item too list one item, with taking photo's set up and insertion. Between Ebay and PayPal Costs are about 15% Previously used ebay ( several years ago) to sell many items and didn't take so long and costs were lower. Shipping rates have gone sky-high since the start of the new year Overall I feel that Ebay is shooting themselves in the foot with higher costs for listing and selling harder to list items They may be making money right now but I bet they are loosing sellers, and will in the near future see total listings going down and income going down. Using paypal as a debit card should help there bottom line but PayPal does not work like your debit card with different rules and regulations all tilted to PayPal favor. JMHO of course but the experience was frustrating, time consuming for the amount of money made from selling.</Msg><Username>pcforyou</Username><Timestamp>1358955079336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 10:31:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358958730881-4</Id><Title>Ebay was up 1.65% this morning</Title><Msg>Now the piece of #$%$ is down with the markets sitting near the tops of the day. POS POS POS POS</Msg><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1358958730881</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 11:32:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358959718872-5</Id><Title>WOW</Title><Msg>EBAY is up a penny as of now. NOW that is a good stock to have. YEAH RIGHT</Msg><Username>marty81274</Username><Timestamp>1358959718872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 11:48:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358984379911-6</Id><Topic><Title>After listing several items for sale on Ebay some interisting info</Title><Username>pcforyou</Username><Timestamp>1358955079336</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 10:31:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes me about 5 minutes per ad to list on Ebay You might try changing the way you upload your pictures Are you using "standard" "copy web files" "self hosted" or "basic" when uploading pictures?</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1358984379911</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-23 18:39:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>