<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373345461464-1</Id><Topic><Title>"You really need to find some friends or just someone real to talk to I feel sorry for you now :-( You're all ALONE. . ."</Title><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1373288314292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 08:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Sybil. No one is fooled that you ever have "friends". You've lived on this chat board longer than even 13 year Johnie Osborne. You believe the same myths, and hate the same people, using the exact same words, while you cuddle "Sully", who intelligent people know is still you, only shows you're the loneliest sock puppet troll of all. You wasted 10,000 IDs that sputtered 100,000,000 words in 100,000 posts at me, accomplishing nothing. I am alive and well. "Nothing" is your epitaph. You'll have to share it with Johnie "I wrecked my own family" Osborne. It would be completely sad if you were not the same poster. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373345461464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 00:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373346077680-2</Id><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Msg>I'm so very happy this long restful summer with my family. My garden is blooming, my grand kids are playing peacefully and I know my latest graduating students are headed to much more productive lives than being long term chat board trolls, or post and ID deleting beancounters. Maybe I'll re-post some Best Writer posts. The Board Elders unanimously agree that one poster in particular is badly missed. Along with all the many intelligent posters they ran off. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373374400340-3</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>............../´¯/)........... (\¯`\ ………... ............/....//........... ...\\....\ ……….. .........../....//............ ....\\....\.......... ...../´¯/..../´¯\.........../¯ `\....\¯`\ .. .././.../..../..../.|_......_| .\....\....\...\.\.. (.(....(....(..../.)..)..(..(. \....)....)....).) .\................\/.../....\. ..\/................/ ..\................. /........\................../ ....\..............(.......... ..)................/ ..</Msg><Username>marin_beencounter</Username><Timestamp>1373374400340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 08:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373374604347-4</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you still molesting your grandchildren?</Msg><Username>pota_is_a_loser</Username><Timestamp>1373374604347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 08:56:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373375352347-5</Id><Title>Going to $60?</Title><Msg>Keep dreaming! eBay is a dog - listen to it bark - woof woof!</Msg><Username>skirtt_chaser</Username><Timestamp>1373375352347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373377407999-6</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Are you still molesting your grandchildren?" Hey not everbody is like ole Sully here, some people actually have morals. ROTFLMFAO!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sully_the_drunken.dwarf</Username><Timestamp>1373377407999</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373377817326-7</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY DOES NOT PRTECT SELLERS USING INTERNATIONAL FIRST CLASS MAIL</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1373180014483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 02:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"get what they desrve." Wow I may want to take another crack at that sentence. Well that's what happens when Sully posts drunk. ROTFLMAO!!!! "HICCUP" Sully</Msg><Username>sully_the_drunken.dwarf</Username><Timestamp>1373377817326</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373379845107-8</Id><Title>Good Morning Fellow Ebayers</Title><Msg>It's a great day to Ebay In fact everyday is a great day to Ebay You want it they got it</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379845107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373379890649-9</Id><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Msg>It should have NO problem breaking $60 this week</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373380272359-10</Id><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Msg>That would me, myself &amp; I the self proclaimed king of dirt My pick, shovel &amp; hoe are second to none My selection of nutrients is tops I guess I get the 2013 GREEN THUMB award The competition was STIFF this year but in the end I buried them</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373385584608-11</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what do you have to show for it but dirty hands? Some of us PAY others to do landscaping and yardwork because our jobs (ie: earning money) keep us far too busy. Then again, bragging about growing dope on a public message board when you're 55yo+ is pretty gay.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373385584608</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 11:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373386000252-12</Id><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Msg>Oh poor John Osborne. Haven't you had enough already? Seems you switched ID's (an understatement after your glaring breakdown last month), any reason why ebay_pays_my_bills ID was abandoned? Too much heat maybe? In any event, it's obvious you still haven't absorbed the message into your think, dope laden skull. Your 13 year old board war is over. Time for you to vacate the premises like you and your family vacated your foreclosed houses.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386212733-13</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all can't be the same I'm happy you have a job that pays well and you can afford to pay others for services I don't have much money but I make it up with love My garden makes me happy It grows green and thrives in the sun I harvest my crop and it serves me well Yes, I'm very gay/happy PS: You got something against senior citizens? And if you really want to see "bragging" you should see my YouTube channel</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373386212733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:10:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386365139-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coming from someone with no vested interest in the stock, it's all very myopic. Someone who hinges on his current marijuana crop as the solution to all his problems, yet in the advent of circumventing said problems, creates new problems. Hey Johnny boy, want a solid solution to your problems????? No offense intended.... Get a job. Growing dope while living off the state is not an answer. You need to grab the problem by the balls and get a job and work your way out of debt. You know what they say about an honest day's work? Well, then again, you haven't done an honest days work in the last 13 years since you started trolling this board.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386365139</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386400675-15</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! It didn't take a rocket scientist to figure that one out. Heat? Yea, the FBI came over and had a long talk with me. They understand the whole situation here Hope that helps</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373386400675</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386652743-16</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are YOU so worried about me getting a job? I like what I'm doing I get my EBT loaded each month with FREE money I'll get FREE Obama care next year (won't cost me a single penny and I won't have to pay a fine) It's the new American way of life Just think, in a few years I'll get my Boeing retirement and SS OH YEA</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373386652743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386764789-17</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John, personally, I'm all for senior citizens and 100% for legalization nationwide. I have absolutely no issues with pot, have always believed it is far less harmful than alcohol, however, you give it a bad name. Look up the word, "tact" "a keen sense of what to say or do to avoid giving offense; skill in dealing with difficult or delicate situations. " As someone who once followed the Grateful Dead when I was 18yo, I learned, that you go into a community and abide by their standards. Make waves and you will get a tidal wave cast back on you. This is your problem. You make too many waves when you should probably find some growers board to chat on, not here. Stock market is a hostile environment. throwing your weed culture nonsense in here asks for attacks. you get what you put in it. Now it's time for your to silence and move on.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386764789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373386957584-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your OK in my book Just wish YOU wouldn't post my name and ebay ID "tact" as YOU call it And you're right, I've found other forums to post on these days I'll be here less often for sure Hope you make all the MONEY in the world, I wish you LUCK</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373386957584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373387272647-19</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even after all that, you still haven't figured out what you're doing wrong? To quote your "John Osbourne" namesake aka Ozzy Osbourne in the song Revelation Mother Earth.. Mother please forgive them For they know not what they do One thing I've realized over the years in law enforcement is that some people just never "get it" ~ habitual offenders. Sure, you're being nice at the moment on this new ID but that doesn't reconcile the "death threats" you made towards myself and my family. Remember stating you were going to kick my head in with your red wing boots, etc ??? You marked yourself as dangerous in making threats to anonymous people on the internet. I still believe your dangerous. Glad the FBI has you in their sights.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373387272647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373387714361-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish you the same but you did let intense conversation escalate into personal threats against myself and my family. You stepped over the line and forced my hand in reporting you to authorities as a potentially dangerous person. Granted, I know you have no clue who I am. I never made the mistake of revealing myself in macho bravado to this board as you did several years ago. Your mistake. You make a lot of enemies and you made yourself personal. Something you will be dealing with for years and years. I can assure you one thing. All you have to do is stop posting here in one form or another and you will be forgotten. Some other fool will come in to take your place.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373387714361</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373387817971-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If taking government handouts is the "new way of life", I'm in the wrong country.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373387817971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373388303472-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing's free. you pay for it one way or another. By taking EBT, you've put your family in the national database. I know you don't care about your kids, but they're tagged thanks to you. This is coming from a former NSA database administrator. Your whole family is tagged in the database now. You or them will never pass a level 2 background check for employment. Your credit rating is toast for life. Best of luck. Actually John, it's pretty dumb for pot growers to accept govt funds because accepting federal funds while in commission of a federal crime is doubly punishable. You do know, growing weed is still a federal crime? Growing weed while accepting welfare can nail you a 10-15 year sentence in a federal penitentiary. Guess what, they go after little guys like you. You're worth more to them locked up than free. you might want to re-think your stance bro.</Msg><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373388303472</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373388573997-23</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"some people actually have morals" DRIBBLES, That is one thing that can never be said about you. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass2013</Username><Timestamp>1373388573997</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373388688434-24</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY DOES NOT PRTECT SELLERS USING INTERNATIONAL FIRST CLASS MAIL</Title><Username>stoptheinsanity2000</Username><Timestamp>1373180014483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-07 02:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRIBBLES, I intentionally spelt it that way to see if you would bite hook, line and sinker. AND YOU DID!!! What a sucker yiou are. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass2013</Username><Timestamp>1373388688434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373389804086-25</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't say I remember making that so called "threat" and did I actually say you would die from my Red Wings? Can you link me to my post? Were you posting under a different ID? Was I? PS: The FBI has it's eyes on all the posters here</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373389804086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373389952776-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Boards BEST Gardener</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373380272359</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't reveal myself The "deceased" James Roberge revealed who I was to this board. Hope this helps (as he would say)</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373389952776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373390255368-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! Free room and board for life on the taxpayers DIME Where do I sign up I need a hip replacement and a bridge fell out of my mouth on my birthday As I age I could really care less about what happens to the world around me No one cares about my garden except me I'm in the process of making a new kind of growlight It'll be cheap to buy and cheap to run, low heat and good results ONLY IN AMERICA</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373390255368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:17:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373390422426-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay $54.25 and MOVING FAST</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373379890649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll never work again so I have nothing to offer Uncle Sam Level 2 clearance? I left the aerospace industry long ago I moved on to GREENER pastures - LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373390422426</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373393799836-29</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong as usual just like that idiot Alaskaclown was. Once again Fool I'm not "Dribbles". I guess all the shots to the head you took on the sports message boards has left you totally ignorant, but then again you were pretty stupid on those boards too. LOLOLOLOL Such an easy target you are, just throw out any bait and you bite(the wrong hook of course). ROTFLMAO!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sully_the_drunken.dwarf</Username><Timestamp>1373393799836</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 14:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373394565926-30</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"law enforcement"? I highly doubt that with the stalking you've done here, posting names &amp; ID's Not a chance</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373394565926</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 14:29:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373403302214-31</Id><Title>Ebay's Going to $60</Title><Msg>That will be an ALL TIME HIGH</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373403302214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 16:55:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373405510571-32</Id><Title>The next PayPal is NETE..up $1.10 or 22% today !</Title><Msg>Worldwide mobile commerce payment !</Msg><Username>bomber1882</Username><Timestamp>1373405510571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373405573683-33</Id><Title>Good momentum, good go to high 60s!</Title><Msg>If market stays high then it is possible..</Msg><Username>sam_boy4u</Username><Timestamp>1373405573683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373411487365-34</Id><Title>Citigroup rated ebay as buy</Title><Msg>Today. Google it.</Msg><Username>boomyy</Username><Timestamp>1373411487365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 19:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373423535434-35</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone here knows it was John Osborne (John's Joint) who was publicly drooling over his young son's Boy Scout members and had his own grandson taken away for his grandson's protection. We see you're back to you "projecting" again with all your many failed IDs.</Msg><Username>id_dejour</Username><Timestamp>1373423535434</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373423747315-36</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep those cards, letters and calls coming. There is no reason not to expose Johnie O for all his 13 years of publicly posted crimes here. I see he's back to faking up his recs and crashing down yours. It will be my gift to you when that suddenly stops.</Msg><Username>id_dejour</Username><Timestamp>1373423747315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373423907212-37</Id><Topic><Title>Alive And Well In Beautiful Philadelphia. The Home Of Free Speech.</Title><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1373346077680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 01:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you only had a nickel for every time you thought you knew I'm right here not over there. . .</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373423907212</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373424041990-38</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the same gift you gave James? We gardeners think alike Hope that helps PS: My Red Wings have your name on them!</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373424041990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:40:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373424257588-39</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay's Going to $60</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373403302214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 16:55:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Johnie Boy, everyone knows you have no skin in the stock game, come have a nooner with me, you'll always have skin on my tiny little loofah. Lickity lickity.</Msg><Username>flyktning_loofah</Username><Timestamp>1373424257588</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:44:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373424371225-40</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Johnie Boy, any intelligent person would know your threats are about to put you in a cage. Come have a nooner with me before they force them on you. Lickity. Lick.</Msg><Username>flyktning_loofah</Username><Timestamp>1373424371225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:46:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373424906014-41</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't go to jail for threatening to kick a fat guys but with American Made Red Wing Boots especially in Texas</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1373424906014</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 22:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373425432163-42</Id><Topic><Title>ebay_pays_my_bills is now johns_joint ??????</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1373386000252</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 12:06:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next time my "Warriors" try to get out of our armchairs we won't align with a 13 year long idiot chat board troll known for molesting Boy Scouts and obsessing over a long ago poster who ruined every bit of our, and the Hammerskin's programs. You'll do ok in prison though John, just be a soap picker upper and someone like Flyktning will surely feel sorry for you. We no longer do. You wrecked it all.</Msg><Username>kfir.alfia</Username><Timestamp>1373425432163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 23:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>