<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372916470578-1</Id><Topic><Title>WHOA!!! What a ssssslap, John. Ignored.</Title><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1372864277905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 11:11:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm so glad you share me and John's disease. Same words, same obsession, same names, same jabber delusions, but why does we get burning red septic lesions when we squeeze out our every post?</Msg><Username>flyktning_onde</Username><Timestamp>1372916470578</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 01:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372936100827-2</Id><Title>HAPPY 4th OF JULY</Title><Msg>John, Fly, Sully, Middy and all other good people here..... have a great day. This country is beautiful and free! -Sully Rules</Msg><Username>sullys_ebay_board</Username><Timestamp>1372936100827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 07:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372968486723-3</Id><Title>eBay Top Rated Status</Title><Msg>Did you know that even though you meet all requirements for Top Rated, eBay can at their whim remove your top rated status? This means you pay 20% more for fees and Paypal holds your money for 21 days. Please understand that you still meet all requirements for Top Rated status! This has happened to me and I have stopped buying and selling on eBay until they raise me back up to Top Rated status. Each Month this will cost eBay about $2,000. If you have experienced the same unfair treatment, please stop buying and selling until eBay raises you back up too. This is the only recourse we have against eBay. Together we can make a difference! Are you listening eBay stockholders? Please complain to eBay about this unnecessary and unjust loss of revenue!</Msg><Username>bdlgold</Username><Timestamp>1372968486723</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 16:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372973920579-4</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook and many other platforms don’t offer the opportunity to specifically target like offers of Local Corp with premium content</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372610642842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:44:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the sectopr finance 548 results Page 1 of 55 Should You Use a Tax Professional for Your Tax Preparation? Categories: If you have difficult taxes with deductions and property, professional tax preparation can help. Learn more about when you should call in a pro....more Is Debt Financing or Equity Financing Better For Your Business? Categories: Making Money Read about the differences between debt financing and equity financing, and which option would be best for your business....more Financing Surgery Based on the Payments You Can Afford to Make Categories: Life Events Financing plastic surgery is much like financing any other product that entails payments. Find out about what it entails!....more Tips to Remember When Purchasing a New or Used Car Categories: Life Events Learn more about car financing for a new or used car. Read more to help you decide whether you should finance a new or used car....more Financing Surgery Based on the Type of Procedure You’re Having Categories: Life Events Financing surgery can be done, depending upon the procedure you need. Learn about what’s available for financing....more Why You Should Stick With a Used Car for Your Teenager Categories: Life Events Read more to learn why you should buy used when it comes to your teenager’s first car....more How to Protect Your Personal Finances During a Divorce Categories: Life Events Learn how to handle divorce finances to best protect your interests. Learn what you can do to help yourself during divorce....more Learn Why Financing a Psychology Appointment Requires Some Thought Categories: Life Events Financing a psychology session can be done, no matter what your means. Read more about how to go about getting help....more Less</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372973920579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 17:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372995845466-5</Id><Title>Buy Now Price</Title><Msg>Their Buy Now Price seems way simpler. Why bother doing the auctions? What percentage of transactions are completed with auctions?</Msg><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1372995845466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 23:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>