<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-26"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369578007981-1</Id><Title>Ebay's Milo hurt an important patent of Local Corp</Title><Msg>We also fundamentally believe that our pattern portfolio is undervalued, so we think the value of our IP will be realized as we make progress and protecting our life under our patterns. We have a dozen patterns, three of which are in the emerging pay-per-call space, a multibillion ad revenue opportunity in mobile. We’re actively reviewing potential infringes of our pay-per-call intellectual property and expect to take action to preserve our IP raised in mobile later this year." Source: Transcript of Conference Call (Read the complete text on Seeking Alpha) •12 patents issued, 8 pending »Key patents –Local web indexing (for indexing local web sites across the web) –Pay per call for local and commercial searches via a mobile device (multiple patents) •The billion dollar industry question: How do we monetize mobile? –Dynamic cascading menu search (for product search on tablets and smart phones) –Bulk domain registration and content management (for very large scale SEO</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1369578007981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 10:20:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369583208393-2</Id><Title>within the past few weeks</Title><Msg>every seller that I'm in contact with has said the same thing: both page views and sales are DOWN</Msg><Username>zescrowman</Username><Timestamp>1369583208393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 11:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369609860686-3</Id><Title>Interesting Thread</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=78631a4b-b530-3be5-8fa1-cfdcb958c00a&amp;tid=1369495871912-94c37095-175f-4b10-ad19-78b897a08140 Great stuff! Go to the head of the class. ;-D Enjoy your evening!</Msg><Username>dr.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1369609860686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369614098192-4</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting Thread</Title><Username>dr.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1369609860686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 19:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The most "interesting thread" is that you are the fake Professor Madbezos. I's obvious when none of the 247 board trolls here bother you. They know. And we know. You must dress in your Master's clothes. Funny!</Msg><Username>shaq.factor</Username><Timestamp>1369614098192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369615485365-5</Id><Topic><Title>It's Not Really Fair Is It John Osborne Ebay's Failed z50com and VW And All Your Faggo IDs Blithering.</Title><Username>id_dejour</Username><Timestamp>1369531253652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 21:20:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John z50com can never end his failed board war since his incredible guilt manifests itself as masochism. Flyktning has it too, compounded by a sociopath's lack of empathy and extreme narcissism. PS: My friends should check their emails. Ian's monthly report is extremely funny and factual this time.</Msg><Username>shaq.factor</Username><Timestamp>1369615485365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-26 20:44:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>