<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359976037563-1</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay's Milo hurts patents of Local Corp</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1359495976652</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 16:46:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A localization service is provided that provides users with online information on local retailers that sell particular products. A user can perform a search using a web page associated with the localization service or by searching using an internet search engine. The user's search includes a search origin. The search origin may be defined in terms of location information such as a place name or a postal code. A search for a particular product at local retailers may be made using search parameters such as search origins, product names, model numbers, product categories, and product attributes. The localization service may provide the user with search results in the form of web pages that list which retailers sell the desired product in the vicinity of the search origin. A targeted advertisement server at the localization service may use display criteria to determine which targeted advertisements should be displayed for the user.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1359976037563</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 06:07:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359992982501-2</Id><Topic><Title>ebay going to break old high of $58.21 back in nov.29 2004 then it had later split feb 17 2005 2-1 $42.21</Title><Username>tonyd1950</Username><Timestamp>1359908159777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 11:15:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes I totally agree, I was also looking at a stock split possibility. I had owned this stock back early on when it split a few times; I did very well. However, I had to sell it all for the daughters wedding. I am at that time again where I can make a few more investments. I feel that after all the cut-backs, re-structuring and layoffs, companies have tons of cash on the side lines and things are ready to explode. I believe we are at the bottom of another great five year bull market. JMHO It looks like everything is going the way of E-commerce with the cell phones, credit cards, etc. They keep saying cash will go away as well, hence PayPal. Ebay/PayPal will only profit because they are in the forefront of all these activities. I would welcome a split! Enjoy your day please</Msg><Username>back2da50s</Username><Timestamp>1359992982501</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:49:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997291229-3</Id><Topic><Title>eBay almost minus one % today. Don't worry next 3 days should be 59.8 $</Title><Username>jorge.kunz</Username><Timestamp>1359407326991</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:08:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>johnmorrill470</Username><Timestamp>1359997291229</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:01:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360009061655-4</Id><Topic><Title>Do You Think EBAY is a BUY?</Title><Username>krajnakvickie</Username><Timestamp>1359993585858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:59:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>orchardistemily</Username><Timestamp>1360009061655</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:17:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360025008947-5</Id><Title>EBAY ranked # 6 in a top ten most Overvalued index at Extreme Value Stocks Check it out, Awesome.</Title><Msg>EBAY ranked # 6 in a top ten most Overvalued index at Extreme Value Stocks Check it out, Awesome.</Msg><Username>roseleeroselee</Username><Timestamp>1360025008947</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 19:43:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>