<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372568830274-1</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can never understand this board because you cannot admit the manipulations of one portly poster. It is possible but unlikely I caused you to lose an ID. If I did, I am sorry for being drawn into such a cesspool. Most likely you lost your ID to the same Texan who took Madbezos's. Face it.</Msg><Username>flyktning</Username><Timestamp>1372568830274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 01:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372586970114-2</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the same thing when I read her post You didn't delete her ID he did Even I would've liked her to acknowledge that he existed But I didn't push her on the subject</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372586970114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 06:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372593319062-3</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke John Osborne, everyone saw you and Flyktning publicly admit to deleting posts and posters. Everyone knows you blamed others. No need to weave more lies. No wonder you're already in hades. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1372593319062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372593385706-4</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would she be friends with someone who has personally publicly threatened her many many times? LOL! No wonder you're already in hades. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1372593385706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372593559427-5</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good you're practicing for hades. Real good. Thankfully, in Amherst we have AC. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1372593559427</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 07:59:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372593735161-6</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John, wait for my order to start creeping out Midwife and making threats again. Remember I'm the boss.</Msg><Username>flyktning_onde</Username><Timestamp>1372593735161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 08:02:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598109816-7</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor fake Sully with NO friends She already said she has no problem with me in her own words You can try to twist it anyway you want but her writing in on the wall PS: She won't even admit you exist - LOL</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372598109816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598240838-8</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saturdays high was 112.6°</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372598240838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372598423225-9</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can buy all the amethyst i want on ebay without AC I'll bet you don't even know your school colors I can picture you walking in the quad with those rose colored glasses So hip, so cool, so YOU</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372598423225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372599236846-10</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fly, you admitted on the board you took that ID then you told me you saw me start being nicer afterwards. It was as if you thought you taught me a lesson of some sort then were proud of yourself afterwards thinking said lesson worked. I never mentioned I lost the ID prior to that point and I was never nasty to you prior to that point. That changed things just as Shack et. al. has changed things. Not the first two times I thought someone was my friend then got stabbed in the back. It used to happen in high school all the time.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1372599236846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372601680508-11</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have a poor memory. You accused me of reporting your posts several times before I ever did. Why would you do that? You were anything but nice in the months leading up to your ID deletion. It is impossible to know what caused a deletion, but yes I reported a post just before you were deleted so it could have been me. High school sucks for most people. Thank God there is life afterward.</Msg><Username>flyktning</Username><Timestamp>1372601680508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372604613656-12</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Even I would've liked her to acknowledge that he existed But I didn't push her on the subject" Don't you love these people who take on Charlie's enemies, use his rhetoric, buy his accusations and then say there is no Charles and they aren't part of any board war? Masturbates 247 was the latest and he fell hook, line and sinker. What's-her-name in Chicago never stopped believing Chuck was a whole slew of posters.</Msg><Username>flyktning</Username><Timestamp>1372604613656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:03:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372607717436-13</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My point was it is so "high school" to be two faced. This board was full of people (Shack, et al.) who would be a friend under the ID one thought they were then make up a new ID to take a shot at their "friend". (2) Fly, why do you care so much about who is for or against your friends or enemies? While we're talking here, why was it so important to you that Lori or I or Mad or anyone else be on your "team" and fight "your" battles along side you? Did I ever demand you attack elike? seichiro? just because I didn't like them? So what if people think there is a Charles or there is not a Charles or if they fall for posts hook, line &amp; sinker, etc.? Why do you care so deeply? That is something I could never understand.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1372607717436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 11:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372610642842-14</Id><Title>Facebook and many other platforms don’t offer the opportunity to specifically target like offers of Local Corp with premium content</Title><Msg>The Top Three Ways A Premium Online Ad Network Delivers Scale And Localization 5/2/2013 - Adotas ADOTAS – In some ways, it’s easier than ever to mount a national online advertising campaign. Programmatic platforms and DIY advertising tools promise the opportunity to reach a target audience at scale, using technology that eliminates the untold hours advertisers would otherwise have to spend contacting sales teams from publisher sites around the country or the world. But not all of these large-scale programmatic offerings solve the problems advertisers have in reaching their target audiences in local markets. Facebook and many other platforms use geo-targeting and publicly available user data to serve ads to the intended audience, but they don’t offer the opportunity to specifically target the kinds of publisher sites and vertical category pages where those ads will appear. If consumers aren’t seeing your ads — if they’re not positioned above the fold or adjacent to relevant content — the money you’ve spent for that inventory is wasted. From a branding perspective, it’s valuable for your ads to appear alongside content in trusted media sources, and on sites that cater to markets and verticals valuable to the advertiser. Advertisers and brands are increasingly acknowledging the merits of advertising on the local level, with local online advertising predicted to rise from $23.7 billion to $25.7 billion by the end of 2013.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372610642842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372619793689-15</Id><Topic><Title>Facebook and many other platforms don’t offer the opportunity to specifically target like offers of Local Corp with premium content</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372610642842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 12:44:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Premium networks like Local Corp can guarantee placement adjacent to the content users most desire Premium content adjacency: Above-the-fold inventory adjacent to premium content — the content most relevant to and valued by users — will always be premium inventory. It’s increasingly important to make sure your ads appear alongside premium content, and simple branding backs that up, with more than 60 percent of agencies and marketers saying premium content assists branding objectives. When consumers notice your ads near the targeted content they value, they’re more inclined to feel an affinity to your brand, which has a halo effect that spreads wherever else they go. Premium networks can guarantee placement adjacent to the content users most desire.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372619793689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 15:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372635219148-16</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's high was 115.5° This kind of weather doesn't fare well for LARGE TUNA</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372635219148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372641232725-17</Id><Topic><Title>It was a hot one today in the desert</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372480227362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 00:30:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow John, when you get all sweaty, hateful and demented you remind me of our Ripple Club dates. I counted beans in pairs then! So cool. We looked like the Pet Shop Boys.</Msg><Username>flyktning_onde</Username><Timestamp>1372641232725</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>