<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372143185585-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why the valuation of Local Corp with lower than 40 million is one of the biggest jokes the Nasdaq had ever seen</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370206414151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 16:53:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flankenking flankenking • Jun 22, 2013 6:23 PM Flag0 users liked this posts users disliked this posts 0 Reply Lori Chavez comes from Local Corp Debunking 4 Local Advertising Myths 6/21/2013 - MediaPost by Lori Chavez Fact or fiction – local advertising is a waste of online marketing dollars? If you answered fact, you could be missing a potential $38 billion market opportunity. The challenge is how do brands take advantage of deploying the right tools to reach and engage local consumers. Not everyone gets it right. Of all the misconceptions brand marketers have about ad networks and local advertising, perhaps the most critical is that it can’t be done well. In reality, it’s been something of an after-thought. As a result, some brands don’t embrace the nuanced approach necessary to target those markets in a way that drives desired results. Today, it’s essential to debunk some of the long-standing myths that are holding local advertisers back from success in their local market. Here are four brands need to know to avoid the pitfalls of misinformation</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372143185585</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 02:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372150835647-2</Id><Title>I'm so wired weird and awake I called the soldier's Mom!</Title><Msg>Yep, and he's still dead for Bush's lies. I weep when I think how we PWs misused her. Worms who caused worm food. I weep when I think of the US building Israel's shelter yet me and Allen aren't invited. None of our team is invited. What? Some of is are going to dress up like HIM again for the end times. It's all we have left.</Msg><Username>kfir.alfia</Username><Timestamp>1372150835647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 05:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372164926052-3</Id><Topic><Title>"Team" Is Only John And Fake Sullied</Title><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1372130474165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 23:21:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRIBBLES, 1) Why do you want to be me? 2) Why do you self-rec your own posts? ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass2013</Username><Timestamp>1372164926052</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 08:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372165070756-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay Discussion Boards</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1371994233732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRIBBLES, 1) Why do you want to be me? 2) Why do you self-rec "thumbs-up" your own posts? Just so you know, I am the one who voted "thumbs-down" on your post. ROTFLMAO!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass2013</Username><Timestamp>1372165070756</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 08:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372168392455-5</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay Discussion Boards</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1371994233732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ebay discussion boards are DOWN</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372168392455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372180255034-6</Id><Title>DO NOT SIGN UP FOR GLOBAL SHIPPING PROGRAM AS ONCE YOU DO YOU CAN NOT OPT OUT!!</Title><Msg>They will not let you edit your preference once you have said yes and the calculations are way off for pricing. An example one lego minifigure that weighs less than 3 ounces would cost 43.76 in shipping charges and 42.00 in import charges on a 275.00 c3po lego minifigure to japan thru the program and 16.95 in a small flat rate box priority without the program. Worst part about all this is you cant turn it off in the site preference. You have to into every listing from then on and uncheck the box for each and every listing unless you close your account and open a new one under a new email address!! are #$%$%$ing kidding me!!!</Msg><Username>mountainl8ke</Username><Timestamp>1372180255034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182014561-7</Id><Topic><Title>DO NOT SIGN UP FOR GLOBAL SHIPPING PROGRAM AS ONCE YOU DO YOU CAN NOT OPT OUT!!</Title><Username>mountainl8ke</Username><Timestamp>1372180255034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:10:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would you have a new program that says "give it a try" and "get started now" and then not be able to return back to the way it was before you pressed the button?? Are you f&amp;%$#ing kidding me!!</Msg><Username>mountainl8ke</Username><Timestamp>1372182014561</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372195846619-8</Id><Title>My favorite for a buy of Local Corp is Rakuten, because this will produce the biggest synergies - First US-Buy was Linkshare in 2005</Title><Msg>Japanese Internet shopping portal Rakuten is buying Internet Capital Group partner Linkshare Corporation for about $425 million in cash. Rakuten is very well known in Japan for its on-line shopping, travel, golf reservations, community and greeting cards sites. This will be the company’s largest acquisition to date. “We are extremely pleased that LinkShare has agreed to be acquired by Rakuten under the proposed terms,” said ICG chairman and CEO Walter Buckley. “Since we acquired a stake in LinkShare in 1998, we have strongly believed in LinkShare’s potential to be a market leader, the strength and vision of its management team and the value it delivers to merchants and affiliates, added Buckley. “We view this event as a great illustration of the ICG model, as it demonstrates the full cycle of owning, building and realizing the value of one of our Core partner companies.” AP provides a little background info on LinkShare: LinkShare runs a performance-based online advertising business called affiliate marketing service. LinkShare places client companies’ advertising on blogs and other Web sites managed by individuals, and the site creators can get compensation once the viewers of the sites buy advertised goods. Established in 1996, Linkshare posted a revenue of $32 million for the fiscal year ended June last year. Its clients include such companies as Dell Inc. The deal is still subject to customary closing conditions, but is expected to reach completion within about four to six weeks. ICG is expecting to get about $150 million out of the deal. Chris is a staff writer for WebProNews. Visit WebProNews for the latest ebusiness</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1372195846619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372200428294-9</Id><Topic><Title>POST OF THE YEAR = "agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!"</Title><Username>post_judge</Username><Timestamp>1371910766840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 10:19:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a sick FK. Hope this helps.</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1372200428294</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 18:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372205667437-10</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a sick FK. You must be going crazy(er) now that your sickness has been forced to an end. Whatever will you do? Perhaps come out of the closet in more ways than one? Hugs!</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1372205667437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 20:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372205992770-11</Id><Topic><Title>agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1371748954855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:22:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.S. Your Johns_lunch_bucket ID shows just how over the edge you have gone now that your playground has collapsed. I do feel sorry for you. Hugs!</Msg><Username>midnite.oasis</Username><Timestamp>1372205992770</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 20:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372206625183-12</Id><Title>Ebay should be ashamed of promoting Canada Shipments</Title><Msg>Ship to Canada via Staples and UPS will come back for more money and wreck your credit rating. CAN YOU SAY SCAM!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>upstocanadaascam</Username><Timestamp>1372206625183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 20:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372216661371-13</Id><Topic><Title>POST OF THE YEAR = "agqut, Gina, Shack, and countless others were......, ME!!!!!"</Title><Username>post_judge</Username><Timestamp>1371910766840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 10:19:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Midnite. It's good to see you as I thought the Flyktning Gang's public threats had run you away, like so many of the other intelligent posters. My wife and I just watched Wings Of Desire again, a movie about angels that gets better with each viewing. Narry a bean counter in it.</Msg><Username>madbezos.angels</Username><Timestamp>1372216661371</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372216994828-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay Discussion Boards</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1371994233732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are always DRIBBLES. Why do you repeat yourself and flap John Osborne's same endless lies? Oh I forgot, it's all you have in life. ROTFLMAO!!!!!!!!!!! Sully</Msg><Username>sullyinmass.2012</Username><Timestamp>1372216994828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372218210635-15</Id><Topic><Title>Ebay Discussion Boards</Title><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1371994233732</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-23 09:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just couldn't resist What was your name again? I guess it really doesn't matter as your life is just a fantasy PS: Why do you want to be Sully?</Msg><Username>johns_joint</Username><Timestamp>1372218210635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>