<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364618223756-1</Id><Topic><Title>SELL SHORT wait for $25!</Title><Username>happydayis</Username><Timestamp>1363897159947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:19:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>25 HUNDRED???</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1364618223756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 00:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364647586915-2</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY Bounce Report !!</Title><Username>gosselinwillie</Username><Timestamp>1363629476162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 13:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thenks!!11</Msg><Username>ednamutchler</Username><Timestamp>1364647586915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 08:46:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364650093239-3</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY Bounce Report !!</Title><Username>gosselinwillie</Username><Timestamp>1363629476162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 13:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that very useful!!!</Msg><Username>wilma.castillo</Username><Timestamp>1364650093239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 09:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364653085121-4</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY Bounce Report !!</Title><Username>gosselinwillie</Username><Timestamp>1363629476162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 13:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank for search!</Msg><Username>janetschmitd</Username><Timestamp>1364653085121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 10:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364657593293-5</Id><Topic><Title>From Cactus Lane to Flowertown</Title><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364614369028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke mentally diseased Johnie Osborne, ebay's failing z50com, who trashed his own daughter, wife and grand child being our 12 year long board troll and stalker here, it is hard for you to claim someone else is psychotic when we see you here trying to daily stalk, post info on people, harass your enemies in 1000 hate spams, and even taunting those you think are dead. Your 10 to 1 posts reveal who the psycho is. We all see your psycho loser tail used to dwell at Hanover Circle and lost that too! I was so proud that HE sent your address and I posted it. No amount of you daily hate spam has any impact here (except on you) and DHS is watching no one but you and your Klan cyber bully cyber stalking buddies (or is it just your other IDs?). Time is short and yours is getting shorter. We all see you're useless and can't help yourself. I bet you take the lone shooter psycho way out and your posts fully confirm that. Just one of many Flyktning regrets. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364657593293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364658730407-6</Id><Title>Is It Really 3 Psychotics Here Or Just John Osborne, Ebay's Failing z50com, In All His IDs?</Title><Msg>We all see dozens of psychotic posts a day, all hating the same people, all using the same phrases, with the same typos. It would be a sad commentary on the diseased mental states this stock attracts if it was really 3 people doing it, but I bet it's just John Osborne, ebay's failing z50com, in all his IDs. Any fool could see his 12 years of daily hate has only cost him everything: his daughter, his grand baby, his wife, his drug growing shack on Hanover Circle Cypress CA, and his sanity. Mommy Yahoo is allowing his sick screeds to gather info for DHS since we all see John is heading to Adam Lanza land. Even Flyktning abandoned John but that will never lessen his liability. Poor broke delusional John. He spews into the internet and all it does it take from him and leave him lonelier and broker than before. The light at the end of the tunnel will bring his long overdue sobering. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364658730407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364659022910-7</Id><Topic><Title>From Cactus Lane to Flowertown</Title><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364614369028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"post info on people" The evidence shows YOU post info Where have I posted your Ebay ID? Is that mine in the post I'm replying to. . .</Msg><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364659022910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364659903446-8</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY Bounce Report !!</Title><Username>gosselinwillie</Username><Timestamp>1363629476162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 13:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice job!</Msg><Username>ronniem88a</Username><Timestamp>1364659903446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364662641225-9</Id><Topic><Title>From Cactus Lane to Flowertown</Title><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364614369028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:32:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People simply deserve to know who John Osborne z50com is, as he is a daily danger to himself and others. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364662641225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364662790874-10</Id><Topic><Title>Who Posts More? Angel or Pays</Title><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364659107152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:58:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A simple understanding of statistics shows you always have erroneous input, therefore always erroneous conclusions. No one but you believes the other psychos aren't just you. You're a known liar and your posts reveal your insanity. When the bright light shines on you, all will be clear, for the first time in your "life".</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364662790874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364662862521-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is It Really 3 Psychotics Here Or Just John Osborne, Ebay's Failing z50com, In All His IDs?</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364658730407</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your posts are quite revealing of your sick mind. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364662862521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364663652024-12</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY Bounce Report !!</Title><Username>gosselinwillie</Username><Timestamp>1363629476162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 13:57:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very helpful report!</Msg><Username>burkejosh93</Username><Timestamp>1364663652024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 13:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364667305964-13</Id><Title>Madbezos is GONE</Title><Msg>Charles, you can't bring him back He's GONE You're all alone here now Yes, we are all ONE poster ~ LOL</Msg><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364667305964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 14:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364670500579-14</Id><Title>Nothing has changed here con't</Title><Msg>"..... blues to a world which will continue to reject him because of his irrational behavior and vile rantings. If Charles had even a spark of positive self-esteem in him he would realize that all of this is a waste of his time and he would walk away from it and get a life. But he can’t because this IS his life - a life that is defined ONLY by the need to cry the blues about how much he and others have been wronged and to constantly warn others about the evil perpetrators. Charles is a rebel with the futile cause of the exaggerated victim who takes no responsibility for his own negative behavior - behavior which in his mind is always justifiable in the service of his mission. This futile and worthless mission defines both his personal and political life. And it is all for naught. It is very sad indeed. But do not be angry with Charles. Pity him and then ignore him, for he is a very sick man,. Actually, ignoring him is what John should do but he can’t because he enjoys his ongoing ownership of Charles too much to stop taunting him. John and Charles are fatally attracted to each other. They have been involved in a very, very sick dance with each other for many years. But John is always the winner of the sick games. because to him it is simply sport like shooting ducks in a pond while he conveniently languishes on the Ebay board in between checking the status of his auctions, whereas to Charles it is all very serious and vital to his warped self-esteem that he constantly blow the trumpet of victimization at the hands of the evil Ebay message board perps. And for the rest of us? We are entertained at times, but mostly we are bored and wish it would all just go away. TUT * now Charles refers to the gang as FLYKTNING’S gang”"</Msg><Username>fact_hors_dourves</Username><Timestamp>1364670500579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364671604648-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing has changed here</Title><Username>fact_hors_dourves</Username><Timestamp>1364670155114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:02:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor sick Johnie Osborne z50com! We heard this under all your other IDs, endlessly, every day for 12 years. Long before your enemies got here, and long after they left. Everyone sees you up here melting your lonely hate, stalking people and taunting people that you mistakeningly think are dead. YOU will spend eternity with that. That's you Car-Ma! We can ALL see why your wife, daughter, grand baby and Flyktning left you. HE left long long ago with HER. Everyone with a wife 20 years younger raise your hand... ha, thought so losers. Beep to the Mother...in' beep yo! Get a tow truck and move these rusting junk heaps to the side.</Msg><Username>a_car_that_fine</Username><Timestamp>1364671604648</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364671855342-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing has changed here con't</Title><Username>fact_hors_dourves</Username><Timestamp>1364670500579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:08:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We already heard you Johnie Osborne z50com. That's a lot of words to just repeat your 12 year mantra of "that cwazy wabbit!" Go out and kiss a rattlesnake, it's long and hard and as close to warmth that you'll ever get again. Oh, and by the way, remind Flyktning that HE left with HER and lives happily ever after! I can hear that radiator of hate boiling over now. Beep beep! Move it scrap heaps. Rusting old wrecks.....</Msg><Username>a_car_that_fine</Username><Timestamp>1364671855342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364672343196-17</Id><Title>John Osborne z50com Wastes a Lot Of Words Trying To Be "Board's Worst Author". She Wins!</Title><Msg>Generally, good writing contains facts, not a string of lies. "Someone" labors under the illusion that if we all were quiet, the board would be nice, but we all sadly see John Osborne z50com continue her failed board war all be her lonely self. These are simply publicly observable facts. I hope that helps.</Msg><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364672343196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364673821623-18</Id><Title>1 Man 1 ID</Title><Msg>1 Charles Kelly 1000 ID's He'll be anyone but his FAT self. . . PS: How's the diabetes treating you lately?</Msg><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364673821623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364674567856-19</Id><Title>crwatch website</Title><Msg>Looks like you're a week overdue on that domain payment Anyone want to be Charles? ROTFLMAO I just might have an extra $9.99 laying around</Msg><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364674567856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364678612292-20</Id><Topic><Title>1 Man 1 ID</Title><Username>ebay_pays_my_bills</Username><Timestamp>1364673821623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 16:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor broke g @ y failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy. You're not a man, never were, and we all see you posting the same endless mental illness out of all your many IDs year after year after year while z50com goes down the drain. Your diabetes isn't why me, Mom and Grand Baby Dimebag abandoned you! It's your sick mind!</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1364678612292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364678918001-21</Id><Title>So Why Does My Failed Daddy Failed Grand Daddy (John Osborne z50com) Want Exposed Daily?</Title><Msg>One would think a known tool fencer and liar would keep a lower profile. Failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy, when you molested me and abandoned me to a McDonald's dumpster, the man you cyber stalk brought me food. He met you and even let you live although you melted up here daily. What a waste of oxygen you turned out to be. Hopefully, with better parents, Grand Baby Dime Bag might have a chance in life.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1364678918001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:28:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364679218180-22</Id><Topic><Title>John Osborne z50com Wastes a Lot Of Words Trying To Be "Board's Worst Author". She Wins!</Title><Username>angel.madbezos</Username><Timestamp>1364672343196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 15:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Team failed Daddy failed Grand Daddy: parents gone and deeply shamed, grand parents gone and horribly shamed, wife gone, daughter gone, grand baby dimebag gone, son a psychotic lunatic like g @ y old Dad, fellow IDs limping along repeating themselves daily. 1 to go: z50com and tool fencing the trailer.</Msg><Username>jen_dimebag</Username><Timestamp>1364679218180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364696414081-23</Id><Topic><Title>EBAY RAISING FEES AGAIN UNDER GUISE OF LOWERING THEM</Title><Username>masterbates649</Username><Timestamp>1363714244981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 13:30:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeff, your statement is simply untrue. This is what sellers cannot stand with eBay - the constant LIES under the ruse of a lowering fees. I didn't even hear of these increases until I went to use EBAY's FEE Calculator this morning - I was shocked when I saw the fee increases coming. CLEARLY, I can see how much my fees will go UP (and drastically up!) in the next 2 weeks by using your own fee calculator. As an example, I sold a $2100 item, my current fees were $84.55, but my New Fee shows it will be $189.00 in two weeks - we're talking more than DOUBLE, and you're saying my fees will increase slightly?? Please. I can barely make a profit on anything I sell on eBay the way it is, and this surely is forcing me to find other avenues to sell, or just the final straw that will force many sellers to throw in the towel. What's the point of sellers listing on eBay if most the profits or proceeds will be taken away? This is going to backfire on eBay BIG TIME. Ebay is just a parasite killing off its host (Sellers) - soon the host will be dead, and so will eBay.</Msg><Username>autochains</Username><Timestamp>1364696414081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 22:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>