<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346043174108-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mayer's First Move</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345938719664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't tell retail shareholders, as all the CEOs and BODs over the past 5 years have said "we are here to build shareholder value", and then disappoint them by keeping the stock at the same price while the BOD has enriched themselves with free options. If you say it, they believe you, and then you've tied up their money. Easy to say "just sell". People held and believed, and with good reason, as they saw some like Bartz take the stock up to $18, and somehow, 2 CEOs later, and a new board, we're under $15. And frankly, you don't know if all the Yahoo employees are "not complaining". If they've seen their stock go from $30 to $15 over a 5 year period, and they're not complaining, at least to themselves, they are not normal while watching GOOG and others take off. Personally, I've made money selling calls, but they haven't fetched much of a premium out of the money.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346043174108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 00:52:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346064411809-2</Id><Topic><Title>Nobody but spammers on Yahoo!</Title><Username>r1mtnking</Username><Timestamp>1345924498292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 15:54:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Yahoo mail is nothing but spam -- even though that address has never been given out or used for correspondence.Go figure....</Msg><Username>bowsprit999</Username><Timestamp>1346064411809</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 06:46:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346065724984-3</Id><Topic><Title>New Message Boards are Awesome!</Title><Username>view12347</Username><Timestamp>1345956657144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:50:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>7th grade, another good one, I'm just coming down to your level to have a laugh. Why so serious???</Msg><Username>view12347</Username><Timestamp>1346065724984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346066593933-4</Id><Title>Yahoo ripe for the picking</Title><Msg>Don't they realize less people will come to these Message boards, thus less people will see the ads! Someone in Yahoo mgt. is not very bright! Look for yahoo to be bought out at a very low price!</Msg><Username>trattles</Username><Timestamp>1346066593933</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346066949888-5</Id><Title>YHOO to $38? don not tell BOD or Marissery-read</Title><Msg>6 inShareYahoo! Is on Track to Reach $38 (Or More) Published: August 22, 2012 | Be the First to Comment Sebastian Bergmann Call: Buy Yahoo! Nasdaq: YHOO Contributor: Ben Michaud. Firm: H.M. Payson &amp; Co. Type: Hedge Fund. Location: Portland, ME. Timeframe: 2 Years + Recent Price: $14.95 Target Price: $38.00 Strategy: Event/Special Situations. Disclosure: The author of this report had an active position in this security at the time of its posting. Disclaimer: This is a highly-abbreviated version of a full SumZero report republished with the author's consent. On a sum-of-the-parts basis, Yahoo! is currently worth approximately $18.67 per share – with non-core assets of $12.27 and an estimated $6.40 valuation for Yahoo! “Core”. I estimate this figure will rise to approximately $23.32 per share by mid-2015 through a combination of growth in Alibaba’s enterprise value to $55B from $35B, growth in EBITDA to $1.8B from $1.564B and annual FCF generation of ~$579MM, for an estimated 3-year IRR of ~16% per annum. Where Yahoo! becomes a highly compelling investment is through simple yet intelligent deployment of ~$18B of non-core assets over the next three years. A large-scale, multi-stage buyback program at an average price of ~$18.90 per share boosts the mid-2015 target price to $38.01 per share, for an estimated 3-year IRR of ~36% per annum – this figure only rises with tax-efficient disposal of certain non-core assets and/or a higher-than-expected terminal EV/EBITDA multiple. Such math has compelled many a hedge fund manager to take a position in Yahoo! – entrenched management, a dysfunctional Board and lack of strategic focus, however, have led to the oft-posited conclusion that Yahoo! is where hedge fund managers go to die, as Yahoo!’s perceived hidden value has thus far failed to be unlocked. The latest hedge fund manager to give it a go is Third Point – an activist, event-driven investor with a ~6% stake representing over 10% of AUM (by far its largest single-security position). Through a recent settlement with Yahoo! in order to avoid a proxy contest, Third Point received three seats on the Board (25% of total seats), two of which are occupied by restructuring experts Dan Loeb, head of Third Point, and Harry Wilson, Chairman and CEO of turnaround and restructuring boutique MAEVA Group. Since Third Point first disclosed its position in September 2011, three key overhangs – lack of strategic direction, dysfunctional Board of Directors and unsubstantiated Alibaba valuation – have been addressed, two of which were the direct result of Third Point’s involvement (the sale of half of Yahoo!’s Alibaba stake was largely independent of Third Point as far as I can tell). With the key overhangs removed, I believe the path is clear for Third Point to catalyze the series of shareholder-friendly transactions so desperately sought by prior hedge fund investors over the next three years, alongside likely operational improvements. Yahoo! announced that it is suspending its $5B buyback program designated to return the Alibaba sale proceeds to shareholders – the stock sold off considerably in the wake of the announcement upon fears of a dilutive acquisition-focused turnaround strategy. While the rumors currently flying around the tech blogosphere of Mayer wanting to make a “big splash” acquisition are relatively disconcerting, I strongly believe shareholder capital is in good hands with Third Point representation on the Board. A more likely scenario is that the Board gave Mayer the opportunity to start from scratch with all aspects of the Company, including capital allocation. Valuation Yahoo! Core trades at ~2.1X NTM EBITDA versus ~5X for AOL, its nearest comp – a multiple that fails to reflect Yahoo!’s strong cash flows, leading brand name and strong traffic base. Valuing Yahoo! Core at 5X NTM EBITDA and assuming $12.27 of non-core assets per share, Yahoo! is worth $18.67 per share today. The base-, mid- and best-case mid-2015 scenarios are $38, $45 and $67 per share. All three scenarios assume mid-2015 EBITDA of $1.8B, an Alibaba EV of $55B, accumulated free cash flow of $1.74B and a 4-stage ~$18B buyback program. Key differences between the estimated target prices include a tax-free sale of Yahoo! Japan for the mid- and best-case scenarios and a “take-out” multiple for Yahoo! Core in the best-case scenario. Click here to get more research from SumZero. Have great investment ideas of your own? Click here to enter the Value Investing Challenge and win a chance to speak at the next Value Investing Congress in NYC this October.</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346066949888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346067639378-6</Id><Title>NEW MSG BD FORMAT SUXXX</Title><Msg>You dumbed it down, Yahoo. Made it harder for real discussion or debate. Discourages LINKS Very subtle cave in and sell out to corporate interests and stock pumpers. Soon anyone with a brain will be gone and the idiots will reign</Msg><Username>annony_moose</Username><Timestamp>1346067639378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346069117488-7</Id><Title>Emergency Owners Meeting-Look at AOL-BUYBACK &amp;</Title><Msg>special dividend neeed this morning --aol $13 to $35 this year</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346069117488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346069245005-8</Id><Title>yahoo msg boards becoming spam delivery system</Title><Msg>Yahoo cares more about money than free speech</Msg><Username>annony_moose</Username><Timestamp>1346069245005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346069287413-9</Id><Title>AOL-Buyback &amp; Specia Div.-13 to $35 -BOD &amp; marissery</Title><Msg>have to be stopped--we just need buyback &amp; Special dividend</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346069287413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346069399626-10</Id><Title>LOEB-Special Dividend &amp; Buyback--we need this AM</Title><Msg>or many many many Lawsuits should be flying</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346069399626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:09:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346070658966-11</Id><Topic><Title>yahoo msg boards becoming spam delivery system</Title><Username>annony_moose</Username><Timestamp>1346069245005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whole internet in danger of being one vast conveyance vehicle for corporate interests?</Msg><Username>pacificinternational40</Username><Timestamp>1346070658966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346070763142-12</Id><Topic><Title>LOEB-Special Dividend &amp; Buyback--we need this AM</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346069399626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:09:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"or many many many Lawsuits should be flying" Then why don't you file a lawsuit? You keep complaining, but I never see you take any action other than posting on a number of different stock forums. Are you all Bluster reebok77 or are you a player?</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1346070763142</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346072022325-13</Id><Title>AOL Screaming HIgher this morning! UP 150% this Year!!</Title><Msg>How Y'all doing?</Msg><Username>jmambo54</Username><Timestamp>1346072022325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346073211995-14</Id><Topic><Title>AOL Screaming HIgher this morning! UP 150% this Year!!</Title><Username>jmambo54</Username><Timestamp>1346072022325</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Armstrong is a GREAT CEO. We've never had one here at YHOO. I'm still hoping that sanity prevails and we SELL THE COMPANY!</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346073211995</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346073640724-15</Id><Title>I hope Loeb doesn't get the Yahoo Syndrome</Title><Msg>thinking that the co. might grow with no REAL turnaround leadership. 19 takes the co. and where are the buyers? The liars never had any interest after MSFT. They should be sued again and again for deceiving stockholders with their phony "the co. will listening to interested buyers."</Msg><Username>bhark114</Username><Timestamp>1346073640724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346074767525-16</Id><Title>OUR COMPANY MONEY MANAGERS DUMPED ALL YAHOO</Title><Msg>This is kind of odd. I think they viewed it as dead money. I have to agree. I'm even right now but I'm dumping. Better things to invest in.</Msg><Username>stsomp</Username><Timestamp>1346074767525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346075386082-17</Id><Title>New board format sucks.</Title><Msg>I hate the new format... its horrible. What 2nd grader designed this?</Msg><Username>geekcomputing</Username><Timestamp>1346075386082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346075530533-18</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO to $38? don not tell BOD or Marissery-read</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346066949888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo is at it's bottom.</Msg><Username>brex742</Username><Timestamp>1346075530533</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346075667535-19</Id><Title>Loeb=Yang</Title><Msg>Can a new LBO offer be on the horizon?</Msg><Username>toperj</Username><Timestamp>1346075667535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:54:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346075811372-20</Id><Title>Yahoo is destroying itself with this new message board format.</Title><Msg>The simple truth is that almost everyone that is involved with markets uses the Yahoo message boards to some extent. Understanding this my only hope to come out of the disaster is a new stock message board will gain traction on some other site. InvestorsHub, Investors Village, StockHouse or maybe Silicon Investor. How anyone could begin to think about purchasing Yahoo stock understanding how vital to Yahoo revenue the message boards are is beyond me.</Msg><Username>lookmil</Username><Timestamp>1346075811372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:56:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076148328-21</Id><Topic><Title>I hope Loeb doesn't get the Yahoo Syndrome</Title><Username>bhark114</Username><Timestamp>1346073640724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:20:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the co. will listening to interested buyers." I am sure they would if there were any interested buyers. Who would want to buy Yahoo? It can't and won't be fixed. If a CEO proposed buying Yahoo his board would fire him on the spot.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1346076148328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076363864-22</Id><Topic><Title>OUR COMPANY MONEY MANAGERS DUMPED ALL YAHOO</Title><Username>stsomp</Username><Timestamp>1346074767525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:39:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is dead money. Will not see $16 again for a long time.</Msg><Username>justtryingtotrade</Username><Timestamp>1346076363864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076693417-23</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo is destroying itself with this new message board format.</Title><Username>lookmil</Username><Timestamp>1346075811372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes...I use the Sprint board...They have also switched to the new format....It is almost unusable.....Given feedback may times....I really do not think they care. Not sure I would be very happy if was an investor in Yahoo or an advertiser....Maybe time for some of the bloggers to get involved...Their higher profile would likely at least get a response from somebody...but again I question whether they even care.</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346076693417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076915388-24</Id><Topic><Title>yahoo msg boards becoming spam delivery system</Title><Username>annony_moose</Username><Timestamp>1346069245005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 08:07:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree....They block most of what I put up on the Sprint board...It will say a post was put up like 15 seconds prior...but when I check my post nothing shows up!!!</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346076915388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346076995798-25</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO to $38? don not tell BOD or Marissery-read</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346066949888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bought this morning at $14.79.</Msg><Username>shelcorecrust</Username><Timestamp>1346076995798</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:16:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346077437429-26</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo is destroying itself with this new message board format.</Title><Username>lookmil</Username><Timestamp>1346075811372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow it truly is a sad day. Using the message boards for 15 years. Many years ago Raging Bull was better than Yahoo and really so was Silicon Investor--both have gone into oblivion for the most part. Hopefully someone at yahoo changes course--when something works dont try to fix it. They are asking for many less eyes</Msg><Username>erickn122</Username><Timestamp>1346077437429</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346077544164-27</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo is destroying itself with this new message board format.</Title><Username>lookmil</Username><Timestamp>1346075811372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Google and MSN should use this to their advantage. They now have a huge advantage if they set up something better.</Msg><Username>ace_n_z_hole</Username><Timestamp>1346077544164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346077587146-28</Id><Title>Unreal to contrast AOL performance with YHOO! And where is Jack Ma? He has...</Title><Msg>...been very quit and one has to wonder how the 20% deal is coming. AOL sells patents and does share buyback and soars. YHOO caves w/ FB and says may not do share buy backs and drops big. The Mayer/Loeb honymoon is way over and something big needs to be done by YHOO ASAP..</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346077587146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346077733474-29</Id><Title>no power</Title><Msg>Up only 1 to 3 cents, but down more than 10 cents, will be under 13 soon!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1346077733474</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346077897416-30</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO to $38? don not tell BOD or Marissery-read</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1346066949888</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 07:29:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo! Core trades at ~2.1X NTM EBITDA versus ~5X for AOL, its nearest comp – a multiple that fails to reflect Yahoo!’s strong cash flows, leading brand name and strong traffic base. Valuing Yahoo! Core at 5X NTM EBITDA and assuming $12.27 of non-core assets per share, Yahoo! is worth $18.67 per share today.</Msg><Username>netprofitreturns</Username><Timestamp>1346077897416</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346078461604-31</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo is destroying itself with this new message board format.</Title><Username>lookmil</Username><Timestamp>1346075811372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:56:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I remember both...Especially Silicon Investor...I was a regular on the Micron board there back in the mid 90's.....but yes it is a shame that Yahoo really has the market for message boards in the business community locked up and they don't seem to know it or care!!!!</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346078461604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 10:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346080467412-32</Id><Title>Yahoo Deleting Topics???</Title><Msg>Interesting...Where did that Yahoo destroying itself topic that I replied to go?...It was about how bad the new format is....Yahoo just doesn't seem to get it.</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346080467412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346080966780-33</Id><Title>whats for lunch today??</Title><Msg>hope ceo enjoys free lunch today with 5 year $70 000 000 contract for dessert. Also hope employee's enjoy their free lunch paid for with shareholder money. I could live with this but ceo has yet to make any money for shareholders. As a matter of fact yhoo is down around 10% ( in excess of $100 000 000 ) since new ceo took over. Please do not forget that alibaba and yhoo japan windfalls were already arranged while new ceo was still a google employee. Of course in her wisdom shareholders no longer have to worry about this because she has stated that after years of waiting for this windfall she has decided that shareholders will not partake in this windfall. Does anyone know whats for lunch????</Msg><Username>rlclark4</Username><Timestamp>1346080966780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346081587737-34</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Deleting Topics???</Title><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346080467412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just click on "news" on home page, then go to bottom of page and click on all yahoo sites and choose what you want. I like to see the health and opinion sections in addition to others.</Msg><Username>mechicksexer</Username><Timestamp>1346081587737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:33:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346081713012-35</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Deleting Topics???</Title><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346080467412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No URL'S Hope this terd tanks. All it does is help the short analysts.</Msg><Username>wsmcgruff</Username><Timestamp>1346081713012</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346081723314-36</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Deleting Topics???</Title><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346080467412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you need to take some remedial writing classes.</Msg><Username>mechicksexer</Username><Timestamp>1346081723314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346081930651-37</Id><Title>How long will Yahoo shareholders be left in limbo while Mayer reviews what to do with Yahoo's $4.3B from Alibaba Group?</Title><Msg>Mayer needs to make it clear what plans she has for the $4.3B that was promised to Yahoo shareholders. Mayer stinks at PR.</Msg><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1346081930651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346082576831-38</Id><Title>Short Yahoo ..Big brother is deleting topics.</Title><Msg>Does anyone at yahoo realize they are killing the only good thing yahoo has left.. if you send feed back, it is apperent that the people working there can not read.. SELL YAHOO</Msg><Username>dkwilk</Username><Timestamp>1346082576831</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346082582509-39</Id><Topic><Title>whats for lunch today??</Title><Username>rlclark4</Username><Timestamp>1346080966780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:22:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chinese food while Yahoo employees eat gourmet R they fattening the employees up for the slaughter house?</Msg><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1346082582509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346083126015-40</Id><Topic><Title>How long will Yahoo shareholders be left in limbo while Mayer reviews what to do with Yahoo's $4.3B from Alibaba Group?</Title><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1346081930651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mayer and Loeb are planning one day for all the news. Alibaba will pay Yahoo early, there will be a Yahoo Japan deal and Yahoo will make a major acquisition.</Msg><Username>opengslide</Username><Timestamp>1346083126015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346083955339-41</Id><Title>Market up, yahoo down</Title><Msg>Same story, different day. This stock is going nowhere fast. Slow, slow decline in the stock price. Then the new CEO will go out and make a stupid purchase with their cash, and the stock will go down further.</Msg><Username>justtryingtotrade</Username><Timestamp>1346083955339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346084818999-42</Id><Title>Yahoo Going to 3 Dollars, Then Comes Delisting</Title><Msg>this message board format tells you everything you need to know about this fcked up company.</Msg><Username>kasparhauser79</Username><Timestamp>1346084818999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346085025719-43</Id><Title>AOL vs. YHOO</Title><Msg>Tim Armstrong on CNBC this morning looking out for his shareholders, with last year's auction, doubling his share price, now special dividends, etc. AOL, once a bottom of the barrel stock and technology really turned itself around while the Yahoo board and revolving door CEOs all enriched themselves. I've been long, believed in the Alibaba deal, woke up to see Ma take one of the pieces away while Yang was on their board (too much golf?), now Mayer takes the dividend away, etc, etc. What a joke.....it's all about the board, the CEOs, anyone but the shareholders.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346085025719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:30:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346085361730-44</Id><Title>Keep Keeping Your Silence</Title><Msg>Way to go M. Keep keeping your silence. Real comforting to those of us who bought in when it appeared the Board may have finally gotten it right with their CEO choice. They still may well have, who am I to say? But be sure that from the "cheap seats" it is getting more and more difficult to see and-or know that with the longer you keep your silence about your "strategy review" while the stock price keeps moving down and down. Information, that's what you owe us longs ...</Msg><Username>watching_yhoo</Username><Timestamp>1346085361730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085487398-45</Id><Topic><Title>AOL vs. YHOO</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346085025719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You want to see something really hilarious? Go get a1 year chart for Yahoo and then compare it to AOL!! Aol has done 7, yes SEVEN times better than Yahoo. Someone here used to link to those charts, so now Yahoo has prohibited adding Links because they were losing shareholders! You watch!!! Next year RIMM or HPQ or DELL.....or ALL of them......Will seriously OUTperform Yahoo. If you didn't know it by now, Yahoo is a DOG which is absolutely CONTROLLED by the Shorts!</Msg><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1346085487398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085773802-46</Id><Topic><Title>AOL vs. YHOO</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346085025719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:30:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why do so many more people spend so much more time on yahoo?</Msg><Username>gup1x</Username><Timestamp>1346085773802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085855366-47</Id><Topic><Title>How long will Yahoo shareholders be left in limbo while Mayer reviews what to do with Yahoo's $4.3B from Alibaba Group?</Title><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1346081930651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 11:38:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo is overdue for a statement.</Msg><Username>trotlightly34</Username><Timestamp>1346085855366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346085875444-48</Id><Title>YHOO is the worst! Mayer is no help and company just has to be sold ASAP.</Title><Msg>Down every day or up just a few pennies when market is way up. Compare YHOO to any of its peers for the past year! They change things that work, and that users are happy with, because they have lots of employees and they have to do something for the big checks and free food. They need to really clean house of extra employees and sell off parts of entire company. So far MM has only done harm.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346085875444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346085908966-49</Id><Topic><Title>Keep Keeping Your Silence</Title><Username>watching_yhoo</Username><Timestamp>1346085361730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mayer needs to speak up.</Msg><Username>trotlightly34</Username><Timestamp>1346085908966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346086078710-50</Id><Title>Of course Yahoo is down, what did you expect?</Title><Msg>It will stay down until Mayer is gone.</Msg><Username>specialforceshol</Username><Timestamp>1346086078710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346086246573-51</Id><Title>This is the first step we all "herd about".</Title><Msg>Only the powers that be,"STATE CONTROLLED MEDIA".</Msg><Username>wsmcgruff</Username><Timestamp>1346086246573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346086635244-52</Id><Title>I have never before used ignore feature but finally put thecodone and a few of....</Title><Msg>...his obvious aliases (will add more-basically anyone who sings his priases) on ignore. He just clogs up the board. May have to put hotmodel on ignore too. He should just ignore thecoldone.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346086635244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346087137175-53</Id><Topic><Title>I have never before used ignore feature but finally put thecodone and a few of....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346086635244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:57:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi hotmodel!!! LOL!!! ROTFLMAO!!!</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1346087137175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346088575899-54</Id><Topic><Title>Of course Yahoo is down, what did you expect?</Title><Username>specialforceshol</Username><Timestamp>1346086078710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe they chose Mayer (instead of an experienced and competent CEO) becuase they figuered that she would not care much about angry sharehlders as she has more important things (baby) on her mind and the distain from sharholders might not be so bad as since she is pregnant she would get a break. It is amazing how little she has said or done (free food means nothing!).</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1346088575899</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346088861601-55</Id><Title>Marrissa take a Hint from Tim</Title><Msg>AOL to return $1.1 billion to stockholders via special dividend, accelerated buyback plan geez AOl didn`t even sell any stake... hey Ceo &amp; BODs take a hint!!!</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1346088861601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346089578810-56</Id><Topic><Title>Marrissa take a Hint from Tim</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1346088861601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:34:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"AOl didn`t even sell any stake..." Ah, they sold their patents. Duh!</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1346089578810</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346089848334-57</Id><Title>According to My Calculations &amp; Chart, this has been DEAD Money for 4 Years!!!</Title><Msg>Nasdaq is UP about 40%! Yahoo is EVEN to DOWN! Nuff said.</Msg><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1346089848334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346090118598-58</Id><Topic><Title>According to My Calculations &amp; Chart, this has been DEAD Money for 4 Years!!!</Title><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1346089848334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo was at $11 a year ago when coldone told you to buy but you shorted Yahoo. You lose and coldone wins.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1346090118598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346090985777-59</Id><Topic><Title>According to My Calculations &amp; Chart, this has been DEAD Money for 4 Years!!!</Title><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1346089848334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 13:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey coldone, check out Newags thread where he says he has "Never used the ignore feature...", your Nanobot ID is listed there as an alias! The Subject line of THIS thread, for Dunces such as yourself, refers to 4 Years ago. You reply with something a year ago. Can you read? Why don't you go do some research and tell us all where Yahoo was selling for 4 YEARS ago! Go.....we're waiting.....GET BOY!!</Msg><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1346090985777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:09:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346091069886-60</Id><Title>YHOO is a rudderless ship</Title><Msg>Too bad I always liked it</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1346091069886</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346091654431-61</Id><Title>slow chinese water drip torture- down to 11</Title><Msg>be happy- affirmative action hire marissa well make millions. americans are slowly learning!!!</Msg><Username>oregon_bob</Username><Timestamp>1346091654431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:20:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346093185181-62</Id><Title>brought yhoo @ $0.645833 16 years ago at the morning</Title><Msg>Sell sell sell, take my profit!</Msg><Username>teaandtea</Username><Timestamp>1346093185181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346093818771-63</Id><Title>AAPL got 1 billion, YHOO got ZILCH!</Title><Msg>sooooo... where's everyone that was talking about how great YHOO's patents are? come on suckers, show yourselves! AAPL got 1 BILLION from samsung... YHOO got zero, zilch, nada, goose egg from FB. gotta love those sweet, sweet patents that actually turned out to be dried turds. LOL</Msg><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1346093818771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346094783257-64</Id><Title>Seeking insights on a specific options strategy...</Title><Msg>Greetings: Before I ask my real question, some background for those interested in my perspective. As a technologist with 20+ years experience, I know that from technology point of view, there is hardly anything magical about what any of these companies do. I also know that if management is stupid, there is so much waste and lot of #$%$ goes around. When management is strong and knowledgeable, and has right attitude lot of #$%$ disappears. Last year, I had an opportunity to meet with Marissa Mayer at a conference and I feel she has what it takes to turn the company around. So here I am - they guy who never bought even one stock of Yahoo before, looking at options strategy. I am mildly bullish on Yahoo and believe that this baby will see $20+ price before end of the year - they need just one positive announcement. I am looking at Oct12 put spreads for net credit of $1,810.00 for example 10 contracts on each leg. Hope is that stock will rise and these will expire worthless resulting in profit of $1810. If Yahoo doesn't do well, then I loose $190 in this example! Before I take a significant trade, I thought I will check with the community. Does this make sense to anyone? Am I missing something here? LEG-1: Buy 10 YHOO Oct12 16 Put $1.34 $1,340.00 / LEG-2: Sell -10 YHOO Oct12 18 Put $3.15 ($3,150.00)</Msg><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1346094783257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346095015717-65</Id><Topic><Title>Seeking insights on a specific options strategy...</Title><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1346094783257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:13:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forgot to mention that I was intrigued by this SumZero article I received in my inbox... well google "SumZero Yahoo $38" and you will get to the article. I could not post a link here.</Msg><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1346095015717</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346096101321-66</Id><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD FORMAT SUCKS</Title><Msg>YEPP!</Msg><Username>mitt_the_liar</Username><Timestamp>1346096101321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096143485-67</Id><Topic><Title>Market up, yahoo down</Title><Username>justtryingtotrade</Username><Timestamp>1346083955339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 12:12:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the only thing anybody that comes to the Yahoo message board is going to see is endless complaints about the new message boards and how bad they are....and most important, that it seems that Yahoo does not seem to care!!!!</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346096143485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:35:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346096169781-68</Id><Title>put yahoo out for sale......</Title><Msg>yahoo need to be sold to help the stockholder, all I can see management and the board just helping themself...discusting..I AM LONG AND SORRY TO BE....MAYER HELP US...</Msg><Username>tobyt001</Username><Timestamp>1346096169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:36:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346096363027-69</Id><Title>She must take it up!</Title><Msg>She's too smart, too tech profit savvy to become a loser now.</Msg><Username>gup1x</Username><Timestamp>1346096363027</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346096496136-70</Id><Topic><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD FORMAT SUCKS</Title><Username>mitt_the_liar</Username><Timestamp>1346096101321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait till they convert more message boards...It will be the only topic on the Yahoo message board...After all the only reason I am here is because they jacked up the Sprint board to the point where it was unusable. Of interest is the login...A couple of times now in the new format I have had to re-login when I was clearly already logged in at the top of the page.</Msg><Username>phennes591</Username><Timestamp>1346096496136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346096805358-71</Id><Title>YHOO email/stock quotes start popup some f'ing advertisements</Title><Msg>YHOO email/stock quotes start popup some f'ing advertisements look like spams!</Msg><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1346096805358</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:46:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346098420650-72</Id><Topic><Title>put yahoo out for sale......</Title><Username>tobyt001</Username><Timestamp>1346096169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the only answer for YHOO longs. We thought they had dne that last year but it was just another YHOO scam.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346098420650</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346098609080-73</Id><Title>AOL up almost a buck and has trippled in past year. YHOO always down and is down over....</Title><Msg>...the past year and indeed just about forever. And they hire an amatuer CEO who is pregnant and seemingly hiding out from shareholders.</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1346098609080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346098936257-74</Id><Title>The new CEO from Google deserves a pop to $20...</Title><Msg>The new CEO from Google deserves a pop to $20. $7B from Alibaba could also help on it. This should happen in three to four months.</Msg><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1346098936257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346100447191-75</Id><Title>Loeb must be in a coma</Title><Msg>to allow this crap to continue. Wonder if Third Point investors will be receiving a month-end performance statement.</Msg><Username>longshank028</Username><Timestamp>1346100447191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346101711029-76</Id><Title>banks are doing a craw back</Title><Msg>lets do carol..make her pay back lost opportunity freeze all stock options meanwhile Marissa needs to get her act together otherwise no money honey or even stock options seems like someone always has to come in a coprrect past ceo s mistakes...meanwhile shareholders take a back seat..</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1346101711029</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346102170173-77</Id><Topic><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD FORMAT SUCKS</Title><Username>mitt_the_liar</Username><Timestamp>1346096101321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they dont even read the msgs new board is not well received.. its probably just a new tool to better invade your privacy.</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1346102170173</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346102344790-78</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO email/stock quotes start popup some f'ing advertisements</Title><Username>gowiththewave</Username><Timestamp>1346096805358</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:46:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>try google finance. they have better charts. msg boards are dying here.</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1346102344790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346102582393-79</Id><Title>New Format sucks out loud</Title><Msg>Almost unreadable. Whole internet becoming vast SPAM WASTELAND</Msg><Username>cooperrex</Username><Timestamp>1346102582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:23:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346103719818-80</Id><Title>pb%j on what?</Title><Msg>Well, as we all wait for Yahoo! to be something (???) we can now also contemplate what kind of bread the pb&amp;j will be spread on. Is this the kind of bread that rises with body and substance or is it of the wind pudding "Wonderbread" type that leaves you wondering why it is even made?????? Also, it would be nice if Yahoo actually made some bread....... IMO Yahoo! is just flat out frustrating. It has taken them so long to restructure and we have no idea what the new structure will be. I admit, I expected to see more positive things happen faster so that my holdings actually looked like an investment vs. what ever they are now????? Right now they seem to be spreading things thin and on a sour dough with questionable yeast????? ...My skepticism will change when and if Yahoo makes some new bread and the share prices rises above 17.......</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1346103719818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103858455-81</Id><Topic><Title>New Format sucks out loud</Title><Username>cooperrex</Username><Timestamp>1346102582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, just anything Yahoooooo touches.</Msg><Username>blueline_4321</Username><Timestamp>1346103858455</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:44:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346103985624-82</Id><Topic><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD FORMAT SUCKS</Title><Username>mitt_the_liar</Username><Timestamp>1346096101321</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, same here. And I could not logon until I did something strange to do it.</Msg><Username>blueline_4321</Username><Timestamp>1346103985624</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346104376425-83</Id><Title>FCUCCK YAHOO censorship</Title><Msg>Won't take a URL for a New York Times article in a post????? They're just DUMBING DOWN the boards in the name of stopping SPAM Stop the SPAM - don't stop legit. sharing of links</Msg><Username>m.skellern</Username><Timestamp>1346104376425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346104932737-84</Id><Title>AAPL hits new high...YHOO down again. Sweet, sweet patents!</Title><Msg>YHOO and it's sweet, sweet patents! worthless... and P.S.... I'M ALREADY LOGGED IN YOU IDIOTS... do i really have to login everytime i post????</Msg><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1346104932737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346104994738-85</Id><Title>I HAVE AN IDEA!</Title><Msg>For years, clueless Yahoo directors, managers, employees and even the outside CPA (PricewaterhouseCoopers) have allowed a serial spamming ring to operate with impunity on Yahoo message boards. Using unlimited ID's, teaser headlines and multiple URL's, these scammers have stolen from Yahoo users and paying advertisers by offering phony stock market letters and useless advise. It has been a very profitable business run off the backs of Yahoo shareholders . Now, suddenly, the message board format has been changed to prevent these thieves from posting on the revised boards. Therefore, the spammers should use all of their ID's to post messages on the new Yahoo boards and to send complaints to Yahoo saying how bad the new format is so that Yahoo goes back to the old system that allows them to steal again. What do you think?</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1346104994738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346106827794-86</Id><Title>A Useless Company...</Title><Msg>0 share holder value... How much longer to $12?</Msg><Username>fjc35</Username><Timestamp>1346106827794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346106973124-87</Id><Topic><Title>FCUCCK YAHOO censorship</Title><Username>m.skellern</Username><Timestamp>1346104376425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazon doesn't allow URL's in their reviews and they are certainly a more user-friendly, customer responsive company than Yahoo will ever be. You can always put in something that CAN"T be clicked on but needs to be copy-paste. Try h**p plus the url using spaces. Anybody who cares to follow up will be able to do it.</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1346106973124</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346108501779-88</Id><Title>Now we are on track with lots more</Title><Msg>good hires.....maybe an all woman management team!!</Msg><Username>pinionman</Username><Timestamp>1346108501779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346108946635-89</Id><Title>goodness....it's a freaking tupperware party</Title><Msg>gonna have to change name to "yahooettefree" but hey, what the heck..... where else can you find a 3 dollar stock with no debt and billions in the bank free baby cribs, strollers, pampers and for those non lactating moms free formula</Msg><Username>madcow_muffin</Username><Timestamp>1346108946635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110528341-90</Id><Topic><Title>pb%j on what?</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1346103719818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:41:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol, oh well, so much for playfulness. Few folks on this thread have a sense of humor anyway.</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1346110528341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346110554467-91</Id><Topic><Title>Loeb must be in a coma</Title><Username>longshank028</Username><Timestamp>1346100447191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that made me laugh out loud when I saw the headline - thanks</Msg><Username>axis1231</Username><Timestamp>1346110554467</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346110912713-92</Id><Title>The pinata is growing</Title><Msg>More executives, more salaries, more bonuses, but no action up on the shares price.</Msg><Username>fdc17422000</Username><Timestamp>1346110912713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346110976030-93</Id><Title>circus</Title><Msg>Isn't this a circus. Load the company up with women and watch things deteriorate big time. Looks like I had better sell. Never lost trading this dog yet but I am not going to ride it down. A tiny loss is better than a slaughter.</Msg><Username>mechicksexer</Username><Timestamp>1346110976030</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346111447399-94</Id><Title>Wonder how much money they lost</Title><Msg>redesigning everything that worked perfectly well and replacing it with untested and unreadable garbage. I've been using Yahoo for 15 years, but I am really ready to leave for good.</Msg><Username>beyondtheverge</Username><Timestamp>1346111447399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346112333606-95</Id><Topic><Title>A Useless Company...</Title><Username>fjc35</Username><Timestamp>1346106827794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 18:33:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shareholders demand this POS is sold now.</Msg><Username>fjc35</Username><Timestamp>1346112333606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346113919464-96</Id><Title>Ms. Savitt will have to prove herself</Title><Msg>Ms. Savitt will have to prove herself</Msg><Username>dbaaaa</Username><Timestamp>1346113919464</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346114114168-97</Id><Title>Savitt Salary, Bonus, Options Guaranteed</Title><Msg>Performance..........oh well, we'll see. This is a private company pretending to be a public company. Screw the shareholders, let's conduct social politically correct experiments.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346114114168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346114256804-98</Id><Topic><Title>goodness....it's a freaking tupperware party</Title><Username>madcow_muffin</Username><Timestamp>1346108946635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:09:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more than 2 out of 3 new executives hired are ladies. Men couldn't get it done in the last 5 yrs. Women are more of task masters than slick alpha males (takers Not workers).</Msg><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1346114256804</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346114703334-99</Id><Title>YAHOO SUCKS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>..............</Msg><Username>ryanpass05</Username><Timestamp>1346114703334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:45:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346114711499-100</Id><Topic><Title>Savitt Salary, Bonus, Options Guaranteed</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346114114168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marissa's 100Million girl friend club. How much can she give away before any trickle of results is proven So far No Mission and Vision Statement No idea what revenue and income she can create. No idea what she will spend the $4 Billion Alibaba proceed. No idea IF Alibaba $4.2 Billion is forthcoming- ANY DEADLINE or is it never never land?? No idea IF Loeb is quietly dumping stock, or shorting it, after realizing This Is Not Good. We do know Ms. Mayer is spending OPMillions like Sex In The City money whooYAhoooooo !!!</Msg><Username>evilwallstreet</Username><Timestamp>1346114711499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:45:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346114903656-101</Id><Topic><Title>goodness....it's a freaking tupperware party</Title><Username>madcow_muffin</Username><Timestamp>1346108946635</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:09:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uh....remember Yahoo's Susan Decker, oh, and you already forgot Carol Bartz? Women like to selectively remember the good ones. I owned Lucent-Alcatel for years under CEO Patricia Russo, she kept the stock in the $2 range, and got filthy rich off the options. Again, selective memories. A few months ago, a women's business group insisted that Facebook put a woman on their board. That's when the IPO was coming out at $38, and they thought F was going to be a $100 stock. Facebook appointed one, now the stock is at $20, and nobody's interested anymore.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346114903656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346116169498-102</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder how much money they lost</Title><Username>beyondtheverge</Username><Timestamp>1346111447399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 19:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same here altho I still use the finance site message boards included. Probably more than 15 years for me.</Msg><Username>bosshebee</Username><Timestamp>1346116169498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346117155592-103</Id><Title>Swing Trading Long Yahoo Inc. (YHOO)</Title><Msg>Good Afternoon: It seems to me it´s time to get into this undervalued company. New CEO &amp; CMO both expertienced running business with strong trademarks YHOO is right now navigating on mid-term support, and with oversold condition Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>eaglesssnest</Username><Timestamp>1346117155592</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346117161067-104</Id><Title>Yahoo boner - Msg boards now like idiot TV</Title><Msg>Yahoo, by censoring URL's in one move has turned a legitimate discussion format into a one-way medium like TV, no different. All that will survive will be idiots trying to pump/hype to idiots too dumb not to tune out.</Msg><Username>bongo.drum</Username><Timestamp>1346117161067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:26:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117250857-105</Id><Topic><Title>FCUCCK YAHOO censorship</Title><Username>m.skellern</Username><Timestamp>1346104376425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:52:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump it to the top and keep bumping - thanks</Msg><Username>bongo.drum</Username><Timestamp>1346117250857</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346117399511-106</Id><Topic><Title>New Format sucks out loud</Title><Username>cooperrex</Username><Timestamp>1346102582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm leaving the msg boards completely due to yahoo's idiocy and sellout to commercialism which is what the new format represents</Msg><Username>bongo.drum</Username><Timestamp>1346117399511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346118486008-107</Id><Title>so now Yahoo is going to bailout the social website run by the new marketing chief</Title><Msg>do not tell us that that site is worth $50 Mil.</Msg><Username>not_in_2013_wait</Username><Timestamp>1346118486008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118573193-108</Id><Topic><Title>New Format sucks out loud</Title><Username>cooperrex</Username><Timestamp>1346102582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just posted the similar under NAT as it is one I look at. Then I remembered I had bought some Yahoo when the new girl came on board. THAT WAS A MISTAKE. I have always like Yahoo financials but I don't remember any change in the last 15 years or whatever that made it better. Yahoo was always fast to load but when it is difficult to read then I guess I need to find something else. Any suggestions.</Msg><Username>bancroftm60</Username><Timestamp>1346118573193</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346118934157-109</Id><Topic><Title>New board format sucks.</Title><Username>geekcomputing</Username><Timestamp>1346075386082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Probably Yang, all crap comes from him including turning down Microsofts $35 offer. No one more ignorant in the biz.</Msg><Username>hedgefunddude08</Username><Timestamp>1346118934157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 21:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120000864-110</Id><Topic><Title>Loeb must be in a coma</Title><Username>longshank028</Username><Timestamp>1346100447191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish he'd get REAL. Does he really think Marissa is the answer. I hope to hell there is a plan where her pregnancy doesn't matter like a BUYOUT, otherwise I have my doubts of Loeb's competency.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346120000864</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120317330-111</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL got 1 billion, YHOO got ZILCH!</Title><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1346093818771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO. The patents were violated. We had FB by the short hairs. Why do U think that FB almost immediately ran out and bought 600 million dollars worth of patents. They were scared!! YHOO screwed up with another "Bright" mgmt decision.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346120317330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120551067-112</Id><Topic><Title>put yahoo out for sale......</Title><Username>tobyt001</Username><Timestamp>1346096169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agreed. BUT Mayer is NOT the answer.SELL, SELL to a more viable company. We should of had Armstrong as our CEO. Just look what he's done at AOL which I thought was a piece of crap next to YHOO.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346120551067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:22:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346120716853-113</Id><Topic><Title>Savitt Salary, Bonus, Options Guaranteed</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346114114168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what exactly was the problem with the guy who was taking our share price up but he didn't have a computer science degree?????? Thompson, was it??? How many CEOs &amp; severance packages do we have to go through before we get a $$$$ infusion in our investment???? So disappointing...</Msg><Username>sfm211myutmost</Username><Timestamp>1346120716853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:25:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346121021293-114</Id><Topic><Title>New board format sucks.</Title><Username>geekcomputing</Username><Timestamp>1346075386082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where are people posting these days??? I've checked over on IHub but no YHOO activity there. Maybe in time interest will return to YHOO Finance board but all that is happening here currently is politics, some of which I agree with but will not rate or respond because IMO this is not the place for it. Sadly, they must not know of the multitude of sites where they can relevantly post. :( Well there is also ranting &amp; nonsense here also but I don't want to read that garbage either...</Msg><Username>sfm211myutmost</Username><Timestamp>1346121021293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346121440415-115</Id><Topic><Title>put yahoo out for sale......</Title><Username>tobyt001</Username><Timestamp>1346096169781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 15:36:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really, they just need to sell this company. The reason the shares are down so much since MM is because all her actions reflect one who expects to run YHOO for a while and one whom does not understand or care much about how longer term YHOO investors have only seen losses, and are anxious for a faster return and not so much for yet another turn around attempt. They need to get the value out of the YHOO holdings ASAP!</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346121440415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346121993357-116</Id><Topic><Title>AOL up almost a buck and has trippled in past year. YHOO always down and is down over....</Title><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1346098609080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Armstrong should of been working for us, NOT AOL. Where is the thinking at YHOO. I thought Loeb was a thinker but now I wonder. These kinds of moves may prove to be too expensive. Just SELL the company.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346121993357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346122175326-117</Id><Topic><Title>The new CEO from Google deserves a pop to $20...</Title><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1346098936257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 16:22:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This should have "ALREADY" happened!!!! YHOO moves too slow and is hamstrung by INEPT mgmt. This has been the case for quite some time. I thought because Loeb had soo much at stake that things would be different now.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1346122175326</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346122455813-118</Id><Topic><Title>Savitt Salary, Bonus, Options Guaranteed</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1346114114168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 20:35:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scott wasn't taking the share price up much, (it was down under his tenure as well). What he needed to do was get YHOO sold ASAP or at least get Y-Jap sold and AG deal done. But, like MM, he was a kid in a candy shop, in over his head, but hoping to grow into a job he would have for a long time. And the FB suit-which may have had real merit if done sooner and properly (Thompson or YHOO did not even try to negotiate w/ FB) rather than like an ambush-was not a plus. What he needed to do was just sell YHOO! That is still the only real answer.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1346122455813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 22:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346126289881-119</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL got 1 billion, YHOO got ZILCH!</Title><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1346093818771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 14:56:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh, i get it... the patents were SO GOOD, YHOO decided to drop their case against FB?? is that what you're saying?</Msg><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1346126289881</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 23:58:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>