<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344662174119-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mayer really showed her inexperience and hurt YHOO shareholders badly.</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1344617519147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are totally missing the point-definitely not the way she &amp; the board (including mr.loeb) did it! was underhanded &amp; lack of regard for all the shareholders that bought based on promises previous made by mgt.! they could of came out &amp; explained the situation rather than making no announcement whatsoever- knowing that this would be a major concern for the shareholders! it shows continuation of previous mgt. lack of character!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1344662174119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 01:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344682858283-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mayer really showed her inexperience and hurt YHOO shareholders badly.</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1344617519147</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she made the right decision. Tech is not like your typical industry, the speed and capital needs to stay ahead are important. Non of the old veteran CEO's made it work, I think she may just turn things around. Having old school ad people and a attitude CEO didn't work so having an innovative, young and dynamic one may work. Giving money back to shareholders is nice in the short term but will constrain YHOO's ability to make strategic moves if and when they present themselves. Cash is king right now and its the right thing to do at this point considering YHOO has made no progress over the last 5 yrs.</Msg><Username>digi051669</Username><Timestamp>1344682858283</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 07:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344686734981-3</Id><Title>61 million shares jumped out on friday....</Title><Msg>ask Loeb why?</Msg><Username>nuchilou</Username><Timestamp>1344686734981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344687955202-4</Id><Title>Tim Morse--Fall Guy for keeping Shahreholders Money?</Title><Msg>because he stated over &amp; over-even last CC--money going to shareholders</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1344687955202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344688182520-5</Id><Topic><Title>Poll: What Will Marissa Mayer Buy?</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1344622965479</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:22:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like yelp, bing or stripe(new paypal). Something fresh/new in social relm. Something that has a button for different age groups where people can discuss subjects relative to their age as well as a button for all ages.</Msg><Username>camero_returns</Username><Timestamp>1344688182520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344690756529-6</Id><Title>testing</Title><Msg>testing</Msg><Username>sgeneris1</Username><Timestamp>1344690756529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344693526777-7</Id><Topic><Title>You whiners think Loeb is upset??</Title><Username>johnberchick</Username><Timestamp>1344647868261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets put this in prospect...I believe most of the whiners are traders that bought yahoo to hold for a short term because of the presumed cash distribution, now that the cash plan has changed…of course they're complaining. This is not the market of 20 years ago when you bought a stock for investment purpose, now you buy and sell a stock in a NY minute. This is the way the world is you can’t really blame them. PS- I Bought yahoo and will hold till the stock is twofold from yesterday price, I believe it will!</Msg><Username>livefromnewyork1958</Username><Timestamp>1344693526777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 09:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344693694309-8</Id><Topic><Title>You whiners think Loeb is upset??</Title><Username>johnberchick</Username><Timestamp>1344647868261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen.</Msg><Username>view12347</Username><Timestamp>1344693694309</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:01:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344695266232-9</Id><Topic><Title>61 million shares jumped out on friday....</Title><Username>nuchilou</Username><Timestamp>1344686734981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:05:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't understand your post..."jumped out". I See where intelligent people bought in 61 million shares on the cheap Friday. Shares held by weak and scared holders. From the trading pattern on Friday, it appears that YHOO bought in some shares also. This buying opportunity will not last long. If there were only 10 shares of YHOO outstanding, what would each share be worth? Well, we are headed down in the number of shares to split the pie with. If you own YHOO, you must think it is worth more than 16 a share. With every share retired that 16 goes up. I read all the negatives on share buy backs, some work some do not...think AutoZone, then compare it to Sears Holdings , same people but separate circumstances. YHOO is more like Auto Zone, a profitable company using cash generated to buy back stock. Eventually, a point is reached where buybacks work. To date YHOO's buybacks have not work because at the same time, they pi^^ed away billions on bad aquisitions. With a motivated holder of 6 plus%, Dan Loeb, in charge, buybacks will work. My thinking is his target is for a max capitalization of 750 to 800 million before YHOO Japan and the other 20% of Alibaba are sold. Lets value core at 4B Japan at 4.5 after taxes,and the balance of Alibaba at 10B post ipo. close to 20B divided by the then 750M shares and you get what value per share? I see it at north of 25. Ride it out, buy more, relax and enjoy the journey.</Msg><Username>goldeagle14</Username><Timestamp>1344695266232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:27:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344695649869-10</Id><Title>Yahoo options - think it through</Title><Msg>Ok, how can yahoo get the most out of its Alibaba investment? They can sell off 1b without taxes, since they paid that much for Alibaba stake, So lets agree on the first billion in cash (cashing out) Now they can either take the rest in cash or equities. If equities they they avoid taxes in cash they pay taxes. So, if they decide to pursue acquisitions, why not structure it before the actual transaction and take equities instead of cash (this ups their equity by about two billion in tax savings. The announced plan suggested that they would take some in preferred Alibaba shares (in the projected IPO). Preferred shares generally pay out a dividend/interest that common shares do not (note Berkshire's Bank of America preferred holdings). So, this is one way of avoiding taxes and assuring a 6-7%/y gain in a growing company. There are a wide range of other options in the: Why pay 4 billion in cash to shareholders and 2 billion to the IRS category. If Yahoo and Alibaba are planning on an expansion of the US brand of Alibaba and Alibaba holds equities that it bought in the US, then trade them to Yahoo, and have that as a basis for a yahoo stake in that operation. Note that yahoo still will hold a % of the whole which is likely to grow. This way they would increase their growth. As for the 1 billion that they cash out buy back shares to give shareholders a return that actually grow over time as other structural investments payoff and Yahoo moves up in pps. Ok...what are your ideas???</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1344695649869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:34:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344697217940-11</Id><Topic><Title>61 million shares jumped out on friday....</Title><Username>nuchilou</Username><Timestamp>1344686734981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:05:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on!</Msg><Username>view12347</Username><Timestamp>1344697217940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344698059151-12</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo options - think it through</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1344695649869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 10:34:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They can sell off 1b without taxes, since they paid that much for Alibaba stake" Well, right off the bat you are wrong. You better hope the IRS doesn't read these posts or I suspect they will be coming to look at your tax returns. Think in terms of proportional to sale.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1344698059151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 11:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344701214805-13</Id><Title>Imo; Close your eyes and BUY YHOO close to $15/shr..</Title><Msg>Then close your eyes and SELL YHOO when it's close to $16/shr. This idea that YHOO is really worth $18 or $19 a shr is great but it's like saying your favorite MLB team that is 9 games out of first is really a lot better than that. On Monday (again) I'll close my eyes and BUY close to $15 and in 3 weeks (or less) I'll bet I will SELL the same amt ~ $16/shr. It's kind of like kissing your sister; but it's still dough-re-me.</Msg><Username>augustbroker</Username><Timestamp>1344701214805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344704290167-14</Id><Topic><Title>61 million shares jumped out on friday....</Title><Username>nuchilou</Username><Timestamp>1344686734981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 08:05:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>60 + million shares traded = approx. 30 mil. bought and 30 mil. sold....</Msg><Username>hilemann</Username><Timestamp>1344704290167</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344704298772-15</Id><Title>Marissa ?YHOO BOD and Kodak patents</Title><Msg>Hopefully,between Marissa and the Yahoo board of directors they have done their"due diligence concerning Eastman Kodak and the Patents sale". What a "sore eye" for Google to let Marissa escape, and have her harpoon the Google Management team in the patents arena. What an "outstanding investment" to make for your current/future shareholders of Yahoo.Make everyone"man-up" Marissa, you go girl! The Lord is coming and boy is she #$%$!!</Msg><Username>bobbyckirch</Username><Timestamp>1344704298772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344704393273-16</Id><Topic><Title>Imo; Close your eyes and BUY YHOO close to $15/shr..</Title><Username>augustbroker</Username><Timestamp>1344701214805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:06:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes...but yhoo could easily go to 14 or lower...way before it goes to 16.....steady as she goes buying....</Msg><Username>hilemann</Username><Timestamp>1344704393273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 12:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344715250295-17</Id><Title>How much can they get from Yahoo Japan?</Title><Msg>I am not good at math.</Msg><Username>value_oriented_123</Username><Timestamp>1344715250295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:00:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344716981376-18</Id><Title>Yahoo has a long term tax liability of $895,941,000</Title><Msg>What is it actually?</Msg><Username>the_performance100</Username><Timestamp>1344716981376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344717706292-19</Id><Title>Democrat Senate hasn't passed a budget in 3 years</Title><Msg>So how can Ryan cut the budget when the Senate doesn't pass? Wake up yahoo "news"! Where the ____ have you been?!</Msg><Username>fishnman1973</Username><Timestamp>1344717706292</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344718444772-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mayer to replace almost the entire Yahoo executive team, from its CFO Tim Morse on down</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1344654828260</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 23:13:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When she succeeds at getting some board members I will be impressed. They are still the problem.</Msg><Username>u238e</Username><Timestamp>1344718444772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 16:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344720700520-21</Id><Title>Not a good time</Title><Msg>With all the past heads of Yahoo and the present one, and their pay packages, for doing nothing, she wants to make herself look good by the Shareholders paying twice for their mistakes. The yahoo Stockholders deserve and will demand their Cash or Shares received from Yahoo of Japan, No Money,for shareholders, NO money for Officers and Directors!!!!</Msg><Username>rkwirth</Username><Timestamp>1344720700520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 17:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344726889456-22</Id><Title>Yahoo should buy Yelp, Pinterest, or Zillow</Title><Msg>An article on The Big Stock is suggeting Yahoo buy Yelp, Pinterest, Zillow, and some ad tech. It says Yahoo shouldn't consider Foursquare, Vimeo, Zinga, Opentable, or Hulu.</Msg><Username>soma022</Username><Timestamp>1344726889456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344732640481-23</Id><Topic><Title>You whiners think Loeb is upset??</Title><Username>johnberchick</Username><Timestamp>1344647868261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:17:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is what make YHOO special in this environment. You don't need to trade it but rather accumulate on the dips and be patient. Maybe sell a few calls along the way and just sit back and relax. I even sold some September puts. If the shares get put to me, will be at effective PPS of 14.63. Fine by me......in no rush.</Msg><Username>johnberchick</Username><Timestamp>1344732640481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 20:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344733319650-24</Id><Topic><Title>Is it likely going to be just 1 bad day</Title><Username>jctuttle12</Username><Timestamp>1344706086816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 13:28:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No reason for YHOO to change direction. Mayer needs to tell shareholders new plan before we have a change of direction.</Msg><Username>chaolopez</Username><Timestamp>1344733319650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 21:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344735165894-25</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo should buy Yelp, Pinterest, or Zillow</Title><Username>soma022</Username><Timestamp>1344726889456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 19:14:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a little more indepth than the poll</Msg><Username>soma022</Username><Timestamp>1344735165894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-11 21:32:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>