<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345299111016-1</Id><Title>Marissa can't speak for herself_ so X-Yahoo Krisnan spoke for her?</Title><Msg>That was a strange intervu w Bloomberg's Emily Chang..... y an ex-employee tried to speak for Marissa? The take away were: 1- Marissa has not announced her CEO vision for Yahoo going forward (I t has been a month since her hiring) 2- Krisnan said people at Yahoo really love Marissa bcuz she is open and honest w them (we'll see) 3- Marissa wants to replace the GAPING HOLE left by the departure of Levinsohn (That is the COO she needs to run media side like Levinsohn was doing in Santa Monica) 4- Marissa promise to focus on product development and get them out QUIKLY. Krisnan said Marissa wants Yahoo get back to doing what it does best, develop fun exciting products. WHAT ABOUT LAUNCH A MOBILE SEARCH ENGINE W AXIS ??? Pictorial search rather than word search...... which Google is also trying to develop- to search w your camera images.</Msg><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1345299111016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345301965851-2</Id><Topic><Title>Apple Acquisition</Title><Username>ollopa100</Username><Timestamp>1345247236816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 19:47:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAPL should and so should MSFT. Pocket change for them and it is the only thing that will save YHOO shareholders from the debacle of these past years and the gamble of a slow rebuild under Mayer. How about one share of AAPL for 25 of YHOO which would come to about $25 a YHOO share (fair all around) and not dilute AAPL hardly at all. Plus they end up w/ ammo vs. GOOG/MSFT and $12 bil or so cash (ergo picking UP YHOO cheap) and still 20% of AG, the YHOO core, sites, email, patents, Y-Jap asset left over, whatever talent they want to keep (for ex. keep Marissa but get rid of the baby, or visa versa), etc. Winners all around!</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1345301965851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 10:59:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345302338923-3</Id><Title>I guess we would no longer take a share of FB for a share of YHOO.</Title><Msg>If YHOO had not caved on the patent lawsuit they could now take some credit for the FB IPO debacle. No one who bought FB can be very happy. Sorry I did not short it and ZNGA too. YHOO does not need to make a big purchase but needs to sell itself outright ASAP and or do a Dutch auction a la AOL at $22 os so with all the AG and Y-Jap cash. Of course they need to close those deals. Where is Jack Ma hiding and why can't Son do a deal? I see he still holds the biggest share of AG now that YHOO sold 20%.</Msg><Username>dariencat8</Username><Timestamp>1345302338923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 11:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345308598595-4</Id><Title>Yahoo new Idea Of New Layouts</Title><Msg>Yahoo just updated some pages in Finance Page ex: front of Finance and some few pgs. too But not all Ex:earning Calendar I hope a Shareholder Nor Analyst who ask these question Why is Finance pg updated "Layout" but not the Earning pg.?</Msg><Username>tyler.fetty</Username><Timestamp>1345308598595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 12:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345313893784-5</Id><Topic><Title>Marissa Mayer inexperienced as CEO</Title><Username>b2btrillionsayear</Username><Timestamp>1345212460801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:07:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Marissa Mayer should have been hired as CTO and not as CEO. She's a techy and not experienced in running business especially a $15+ bln company as she never ever ran even $100 mln company imho.</Msg><Username>b2btrillionsayear</Username><Timestamp>1345313893784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345316036553-6</Id><Topic><Title>Marissa Mayer inexperienced as CEO</Title><Username>b2btrillionsayear</Username><Timestamp>1345212460801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:07:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they are looking for a COO to add value to the CEO position. That is how it is framed now, because they made the mistake of hiring someone inexperienced in what matters most - turnaround and finance. I bet the COO will essentially be the co-CEO, that saves face for yahoo board, Marissa, and Loeb. But does that mean yahoo shell out another $70 million package for the new comer. This is comedy central at yahoo, wait for the next episode.</Msg><Username>idbtc</Username><Timestamp>1345316036553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 14:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345330330118-7</Id><Topic><Title>Now if YHOO had moved up a buck from $16 to $17 instead of down to $15 during Mayer's first...</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1345238759042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 17:25:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unreal how low the YHOO share price stays with less shares outstanding and Alibaba worth so much more now from just a couple of years ago.</Msg><Username>klmldsi</Username><Timestamp>1345330330118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345348077898-8</Id><Topic><Title>PUT YOUR WORST FOOT FORWARD - A COMPANY POLICY</Title><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1345129541862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 11:05:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5d charts STILL NOT WORKING !! PORTFOLIO PROBLEMS,, MESSAGE BOARD PROBLEMS,, CHART PROBLEMS, , , YAHOO - DO YOU EVEN CARE ???????</Msg><Username>rbh411</Username><Timestamp>1345348077898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 23:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>