<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348294648493-1</Id><Title>Yahoo can't cut search partnership w MSFT unless willing to pay a big fee to break contract</Title><Msg>So Run a beta test search engine outside of Yahoo. It will take about a year for the termination of Bing search as MSFT commitment $$ runs out any way. Marissa knows the flaw and better version search engine than Google. Imagine how awkward the Bing engineers were when they met with Marissa- she found out whom was the key leaders and their issues and shortcomings. Ballmer is thinking MSFT needs a change at Bing like another high ranking Google search engineer/developer.</Msg><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348294648493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:17:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348295148676-2</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo can't cut search partnership w MSFT unless willing to pay a big fee to break contract</Title><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348294648493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your so wrong, yhoo can terminate the contract anytime they want in the first 3 yrs of the ten yr agreement if its not working to yhoos liking. read the agreement before you speak idiot.</Msg><Username>delmundosoftball</Username><Timestamp>1348295148676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348301533380-3</Id><Topic><Title>Again, the only option that is good for shareholders and the company is to sell the entire....</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1348257876973</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh my....... whenever i've thrown out my takeover numbers, i just tack on 33% to current share price (usually good enough). dr gloom brings up a very good point, NO premium on cash, and now that i think about it, probably not a big premium on investments (asian assets) either... doh!</Msg><Username>lapetye</Username><Timestamp>1348301533380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 04:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348301675880-4</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo can't cut search partnership w MSFT unless willing to pay a big fee to break contract</Title><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348294648493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per AllThingsD: "There is the issue of the contract with Microsoft, which could lead to a potentially explosive legal struggle Yahoo can ill afford. “They can try to get out of the deal,” said one person at the software giant. “But that’s a lot easier threatened than done.” Name calling make u look like a #$%$ LOL</Msg><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348301675880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 04:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348307913750-5</Id><Topic><Title>LEAKED- someone spent $350M in the last 15 minutes to buy 22M shares !!!</Title><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1348259432636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strong Buy ! 700 million ! Great Co &amp; CEO</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348307913750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 05:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348316209974-6</Id><Title>theecoldone challenge</Title><Msg>You posted..."Ever hear of options expiration. Stop showing your ignorance." Please explain to the board exactly how options expiration caused the 35 plus million shares to change hands in YHOO. Personally I am as dumb as a box of red bricks, so I need a lot of exact details. If you can not make a post and provide information on how you came to a conclusion, your useless. Personally, I saw 100's of companies with options expiring, and many with much larger outstanding option positions than YHOO. Humm, I ask, why did they not trade 35M shares in the last few minutes of trading and after hours. Much to the relief of the writers, the 16 calls expired worthless, and drove no trading there. Is what we are seeing in the stock volume, MM's returning cash to share holders? For sure I can tell you that the buyers of the recent large volume days have made a very big bet on YHOO. It is obvious for the last several days that some one is buying and someone is selling, and you can bet the buyers are anticipating an increase in stock price. Sellers have many more varied reasons to sell than just the anticipation of the stock trading flat or down. On balance, I would guess YHOO stock being sold recently is moving into stronger hands. I bought a couple myself. I rate YHOO a VERY strong buy!</Msg><Username>goldeagle14</Username><Timestamp>1348316209974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348318432141-7</Id><Title>The next offer coming is for $35 and it's not from Microsoft. Steve Ballmer is too old to run a content / media portal. It will be</Title><Msg>a cable operator and a big one. See ya there.</Msg><Username>jimmy_fabs</Username><Timestamp>1348318432141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348319879671-8</Id><Title>Has anyone noticed the huge</Title><Msg>call option buying for Oct. Never seen it that big.</Msg><Username>bhark114</Username><Timestamp>1348319879671</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 09:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348323302961-9</Id><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Msg>So many different ways for Mayer to give back to shareholders. Maybe a # of special dividends like HFC is doing. 3 bil$ back to 1 bil shares is alot.</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348323945939-10</Id><Topic><Title>The next offer coming is for $35 and it's not from Microsoft. Steve Ballmer is too old to run a content / media portal. It will be</Title><Username>jimmy_fabs</Username><Timestamp>1348318432141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, I think Comcast!! load up !</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348323945939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348324098339-11</Id><Topic><Title>theecoldone challenge</Title><Username>goldeagle14</Username><Timestamp>1348316209974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. Very strong buy !</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348324098339</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348324341865-12</Id><Topic><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What Yahoo gives to you makes Yahoo worth less. The market will not ignore that the value of Yahoo goes down $3 billion on paying shareholders $3 billion. The cash you get is taken of the share price. There is no free money.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348324341865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348324964017-13</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo! Japan Sold Leaves Yahoo Vulnerable</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1348089501977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo cant get out of it's own way. It goes up a couple of pennies and everybody's ready to go out and buy a new Lexus. Yahoo has jumped out of the plane with the boyscouts nap sac and has been in a steady spiral down for years. Yahoo is stuck in the 80's and will cost more than it's worth to update it and I see NO signs that Mayer is going to change things especially if the BOD is stuck in neutral</Msg><Username>garybirch55</Username><Timestamp>1348324964017</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348325388180-14</Id><Topic><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it comes out like any dividend, it also forces those short to pay the dividend which raises the stock price along with buybacks. Once the payment is announced the stock price rises to that amount, be it .50 cents or 3 $ , after the div goes xdate it returns to the previous price . Just watch the stock price when the payment is announced it will go up that amout or more.</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348325388180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348325766298-15</Id><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Msg>Lets just consider this little idea. What if Yahoo as been buying back stock for the last month or so? What if that big buy at the close was a Yahoo purchase? O.K., that would mean that a large broker is buying hand over fist. Yet, the stock price isn't running through the roof? Usually when an acquirer of stock (Outside investor or the company itself) starts making large purchases other industry folks will get wind of it and buy the stock to try and make a few bucks at low risk. But, except for the days when large blocks trade, Yahoo's volume is actually below the daily average. That doesn't make sense. So who is selling the large blocks? It has to be a seller with a large stake, because to put together those blocks from small stake holders would be a difficult thing to do. Interesting, If Yahoo is buying or if someone else is buying a lot of investors want out and think the mid to high $15's is a good place to get out. Looks like Yahoo has a significant cap on the share price. As I've said before, Dan Loeb has bought a Dead Horse that even the glue factory won't take.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326218235-16</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3 billion dollars can buy back 1/3rd of the float if they wanted to so I disagree think the stock goes much higher</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348326218235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348326971886-17</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they buy back a third of the stock they are admitting they don't have a growth plan. The PE ratio will contract and the stock will be at or lower than the present price. It will be even worse when they sell Yahoo Japan and lose that dividend. No Growth, No Increase in share price. PE contraction. Go ahead, do the buyback. Loeb needs to get out of this dog and he'll tender since his fund has about 35% of its assets tied up in this dead money stock.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348326971886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348327261969-18</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo can't cut search partnership w MSFT unless willing to pay a big fee to break contract</Title><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348294648493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hotmodel: The only thing I can add to your statement is that it will take Yahoo at least a year maybe more to rebuild a search engine. That is a lot of expense to undertake while the whole time MSFT knows it isn't keeping the business so it isn't working to improve Bing (or the Yahoo version of it) so everything continues to deteriorate. And then they still only have a desktop search engine, not one specifically designed for mobile and will be even further behind Apple's Siri as it become the premiere search engine. (Yea, I know I keep pushing Siri, but I still think I'll be right. Maybe not.)</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348327261969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:21:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348327521472-19</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hotmodel: On a lighter note, I have a new Cheesehead nation T-Shirt. Brats, $25 Beer, $50 Tickets, $75 Kicking Minnesota's #$%$: Priceless. Although considering how poorly we are playing, I am not at all comfortable heading into your house this year.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348327521472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348327844137-20</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the buybacks and special dividend is the way to go, like I stated before HFC (Holly the refiner) is doing .50 special divs the last 2 quarters along with reg div .15 yhoo is buying back stock already and with many special divs is like a xmas present IMHO</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348327844137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:30:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348327977380-21</Id><Topic><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buybacks and special dividends do little raise the stock price. Never have and never will. Both make the company worth less and that is what you will see in the stock price. Shorts pay the dividend but also have the opportunity of covering at the lower share price so there is no loss or gain for them any more than regular shareholders. 27 Aug 2012 – AOL Inc. announced a $600 million accelerated stock buyback agreement and a special cash dividend of $5.15 a share payable on December 14, 2012 to shareholders of record at the close of business on December 5, 2012. The share price rose 94 cent the day of the announcement. Closed Aug 24 at $32.92 and Aug 27 at $33.86. AOL is now at $33.79 and has gone down to $32.57 since the announcement. Looking at a chart of AOL movements August 27 does not stand out. We can expect AOL to drop $5 on opening December 6, 2012.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348327977380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:32:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348328883762-22</Id><Topic><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AOL was 27$ on June 24th once buyback kicked in started rising and is 34$ today so it went up 7 bucks after the buyback and special dividend YHOO could do something similar IMHO</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348328883762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348329138160-23</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holly is a great example. Lets consider. Holly has access to a lot of mid-west shale oil which it is buying cheap and selling at a great premium. It is making money hand over fist (Key word Making - not selling off investments) Holly trades at a PE of just under 6 I believe, meaning that shareholders don't believe the earnings will last. But, the company is rewarding shareholders during these extra flush times with a special dividend. Great!! But again, that special dividend is from exceptional earnings and cashflow, not from the liquidation of its business. If Holly was selling assets to pay a special dividend, ie inefficiently Liquidating itself, you would not be so happy to get the extra cash as it would be damaging to the future earnings of the company. (The same could be said of over paying for an acquisition at a time of inflated prices.) That is the important point!! The situation is completely different at Holly as opposed to Yahoo. Oh, and Holly has some really good management, unlike you know who.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348329138160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348329498540-24</Id><Topic><Title>Lets Consider:</Title><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348325766298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:56:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I disagree YHOO paid 1 bil for Alibaba a few years ago today its worth 8 bil to them, thats a good investment</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348329498540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:58:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348329743042-25</Id><Topic><Title>Rather be long YHOO than short</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348323302961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:15:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AOL Aug 24, 2012. Last trading day before announcement. Open 32.65 High 32.98 Low 32.33 Close 32.92 finance yahoo AOL Historical Prices June 24th has nothing to do with anything. Buyback is only permitted at last price or lower. A company can not buy back stock at higher than last trading price.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348329743042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:02:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348330326107-26</Id><Title>AOL 27$ on July 24 r</Title><Msg>The stock actually rose because of a patent sale to MSFT aka selling of the company, then preseded to rise so July 24 th means something you just didn,t see it.,</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348330326107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348330963887-27</Id><Topic><Title>AOL 27$ on July 24 r</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348330326107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the context of stock buyback and special dividend it has no relevance. Selling an asset for more than the market had valued that asset will give most stocks a boost. Yahoo´s sale of the Alibaba part was done at a price lower or the same as most has expected.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348330963887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:22:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348331887028-28</Id><Topic><Title>AOL 27$ on July 24 r</Title><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348330326107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bought Alibab for 1 bil 2005 sold part for 4 bil, remaining stake worth about 4.9 bil, how is that not a good investment? Returning part of that to shareholders and increasing buyback, perhaps an acquisition is sound business stratgy, and Meyer is doing well, with her duties, Yhoo is a great site for message business boards Cramer even uses it, stock is undervalued at present IMHO</Msg><Username>gooferb</Username><Timestamp>1348331887028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348332437072-29</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Escape Clause in Microsoft Search Deal</Title><Username>emclights</Username><Timestamp>1348332321740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was a terrible deal for Yahoo!</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348332437072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348333925169-30</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo can't cut search partnership w MSFT unless willing to pay a big fee to break contract</Title><Username>bollingr_band</Username><Timestamp>1348294648493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 02:17:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all things digital is an idiot, been reading her articles for yrs, they dont always remember everything when they write something.</Msg><Username>delmundosoftball</Username><Timestamp>1348333925169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348338806231-31</Id><Topic><Title>The new format for YMB</Title><Username>ralph_c34</Username><Timestamp>1345820084078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 10:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the new finance message boards are indicative of the quality of software engineers and project managers that work at Yahoo, it's no wonder that the company has been in the dumps for the past ten years.</Msg><Username>dcxavier</Username><Timestamp>1348338806231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 14:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340578535-32</Id><Topic><Title>theecoldone challenge</Title><Username>goldeagle14</Username><Timestamp>1348316209974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:16:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why Conversions and Reversals Cause Stock Volume Spikes on Expiration Days to truly understand the cause of volume spikes on Option expiration days, we must comprehend the Put-Call Parity structure that is associated with Conversions and Reversals. recall an earlier discussion about Put-Call Parity equation. in a gist, a Put is a Call and a Call is a Put. if this sounds confusing, you are on the right track 8-) [u]Put-Call Parity[/u] Call = Put + Stock - Strike + Interest - Dividend and by rearranging this formula, Long Stock = Long Call - Short Put + Option Strike Price - Interest (carrying cost) + Dividend (of stock) in otherwords, any Long stock position can be synthetically created by using Options and using some combination of Options, Long or Short stock positions can be synthetically created. now, this is a powerful tool and knowledge. Market Makers (MM) seize this knowledge to their advantage. In fact, Conversions and Reversals are strategies utilized by market makers every trading day. they have to do so, because they have to accept all orders, both buy and sell. in order to make a profit, they cannot always choose only to buy or sell. almost all market makers will buy and sell throughout the trading session. one of their primary functions is to provide liquidity and get rewarded. however, at times, they find themselves too Long or Short, and risks mount. to defray risks, they "convert" their stock positions into synthetically opposite trades. by doing so, they remove directional bias without having to liquidate existing stock positions yet. so, if a MM is uncomfortable being too Long XYZ at $100, he/she will immediately Long 100 Put and Short 100 Call to form that Conversion. the MM "converted" his Long stock position into synthetically short stock position, removing his directional risks. now, come that Friday expiration, the synthetic Short stock (Long Put and Short Call) position could well need to be exercised, if XYZ falls below $100. the market makers does so and automatically, that Long XYZ stock gets sold in the open exchange. even if XYZ price was higher than $100, the fact that those options are expiring, exposing the MM with Long stock directional risks, these Long stock positions will be liquidated. this action contributes to the increase stock volume transactions. MMs are in the business of speculating market directions. the same can be explained about Reversals, which is Short Stock + Long Synthetic Stock (ie. Long Call + Short Put) on Option expiration day, if those Long Calls are exercised, the relevant Stock will be purchased. retail players do not usually enact Conversions and Reversals. only MMs do so, in order to profit from a) buying the Bid and selling the offer b) arbitraging the difference in price of direct stock purchases/selling and synthetic shorts/longs c) interest rate outlook; conversions are interest rate bearish and reverses are interest rate bullish strategies these advantages above are very tiny, sometimes less than 5 cents but due to the size of their transactions and very low to near zero commissions on trades, they can make substantial profits if they get them right. MMs are by far the single largest contributor to stock volume transactions...retailers, commercials and in-house traders trade with them. so, please don't try Conversions and Reversals unless you are fully aware of the intricacies involved... and so, now we know the reason for the consistent Stock volume spikes on Option expiration day...because Conversions and Reverses are closed off by MMs. Why Conversions and Reversals Cause Stock Volume Spikes on Expiration Days to truly understand the cause of volume spikes on Option expiration days, we must comprehend the Put-Call Parity structure that is associated with Conversions and Reversals. recall an earlier discussion about Put-Call Parity equation. in a gist, a Put is a Call and a Call is a Put. if this sounds confusing, you are on the right track 8-) [u]Put-Call Parity[/u] Call = Put + Stock - Strike + Interest - Dividend and by rearranging this formula, Long Stock = Long Call - Short Put + Option Strike Price - Interest (carrying cost) + Dividend (of stock) in otherwords, any Long stock position can be synthetically created by using Options and using some combination of Options, Long or Short stock positions can be synthetically created. now, this is a powerful tool and knowledge. Market Makers (MM) seize this knowledge to their advantage. In fact, Conversions and Reversals are strategies utilized by market makers every trading day. they have to do so, because they have to accept all orders, both buy and sell. in order to make a profit, they cannot always choose only to buy or sell. almost all market makers will buy and sell throughout the trading session. one of their primary functions is to provide liquidity and get rewarded. however, at times, they find themselves too Long or Short, and risks mount. to defray risks, they "convert" their stock positions into synthetically opposite trades. by doing so, they remove directional bias without having to liquidate existing stock positions yet. so, if a MM is uncomfortable being too Long XYZ at $100, he/she will immediately Long 100 Put and Short 100 Call to form that Conversion. the MM "converted" his Long stock position into synthetically short stock position, removing his directional risks. now, come that Friday expiration, the synthetic Short stock (Long Put and Short Call) position could well need to be exercised, if XYZ falls below $100. the market makers does so and automatically, that Long XYZ stock gets sold in the open exchange. even if XYZ price was higher than $100, the fact that those options are expiring, exposing the MM with Long stock directional risks, these Long stock positions will be liquidated. this action contributes to the increase stock volume transactions. MMs are in the business of speculating market directions. the same can be explained about Reversals, which is Short Stock + Long Synthetic Stock (ie. Long Call + Short Put) on Option expiration day, if those Long Calls are exercised, the relevant Stock will be purchased. retail players do not usually enact Conversions and Reversals. only MMs do so, in order to profit from a) buying the Bid and selling the offer b) arbitraging the difference in price of direct stock purchases/selling and synthetic shorts/longs c) interest rate outlook; conversions are interest rate bearish and reverses are interest rate bullish strategies these advantages above are very tiny, sometimes less than 5 cents but due to the size of their transactions and very low to near zero commissions on trades, they can make substantial profits if they get them right. MMs are by far the single largest contributor to stock volume transactions...retailers, commercials and in-house traders trade with them. so, please don't try Conversions and Reversals unless you are fully aware of the intricacies involved... and so, now we know the reason for the consistent Stock volume spikes on Option expiration day...because Conversions and Reverses are closed off by MMs.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1348340578535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348340710493-33</Id><Topic><Title>LEAKED- someone spent $350M in the last 15 minutes to buy 22M shares !!!</Title><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1348259432636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More than likely, it was market makers transferring accumulated shares to Yahoo? I have a strong feeling that options expiration also had something to do with it. I know one thing for sure, it there is anybody still short on yahoo, they have much higher probability of getting burned than them making money out of it! If you look at the tangible value of all its parts and investments, you will see that there is no way this stock can go much lower than where it is at right now! I know that there are enough greedy people who will fail to see this simple "arithmetic" and continue digging themselves deeper! Honestly, I wouldn't be surprised if they bring private equity and take Yahoo private, only to relaunch it with a new IPO within couple of years.</Msg><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1348340710493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:05:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348344609385-34</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Escape Clause in Microsoft Search Deal</Title><Username>emclights</Username><Timestamp>1348332321740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 12:45:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo can back out of the deal. The only one to lose if Yahoo backs out is Yahoo. Microsoft has been able to increase their market share more than expected using Bing, Yahoo has not been as successful. Yahoo has two choices; 1. To back out and incur the billions in cost of restarting their old obsolete search engine. Losing the $500 million or more gains they get from the Microsoft deal and with very possible accelerated market share and revenue loss. 2. Stay with Bing and reap the benefits while trying to increase their market share and revenue Yahoo sells ads and if sales are down it´s Yahoo that is not doing its best. Blaming Microsoft, or anyone else, doesn´t fly.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348344609385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:10:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348344737661-35</Id><Topic><Title>LEAKED- someone spent $350M in the last 15 minutes to buy 22M shares !!!</Title><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1348259432636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As in most cases involving Yahoo, it is probably nothing. Absolutely nothing. Now, go back to sleep.</Msg><Username>specialforceshol</Username><Timestamp>1348344737661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348346320476-36</Id><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Msg>IMO EOM</Msg><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348346866159-37</Id><Topic><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could it possibly be YHOO's stock buyback program? There are only three companies that can digest a big fish like YHOO. They could only be GOOG, MSFT, and AAPL.</Msg><Username>bhttsl</Username><Timestamp>1348346866159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:47:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348347560974-38</Id><Topic><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comcast, Disney, Time Warner, Cablevision, Need I go on?</Msg><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348347560974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:59:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348351719313-39</Id><Topic><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That makes sense, whoever does will end up being #1</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348351719313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348352908255-40</Id><Topic><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're right!! Yahoo is a winner !!</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348352908255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348353596418-41</Id><Title>I.P. Address Check</Title><Msg>M. Mayer needs to run an I.P. Address check on the people who post on this board! Far to many Yahoo employees are posting things that are designed to inflate the value of Yahoo so they are not part of the 10,000 that need to be terminated with extreme prejudice. Fire them Marissa and do Yahoo a favor. 13,000 worthless Yahoo's can't fix your company, but 600 good programers can save your job. Unfortunately, you will need to hire them from (company name to be kept quiet) Grey</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348353596418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348356272490-42</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo! Japan Sold Leaves Yahoo Vulnerable</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1348089501977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, Yhoo will be a streamlined takeover target. Prime! Cash, no debt, income stream, and a negotiated deal for the final , growing, post ipo Alibaba assets. However, to date Yahoo Japan has not been sold,</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1348356272490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:24:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348356486286-43</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo! Japan Sold Leaves Yahoo Vulnerable</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1348089501977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:18:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still don't have a buyer and not even the glue factory wants this dead horse!</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1348356486286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348357071817-44</Id><Topic><Title>LEAKED- someone spent $350M in the last 15 minutes to buy 22M shares !!!</Title><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1348259432636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>******If you look at the tangible value of all its parts and investments, you will see that there is no way this stock can go much lower than where it is at right now! I know that there are enough greedy people who will fail to see this simple "arithmetic" and continue digging themselves deeper! ******** You could be right. Dan Loeb has a ton invested. He NEEDS to show a gain on this investment. Question is how long does he take before he makes a move. I tried to make sense of his hiring of Marissa. I can't. Of more particular interest to me is how much lead time wil we get before a "move" is made. Very likely it'll happen one day before the mkt opens and that old saw "coulda, woulda, shoulda" will play prominently.</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1348357071817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348358324371-45</Id><Topic><Title>The new format for YMB</Title><Username>ralph_c34</Username><Timestamp>1345820084078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 10:54:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must keep the shareholders happy !! Without shareholders and customers we are out of business !</Msg><Username>leestoller</Username><Timestamp>1348358324371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348360696244-46</Id><Topic><Title>The $350M AH buyer looking for a double. There will be a buyout</Title><Username>add_more2</Username><Timestamp>1348346320476</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:38:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well we know its not Yahoo since they are prohibited from buying afterhours. And $350 million is very noticeable so if someone knows something the market does not know and is using that knowledge then someone is going to jail. If there is news Monday those trades will be investigated. But the fact that this happens almost every month makes me want to chalk this up as a normal occurrence.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1348360696244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 20:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348363282937-47</Id><Title>GM invests $1 billion annually in China.</Title><Msg>555</Msg><Username>gilogden44</Username><Timestamp>1348363282937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348371640381-48</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO Should Initiate A Dividend</Title><Username>acts_111_231_111</Username><Timestamp>1348239483153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:58:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that will really work out! use up 80 cents of their yearly earnings &amp; they will have enough money left at the end of the year to invest in lemonnade stands!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1348371640381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348372201909-49</Id><Topic><Title>Yhoo Shareholders get screwed again. while employees get free phones and tickets to the Iheart radio show</Title><Username>jpalopoli</Username><Timestamp>1348244190087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:16:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we get a message that states WE WON'T TELL YOU HOW WE WILL DISTRIBUTE THE MONEY!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1348372201909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>