<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347338928943-1</Id><Topic><Title>I LOVE MB99! I TRUST YOUR SOURCE. PRESS MEDIA IS BSing....</Title><Username>kapoomba</Username><Timestamp>1338756639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-03 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mb99 is the best</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347338928943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347338961343-2</Id><Topic><Title>Let's vote for MB99 as PRESIDENT of YHOO BOARD here!!! GO MB99...</Title><Username>kapoomba</Username><Timestamp>1338756377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-03 16:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mb99 knows all the news first</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347338961343</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347339088670-3</Id><Topic><Title>hi MB99 where are you? long time no to see</Title><Username>qingchunegg</Username><Timestamp>1337914969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-24 23:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I were mb89 I would change my ID. MB99 is a genius and makes mb89 look like a cheap knock-off.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347339088670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347339122647-4</Id><Topic><Title>MB99 announced this great news over one month ealier...thx!</Title><Username>shiquanp</Username><Timestamp>1332351181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-03-21 13:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mb99 always gets it right.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347339122647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:52:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347339147804-5</Id><Topic><Title>What's da Scoop MB99?</Title><Username>raymondnmc</Username><Timestamp>1326840290000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-17 17:44:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mb99 says Yahoo will layoff 1000.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347339147804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 00:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347342152263-6</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Big Change Marissa Mayer Is Bringing To Yahoo!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345765090589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A firm December 1 deadline on Mayer's favorite Yahoo project. This has to be big.</Msg><Username>smedleypuddles</Username><Timestamp>1347342152263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 01:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347342308638-7</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Cash Will Yahoo Have in November 2012?</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347049826866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:30:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$12 billion is a lot of cash for a company with an $18 billion market cap. Yahoo will still own 20% of Alibaba Group valued at $20 billion at the time of an Alibaba Group IPO.</Msg><Username>smedleypuddles</Username><Timestamp>1347342308638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 01:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347342416397-8</Id><Topic><Title>$7.1 billion from Alibaba Group or Yahoo! Japan Deal</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1347205803869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo's cash is going to grow by 600%.</Msg><Username>smedleypuddles</Username><Timestamp>1347342416397</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 01:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360456671-9</Id><Topic><Title>MB99 announced this great news over one month ealier...thx!</Title><Username>shiquanp</Username><Timestamp>1332351181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-03-21 13:33:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360456671</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360483344-10</Id><Topic><Title>hi MB99 where are you? long time no to see</Title><Username>qingchunegg</Username><Timestamp>1337914969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-24 23:02:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360483344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360515129-11</Id><Topic><Title>Let's vote for MB99 as PRESIDENT of YHOO BOARD here!!! GO MB99...</Title><Username>kapoomba</Username><Timestamp>1338756377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-03 16:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360515129</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:48:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360517051-12</Id><Topic><Title>Let's vote for MB99 as PRESIDENT of YHOO BOARD here!!! GO MB99...</Title><Username>kapoomba</Username><Timestamp>1338756377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-03 16:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360517051</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360541807-13</Id><Topic><Title>What's da Scoop MB99?</Title><Username>raymondnmc</Username><Timestamp>1326840290000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-01-17 17:44:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360541807</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347360587447-14</Id><Topic><Title>I LOVE MB99! I TRUST YOUR SOURCE. PRESS MEDIA IS BSing....</Title><Username>kapoomba</Username><Timestamp>1338756639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-06-03 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a total fraud, MB99. Re: Yahoo Board Meets Wednesday to Confirm Levinsohn As CEO By mb525799 . 19 days ago . Permalink Yahoo's board just confirmed Levinsohn as CEO.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347360587447</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 06:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347367774869-15</Id><Title>QE is heroine to the market and the market needs another fix now!</Title><Msg>100% chance Ben will give the market it's fix tomorrow. QE is obviously not for the ecomomy it is to boost the financial markets.</Msg><Username>joeyfalcone320</Username><Timestamp>1347367774869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 08:49:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347371753876-16</Id><Topic><Title>$7.1 billion from Alibaba Group or Yahoo! Japan Deal</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1347205803869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not a bad idea, maybe more, as they now have 14K+ on the payroll. FB has fewer than 4K</Msg><Username>pinionman</Username><Timestamp>1347371753876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347371903149-17</Id><Title>NTWK $5.5 UP 15c....UP AGAIN AFTER MONESTER EARNINGS AND 40% REVENUE GROWTH &amp; $1/SHARE 2013 GUIDANCE...PRICE TARGET RAISED TO $16......NTWK .has been up every day after a minor post-record earnings profit taking. The stock is just starting to rally and with a 3 million share float $15 soon is just around the corner (see chart). That would make it a 12 forward PE which is conservative for a company expecting to deliver $1/share net income and grow revenues 40% in 2013.........still very cheap even at $15</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In addition to legacy license-based products gaining strong momentum, the company's cloud divisions are starting to show significant growth as well. The company's Cloud division Vroozi is growing exponentially NTWK announced a new North America cloud business unit last week. Larger companies are swallowing fast growing enterprise cloud providers with SAP and ORCL certification and compatibility. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.process of testing our new message boards. Please provide your feedback so that we can optimize the user experience</Msg><Username>jasmin_jk</Username><Timestamp>1347371903149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 09:58:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347373089637-18</Id><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Msg>Assuming Yahoo! finalizes its first two Asian deals and has access to a net of 12B (including existing cash and current funds) by November as many hope. What will they do? Here are some of the options that I see: 1. Use funds to restructure for new growth by buying start-up companies with synergies to existing and developing Yahoo IP? [may take years for significant return on investment but could make Yahoo! relevant for many years to come] 2. Position themselves for a cash rich purchased by another company - for example Apple or Microsoft. The cash would be a bonus and could be used to leverage the value of that company buying a third company. For instance apple could gain significantly by purchasing both Yahoo (eyes, content, and IP) and Nuance (voice, IP) to go along with their push towards voice and content. 12B in cash would make a leveraged deal, say for 26B for Yahoo, easy to do at a net cost of16B and they could partition off the remaining 20% of Alibaba (selling it for 7-8B and bringing the cost down to 6-7B) or use it to develop Asian wing of franchise. 3. Buy back shares to bring float down to 1B, or even 0.8B, and spend the rest on buying IP from strategic start-ups or small companies. [may take 2-5 years for a significant return on investment] 4. Buy a large company using most of the money and set up an alliance with a third company like Apple, microsoft, google, or IBM...that might otherwise have SEC problems in closing a purchased deal themselves. [could result in immediate return on investment - particularly with a good contract with a third party] 5. Pay out the bulk of the money to shareholders, with an expected proportional decrease in share price [I have a hard time coming up with any positives on this other than some cash in the shareholder's pocket which they can use to invest in anything]. These are just a few possibilities. I don't know what they have in mind - What do you think?</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347373629076-19</Id><Title>I'M 100% LONG AHEAD OF THE I-PHONE5 AND QE3 RELEASES</Title><Msg>99.999 sure Ben will cough up 2 trillion in QE3. Will sell by Friday the 21st</Msg><Username>joeyfalcone320</Username><Timestamp>1347373629076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347374686814-20</Id><Topic><Title>I'M 100% LONG AHEAD OF THE I-PHONE5 AND QE3 RELEASES</Title><Username>joeyfalcone320</Username><Timestamp>1347373629076</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:27:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it would be great to see yahoo as the default search engine for all those new i-phone5's being sold.</Msg><Username>pauljryan2003</Username><Timestamp>1347374686814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347375030971-21</Id><Title>MSFT search candy...</Title><Msg>Sweet but poisonous... Mayer, get rid of it! Thanks!</Msg><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347375030971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347375614049-22</Id><Topic><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello firsttestcase. I am rather shocked that you would put so much effort into a post on this messege board. But, you make good points. But let us back up al little, please define what Yahoo! Inc. is. There has been much debate, as i undrstand it Yahoo does not ev en understand what they are. Please state what you believe Yahoo! Inc. is.</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347375614049</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347377219601-23</Id><Topic><Title>Are those that bought at $11 taking profits?</Title><Username>emclights</Username><Timestamp>1347374133386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am adding to my buys in the $11s and $12s.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347377219601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347377820742-24</Id><Title>$16 is back...</Title><Msg>Soon.</Msg><Username>yinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1347377820742</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:37:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378259880-25</Id><Topic><Title>To whom it may concern.</Title><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1276031248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2010-06-08 17:07:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep on buying, buying and buying. I love spending your money.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1347378259880</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347378421141-26</Id><Topic><Title>Are those that bought at $11 taking profits?</Title><Username>emclights</Username><Timestamp>1347374133386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm adding shares until Yahoo hits $30 at Alibaba Group's IPO.</Msg><Username>bflathalfdim</Username><Timestamp>1347378421141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347378632795-27</Id><Title>SQUEEZE IN AMD and soon in DELL</Title><Msg>buy AMD now, squeeze is happening now. New trend is forming and DELL will pop soon. Watch and learn. AMD for sure will hit $4 today Tsunami buy is forming</Msg><Username>byuzorro</Username><Timestamp>1347378632795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 11:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347383939494-28</Id><Topic><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Please state what you believe Yahoo! Inc. is." Yahoo is a stock where professional investors go to destroy their careers. Or It is a fantasy where investors go to have their hopes and dreams crushed. In either case Yahoo is a DREAMLAND best described by Poe. "By a route obscure and lonely, Haunted by ill angels only, Where an Eidolon named NIGHT, On a black thrown reigns upright, I have reached these lands but newly, From an ultimate dim Thule - From a wild weird clime that lieth, sublime, Out of Space and Out of Time."</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1347383939494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:18:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347384798311-29</Id><Topic><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI - Yahoo! Discusses what they believe they are on their corporate website. "Our vision is to deliver your world, your way. We do that by using technology, insights, and intuition to create deeply personal digital experiences that keep more than half a billion people connected to what matters the most to them – across devices, on every continent, in more than 30 languages. And we connect advertisers to the consumers who matter to them most – the ones who will build their businesses – through our unique combination of Science + Art + Scale. " ...... "Today, Yahoo! stands out as one of the most visited and most trusted Internet destinations because we uniquely pair innovative technology with a human touch to personalize the digital world. Our business focuses on creating a content, communications, and community platform that delivers rich consumer experiences and advertising solutions across the screens of people’s lives — from desktops to mobile devices, from tablets to connected TVs. Yahoo! is headquartered in Sunnyvale, Calif., and has more than 12,000 employees in 25 countries, provinces, and territories." IMO the parameters provide for creativity and change and I am hoping to see both!!! Unfortunately, this creative framework leaves boundaries unclear and without strong leadership such ideals can be hard to achieve. I hope they now have strong leadership...but, like everyone else, I am waiting for Yahoo! to define its direction(s).</Msg><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347384798311</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 13:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347386597278-30</Id><Title>Don't like the new message board format? Go somewhere else....</Title><Msg>But pleeeeaz stop complaining about something that is given to you for free! I can guarantee you that if you go to a different message board format.... they won't come after you! Go get a life!</Msg><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1347386597278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:03:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347386917966-31</Id><Topic><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo! Inc. as well as all the other Yahoo entities is first and foremost an advertising effort. Since the begining Yahoo has derived the bulk of it's revenue from advertising. The content displayed and search engine are bait to lure the user to the site only. Once the user is on the site then it is Yahoo's effort / hope that the user will find ads display on the many web pages that exist on Yahoo appealing or interesting enought to entice the user "to click on" the ad thereby generating revenue. Yahoo! Inc. is a billboard and or a show case and little more. Thankfully Mr. Yang made the investment with Mr. Ma. Without that event taking place Yahoo! Inc. would be what? A major obsticle for Yahoo! Inc. is that in the past Yahoo has been free to the user and supported by the revenues derived from online advertising. To change that format is very difficult as Yahoo Inc. offers little that it can charge the user for that is not available somewhere else for free. So to accurately dscribe Yahoo! Inc. one would need to answer that it is indeed an advertising company that had a foundr that made a wise investment choice. Arguments?</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347386917966</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347388588584-32</Id><Topic><Title>Alibaba's transaction Value more than AMZN &amp; EBAY</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1347115499868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alibaba Group, expects to sell merchandise this year worth more than that sold by Amazon Inc and eBay combined. Unlike Amazon Inc and eBay Alibabas is a free service. Where Amazon Inc and eBay import billions Alibaba Group charges nothing. Free is always popular.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1347388588584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347390590682-33</Id><Topic><Title>What should Yahoo do? Comment on my list and add your own ideas</Title><Username>firsttestcase</Username><Timestamp>1347373089637</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 10:18:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing stops them from selling anything; example, the fad of the moment. since they already have the tech, though, the broad range of advertising is a low cost huge profit source. yes</Msg><Username>gup1x</Username><Timestamp>1347390590682</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347390944333-34</Id><Topic><Title>Alibaba's transaction Value more than AMZN &amp; EBAY</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1347115499868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That additional billion will be good for a quick dollar per share jump in October when the money is paid to Yahoo.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347390944333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347391649143-35</Id><Title>Where's the beef?????</Title><Msg>Isn't this what YHOO investors should be asking? When is YHOO gonna give some Stk Price MOVING info.???? To hold YHOO stk U almost need the patience of a saint!!!! What the hell is going on????</Msg><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1347391649143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347392243545-36</Id><Title>Yahoo Voted DEADEST Stock of Month &amp; Year &amp; Decade!!! Congrats!!!</Title><Msg>Wow a Tripler!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>fred.jackson55</Username><Timestamp>1347392243545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347393454233-37</Id><Topic><Title>Kara Swisher Silenced By Marissa Mayer</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347380670045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 12:24:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's amazing what free food will do.</Msg><Username>smedleypuddles</Username><Timestamp>1347393454233</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347393575036-38</Id><Title>Popularity on msg boards??</Title><Msg>Does anyone know how a new post becomes rated ||||||||||| within a few hours, without heavy response (replies) and with heavy thumbs-down opinions?</Msg><Username>crueloption</Username><Timestamp>1347393575036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347393994295-39</Id><Title>Technical reversal signal on the P&amp;F chart.</Title><Msg>$19.51 intraday print just fired the reversal. While this is not yet a buy signal, we just doubled our small long position on the retrace to the 38.2% fib at $19.42. Technically, this could portend what could be either a breakout or at least an oversold bounce. A retrace to $17.99 as low as $17.50 intraday, then back to $20.01 intraday would fire the very first buy signal on $FB, a double top breakout, and switch the bias to bullish. Alternatively the oversold bounce on this swing would fire a buy at $25.01 on the classic P&amp;F chart.</Msg><Username>sandyeggojake</Username><Timestamp>1347393994295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347394010721-40</Id><Topic><Title>Alibaba's transaction Value more than AMZN &amp; EBAY</Title><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1347115499868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that true? Alibaba strikes me as a site that with ordinary rules would be banned from many search engine tracking. They have the dictionary for keywords, when META keywords are supposedly ignored or are passe, they often don't actually have what one is looking for, they provide links to many other sites, often in China or otherwise outside the US, and especially in the product line I am most interested in, are intrusive, showing up on many pages (there's a trick I'd like to learn).</Msg><Username>crueloption</Username><Timestamp>1347394010721</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:06:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347395734883-41</Id><Topic><Title>Popularity on msg boards??</Title><Username>crueloption</Username><Timestamp>1347393575036</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The multi-ID idiot is doing it.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347395734883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:35:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347398726285-42</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's strength has quieted the board bashers...Ha!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347291360488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo stock sucks worse than the pumpers who pump this crap.</Msg><Username>thegoldude747</Username><Timestamp>1347398726285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347399345316-43</Id><Topic><Title>Technical reversal signal on the P&amp;F chart.</Title><Username>sandyeggojake</Username><Timestamp>1347393994295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 16:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts are getting crushed, and the squeeze is on. Doesn't count for the P&amp;F, but the AH cut above $20 certainly sets the prob of an intraday at $20.01 and higher. A $20.01 intraday on 9/12 allows for more breathing room in the bottoming process to a classic buy signal, as it permits a basing to $18.49 to $18, with a double top breakout buy at $20.51. Or of course it brings us just that much closer to the oversold bounce buy point.</Msg><Username>sandyeggojake</Username><Timestamp>1347399345316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:35:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347403169173-44</Id><Title>AAPL will drop one day.</Title><Msg>Fer sure!</Msg><Username>w.buffe</Username><Timestamp>1347403169173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:39:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347406648064-45</Id><Title>Anyone</Title><Msg>Is anyone else having trouble with yahoo tonite. Slow loading of practically everything. I'd like to know, otherwise it could be my small internet provider or maybe the land line provider.</Msg><Username>bosshebee</Username><Timestamp>1347406648064</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 19:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347410945435-46</Id><Topic><Title>Don't like the new message board format? Go somewhere else....</Title><Username>hello_midwest</Username><Timestamp>1347386597278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 14:03:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK.....</Msg><Username>i_got_cool_id</Username><Timestamp>1347410945435</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347410961087-47</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will drop one day.</Title><Username>w.buffe</Username><Timestamp>1347403169173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About as useful as "the earth will end one day". Thanks for the insight.</Msg><Username>johnberchick</Username><Timestamp>1347410961087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347415895167-48</Id><Topic><Title>AAPL will drop one day.</Title><Username>w.buffe</Username><Timestamp>1347403169173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 18:39:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someday my prince will come! Why do you post this garbage? And this even the AAPL board.</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1347415895167</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347417884705-49</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the beef?????</Title><Username>joco52</Username><Timestamp>1347391649143</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is my 1 year anniversary as an investor in this company, and I am very disappointed by my ROI . The BOD obviously does not care about shareholders. I am reconsidering my position, the stock price has been grid locked between 15-16. Tons of speculations floating around everywhere, but very little action is taken to reward shareholders.</Msg><Username>ms1367529</Username><Timestamp>1347417884705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 22:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347419710521-50</Id><Title>didnt yhoo not drop the law suit for search</Title><Msg>fb mentioned today that they are getting into search, arent we goona sue again- did i miss something</Msg><Username>man030967</Username><Timestamp>1347419710521</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 23:15:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347420302679-51</Id><Title>Yahoo paid mail SUCKS</Title><Msg>When I find an email on search it does not open When i send a letter the list of people to send it to does not come up YAHOO stock should be $5</Msg><Username>invstruth</Username><Timestamp>1347420302679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 23:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>