<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343452233865-1</Id><Title>$39.00 pps</Title><Msg>By end of September IMO Go YHOO Go Marissa</Msg><Username>biz4biz</Username><Timestamp>1343452233865</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 01:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343455700801-2</Id><Title>can some billionare help please</Title><Msg>We have found our show pony! Maybe bill gates can give bing to yahoo as a present for the new baby! maybe some rich men that want free passes will help this woman! I pray people see how blessed this woman is. Look everyone in the valley knows it good luck to have babies at a startup. And for the CEO to be having a baby mean someone at home is happy. people at home that are happy make great leaders. The hacker will hurt and eat anyone that talks even a little bit bad about her. Please tell her to see DR kerri parks. My family is huge in the medical field and I have been to many medial school and she is by far the best! they are going to try to kill your baby. kkekkwek32k32j2399f andfj0qnwjnajdjadsnf9ads0f9jna0d9sfnasjdfnads90j0ds9fj9asdjfn0jjmm.mm2m k23m 2k3n2l jwfasodfjwef adsf.cv.zcxvj ailj iew asjfpaojaije rkqnmripaj[fqjji oadfl;ajdsfioau erjadsf. BTW we will kill everyone of your family including the woman and kids if that baby is killed. Its going to be a man from the UK he will be white.</Msg><Username>bs_checker</Username><Timestamp>1343455700801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 02:08:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343456028950-3</Id><Title>bring the founder back</Title><Msg>I really think they should bring back the asian founder now that we have a hot white girl. It will be a match made in heaven. It will bring more jobs and more share holder value than ever dreamed. G-d told me you two would change the world! Not as lover but as a weapon on how leader should behave! If you look at all the pieces I have built for you two. They will fit like a great glove and drive like a car from italy</Msg><Username>bs_checker</Username><Timestamp>1343456028950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 02:13:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343468366177-4</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats!</Title><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1343402543532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-07-27 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KNUMBZ TELLING YOU TO BUY TOO.</Msg><Username>knumbz</Username><Timestamp>1343468366177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 05:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343481958350-5</Id><Title>Barrons Today--to mid 20's?</Title><Msg>Yahoo! (YHOO): The fund started buying stock before activist investor Dan Loeb of Third Point took aim at the company. Schoenfeld says he's extremely happy with the new board, and thinks new CEO Marissa Mayer will "try to monetize some of their investments. We think if executed properly the stock should be trading in the low to mid 20s," up from $15.95 last week.</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1343481958350</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 09:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343482736840-6</Id><Title>Barrons also-streaming live music-cool</Title><Msg>So Weir, 64, and some business partners have opened a high-end music studio and teamed up with Yahoo! to stream musical performances over the Internet. Yahoo! runs ads in the videos and splits revenue 50/50 with Weir's San Raphael, Calif.-based studio, known as the Tamalpais Research Institute. TRI in turn splits its revenue 50/50 with the musical acts.</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1343482736840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 09:38:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343488464025-7</Id><Title>IF Marissa can develop mobile ad revenue stream</Title><Msg>when users are transitioning to their cell phone and tablets, Yahoo will become that 100 Billion company it used to be in 2001. Then Marissa deserves to be CEO. And it explains why Levinsohn was passed over for the CEO job.</Msg><Username>irrational_fed_selloff</Username><Timestamp>1343488464025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343499760466-8</Id><Topic><Title>Sold Mine and Going Short On This</Title><Username>lesmwk</Username><Timestamp>1343222134211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 09:15:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Her career bio is no doubt impressive (at least on paper) for a tricenarian; I believe she’s only 39. But to turn YHOO into a mega moolah-generating machine that would in turn boost its stock price significantly, that, would be a very tall order indeed. Just look at the case of Meg Whitman. One would be hard put to match her biz credentials. Hired by HPQ last September to catapult the company forward, she has to date taken its stock for an odious bath, presently a haircut of roughly 18% since her inception. Short of a buyout, some superhuman efforts here are needed to move Yahoo’s current stagnating share price out of the doldrums. In fact, on a recent Charlie Rose’s show, Bill Gates still expressed interest in such a move to boost its internet search engine biz. But Steve Ballmer now calls the shots and apparently has other ideas, otherwise he would have finalized such a deal eons ago. So, if one doesn’t mind having one’s funds stuck in the mud for a considerable lapse of time, rather than putting them to work more productively in this volatile period, then, it’s quite alright to dock them here for relative safety for the foreseeable moons ahead. Best to you.</Msg><Username>lesmwk</Username><Timestamp>1343499760466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343506904790-9</Id><Title>All the hacker love love Marissa Mayer's</Title><Msg>double M is the best thing that has hit the value. The UK has there royal family the valley has something way better. I love Marissa. I love Marissa she having a baby. Just a fyi the mob love Marissa can we have put our flag and money in her stock so nobody better talk #$%$ about the mobs princess. Look but don't touch. we believe in the cutting the hands off on this one boys</Msg><Username>bs_checker</Username><Timestamp>1343506904790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 16:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>