<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344058369190-1</Id><Topic><Title>Kara Swisher -the Google Connection - Marriage Link</Title><Username>mtt819112</Username><Timestamp>1330179765000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-02-25 09:22:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Re: Swisher gets her info from her lesbian wife - senior Google Exec who she's married too. Google has been behind a lot of the leaks through their channels and connections that lead to Swisher . . .some, many, mucho people might assume OMG! Say it ain't so! Well newbie, how long did it take for you to make that assumption? I doubt that anyone on this message board since forever did not know that tidbit you just threw out. As to the association of the parties you have named in your post please note the disclosure at ATD. That association factoid is made very clear. Perhaps you might in the future post something of interest on the board; it would be refreshing as so many others no longer do.</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1344058369190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 01:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344062804685-2</Id><Title>Lovin Yahoo oh Yeah</Title><Msg>I've been waiting on a stock pick that is manipulation proof, that had a headwind that could knock down all comers. Now that Yahoo has the right Captain it is a ship I plan to ride into retirement - one day. I remember watching a news item on TV many years ago in which a professional "namer" explained that the name Yahoo which was NOT picked by a professional marketing company wasn't a good name for a company and didn't bode well for the company to have such a ridiculous name. I remember thinking "what a load of crap", Yahoo is a GREAT name for a company. I can't remember that guy's name but I've been using Yahoo since it was created and have been rooting for the company to come back and be real competition for the rest. I like diversity and Yahoo has become 3rd rate over the years. Funny that the guy who left is being called a "content" guy, my main gripe with Yahoo is the low quality of articles but that is also a side effect of low standards in writing all over the web. Maybe I'm wrong, but my plan is to buy dips and collect the heck out of some Yahoo stock and when it's time for me to quit my day job it will be in part because of making this bet.</Msg><Username>view12347</Username><Timestamp>1344062804685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 02:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344077899847-3</Id><Title>Has anyone seen anything of the expanded relationship with FB per the litigation settlement??</Title><Msg>Sure hasn't done anything for YHOO shares.</Msg><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1344077899847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 06:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344087423624-4</Id><Topic><Title>Has anyone seen anything of the expanded relationship with FB per the litigation settlement??</Title><Username>mewag51</Username><Timestamp>1344077899847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 06:58:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What makes you think that an expanded relationship with Facebook is going to help Yahoo financially? Facebook has begun to lose followers. Facebook is entering the stage where people are saying, what am I here for? What value do I gain now that I've reconnected with a bunch of folks I haven't seen in 10 years and really don't care about? Facebook after its IPO is at the exact same point MySpace was at when News Corp bought that company. The decline is going to be swift. The last thing Yahoo needs is to be more closely tied to a ship that is adrift with a leak in the bow and heading into stormy water. Yahoo is damaged enough, it doesn't need to be more damaged by its association with Facebook. (Yes, I am saying that Yahoo shot themselves in the foot in the settlement but I expected nothing less from Yahoo. Yahoo is going to $8, but tied to Facebook it might go to $0!)</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1344087423624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 09:37:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344088941683-5</Id><Title>Yahoo and Kim Kardashian</Title><Msg>Please new CEO. Stop your writers on Kim Kardashian. There are a hell of a lot better subjects!</Msg><Username>ebglock</Username><Timestamp>1344088941683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344092496801-6</Id><Title>AOL $32.63(good BOD) YHOO Worthless 15.97</Title><Msg>no Shareholder Value!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1</Msg><Username>reebok77</Username><Timestamp>1344092496801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 11:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344097348094-7</Id><Title>$30.00+</Title><Msg>All it takes is a few right moves, Be able to project vision and give Yahoo a direction and we are there. People love an underdog and want to see change. Its Yahoo's turn now. They have everything to offer, Moble is hot and they are racing to meet it...... 60 to 90 days I hope to see this stock break the 16,17, barrier and touch 30.00 Best of luck to everyone Joe Bizz</Msg><Username>biz4biz</Username><Timestamp>1344097348094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 12:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344101876051-8</Id><Topic><Title>Bartz will focus on shareholder value</Title><Username>coldonerules</Username><Timestamp>1277413681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2010-06-24 17:08:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorty why are your pockets full of 4 years of the coldones cash!</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1344101876051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 13:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344107293711-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bought more Yahoo at $15.99</Title><Username>coldonerulesall</Username><Timestamp>1306421462000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-05-26 10:51:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The coldone has had his most embarrassing old posts deleted, too bad he can´t erase memories. Links can´t be posted but you can easily search for; The coldone bought more at $16.99!</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1344107293711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 15:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344112855417-10</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo and Kim Kardashian</Title><Username>ebglock</Username><Timestamp>1344088941683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amen!! Pls add Snooki to the list.</Msg><Username>iloveaseabreeze</Username><Timestamp>1344112855417</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 16:40:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344129919736-11</Id><Topic><Title>It's time to raise the bar</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1344125908710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 20:18:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree, This stock has sat where it is for way to long, Assets, patents and so much more to offer. We just need to monitize moble, Build out social features (Who knows maybe buy Netflix</Msg><Username>biz4biz</Username><Timestamp>1344129919736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 21:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344137699386-12</Id><Topic><Title>Alibaba reportedly close to raising $8B, NY Times reports</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1343743787442</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:09:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo next quarter will see Yahoo at $18.</Msg><Username>gatherat420</Username><Timestamp>1344137699386</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 23:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>