<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347282813598-1</Id><Title>Alibaba's Aliyun OS hopes to be 'Android of China'</Title><Msg>Chinese Web giant says its Linux-based mobile operating system provides a choice for local phonemakers over Google's Android as it offers a better user experience with no challenges to functionalities such as maps and e-mail. Alibaba is pushing its Linux-based mobile operating system (OS), Aliyun, to become the "Android of China" and provide another choice for smartphone makers. A report from Sohu IT on Monday cited Alibaba Group's chief strategy officer Zeng Ming as saying the Aliyun OS is gaining traction among mobile phonemakers. "We want to be the Android of China and we have quite a lot of new partners in line," he said. According to Zeng, the total number of smartphone vendors adopting Aliyun will increase to five from the current two, namely K-Touch and Haier, by the end of the year. However, he declined to reveal the names of other vendors. "If I were a mobile phone vendor and my only choice is Android, I will be quite scared. Any company will want to have at least two suppliers," Zeng said. The original Android OS from Google faces several challenges in China as Google Search, Google Maps, and Gmail functionalities are limited in the country, he said. That is why Android is not able to provide a good user experience while Aliyun can, he added. However, Sohu IT noted several handset makers believe it will be difficult to completely replace Android. This is due to the mobile OS's ecosystem of phonemakers and app developers, it said.</Msg><Username>xetra72</Username><Timestamp>1347282813598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:13:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347283360457-2</Id><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD SERIAL SPAMMER TECHNIQUE</Title><Msg>The message board serial spammers steal from Yahoo paying advertisers and users by posting teaser headlines that lead to URL's with scam stock market advice, videos, etc. Yahoo is currently banning those click-on URL's on new posts so that viewers have to copy-paste to get to the scam URL's. Not the best solution, but better than nothing. I'm guessing that it puts a real dent in these spammer#$%$ and revenue. So the ever-resourceful scammers (using their unlimited ID's) are now BUMPING old messages - some several months old - where the click-on URL's still function. To continue its war against these parasites, Yhoo will need to delete each thread individually as reported until the message board history is clear of this trash.</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1347283360457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347283839145-3</Id><Topic><Title>Alibaba's Aliyun OS hopes to be 'Android of China'</Title><Username>xetra72</Username><Timestamp>1347282813598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:13:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>does YHOO still own 40% of alibaba?</Msg><Username>franksaidso</Username><Timestamp>1347283839145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347284986378-4</Id><Title>Question</Title><Msg>why has Yahoo destroyed its message boards?</Msg><Username>hieronymous_blat</Username><Timestamp>1347284986378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347286327093-5</Id><Topic><Title>Question</Title><Username>hieronymous_blat</Username><Timestamp>1347284986378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"why has Yahoo destroyed its message boards?" Because Yahoo hates its customers as much as it hates its shareholders.</Msg><Username>grey116677</Username><Timestamp>1347286327093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347286535089-6</Id><Topic><Title>$7.1 billion from Alibaba Group or Yahoo! Japan Deal</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1347205803869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well...maybe, not sure if the deal was struck at the price of the stock when the deal went down or valued at the time of the payout? Suspect the price was set when the agreement went in place. Also, need to remember that they get $900M of preferred stock as part of that agreement and continue forward with the remaining 20%. If some of the folks are right who are predicting the value of the IPO, the 20% could be worth another $20B. They would still have the preferred I believe. Comments?</Msg><Username>pinionman</Username><Timestamp>1347286535089</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347286549164-7</Id><Topic><Title>NEW MESSAGE BOARD SERIAL SPAMMER TECHNIQUE</Title><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1347283360457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last one please turn out the lights-</Msg><Username>haiku_blossom</Username><Timestamp>1347286549164</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347287851019-8</Id><Topic><Title>China's Alibaba to pass Amazon, eBay in transaction value</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1347078893661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So how do we get the kind of multiple like AMZN or EBAY?</Msg><Username>coperfit</Username><Timestamp>1347287851019</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287863653-9</Id><Title>If they sell Alibaba the stock will</Title><Msg>go down. They had better keep the whole 40% and start bragging about it. They'll just blow the money and wall st. knows it. They better hang on to Ma's coattails</Msg><Username>bhark114</Username><Timestamp>1347287863653</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347287988001-10</Id><Title>NTWK $5.3 UP 33c....BREAKING OUT!! NEW TARGET $16...NEW CLOUD DIVISION ANNOUNCEMENT IS HUGE!!..September 6, 2012. NTWK created a new division, NetSolCloudVM, that will offer infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS), initially targeting the North American market. Set to launch in September as a division of NetSol North America, NetSolCloudVM will provide clients with IT infrastructure on a monthly tiered subscription basis</Title><Msg>SHORT TERM TARGET $10+ .......2013 GUIDANCE: 40% GROWTH AND $1/SHARE NET INCOME NTWK'S OTHER CLOUD DIVISION VROOZI ALREADY EXPLODED IN REVENUES IN Q4 2012.....POTENTIAL ACQUISITION TARGET WITH CLOSE TIES TO SAP 3M SHARE FLOAT......AFTER EARNINGS PROFIT TAKING OVER.....MAGNIFICENT CHART In its updated public cloud forecast in June, Gartner estimated that IaaS was the fastest growing cloud segment with a projected GAGR of 41.7%, and exceeding a $20 billion global market by 2016. "We made a calculated decision to enter this growing market given our years of experience as a software developer, the minimal investment required, and the revenue potential given just the breadth of our current relationships," said Najeeb Ghauri, chairman and CEO of NetSol. "I am fully confident in our highly capable team, reinforced by our talented group of IT professionals, to scale the business quickly and capture a portion of this burgeoning industry, creating an additional revenue driver and further diversifying our revenue mix by geography." "What we are offering, in essence, is private cloud performance at an elastic cloud price -- giving potential customers in our target market segment the performance, flexibility, reliability, and a no-nonsense fixed pricing model that they have long desired," added Imran Haider, COO of NetSol North America and head of NetSolCloudVM. "As a growing software company ourselves, we have critical insights into the efficiency and productivity needs of NetSolCloudVM's target customer base and look forward to unveiling our new services in the coming months." ===== 4Q and FY 2012 EARNINGS SUMMARY......9/4/2012 NetSol Technologies Reported RECORD Fiscal Fourth Quarter and Year-End Results - 9/4/2012 - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Only 3 million share float - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc.</Msg><Username>nick.jr40</Username><Timestamp>1347287988001</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347289049361-11</Id><Topic><Title>$7.1 billion from Alibaba Group or Yahoo! Japan Deal</Title><Username>trudeau256</Username><Timestamp>1347205803869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The big question is what will Mayer do with all that cash.</Msg><Username>karesh412</Username><Timestamp>1347289049361</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 10:57:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347289970021-12</Id><Topic><Title>China's Alibaba to pass Amazon, eBay in transaction value</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1347078893661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why isnt it cheaper for Alibaba to buy YHOO? it can get its 40% back plus YHOO JAP and get the rest for free....</Msg><Username>coperfit</Username><Timestamp>1347289970021</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347290158058-13</Id><Topic><Title>China's Alibaba to pass Amazon, eBay in transaction value</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1347078893661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who says they won't?</Msg><Username>karesh412</Username><Timestamp>1347290158058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347294809454-14</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's strength has quieted the board bashers...Ha!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347291360488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only have the board bashers been silenced but so has Kara Swisher. The power of free food.</Msg><Username>remmy12554</Username><Timestamp>1347294809454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347295878428-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Big Change Marissa Mayer Is Bringing To Yahoo!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345765090589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will find out in less than 3 months.</Msg><Username>brex742</Username><Timestamp>1347295878428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 12:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347298881564-16</Id><Title>absolutely no news and up 4 cents in a down market...annoucment coming very soon but.....</Title><Msg>what will it be? finally getting the money from Alibaba or Yahoo Japan deal done or both? Acquisitions about to be made? A big time hire? Layoffs?</Msg><Username>crosscourt11</Username><Timestamp>1347298881564</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347298890259-17</Id><Title>absolutely no news and up 4 cents in a down market...annoucment coming very soon but.....</Title><Msg>what will it be? finally getting the money from Alibaba or Yahoo Japan deal done or both? Acquisitions about to be made? A big time hire? Layoffs?</Msg><Username>crosscourt11</Username><Timestamp>1347298890259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347299197630-18</Id><Title>public relations</Title><Msg>With the size, scope, and talent of yahoo, the company could issue press releases of real and continuing accomplishments every hour and still not exhaust its realm. so far ... zero. That is why a couple of other companies are in the hundreds while this remains in the teens.</Msg><Username>gup1x</Username><Timestamp>1347299197630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299648388-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Big Change Marissa Mayer Is Bringing To Yahoo!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345765090589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The suspense is killing me...</Msg><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1347299648388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299773145-20</Id><Topic><Title>absolutely no news and up 4 cents in a down market...annoucment coming very soon but.....</Title><Username>crosscourt11</Username><Timestamp>1347298890259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like a Bartz move.</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347299773145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:56:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347299883600-21</Id><Topic><Title>absolutely no news and up 4 cents in a down market...annoucment coming very soon but.....</Title><Username>crosscourt11</Username><Timestamp>1347298890259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This move should not surprise anyone.</Msg><Username>mb525799</Username><Timestamp>1347299883600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 13:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347302557195-22</Id><Topic><Title>Question</Title><Username>hieronymous_blat</Username><Timestamp>1347284986378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 09:49:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe half the eyes on and clicks! E-Trade can't be happy about that!!</Msg><Username>cap_pig11</Username><Timestamp>1347302557195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 14:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306035678-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Big Change Marissa Mayer Is Bringing To Yahoo!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345765090589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flickr!</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347306035678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306170944-24</Id><Topic><Title>How Much Cash Will Yahoo Have in November 2012?</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347049826866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:30:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12 Billion is the number.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1347306170944</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306471545-25</Id><Topic><Title>China's Alibaba to pass Amazon, eBay in transaction value</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1347078893661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:34:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alibaba Group will be anxious to go public.</Msg><Username>savior2911</Username><Timestamp>1347306471545</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347306989370-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Big Change Marissa Mayer Is Bringing To Yahoo!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1345765090589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:38:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the BABY!</Msg><Username>coperfit</Username><Timestamp>1347306989370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 15:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347307925912-27</Id><Title>We just lost a week's worth of our two cent a day gains-</Title><Msg>We need Yahoo to buy back half the shares, then we may see $20 but even that is not for sure.</Msg><Username>specialforceshol</Username><Timestamp>1347307925912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347308785444-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's strength has quieted the board bashers...Ha!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347291360488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's so strong it closed at the low of the day!</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1347308785444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:26:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347310002561-29</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's strength has quieted the board bashers...Ha!</Title><Username>theecoldone</Username><Timestamp>1347291360488</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 11:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>May have been low but the end of day trades were strong.</Msg><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347310002561</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 16:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347317752514-30</Id><Title>stock sales</Title><Msg>for golden eagle! your reply made sense but it identified your underlying sarcastic personality! glad i was the boss &amp; enjoyed firing face-to-face people like you. the golden eagle has character/class &amp; beauty which you could only dream of! your identified on my list now (&amp; for future replies) as GOLDEN NEMATODE! it's a pest worm (your case a sarcastic pest worm)! cheers or happy meals!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1347317752514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 18:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347321003292-31</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo HQ is moving ?</Title><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347070478106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo might finish off the mb with duct tape and bubble gum.Ask Hommer to be ceo-doh!</Msg><Username>haiku_blossom</Username><Timestamp>1347321003292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 19:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347325854132-32</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo HQ is moving ?</Title><Username>mb525789</Username><Timestamp>1347070478106</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 22:14:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>test xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx test xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx</Msg><Username>srt426426</Username><Timestamp>1347325854132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-10 21:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>