<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367124896299-1</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo at $24.72, not $15.80...Ha!</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366810432378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She asked for it.</Msg><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1367124896299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 00:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367131908814-2</Id><Title>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? Local Corp Is the Best Internet Bet</Title><Msg>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? By Mohsin Saeed - April 27, 2013 Mohsin is a member of The Motley Fool Blog Network -- entries represent the personal opinion of the blogger and are not formally edited. The Internet-advertisement industry is one of the fastest growing markets in the technology sector. With earnings season in full swing, investors can get an update on which companies are making headway in this space. Yahoo! (NASDAQ: YHOO) reported its first-quarter results in recent days. The company experienced an increase in profits but a 7% decline in revenue due to weaker revenue performance in Yahoo!'s core business. The entire company is undergoing a massive overhaul led by its new CEO Marissa Mayer, which has been met with positive investor sentiment. At current valuations, I believe Yahoo! has an upside of 30% and is value play for the US advertisement industry. The industry The US advertisement industry is one of the fastest-growing entities in the entire stock market. This huge industry has been supported by the rise in handheld devices, which ensure that users are connected to the Internet at all times. As compared to PC consumers stuck with bulky devices, which are much more difficult to carry around, handheld users can go online at any time. This single fact has significantly increased the amount of time that users spend online and is the primary reason behind the high expectations surrounding this industry. According to data collected by Reuters, the US Internet-advertisement market grew by 15% last year and currently stands at approximately $36.6 billion. More data from PWC reveals that the key to growth in this space is handheld devices with revenue from smartphones doubling last year.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367131908814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 02:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367136641450-3</Id><Topic><Title>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? Local Corp Is the Best Internet Bet</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367131908814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 02:51:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corp is extreme undervalued by a compare The competition in the US-advertisement arena is getting pretty tough with Google (NASDAQ: GOOG) and Facebook (NASDAQ: FB) leading the way. Google currently holds the number-one position in the US advertisement industry with a market share of approximately 50%, followed by Facebook. Google has reported total US advertisement revenue of approximately $17 billion. The display-ads market is a different story, and is being led by Facebook, which has total revenue of $2.6 billion. Google is quickly catching up with Facebook in the display segment, as well, and some analysts expect that Google's market share will exceed that of Facebook by the end of 2014. Yahoo! is currently at the third position in the display segment and saw negative growth during the quarter. During the quarter, there was an 11% decline and 'ads sold' fell approximately 7% year-over-year. One of the major reasons for this performance was the redesign of the Yahoo! homepage and email, which meant that multiple engagement trends were redefined. The search revenue saw a slightly better quarter, with y-o-y growth of 6.5% (10% of the closure of Korean operations are excluded). There was a significant increase of 16% in paid clicks, but it was somewhat offset by a 7% decline in CPC. Facebook is currently my top pick in the Internet advertisement industry due to its mobile-monetization strength. Although Google has the Android OS on its side, the company has still not fully monetized its potential. Yahoo! will have to further improve its display segment growth if it wants to avoid revenue erosion by Facebook and Google.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367136641450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 04:10:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367136985914-4</Id><Topic><Title>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? Local Corp Is the Best Internet Bet</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367131908814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 02:51:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corp development of Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 18,745,842 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 22,738,206 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 26,410,927 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 24,017,605 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 9.06% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 38.64% year-over-year Compare with the development of Yelp's Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 19,358,705 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 21,017,483 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 22,293,301 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 21,063,155 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 5.52% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 12.66% year-over-year Compare with the development of Google's Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 170,708,977 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 172,771,973 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 174,123,575 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 173,396,028 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 0.42% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 10.73% year-over-year Compare with the development of Zillow’s Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 10,978,144 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 11,366,564 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 14,298,071 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 13,415,496 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 6.17% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 45.23% year-over-year Compare with the development of ANGI’s Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 2,603,340 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 2,551,023 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 3,454,644 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013:3,185,928 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 7,78% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 50,10% Y-o-Y Compare with the development of Meetme’s Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 3,279,980 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 3,129,931 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 2,992,949 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 2,453,968 Monthly Unique Visitors</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367136985914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 04:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367142427233-5</Id><Topic><Title>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? Local Corp Is the Best Internet Bet</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367131908814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 02:51:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corp development of Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 18,745,842 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 22,738,206 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 26,410,927 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 24,017,605 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 9.06% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 38.64% year-over-year Compare with the development of Yahoos’s Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 161,959,555 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 163,582,176 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 164,827,887 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 163,723,320 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 0.67% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 12.10% year-over-year Compare with the development of Linkedins Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 26,050,157 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 26,216,865 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 30,495,948 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 27,410,040 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 10,12% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 7,71% year-over-year Compare with the development of Foursquare Unique Visitors: 11/2012: 2,270,280 Monthly Unique Visitors 12/2012: 2,419,708 Monthly Unique Visitors 01/2013: 2,511,232 Monthly Unique Visitors 02/2013: 2,286,047 Monthly Unique Visitors Decrease of 8,97% (February has only 28 days against 31 in January) against January and an increase of 56,23% year-over-year</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367142427233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 05:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367153177917-6</Id><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Msg>if i type in a phrase in the "search message boards" box ,click on all boards, i receive messages, how do i know which particular message board its coming from</Msg><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367160103654-7</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is an investment board not Yahoo answers.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367160103654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367160477634-8</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Flood of Upgrades</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366731677312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo is moving up faster than analysts can keep up with.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367160477634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367160500296-9</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, move along, you won't find any facts or useful information here.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1367160500296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367160963314-10</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't confuse your uselessness with the intelligent conversation that takes place on this board everyday.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367160963314</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367161045843-11</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's advice to buy Yahoo from $11 to $21 was spot on!</Title><Username>shelcorecrust</Username><Timestamp>1362511915833</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:31:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad coldone backed up his calls to buy Yahoo with information that supported his buys. That is why I bought Yahoo and I am making a killing.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367161045843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367161295609-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why Yahoo Is Worth $34</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1367008387880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't argue with the facts.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367161295609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 11:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367165093098-13</Id><Title>NEED MONEY NOW???</Title><Msg>:INCREDIBLY EASY MONEY(IT WORKS).!!! :it work for me. :This is the way the original post appeared when I first found it. :In days you will make money (it takes only $6 dallors).!!! : A while ago I was browsing through various message sites, : just like you're doing now. I saw this one message, similar : to this one that I'm now writing. It was the topic that : got my attention, "Making Money Fast". : Before I read it, I figured it was one of those things where you : have to do something questionable and you get like $5 a week or : something really #$%$. When I looked at the message, it said I : could make thousands of dollars by investing only $6!!! AND I : would start bringing in the money almost right away. Still : certain that it must be a joke, I read on. Anyway, to make a : long, exciting, money making story short, I followed the : instructions (I copied them down for you below), decided I could : go ahead and waste 6 bucks which I'd probably never see again, : : and, well? It's just amazing if you ask me. : I've already doubled that six dollars about a zillion times : over...oh yeah, the other thing is that I still wasn't sure of : the legality of it all. I called the questions line of the U.S. : Postal Service (1-800-725-2161) just to make sure that the place : where I read the Postal Service said it's legal was telling the : truth (and it is indeed perfectly not against the law), and I've : heard from other people that this is also legal in Britain and : Canada (and must be in loads of other countries too). : Other people have been doing this, and raking in the thousands : just as I have. I haven't exactly kept track, but an example : from another person: : Week 1: About $25 : Week 2: Over $1,000 : Week 3: Over$10,000 Week 4: Just over $42,000 I've been putting : mine in the bank at a high interest rate since I got enough for : one of those accounts, and am now getting even more money. : Forget about playing the lottery and not even being sure that : you'll win. Anyway, here's what you do to get loads of money : (you may want to print this so you can start carrying it out : right away): : STEP 1: Get 6 separate pieces of paper. On each piece of paper, : write these words: PLEASE PUT ME ON YOUR MAILING ADDRESS. Then : also put your name and address on each sheet of paper. : STEP 2: Get six U.S. $1 bills (or, if you're not so lazy, the : currency of the country of the address you're writing to). Wrap : each of the pieces of paper around each of the dollar bills. : This can also help prevent the money being seen through the : envelope so it's not stolen (as if anyone would steal $1 out of : the mail anyway). : STEP 3: Get six stamped envelopes. Place the paper and money in : the envelopes. You should now have 6 sealed envelopes, each with : a piece of paper stating the above phrase, your name and : address, and a $1.00 bill. What you are doing by this is : creating a service. THIS IS ABSOLUTELY LEGAL! : STEP 4: Mail the 6 envelopes to the following addresses: : #1 Mark Armijo 7404 wolfcreek rd santa fe new mexico 87501 : #2) B.J. Grissin 76 Falkirk Ave Wellington 6003 New Zealand : #3 C.A. Spaniel 6503 Ranchito Av Van Nuys, CA 90401-1537 : #4) Matt Frank 6/17 Poate Rd NSW 2021 Australia : #5) Ariel Skye, 20 Franciscan Way, St. Augustine, FL 32084-5308 : #6 James Parker 1402 N. Causeway Blvd Mandeville, La 70471 : PART II: Now take the #1 name off the list that you see above, : move the other names up (6 becomes 5, 5 becomes 4, etc..) and : add YOUR Name as number 6 on the list. : Change anything you need to, but try to keep this article as : close to original as possible. : Now, post your amended article on at least 200 newsgroups on the : Internet. (I believe there are close to 24,000 groups.) : All you need is 200; but, remember: the more you post, the more : money you make! : DIRECTIONS FOR HOW TO POST TO NEWSGROUPS : Step 1) You do not need to re-type this entire letter to do your : own posting. Simply put your cursor at the beginning of this : letter and drag your cursor to the bottom of this document, and : select 'copy' from the edit menu. This will copy the entire : letter into the computer memory. : Step 2) Open a blank Notepad file and place your cursor at the : top of the blank page. From the 'edit' menu select 'paste'. This : will paste a copy of the letter into Notepad so that you can add : your name to the list. : Step 3) Save your new notepad file as a '.txt' file. If you want : to do your postings in different sittings, you'll always have : this file to go back to. : Step 4) Use Netscape or Internet explorer and try searching for : various newsgroups (on-line forums, message boards, chat sites, : discussions.) : Step 5) Visit these message boards and post this article as a : new message by highlighting the text of this letter and : selecting paste from the edit menu. : Fill in the Subject, this will be the header that everyone sees : as they scroll through the list of postings in a particular : group, click the post message button. You're done with your : first one! : Congratulations...THAT'S IT! All you have to do is jump to : different newsgroups and post away, after you get the hang of : it, and it will take about 30 seconds for each newsgroup! : REMEMBER, THE MORE NEWSGROUPS YOU POST IN, THE MORE MONEY YOU : WILL MAKE!! BUT YOU HAVE TO POST A MINIMUM OF 200. : That's it! You will begin receiving money from around the world : within days! You may eventually want to rent a P.O. Box due to : the large amount of mail you will receive. If you wish to stay : anonymous, you can invent a name to use, as long as the postman : will deliver it. : JUST MAKE SURE ALL THE ADDRESSES ARE CORRECT. Now the WHY Part: : Out of 200 postings, say I receive only 5 replies (a very low : example). So then I made $5.00 with my name at #6 on the letter. : Now, each of the 5 persons who just sent me $1.00 make the : MINIMUM 200 postings, each with my name at #5 and only 5 persons : respond to each of the original 5, that is another $25.00 for : me, now those 25 each make 200 MINIMUM posts with my name at #4 : and only 5 replies each, I will bring in an additional $125.00! : Now, those 125 persons turn around and post the MINIMUM 200 with : my name at #3 and only receive 5 replies each, I will make an : additional $625.00! OK, now here is the fun part, each of those : 625 persons post a MINIMUM 200 letters with my name at #2 and : they each only receive 5 replies, that just made me $3,125.00!!! : Those 3,125 persons will all deliver this message to 200 : newsgroups with my name at #1 and if still 5 persons per 200 : newsgroups react I will receive $15,625,00! With an original : investment of only $6.00! ($5 + $25 + $125 + $625 +$3,125 + : $15,625 = $19,530 in just 6 levels of the plan!) AMAZING! When : your name is no longer on the list, you just take the latest : posting in the Newsgroups, and send out another $6.00 to names : on the list, putting your name at number 6 again. And start : posting again. The thing to remember is, do you realize that : thousands of people all over the world are joining the Internet : and reading these articles everyday, JUST LIKE YOU are now!! So : can you afford $6.00 and see if it really works?? : I think so... People have said, "What if the plan is played out : and no one sends you the money?" So what! What are the chances : of that happening when there are tons of new honest users and : new honest people who are joining the Internet and newsgroups : every day and are willing to give it a try? Estimates are at : 20,000 to 50,000 new users, every day, with thousands of those : joining the actual Internet. Remember, play FAIRLY and HONESTLY : and this will work 100%. : Peace for all.</Msg><Username>jamesperrynunnery</Username><Timestamp>1367165093098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367166008570-14</Id><Topic><Title>Why Yahoo Is Worth $34</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1367008387880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In an April 26 article posted on Seeking Alpha, Ryan Perlowin uses 13.83 for g and 3.93 for Y.</Msg><Username>pinionated</Username><Timestamp>1367166008570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367167732872-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why Yahoo Is Worth $34</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1367008387880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok, thanks...still can't make it work for the reported numbers.</Msg><Username>stockscouter9000</Username><Timestamp>1367167732872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 12:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367168826606-16</Id><Topic><Title>Why Yahoo Is Worth $34</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1367008387880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 16:33:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Forward P/E of 25, $30 expectation is for YHOO core and shared revenue coming YHOO Asian assets only. But if YHOO monetize their Asian assets, will be a different valuation. I think due to significant growth of YJ and Alibaba this year, the market valuation of these Asian assets could equate to $25 to $35 per YHOO share defending when YHOO decided to monetize it.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367168826606</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:07:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367169397692-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why Alibaba will be China's next $100 billion IPO</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1366988159863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jack Ma steps down as CEO on May 10. IPO time!</Msg><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1367169397692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367171975419-18</Id><Topic><Title>Why Alibaba will be China's next $100 billion IPO</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1366988159863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 10:55:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alibaba IPO noises likely to start tomorrow until we get the announcement on May 10. With last Friday a YHOO Profit Taking Day, along with YHOO up strongly AH Friday, then market cooperates tomorrow, I think we will see YHOO up very strongly tomorrow too, my personal opinion only.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367171975419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367172002819-19</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wouldn't know intelligent conversation if you saw it. That's why this waste of time conversing with you is over, Richard.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367172002819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:00:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367172053792-20</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel - Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366216500007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing will help that troll. One of her aliases is cowardback.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367172053792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:00:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367172081776-21</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo at $24.72, not $15.80...Ha!</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366810432378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-24 09:33:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hotmodel is a richard.</Msg><Username>turmaniloil</Username><Timestamp>1367172081776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367175268063-22</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like it when battles of wit end early because my opponent ran out of ammunition.</Msg><Username>cowardback</Username><Timestamp>1367175268063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:54:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367175709194-23</Id><Topic><Title>Which Is the Best Internet Bet? Local Corp Is the Best Internet Bet</Title><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367131908814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 02:51:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Local Corp has only a P/E of 7.5 Adjusted Net Income – Adjusted Net Income for 2013 is expected to be at least $5 million, Local Corporation Reports Preliminary First Quarter 2013 Results Company reports positive cash flow from operations one quarter earlier than forecasted Press Release: Local Corporation – Wed, Apr 3, 2013 7:30 AM IRVINE, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Local Corporation (LOCM), a leading online local media company, today reported preliminary first quarter 2013 financial results. Based on preliminary results, the company reports first quarter revenue of approximately $21.7 million, up 4 percent from the prior quarter. In addition, the company reports positive cash provided by operating activities for the first quarter 2013, one quarter earlier than forecasted.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1367175709194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367175792141-24</Id><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Msg>The recent upswing in both MSFT and YHOO has me wondering. Hmmmmmm</Msg><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367177803265-25</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a very valid legitimate reason for MSFT to make another bid on YHOO. First and foremost, the MSFT Board decided and told Ballmer to act now than later whether to keep MSFT online business or get rid of it. Why? MSFT online business have been losing billions$$$ (negative $2B+ last year) for years, never produced a profit. So for your question, you should expect a decision and answer. It is coming baby!!</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367177803265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:36:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367177939093-26</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MM will become the CEO of combined MSFT/YHOO after the merger. HA HA HA.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367177939093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367179775586-27</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about the recent upswing in absolutely stuped speculation like your post?</Msg><Username>still_my_dime</Username><Timestamp>1367179775586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:09:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367181791489-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo's Flood of Upgrades</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366731677312</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo will be $30 this year.</Msg><Username>neo1278alpha</Username><Timestamp>1367181791489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:43:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367183774526-29</Id><Topic><Title>update on Asian Asset values</Title><Username>lutts</Username><Timestamp>1366392472510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IPO at $100B in 2013, $120B in 2014.</Msg><Username>whogeorge69</Username><Timestamp>1367183774526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 17:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367190626857-30</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>probably has you wondering why you write such insignificant things on this board instead of writing something that might add to other knowledge.</Msg><Username>ajblo</Username><Timestamp>1367190626857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367191949998-31</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I said your speculation has validity that YHOO is very profitable entity while MSFT online business have been losing money in billions for over a decade now. Finally the MSFT BOD finding it enough is enough, Ballmer has to make a decision now or his likely "sayonara Ballmer". X-Box is doing good but PC sales is slowing, that is smartphone and IPad taking over and the worst part of MSFT businesses, online business is now hurting the bottom line. MSFT can longer ignore billion dollars of losses of the latter. Act now Balllmer or your gone Ballmer.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367191949998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367193023675-32</Id><Title>Now that the quiet period is over Apple can announce the buying of Yahoo and stop the</Title><Msg>back room whispering and sneakiness.</Msg><Username>chopper_nopper</Username><Timestamp>1367193023675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367195383125-33</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. X-Box is doing WELL!(good is improper English) 2. MSFT is doing far FAR FAR FAR better than Yahoo fundamentally! ALL of the 5 divisions grew DOUBLE DIGITS!(one was 8% YOY) The Microsoft Business Division posted $6.32 billion of revenue, an 8% increase from the prior year period. The Server &amp; Tools business reported $5.04 billion of revenue, an 11% increase from the prior year period, driven by double-digit percentage revenue growth in SQL Server and System Center. The Windows Division posted revenue of $5.70 billion, a 23% increase from the prior year period. Even the money losing Online division had this: The Online Services Division reported revenue of $832 million, an 18% increase from the prior year period. Online advertising revenue grew 22% driven by an increase in revenue per search The Entertainment and Devices Division posted revenue of $2.53 billion, an increase of 56% from the prior year period. ***If you scroll down on that $160M in revenue gain for Online services you'll see the loss fell in HALF for the quarter. Another gain, as it did in the FY12 it'd be profitable. Its revenue is rapidly catching Yahoo, not profitable yet. For a company with $75B-$80B in revenues and GROWING double digits is impressive, why isn't Yahoo? MSFT at $30 has a $1 dividend to boot. As for its rise, its cause they're about to unveil the new XBOX in a few weeks, codenamed "Durango". The current XBOX has been #1 for 27 straight months and made $500M+, this quarter. MSFT isn't buying Yahoo and if 1600 "no's", one for every day they've moved on, doesn't convince you nothing will.</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1367195383125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:29:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367195989118-34</Id><Topic><Title>update on Asian Asset values</Title><Username>lutts</Username><Timestamp>1366392472510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That sounds realistic. 26 million shares short must be scared shitless!!</Msg><Username>raymondnmc</Username><Timestamp>1367195989118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367200745535-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great post hot model. It is refreshing to see someone with common sense. Msft could care less about yahoo. Going to continue buying puts on this one down to 22 bucks or so. Thanks for not pumping this mindlessly. This will be going down as soon as people realize yhoo lost almost 10 percent of adv. revs and only showed a profit because they had stuff to sell. There isn't much left to sell now.</Msg><Username>aeparnell</Username><Timestamp>1367200745535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 21:59:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367202531622-36</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give up online services (last losses reported over $2B, (this is billions $$$$$ baby, not millions $$$$) and sell Bing or merge with YHOO baby, thus hotmodel is completely toast baby then "Coldone will have a big laugh!! HA HA HA</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367202531622</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:28:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367202949697-37</Id><Topic><Title>update on Asian Asset values</Title><Username>lutts</Username><Timestamp>1366392472510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hOTMODEL will file for personal bankruptcy!!! Coldone will have a big laugh.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367202949697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367203152091-38</Id><Topic><Title>off subject message board question</Title><Username>joedotcom2000</Username><Timestamp>1367153177917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well it might be more intelligent if that pump-tard Guido Coldone and his alias gave it a rest...wotta buffoon!</Msg><Username>stockscouter9000</Username><Timestamp>1367203152091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367203375395-39</Id><Topic><Title>Is MSFT preparing another bid for YHOO?</Title><Username>jaxdiamond</Username><Timestamp>1367175792141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:03:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You failed your Logic 101 in college didn't you; or else you wouldn't be making these silly as a goose arguments. BUT in an effort to get ahead of the curve, why don't you give us NOW the excuses you'll use when MSFT never puts in a bid for Yahoo.</Msg><Username>stockscouter9000</Username><Timestamp>1367203375395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367203487551-40</Id><Topic><Title>My Letter to Arbys</Title><Username>luckyflip24</Username><Timestamp>1367026386523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 21:33:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, "lucky" why don't you rest more than your case...just give your keyboard a rest and quit posting useless drivel! CAPICHE.</Msg><Username>stockscouter9000</Username><Timestamp>1367203487551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:44:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367203993804-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel - Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366216500007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:35:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hardheaded hOtMoDeL is losing a lot of money betting against YHOO. Obviously he will deny it once again. If he keeps it up personal bankruptcy will be his best option.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1367203993804</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 22:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367206001758-42</Id><Title>Where have they moved the notification button?</Title><Msg>Crud, they are messing with the board AGAIN. Oh yes it's very pretty, lovely purple, but where tf is the notification button now?</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1367206001758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 23:26:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>