<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-05"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372997121463-1</Id><Topic><Title>FORD</Title><Username>v.karpel</Username><Timestamp>1372992638527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i bought a lot of it &amp; did so with call options! the options were extremely cheap since the option price was very close to the cost of the option!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1372997121463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372997346224-2</Id><Topic><Title>FORD</Title><Username>v.karpel</Username><Timestamp>1372992638527</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 22:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i meant the option &amp; it's cost was very close to the price of the stock! whatever- i made lots of money on it &amp; that's all that matters to me!</Msg><Username>matsky5</Username><Timestamp>1372997346224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 00:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373001314888-3</Id><Topic><Title>sex</Title><Username>gemini_dominant</Username><Timestamp>1372499196631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-29 05:46:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is this guy still here?</Msg><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1373001314888</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 01:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373012358798-4</Id><Topic><Title>MR. YAHOO - Please clean up the Yahoo Messageboards</Title><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1372644121601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post one of your so called letters that you wrote to all these companies I would like to see this master piece. Hopefully you used capital letters at the beginning of your sentences, maybe even some punctuation unlike the non-sense that you write on these boards. You claim to have the intrest of others in mind but since you have already disclosed that you are "shorting this down to a buck...chuck" that just shows everyone that your only here for personal gain and everything you say is disregaurded immediately. Since I have a real regaurd in the best intrest of all people and not just myself, may I suggest covering your short position before the numbers come out here soon, or maybe before the muti-billion $ IPO of Alibaba. Kids don't read Y! message boards and the rest of us are grown ups that know how to use the ignore button. Best of luck!</Msg><Username>jim_bo20203030</Username><Timestamp>1373012358798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 04:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373016123137-5</Id><Topic><Title>MR. YAHOO - Please clean up the Yahoo Messageboards</Title><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1372644121601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, the letter i sent to both the New York Times and E-Trade can be seen under the title"'letter sent to Gen. Mgr. of The NYT" I sent that letter to NYT and Etrade... 1) no, in messageboard writings i don't normally use punctualtion formalities, but do in letters as i wrote to NYT and Etrade 2) the thing about "shorting" this stock to a buck was just for show to get some attention from what seemed, until your sensible normal response, a bunch of people who liked having all the stuff i am complaining about on the messageboards and were taunting me....so i did that solely for attention, and to illustrate that if yahoo's reputation were damaged seriously enough because of my claims, shorting yahoo would be an economically rational thing to do...nonetheless, i am disgusted thoroughly that yahoo doesn't take a stronger stand against the @#$%^ that is on the boards...(i typed the @#$%^ myself, it wasn't done by yahoo)...i have seen postings of rape, and nothing is done by yahoo, postings of animal sex and nothing is done, postings of incest and nothing is done, despite my, and others, making abuse reports on yahoo's system of reporting abusive posts...that is the real issue....you think you can come and talk all nice and reasnable to distract the real issue...why don't you talk about the disugust-ridden messages that are posted everyday here (not just on YHOO), ALSO, i have had a poster use my alias and know of another on the FMCC board who has had the same thing happen...our conclusion is that someone in the yahoo abuse "department" is doing it...because we've made reports on that impersonation and nothing is done there as well....you're trying to deflect the real issue</Msg><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1373016123137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 05:22:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373016528660-6</Id><Topic><Title>MR. YAHOO - Please clean up the Yahoo Messageboards</Title><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1372644121601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what i'm getting at is this: if the whole "world" knew yahoo was tolerating, perhaps to the point of encouraging, postings, like i said of rape, incest and animal sex, by not enforcing THEIR OWN ABUSE POLICIES, and if it got enough attention (like in the press), then, sure SHORT THIS STOCK because yahoo would lose face (unless they somehow coould explain to the public how allowing such posts happened in the first place and could successfully show that they bore no blame)...and the thing about kids never watching these board is also a deflection because they could if they wanted to, the messageboards are not "off-limits" to them...and therefore, to be fair, the fact that they "don't" frequent the boards isn't really relevant</Msg><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1373016528660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 05:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373020298081-7</Id><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Msg>Yahoo owns 24% of Alibaba, so if Alibaba goes public and issues shares of stock, Yahoo would own 24% of the shares. Do the shares get deposited into the Yahoo treasury or will the Yahoo shareholders get the Alibaba stock? And If the IPO is worth 100 billion, Yahoo split is 24 billion, divided by 1 billion outstanding shares, that's $24.00 per share. Is this correct?</Msg><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373021401347-8</Id><Topic><Title>MR. YAHOO - Please clean up the Yahoo Messageboards</Title><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1372644121601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is time to take your medication.. you are crazy...</Msg><Username>luckyexpress</Username><Timestamp>1373021401347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373022711903-9</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmmm the "shares" are irrelevant as Yahoo owns 24% of the whole thing regardless of the number. To answer your question Yahoo already has the shares as they've owned it since 05', its in either the August or October SEC filing that you can get off of the Yahoo Investor Relations site. I think its only a few million shares but don't hold me to that. If it does IPO at $100B then Yahoo is obligated to sell half which is $12B and to pay taxes knocks it down to $8B range. Your assumptions are pretty much correct in that on paper Yahoo has AG//Yahoo Japan/cash that exceeds current valuation which means you could give the core a value of zero and still be ahead.</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1373022711903</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 07:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373026037053-10</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW, in just about one year the IPO has gone from $40 billion to $100 billion with nothing but –I think it´s going to be more than the last Yahoo long estimated- to base it on. And we are already seeing a few posters pumping $120 billion. I guess we will see $200 billion before long. It does bring to mind the time AliPay was supposed to be worth over $25 billion and was then sold at $50 million.</Msg><Username>dr.gloom</Username><Timestamp>1373026037053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373026256555-11</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do realize they made 642 million in net income in Q4? Look at FBs YEARLY net income in comparison. Or even AMZN.</Msg><Username>eric_steiman</Username><Timestamp>1373026256555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:10:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373027165550-12</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hotmodel, Gregory is calculating how much the Alibaba IPO is worth per share of Yahoo, which has about 1 billion shares, so the number of shares are needed for his calculations. Just saying!</Msg><Username>pinionated</Username><Timestamp>1373027165550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 08:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373029538168-13</Id><Topic><Title>YHOO = ANTI GAY</Title><Username>shortiisagirleeman</Username><Timestamp>1371157623862</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 17:07:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YHOO customer care is a joke!</Msg><Username>hairy_is_still_jealous</Username><Timestamp>1373029538168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373029679042-14</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would you give Alibaba a PE of 30 growing as fast as it is? If so they are approaching annual profit of $3 billion. Do the math and you approach $100 billion market cap. Its not a big stretch. 18 month target cap for alibaba is $200 billion based on their growth.</Msg><Username>lutts</Username><Timestamp>1373029679042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373030571305-15</Id><Topic><Title>MR. YAHOO - Please clean up the Yahoo Messageboards</Title><Username>aroadrock</Username><Timestamp>1372644121601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:02:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most of the posters on these boards are either institutional traders, retail traders or paid 'PR" shills from India or elsewhere. These shills are paid by Wall Street vermin to bash or pump a stock. Sometimes they do both. Many of these posters of are fold mouthed, SFB, greedy, AHOLES.However, if YHOO would take action to clean up their boards, the number of posts would crater lowering the amount they get from advertising fees. Recent polls by YHOO found a high level of dissatisfaction by the people who use these message boards. Too bad YHOO's ad clients didn't read the results. Certain groups now appear to be putting pressure on YHOO to censor posts making racial or anti-gay slurs. FYI, it's a simple thing for YHOO to remove these posts or censor the poster, but Mayer appears either too arrogant or too busy reading her press clippings to take any action. Instead of being a vehicle to discuss investing, 90% of the posts are either about politics, short traders trying to instill fear in retail investors, long traders pumping the stock, or just psychopaths acting out.</Msg><Username>the_truth_stinks_2</Username><Timestamp>1373030571305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373031799706-16</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Botttom it will very likely the IPO valuation is between $60B to $1000B; I think the IPO announcement will be this month baby, that huge for YHOO and shareholders.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1373031799706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373032732679-17</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dr.gloom is too stupid to understand what you're saying.</Msg><Username>sublimalt</Username><Timestamp>1373032732679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373032781585-18</Id><Topic><Title>Former Alibaba Exec (David Wei) Puts Alibaba Group IPO Value at $100 Billion</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1372431133661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:52:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Or more.</Msg><Username>sublimalt</Username><Timestamp>1373032781585</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 09:59:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373032828813-19</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel, Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1365776842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hotmodel is crying over her losses.</Msg><Username>sublimalt</Username><Timestamp>1373032828813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373032920366-20</Id><Title>Alibaba's Asset Securitization Product Approved</Title><Msg>(Beijing) – A new asset-backed securitization plan jointly developed by Alibaba's financial arm and brokerage firm Orient Securities Asset Management Co. has won approval from the securities regulator and is expected to be offered to investors soon. A source close to the matter said on July 4 that the plan, which is operated by Orient Securities, will allow people to invest in loans that Alibaba has provided to small businesses on the Internet giant's online platform.</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1373032920366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:02:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034234459-21</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel, Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1365776842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's all she can do.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1373034234459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373034313059-22</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coldone is the genius all listen to or suffer the consequences.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1373034313059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 10:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373038606911-23</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe hotmodel is referring to the number of Alibaba's shares as being irrelevant, not Yahoo's.</Msg><Username>rhubarbpieguy</Username><Timestamp>1373038606911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 11:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373040335621-24</Id><Topic><Title>Former Alibaba Exec (David Wei) Puts Alibaba Group IPO Value at $100 Billion</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1372431133661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:52:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$100B scares the Yahoo shorts.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373040335621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373041001809-25</Id><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Msg>Yahoo Inc., still has a very attractive P/E ratio of 7.5, no debt on its books and a profit margin of 65.66% in 2012. Although, Yahoo does not pay any dividends, the stock is trading very close to its 52-week high of $27.68 per share. The three year EPS growth rate is a robust 44.83% while the recent quarterly change is an impressive 52.17%. Technically speaking, Yahoo looks good and the stock is likely to test the 50-day moving average [MA] of 25.87. A break of this level would see a test of the mid-May highs near 28, which is above the 14.59-27.68 52-week range.</Msg><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373042069141-26</Id><Title>Yahoo .....thank you..</Title><Msg>Thanks for tricking me into taking the "new" mail and giving up the 'Classic' format. Let's see here.......no place to do settings......page is about 1/2 the width.......can't see the subject of the emails.......... That's OK though. I don't waste nearly the time there that I used too. Someday I'll get soooooooo totally frustrated with Yahoo that i'll switch my mail elsewhere and just walk away like thousnads of others have done. Almost every so called improvement Yahoo has made in the last 10 years has been a step backwards.</Msg><Username>keltus1952</Username><Timestamp>1373042069141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373042718542-27</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo + Alibaba math question.</Title><Username>gregorybushell</Username><Timestamp>1373020298081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 06:31:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but Gregory was dividing by the number of outstanding Yahoo shares to get the impact on the Yahoo share price. and that was the question hotmodel was addressing. We agree that the number of Alibaba shares are irrelevant,</Msg><Username>pinionated</Username><Timestamp>1373042718542</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:45:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373043285991-28</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The IPO announcement will give us new high. Depending the IPO valuation, YHOO will get to $30's quickly. I think the announcement will be this month.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1373043285991</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373044749180-29</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>German and Swedes are not WASPs. They're not Anglo. Majority of Germans and Swedes are not Protestants. In fact, majority of Swedes and northern Europeans are Atheists. Also, according to Wikipedia, Mayer's father is Finnish.</Msg><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1373044749180</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:19:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373044802097-30</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You might have a point if you're talking about Cheryl Sandberg, but not Melissa Mayer.</Msg><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1373044802097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373044962831-31</Id><Title>Melissa Mayer for President</Title><Msg>Melissa Mayer, Meg Whitman or Carly Fiorina should be the next president. Not only does the U.S. need a woman president for a change, it needs a president with a successful track record, or any track record, in business and wealth-creation. Doesn't the cashier at McDonald's have more business experience than Obama?</Msg><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1373044962831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373045348969-32</Id><Title>Can Ford continue uptrend for long term?</Title><Msg>Wacha think?</Msg><Username>dimexusagensis</Username><Timestamp>1373045348969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373046003375-33</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yahoo will get to $30 without the IPO announcement.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373046003375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:40:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373047597059-34</Id><Topic><Title>Kara Swisher Gets Silenced By Marissa Mayer</Title><Username>theco1done</Username><Timestamp>1367944535714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:35:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kara Swisher's Yahoo coverage is second rate.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373047597059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373047921971-35</Id><Topic><Title>Melissa Mayer for President</Title><Username>stockgaming.com</Username><Timestamp>1373044962831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 13:22:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do realize MM did all she could to support the current debacle of the WH??? Meg Whitman would be great. Carly Fiorina would be, too.</Msg><Username>sfm211myutmost</Username><Timestamp>1373047921971</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373048651264-36</Id><Title>Yahoo is lagging the market today</Title><Msg>Any reason?</Msg><Username>tr_smtp</Username><Timestamp>1373048651264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 14:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373051078137-37</Id><Topic><Title>Former Alibaba Exec (David Wei) Puts Alibaba Group IPO Value at $100 Billion</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1372431133661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:52:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts like hotmodel lost everything. She stays here to learn from coldone.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1373051078137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373051779831-38</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he husband is jewish</Msg><Username>pantytalker4u</Username><Timestamp>1373051779831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373051959727-39</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bravo is challenged.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1373051959727</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373053051007-40</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What an ignorant comment. For your info she is Lutheran, and anyone's suggestion to you is to lighten up on making stupid comments which you know nothing about.</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1373053051007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373053415168-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel, Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1365776842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hotmodel hasn't laughed in years. matsky5 is another crying hotmodel alias.</Msg><Username>nanobot8042</Username><Timestamp>1373053415168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 15:43:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373055081502-42</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still think the IPO announcement (at stake the IPO valuation) is the boaster YHOO need to get over $30, that is personal opinion only.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1373055081502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373055243324-43</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo: Momentum Could Send The Stock To $27</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1373041001809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 12:16:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need a strong catalyst to get over the hump. I can't think of any except the Alibaba IPO.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1373055243324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:14:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373056873640-44</Id><Title>It's after 4 , that's the time yahoo turns all of our messages over to -</Title><Msg>olamo and his spy in sky official agency NSA. I hope everyone posted kind words about our dictator.</Msg><Username>wgboxman2</Username><Timestamp>1373056873640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373057234965-45</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and BTW---Melissa baby talks out her panties----Yahoo's $ are and will b gone eventually and the stock price down down down----</Msg><Username>pantytalker4u</Username><Timestamp>1373057234965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 16:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373061360675-46</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a republican in favor of a woman's right to abortion without government interference. I'm also pro gay and lesbians along with there right to get married or do anything else they choose as long as they don't hurt anyone. 80% + Republicans are in agreement with me on the issues above. I'm not a big fan of Liberal American Jews that voted for our president who does not have the best interests of Israel in his heart. That said , wellington is a complete Jack off anti Semitic piece of gutter trash. Israel and it's citizens are the USA s best ally and friend in the world. Jews find work in America and rapidly climb to the top of there fields for the these reasons . Dedication , intelligence , religion , character , hard work from a very early age , discipline , and loyalty along with a very tight family unit. I'm sure that these characteristics can not be found in wellington an old racist man who hates anyone not like his ugly self.</Msg><Username>wgboxman2</Username><Timestamp>1373061360675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 17:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373062717489-47</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel, Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1365776842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I laugh every single time you LIE, which you just did calling me Matsky. I laugh when you post phantom buys and use your aliases to think anyone cares. I pretty much laugh every time you post since you fail to see that only your ID's think you're worth a #$%$. Where I don't laugh is this morning when my $26 calls were up over 50% when it was at $26.20 only to be up 25% still...what a jinx you're!!! I also laughed at the "momentum to $27 article" cause I said the exact same thing to Dave on the 1st, am I not awesome???hahahahahaha</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1373062717489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373064948202-48</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yo, boxman........good reply........99% of all antisemites just resent their success which is a direct result of hard work and good money mgt, meaning they don't start buying "extras" untill they have more than enough to buy "extras" ten times over. The same is true of many Asian families.</Msg><Username>trappier</Username><Timestamp>1373064948202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 18:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373067793552-49</Id><Topic><Title>Hotmodel, Do you still think Yahoo was dead money at $15.80?</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1365776842368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-12 10:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lost. Take a hike.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1373067793552</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 19:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373069519028-50</Id><Title>Life after yawnhoo</Title><Msg>There is. After 25 years with yahoo I have found much better news coverage elsewhere and even marketwatch has a good finance part. The only thing yawnhoo has going for it is the message board which I use for info about obscure stocks or the jokes and comments on funny or odd headlines.</Msg><Username>bosshebee</Username><Timestamp>1373069519028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 20:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373074409644-51</Id><Topic><Title>melissa only got her job cause she;s jewish---all internet</Title><Username>wellington1947</Username><Timestamp>1366154085209</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 19:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is a nation of various races. MM is a natural born citizen of this country, therefore, she is absolutely genuine American.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1373074409644</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 21:33:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373080245824-52</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is he?</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373080245824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373080952822-53</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo! or Google are the most likely to buy Hulu</Title><Username>thetoadtimes</Username><Timestamp>1371065098465</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 15:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373080952822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373080971176-54</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo drops out of HULU bidding</Title><Username>mb525799</Username><Timestamp>1372430878622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's my guess.</Msg><Username>sublimalt</Username><Timestamp>1373080971176</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373081024014-55</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo drops out of HULU bidding</Title><Username>mb525799</Username><Timestamp>1372430878622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 10:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DirecTV is the high bidder.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1373081024014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-05 23:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>