<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374317890142-1</Id><Title>Up over a $1 Monday! China announced last night that they will be easing!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Huge for Alibaba and huge for Yahoo!! Market could see a 150+ jump on that information! Can't wait till Monday's open.. jmho</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374317890142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 06:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374322178087-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ironic if We Go By Microsoft!</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1374285403521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 21:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA Is Alibaba going to IPO for over $800 BILLION???? MSFT is STILL a $262B company with revenue's of $75B, 15X's Yahoo's declining revenues. MSFT will not be making a run at Yahoo as they certainly could've when it imploded to $9 in 08', even 2yrs ago when AG was worth $40B and Yahoo shares at $16 they STILL didn't come, then again when Yang wanted to take it private MSFT offered to FINANCE some other buyer. Not even with MSFT supposedly getting dumped in the Bing deal did it happen and as far as I know the terms didn't even improve for MSFT on that threat. MSFT didn't buy for supposedly patent infringements either...some 361' patent when no one has paid BILLIONS in penalties.</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1374322178087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 08:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374322411882-3</Id><Topic><Title>Up over a $1 Monday! China announced last night that they will be easing!!!!!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374317890142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 06:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. That plus YJ earnings , plus possible good comscore could take it to $31. Good that I bought August 31 calls at .32. I definitely prefer to be long, than short now.</Msg><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374322411882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 08:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374324372874-4</Id><Topic><Title>What can you say when you have 363.98% Gains in one day?</Title><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374117940953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right again??? On the Google options? I doubt it cause I was watching Jon Najarian on CNBC and he mentioned that a $43 move was being priced in and yesterday someone posted that the ITM puts from $900, $880, and $860 were all down significantly in the early morning. I have my doubts that anyone outside of option writers made money in the trade. The IV was simply too high in those options to make money. I'm looking at the $855's and even they ended down from the previous day. They were $2.70 going into earnings and opened at $2.41. The $895's opened up but only a few bucks. I haven't looked at every single strike price but I'm going to assume they all were down so you'll have to give some details. I don't see this spiking as its hit $29.60/.70 4X's now and each time its fallen. The market has literally run for 2wks straight and up significantly this year(18%), its due for a healthy pullback. Yahoo is up 20% for the month. Maybe, I'm just dreaming for a mid-$28's so I can get out with my puts(I added significantly the other day) at a slight PROFIT, that happens someone will be eating crow!hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1374324372874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 08:46:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374327628985-5</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone bought at $26.18 in AH</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1374005693334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:14:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>coldone always gets it right.</Msg><Username>strumbollio</Username><Timestamp>1374327628985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374335220909-6</Id><Title>.04 drop</Title><Msg>I wonder if this is a knee jerk reaction to Detroit?</Msg><Username>wb7130</Username><Timestamp>1374335220909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374336058015-7</Id><Topic><Title>What can you say when you have 363.98% Gains in one day?</Title><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374117940953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess then that 15% in my 890 puts was imaginary then....</Msg><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374336058015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 12:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374337009511-8</Id><Topic><Title>What can you say when you have 363.98% Gains in one day?</Title><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374117940953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will take yahoo puts on Wednesday. just before YJ realeases to protect my calls.</Msg><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374337009511</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 12:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374338211279-9</Id><Title>Another curous thing</Title><Msg>MARISSA is in the habit of releasing a big update a week following earrning releases. What will b this time, maybe is finance?</Msg><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374338211279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 12:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374339702444-10</Id><Topic><Title>HotModel, CONGRATS on your Puts!! You're Gonna Make a Ton $$$$</Title><Username>lexi623</Username><Timestamp>1374005842748</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lexi the dope is a hotmodel alias.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1374339702444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374339766233-11</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone bought at $26.18 in AH</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1374005693334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:14:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every buy he ever made on Yahoo is up. I'm proud to be able to say the same thing about my Yahoo buys.</Msg><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1374339766233</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374345450109-12</Id><Topic><Title>.04 drop</Title><Username>wb7130</Username><Timestamp>1374335220909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a knee jerk republican Reaction ,that is the Republican way they think it is good to privatise everything , like Highways, Schools and many other public Institution, it has never worked because everything will cost more and less service and lower Waages, only there fatcats Buddy's skimm off the Money and everybody gets the Shaft that is how it going to end ,the GOVERNORS Cronies going to make out like Bandits by the selloff of all public Property and GETRIoT is beiong left with nothing ,in the End the Bulldozers come and all Houses down so there be only big Business Buildings in the City Limits,that is how Republicans work , I can see it will happen to many other City's in the next 10-20 Years where ever STAAT there is the REPUBLICAN Party in Power.</Msg><Username>tobias.billingham</Username><Timestamp>1374345450109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 14:37:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374346901389-13</Id><Topic><Title>Up over a $1 Monday! China announced last night that they will be easing!!!!!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374317890142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 06:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please give detail information regarding China announced last night.</Msg><Username>scrapman50</Username><Timestamp>1374346901389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 15:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374347284529-14</Id><Topic><Title>.04 drop</Title><Username>wb7130</Username><Timestamp>1374335220909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:47:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a Jerk</Msg><Username>rhfph</Username><Timestamp>1374347284529</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 15:08:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374352386552-15</Id><Topic><Title>Up over a $1 Monday! China announced last night that they will be easing!!!!!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374317890142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 06:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also what is coming for sure and huge news is that Jack Ma or Jonathan Lu announce the IPO date. I hope Monday they will announce it too then wee probably trading $30 to $32.</Msg><Username>goingbravo</Username><Timestamp>1374352386552</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374353647054-16</Id><Topic><Title>Up over a $1 Monday! China announced last night that they will be easing!!!!!!</Title><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374317890142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 06:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China’s central bank, on Friday, announced it would scrap the floor on lending rates, and, for the first time, allow financial institutions to set rates themselves in a move seen by economists as likely heralding further reform measures in the coming year. The People’s Bank of China (PBOC) also eliminated the ceiling limit for lending from rural banks, the official Xinhua news agency reported, but did not remove controls on deposit rates. The PBOC, in a statement, said the move to scrap the floor limit would help cut costs for enterprises in raising funds and more efficiently allocate resources to take forward restructuring. The announcement was hailed as “a breakthrough” by some economists. “Previously people had thought the central bank would only gradually lower the floor on lending rates. Now they scrapped the floor once and for all,” Wang Jun of the China Centre for International Economic Exchanges (CCIEE) told Reuters. Others, however, said that easing controls on deposit rates would be a far more important reform measure. The PBOC said it had not yet removed controls on deposit rates, saying such a move would be more complicated. Chinese officials have acknowledged the need for doing so if the country is to address severe imbalances in the economy and promote consumption as a driver of growth. With low returns on their savings, an increasing number of Chinese have also turned to the real estate sector, prompting concerns of an asset bubble. Recent years have also seen the rise of a shadow banking industry that has increasingly concerned regulators. “Because of a distorted rate, the real interest rate return has been in some years negative so the people want alternatives,” Oliver Meng Rui, professor of finance at the China Europe International Business School in Beijing, told The Hindu. Private enterprises in China have also long complained of inadequate access to funds, with the major banks here seen as favouring politically-influential state-owned enterprises by offering them favourable rates. The announcement is the first major economic reform measure announced by the new leadership under President Xi Jinping and Premier Li Keqiang, which took over in March. In recent meetings, Mr. Li has stressed the need for more efficient allocation of resources and to allow greater play for the market. The Communist Party under Mr. Xi is expected to announce bolder economic reform measures when its third plenum is held later this year, possibly in October. Economists have suggested that further financial reforms, as well as land and income distribution reforms, may be unveiled. “The new leadership wants to take advantage of the honeymoon period,” Mr. Rui said. “Otherwise, they know they will miss opportunities.”</Msg><Username>optionstrader4u</Username><Timestamp>1374353647054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374369078905-17</Id><Title>Front page and etc.</Title><Msg>Isn't this stuff disgusting and useless that yahoo puts out. What a disaster. I went to aol, cnn, msnbc, newser inquisitor and thot I would see what yahoo has to offer=what a let down. Godfrey what a mess.</Msg><Username>bosshebee</Username><Timestamp>1374369078905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 21:11:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374370425419-18</Id><Title>New Yahoo Mail totally broken</Title><Msg>My mails do not reach the adressees, "server hangup" messages hundred times a day, etc. etc. Marissa, please get a baby sitter and get to work.</Msg><Username>friedemanndiederichs</Username><Timestamp>1374370425419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 21:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374371402074-19</Id><Topic><Title>African-Americans: Don’t Be Misled by the Zionist-Controlled Media</Title><Username>pat_buchanan8888</Username><Timestamp>1374364139307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 19:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go to UVXY and read the racist pigs remarks on African American...</Msg><Username>airheadmw</Username><Timestamp>1374371402074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 21:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374372685767-20</Id><Topic><Title>African-Americans: Don’t Be Misled by the Zionist-Controlled Media</Title><Username>pat_buchanan8888</Username><Timestamp>1374364139307</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 19:48:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>politics belong on another message board</Msg><Username>rufusregent</Username><Timestamp>1374372685767</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 22:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374374700149-21</Id><Topic><Title>What can you say when you have 363.98% Gains in one day?</Title><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374117940953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Webdave, Lol I didn't say it was imaginary just that I needed details that is all. You and I both know those Google options on both sides fell significantly and depending how far OTM they were a losing proposition. I noticed a few close strike prices like the $895 made money just not much. Good for you, a profit is a profit, my LULU trade has been up since I got in on Thursday and getting over $67 could send it over $70 or $80 even so what I'm watching next week. In regards to your other status has Yahoo moved on Yahoo Japan news in direct correlation, not one time it rose and the other fell?</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1374374700149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 22:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374376865925-22</Id><Topic><Title>What can you say when you have 363.98% Gains in one day?</Title><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1374117940953</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:25:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can you say? How about "modesty is not my long suit?</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1374376865925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>