<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370664934123-1</Id><Title>iGoogle sunsets soon!</Title><Msg>In case you are not aware... Google's portal page sunsets on November 1st. And guess where all those users will turn to? hmmmm... how about YAHOO!!!</Msg><Username>kwda_838</Username><Timestamp>1370664934123</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 00:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370692251090-2</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When a softbank made the offer a currency position was taken to fix the exchange rate of the deal to protect against currency fluctuations. This is done to prevent the deal from becoming more expensive from these fluctuations in exchange. This is exactly what Loeb did with yahoo and they made a ton of money when they sold thier stock in alibaba. Soft bank could make around $5billion US dollars just from this currency forward and us it as a down payment on T-Mobile. Nice</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370692251090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 07:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370694240807-3</Id><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Msg>bad choice</Msg><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370696284793-4</Id><Topic><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you must be blonde too</Msg><Username>seels54843</Username><Timestamp>1370696284793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370697015819-5</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh okay, I didn't know you were referring to a currency hedge. Thanks for taking the time to explain it.(~~,</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370697015819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370697219230-6</Id><Topic><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No not blonde......just an I D I O T!</Msg><Username>big_saciccio</Username><Timestamp>1370697219230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370697261936-7</Id><Topic><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's pathetic that this board is exposed to a juvenile like you. Have you no shame?</Msg><Username>rlday2010</Username><Timestamp>1370697261936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:14:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370697398790-8</Id><Title>I hope Yahoo is not up to it's ears in the Obama scandal.</Title><Msg>I hope this company is not in bed with the Obama infringement of personal rights, not good. As we see with the IRS government workers can't be trusted to do the right thing. Algorithms or not they are invading everyone's privacy.</Msg><Username>rhomolka10</Username><Timestamp>1370697398790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:16:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370697953323-9</Id><Title>Market Cap Yahoo vs. Google</Title><Msg>To compare, first adjust share price for shares outstanding. Yahoo has 3x as many, thus Goog would trade at $280. That moves its EPS down to $11 per share from $33 per share. IF Yahoo was equal to only 1/4 of Google (and the EPS suggests it should be more like 30%), then Yahoo could be trading at $280 x 30% or $84 per share. The moment Marissa shows revenue growth even without the profits catching up initially, Yahoo will take off. It is a matter of time and Yahoo will make a very significant run. Those catching this ride are buying their tickets today.</Msg><Username>hedgingmywayhome</Username><Timestamp>1370697953323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370699212816-10</Id><Topic><Title>Market Cap Yahoo vs. Google</Title><Username>hedgingmywayhome</Username><Timestamp>1370697953323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree. If we get 5% revenue growth at next earnings stock will rip over 10% and institutions will chase. People wanted it during Q1 but it wasnt there unfortunately. changes are happening though Changes this Q: sponsored ads within homepage newsfeed. yahoo search improvements Yahoo mail improvements continued mobile growth (Flickr, Yahoo weather, etc.)</Msg><Username>eric_steiman</Username><Timestamp>1370699212816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370702656987-11</Id><Topic><Title>I hope Yahoo is not up to it's ears in the Obama scandal.</Title><Username>rhomolka10</Username><Timestamp>1370697398790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:16:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The "Obama scandal" is if anything a Patriot Act scandal overwhelmingly passed by Congress and Pres. Bush in reaction to 9-11. It has been upheld by Dem &amp; Rep again and again. Invasion of privacy has been going on for years and just waits for the next crisis to wrap its "protective" blanket more tightly around us. We have Congress and the Court to ensure our Constitutional rights are being preserved. The President executes the laws and decisions of these two branches. As for Benghazi--as a US general said, "It was 9-11 all over the world". Where's the scandal? As for the IRS, organizations that are anti-big government and possible tax cheat "patriots" should be scrutinized carefully before they are given tax-exempt status.</Msg><Username>schloefhp</Username><Timestamp>1370702656987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 10:44:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370703966448-12</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile has any thing to so with Yahoo?</Msg><Username>scrapman50</Username><Timestamp>1370703966448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 11:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370703987694-13</Id><Title>Organic Traffic of Local Corp (46% of Total Traffic) and Total Traffic of Zillow are equal, but Zillow has with 1,850 million</Title><Msg>the 48-fold market-cap of the idiotic low market-cap of Local Corp of only 38 million. Organic Traffic, der bei Local Corp 13:31 #5219 inzwischen 46% ausmacht (gegenüber fast 0 in früheren Zeiten), ist mit mehr als 16 Millionen Monthly Unique Visitors gleich groß wie der von Zillow, das mit 1.850 Millionen eine Marktkapitalisierung aufweist, die 48-mal so hoch ist wie die idiotisch niedrig Marktkapitalisierung von Local Corp in Höhe von 38 Millionen. The biggest sensation: Organic Traffic of Local Corp was 46% in Q1/2013 Organic Traffic and Direct Revenues produce no cost of revenues and this 46% are a Big Progress on the Way to 50/50 in 2013 and an important step to build a more defensible and sustanainable business Development of Organic Traffic/Monthly Unique Visitors (MUVs): 2010: 88 million = 31% of total traffic 2011: 117 million = 33% of total traffic 2012: 155 million = 37% of total traffic Q1/2013 = 46% (49 million in the first quarter or 196 million in the year by an extrapolation) Goal: 50% of total traffic 16.3 million Monthly Unique Visitors from Organic Traffic (total Monthly Unique Visitors of Local Corp in Q1 was in the average 35.4 Monthly Unique Visitors on the flagshipsite and the network) of Local Corp wasn't reached in total from a lot of competitors with billion-market-caps. For example: Only the organic traffic of Local Corp was equal with the total traffic of Zillow.</Msg><Username>flankenking</Username><Timestamp>1370703987694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 11:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370704203639-14</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, soft bank and yahoo are mutual owners of the same company in Asia. Guess which one?</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370704203639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 11:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370704295280-15</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ontario Teachers Pension Fund has voted in favor of Soft bank. The pension fund is the 15th largest shareholder is Sprint.</Msg><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370704295280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 11:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370707369406-16</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreaded Correction Time"</Title><Username>didoo36</Username><Timestamp>1369842797508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 11:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>06/08/13 Time to think about establishing a long position. Trade Wisely!!!</Msg><Username>didoo36</Username><Timestamp>1370707369406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 12:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370712989319-17</Id><Topic><Title>"Dreaded Correction Time"</Title><Username>didoo36</Username><Timestamp>1369842797508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-29 11:53:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock could push 30s. Solid technicals. Alibaba now getting 200 Billion pricetags for late 2014. YJ still solid. Core and mobile growing with significant improvements. new search on desktop revamped. Interesting to see if Yahoo is prominent in new Apple iOS this week,</Msg><Username>eric_steiman</Username><Timestamp>1370712989319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:36:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370713077114-18</Id><Topic><Title>TRLI: new Christian mobile online media play @ .05......Big names involved. Osteen, etc....multi-bagger..do DD</Title><Username>drap440</Username><Timestamp>1370634039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:40:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TRLI......lookiong very good indeed</Msg><Username>drap440</Username><Timestamp>1370713077114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370713112493-19</Id><Topic><Title>Market Cap Yahoo vs. Google</Title><Username>hedgingmywayhome</Username><Timestamp>1370697953323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I own alot of lottery tix and believe there is reward in the very near future</Msg><Username>mccormickred</Username><Timestamp>1370713112493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:38:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370713904011-20</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is exactly what Loeb did with yahoo and they made a ton of money when they sold thier stock in alibaba. The hedge was put on the Yahoo Japan stuff and for $3B, if I remember right, which was less than half the value of Yahoo Japan meaning an implosion of share price and a hedge would only bring back .50 on the dollar. The Alibaba preferred was to go up incrementally from the dividends thus $800M to $850M to $880M or whatever they finally paid. I have no idea if a hedge was put on that as well. No matter, the hedge protected Yahoo and gave them more money than earnings which could be used to buyback shares. How can Softbank make $5B on just a currency hedge? Yahoo took out $3B in nominal and it cost them hundreds of millions of which they're up, a few hundred million. Softbank would have to have a hedge of $100B costing over a billion to leverage up to $5B. That type of financial engineering is what cause the Great Recession in the 1st place. I highly doubt they go to Plan B cause the whole point is they want Clearwire's expensive spectrum even acquiring #$%$ Sprint which controls Clearwire with over 50% ownership. Now if Dish can go directly to Clearwire shareholders to buy why hasn't Softbank did the same. If you reply cause of Sprint, which owns 50%, then you know the original deal will happen.</Msg><Username>hotmodeltestid122</Username><Timestamp>1370713904011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370714022897-21</Id><Topic><Title>Market Cap Yahoo vs. Google</Title><Username>hedgingmywayhome</Username><Timestamp>1370697953323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 09:25:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hah??? First off I am long 500 July 28's. I would love for this stock to take off. But to compare it to Google like that is ludicrous!! Estimated for Google revenue are about 72 billion next year growing from 60 billion this year. So basically they are increasing revenue at 2 1/2 time each year what Yahoo even brings in as total revenue. So actually looking at the revenue compared to each other it makes me think Google is the cheaper of the two. Now granted if Yahoo can make these acquisitions work and start increasing revenue more substantially then maybe I may see your at least part of your point but right now I think your dreaming a little bit too much and that is what worries me on this stock. Too many treating it like a lottery ticket and things like that don't usually pan out. I like its technical pattern here and am looking for a break to 29's in the the next few weeks barring another market pullback.</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370714022897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370714191667-22</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My advice to buy CSIQ at $4 was genius too as was my call for Tesla at $38. So what's your point???Were in a bull market. Almost everything is flying and all this bragging makes no sense. There are hundreds of stock outperforming Yahoo so it's not like this is the only place to be. LOL</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370714191667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370714470868-23</Id><Topic><Title>Softbank in talks with T-Mobile</Title><Username>randywms55</Username><Timestamp>1370661909486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 23:25:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks. Didn't know that.</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370714470868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370714473979-24</Id><Title>I don't get it????</Title><Msg>Why is this message board littered with people thinking Yahoo is the only stock running?? AWere in a bull market and there are actually hundreds of stock outperforming Yahoo over the last year. Look at Tesla's triple. Or how about Canadian Solars triple? I can go on and on. How about AIG's run from 10 in 2009 to 45+ now. Or BAC's run from 2 to 13 over the same span. I actually shorted this thing down when it corrected and I am now long a ton of calls as it's technically in a sweetspot now. A brak over 27.50 and it runs to 29.</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370714473979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370714615837-25</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone Watch That Show CNBC's American Greed</Title><Username>nolan_ryan_100</Username><Timestamp>1370705163771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 11:26:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Watch it. Big Brother is watching you... You could be thrown in the slammer for that racist comment. I'm not joking around either. In 5 years it will be a common thing thing for people to be tossed in the pen for comments like that.</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370714615837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:03:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370714785976-26</Id><Topic><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well how about Denise Ramos at ITT. Another blonde who actually in her day made Marissa look plain. Denise was a former beauty queen and even in her 50's is a hot blonde. She is considered in the top 5 of CEO's among wall street pros I work with</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370714785976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370715095753-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bolling bands tightening up. Any positive news and this could pop big. I'm going to load up on July 29's</Title><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370399217536</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 22:26:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what stock are you talking about dude???The prices you mention have nothing in relation to any of the stocks I talked about.....What stock plummeted 17%??? I doubt you lost those amounts. You are too stupid to accumulate that to begin with</Msg><Username>dickey_betts44</Username><Timestamp>1370715095753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370716047576-28</Id><Topic><Title>put a blonde #$%$ in as ceo....you know it's over</Title><Username>sydneylocks</Username><Timestamp>1370694240807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 08:24:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha, you don't say - a former beauty queen. That must make her smarter than the fuglies - right? (~~,</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370716047576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370721628539-29</Id><Title>PAL selloff on Friday's news is overdone. Since they are so close to production, smart money will buy here.</Title><Msg>PAL selloff on Friday's news is overdone. Prior to Friday's financing deal, the risk of a potential bankruptcy and/or severe dilution was baked into the PPS by at least 40 cents to 60 cents per share. While a knee-jerk selloff is a typical reaction to 10% dilution in a mining stock, astute investors will realize that PAL is now assured of completing their palladium mine and going into production before the end of this year. This one fact alone effectively de-risks the stock from here to the end of the year. Palladium metal prices have not and will not correlate with gold price deterioration due to its critical industrial uses and a very limited world supply, which have been supporting and driving up the price of the metal. I expect smart money knows this already and will begin buying PAL over the next week. The knee-jerk reaction to Friday's news of financing terms and conditions creates a great ground-floor opportunity for a miner that is very close to beginning production. Just my opinion.</Msg><Username>buythebloodinthestreets</Username><Timestamp>1370721628539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 16:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370724528659-30</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is the Yahoo board. Take your lies somewhere else and stop wasting your time here.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1370724528659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 16:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370724558874-31</Id><Topic><Title>The coldone bought in after hours at $22.70...</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1366149798450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 18:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Coldone must be an insider.</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1370724558874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 16:49:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370724588539-32</Id><Topic><Title>The Coldone is Leaving for Vacation</Title><Username>co1done</Username><Timestamp>1369147048570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-21 10:37:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Higher next week!</Msg><Username>stronghold812</Username><Timestamp>1370724588539</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 16:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370726397726-33</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo Taking Off!</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370634650037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 15:50:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What news?</Msg><Username>sublimalt</Username><Timestamp>1370726397726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370726598627-34</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strongholder--your pitiful , calling other's liars . Your the liar . Stop this non-sense about cafone . We purchased this stock before we ever heard of you or your mentor . Stop sounding so stupid and get off this board .</Msg><Username>lyonsaudit</Username><Timestamp>1370726598627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:23:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370728242007-35</Id><Title>Snapchat</Title><Msg>I was reading about their push to recruit salespeople from Stanford &amp; USC. They are raising $100 million pushing their valuation near the $1 billion mark. It sounds ridiculous to me but what do you all think? Maybe I am missing the boat here. Are they moving aggressively to make themselves an attractive acquisition for a large co. that's been doing a lot of acquiring lately?</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370728242007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370729078222-36</Id><Topic><Title>Snapchat</Title><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370728242007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see, well don't shoot the messenger. I was reading the latest article from Techcrunch said: "Snapchat is aggressively recruiting sales people from Stanford as well as USC for its impending debut of a monetization scheme, we’ve discovered. Meanwhile it’s raising $100 million at a valuation as high as $1 billion to pay them, as well as buy more servers and hire other talent to power its rapidly growing self-destructing messaging app, sources say" Odd yes, but I took it to mean, they are hiring University students to 'sell' Snapchat. Where is this McGill you speak of ?</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370729078222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370730722217-37</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IDIOT .</Msg><Username>lyonsaudit</Username><Timestamp>1370730722217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370731716109-38</Id><Topic><Title>Snapchat</Title><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370728242007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was a joke. I am from Montreal - Monsieur.</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370731716109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 18:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370732708246-39</Id><Topic><Title>Coldone's Advice To Buy From $11 to $23 Was Genius</Title><Username>tetheredbird</Username><Timestamp>1370629977022</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 14:32:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you say such crazy things &amp; why are you harassing Lyonsaudit?</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370732708246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370733634166-40</Id><Title>NSA/PRISM</Title><Msg>Marissa just tweeted a link to Yahoo's Tumblr page, which I can't not post here. (mods really yahoo.tumblr perhaps that should be white-listed) with a response to the NSA/PRISM issue. I may be biased, but I think it is the best response, to date, of all companies that have been mentioned as possibly allowing the US gov't full access.</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370733634166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:20:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370733882714-41</Id><Topic><Title>NSA/PRISM</Title><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370733634166</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:20:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I 'can't not' spell either....</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370733882714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370736182264-42</Id><Title>If true this could be HUGE...</Title><Msg>As you all know on Wednesday Yahoo updated their search result GUI. I did a calculation (you will not see it any place else) of the week over week growth on Mobile Search. Typically the weekly search volume oscillates, picking on the weekends, so is really hard to use daily search volume to calculate growth. But analyzing Thursday's volume, we got a 4.7% week over week jump and doing the same on Friday's I got the same 4.5% week over week growth. Prior average week over week growth was 0.08% on Thursday and 1.2% on Fridays. It is too early to tell, but If this is so, Yahoo will dominate 20% of mobile search by August and by years end they would have 40% of the US mobile search volume. WOW!</Msg><Username>webdave_2000</Username><Timestamp>1370736182264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 20:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370739687324-43</Id><Title>crowdfunding</Title><Msg>This form of investing just became legal. Now, I founded a company and I don't know if this is the best way for me to raise the capital needed. Any opinions?</Msg><Username>dr.linares</Username><Timestamp>1370739687324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 21:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370744051775-44</Id><Topic><Title>Snapchat</Title><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370728242007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we're simple folk in Montreal. (~~,</Msg><Username>basketaetc1</Username><Timestamp>1370744051775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 22:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370745541809-45</Id><Title>the price of copper</Title><Msg>Does anyone know how come the price of copper stays almost unchanged yet gold and silver are on a roller coaster ride?</Msg><Username>dr.linares</Username><Timestamp>1370745541809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 22:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370747137095-46</Id><Title>Quantitative Easing (printing money)</Title><Msg>Will someone please explain to me how is the Treasury Department going to explain to all those "retired" people that live on a fixed income from the T-bills and bonds that they are going to be broke "any minute now"! Because it's all over the news that the Federal Reserve is going to start pulling back their help. In other words slow down their printing of $85 billions a month. Are we ready for this?</Msg><Username>dr.linares</Username><Timestamp>1370747137095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 23:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370747259800-47</Id><Title>New feature release!!</Title><Msg>I just noticed on tumblr app that lots of images are shared from Flickr. This is awesome and integrated very well. Nice job team yahoo/tumblr!! I love it. Further proof that the vision is coming to fruition.</Msg><Username>kwda_838</Username><Timestamp>1370747259800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 23:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>