<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347614611597-1</Id><Title>sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss hhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh iiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii nnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnnn eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo lllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa ___________________________________ 99999999999999999999999999999999999 88888888888888888888888888888888888</Title><Msg>:)</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1347614611597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 05:23:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347615062900-2</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot savaged by editorial boards across the country</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347588061813</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:01:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But the retardlicans will defend him b/c it's like me eating the freezer burned ice cream from my fridge: it's all I got. Pubs say, "Hey, can we have a RNC again do-over????? This time lets pick a Christian." LOL Pubs are sabotaged in November as Stinkeymoney keeps throwing himself under the bus. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1347615062900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 05:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347626869454-3</Id><Topic><Title>KANSAS REDNECKS GONE WILD</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347586175702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:29:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a bunch of scummy ignorant wholeasses these people are: AP: Kansas board delays decision on Obama, ballot Published 9/14/2012 in News : Politics TOPEKA (AP) — Kansas election officials said Thursday that they want more information before deciding whether to remove President Barack Obama from the state's November ballot. The all-Republican State Objections Board heard arguments Thursday on a claim from a Manhattan resident that Obama is not eligible to be president because his father was from Kenya. The resident, Joe Montgomery, also questions whether Obama has a valid birth certificate. The notion that Obama was born anywhere other than in Hawaii has long been discredited, and the White House released his long-form birth certificate last year. Hawaii officials also have repeatedly confirmed his citizenship. His mother was a Kansas native.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347626869454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347626920462-4</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone watch that movie that has all the Muslim's panties in a Bunch? It's rather funny!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1347625148422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah! it was awesome! I wore my t-shirt that has cartoon of a bomb in Mohammed's turbine during it! If this movie was about Jesus Christ, Heelory and Dumbo would be praising it as another great American product!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347626920462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:48:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347627512368-5</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone watch that movie that has all the Muslim's panties in a Bunch? It's rather funny!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1347625148422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And one of them pesky ex-Seals went down thanks to Sam. Great movie, hey billie? !</Msg><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1347627512368</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347628101533-6</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone watch that movie that has all the Muslim's panties in a Bunch? It's rather funny!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1347625148422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't go down because of a movie - now you won't even tolerate free speech? Implying the guy didn't have a right to make his movie - well that is just anti-american at its core. What next - they storm the embassy becuase they don't like m night shyamalan - like the rest of us?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347628101533</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 09:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347628788072-7</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone watch that movie that has all the Muslim's panties in a Bunch? It's rather funny!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1347625148422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 08:19:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heelory vagina licker 'Huma" is clearly an inteliigence leak. Her whole family is in the mooslim brotha 'hood!!! Heelory, Dumbo...traitors at large..do not believe ANY White House statements. State and White House are in complete Foreign Policy meltdown!! Definition: They don't know what the 'F' to do!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347628788072</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 09:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347630232784-8</Id><Title>Freiberg Effect - Fire Him Again - Til This Think Hits $25</Title><Msg>line up another one - shoot him in the county square</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347630232784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 09:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347632894860-9</Id><Title>YEEEEEEEEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA</Title><Msg>EOM.</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1347632894860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347633017420-10</Id><Topic><Title>YEEEEEEEEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA</Title><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1347632894860</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now we have to see if we can hold onto and expand these gains. At $10, until the quarterly, I'd call it a buy rather than a strong buy, for the first time in months.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1347633017420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347633445483-11</Id><Title>AMTD, SCHW, WFC, BAC are you on board? The ETFC train is leaving the station.</Title><Msg>If you don't act soon, you will miss this train. Feds buying MBS is good news directly and indirectly for ETFC. This should be up 20% just on the news.</Msg><Username>ayeque70</Username><Timestamp>1347633445483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 10:37:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347635393886-12</Id><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Msg>from the Sun-Sentinel Republicans are finished Sept. 14, 2012 Win, lose or draw in November, the Republican Party is over, finished, kaput. How do I know? Tampa tells me so — -and demographics. At what should have been the culmination of four years of relentless plotting against President Obama, and in an election cycle that was its to lose, the GOP self-destructed, staging a convention that never got off the ground. It started and stopped and sputtered in between. But it wasn't because of Tropical Storm Isaac. The rain or shine outside had nothing to do with the climate inside, where conditions were inclement at best. Fact is: hardly anyone really likes Mitt Romney, even people who say they do — and it showed. He's everybody's Cracker Jack box without a prize, the kid to whose birthday party no one wants to be invited to, even though his house has a swimming pool. He's the would-be head of the richest and most powerful nation on earth, from whom you wouldn't buy a vacuum cleaner without a money-back guarantee. Click here to find out more! It appears the only way he could get anyone except his wife to speak on his behalf was to let them unofficially launch their 2016 campaigns for president — and barely mention him. But that's not the worst of it. Pick an issue, any issue. The Elephant Party has become the Ostrich Party — burying its head in the sand, refusing to face reality and build bridges to millions of potential supporters. This year's convention was an apotheosis of all the mean-spirited attacks the tea party/Republicans have been waging against women, gays and lesbians, healthcare reform, China, Russia, undocumented immigrants, Iran, Iraq, Social Security, Medicare — without so much as a single, realistic, workable, compassionate solution to attract undecided voters. The GOP today is largely a party of rabid, old, white men in the unhappy dusk of their lives, railing against a nation in which they are no longer the dominant players. It is sad to watch — and sadder to be one of them. You can smell the mothballs of their memories and memorabilia (hats and banners resurrected for the convention), read the rage in their eyes. And then, there was Romney's desperate pandering to thespians. Clint Eastwood lost every vestige of dignity and respect he might still have had by talking to an empty chair, undercutting what was supposed to have been Romney's shining moment. And inconceivably, Romney, ever the kid no one wanted to play with, actually made the executive decision to allow him to speak without vetting his remarks, just to show people he had a friend. But it backfired miserably. If Ronald Reagan vindicated the role of thespians in society, Eastwood set it back for at least a generation. And finally, you could see it in every picture of the Tampa convention, especially contrasted with those from the Democrats: The undeniable truth is that the Republican Party is on the wrong side of demographics, which means it's on the wrong side of history. Tragically for our political system, which depends on a vigorous, healthy two-party system, it has chosen to assume the role of permanent obstructionist, ignoring the inevitable changes in population diversity that will eventually bury it. So, in the end, the GOP will become the party of Romney, which no one will want to attend, no matter how enticing the swimming pool — if it isn't it already.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347636073805-13</Id><Topic><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's funny - a one choice landscape - only democrats. LOL - jizus xxrist on a stick - do you even read the stuff you post?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347636073805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347636699747-14</Id><Topic><Title>E-bank</Title><Username>i_like_tech</Username><Timestamp>959865332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2000-06-01 09:15:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Haaaa.... A very funny post....</Msg><Username>du_fonz</Username><Timestamp>1347636699747</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347636708641-15</Id><Topic><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They populate this MB: " The GOP today is largely a party of rabid, old, white men in the unhappy dusk of their lives, railing against a nation in which they are no longer the dominant players. It is sad to watch — and sadder to be one of them. You can smell the mothballs of their memories and memorabilia (hats and banners resurrected for the convention), read the rage in their eyes."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347636708641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:31:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347636897578-16</Id><Topic><Title>Da Debt Bomb ...when will it go off? ...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1306899888000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-05-31 23:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lolrotf... Old times</Msg><Username>du_fonz</Username><Timestamp>1347636897578</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347637026887-17</Id><Topic><Title>How's E*bank doing</Title><Username>hellasmusic</Username><Timestamp>1347558788895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:53:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saw the E*trade baby, no mention that there is even a bank..</Msg><Username>du_fonz</Username><Timestamp>1347637026887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347641207305-18</Id><Topic><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP will eventually reconstitute itself into something more viable than exists today. There may actually be a brief period of one party dominance. After the election--no matter who wins or loses--the most likely scenario is a rump GOP made up of tea party types.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1347641207305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347641719128-19</Id><Topic><Title>What is wrong with Obama's thinking?</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347568403200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:33:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no mind.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347641719128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 12:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347642354471-20</Id><Topic><Title>Da Debt Bomb ...when will it go off? ...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1306899888000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-05-31 23:44:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is following in Greenspans shoes of creating a bubble in equities which will end badly. These jewish Fed bankers are for sale to Wall Street like kind...enjoy the ride while it last.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347642354471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:05:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347644921881-21</Id><Topic><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benjy Sarlin September 14, 2012, 1:00 PM 5124 A Barack Obama win in November will lead to a meltdown within the Republican Party, said Bryan Fischer, an influential official at the American Family Association. And he isn’t too optimistic about Mitt Romney’s chances. “If Barack Obama wins this election the Republican Party as we know it is finished, it is dead, it is toast — you can stick a fork in it,” he told TPM Friday at the Values Voter Summit in Washington. “And conservatives, grassroots conservatives, are either going to start a third party or they are going to launch a hostile takeover of the Republican Party.” Fischer said he believed Romney would be leading national polls by double digits at this point if he had followed Paul Ryan’s lead and offered more detailed conservative positions on the budget and social issues. “The biggest mistake is they put a bag over Paul Ryan’s head,” he said. Fischer said he was “deeply disturbed” that Ryan didn’t mention the campaign’s opposition to gay marriage in his speech to the summit on Friday. “I got to believe that there was some kind of directive from the top of the campaign: We don’t want you to deal with this issue,” he said. Fischer has never exactly been on good terms with Romney. The Republican nominee denounced Fischer at last year’s Values Voter Summit for derogatory comments he made against Mormons. Fischer was left off the speakers list at this year’s summit, where he’s been a mainstay in the recent past. He also broke with Romney and other top Republican officials last month to strongly defend Todd Akin over his comments that women have an unnamed biological defense that prevents them from becoming pregnant after “legitimate rape.” While he did not predict Romney would lose, he had some advice for conservatives looking to rebuild the party in the wake of an Obama re-election. “I think if Mitt Romney loses this election that the pro-family leaders in the United States should get together with Rick Perry on Nov. 7 and start planning for 2016,” he said.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347644921881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347646549130-22</Id><Topic><Title>Demise of the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347635393886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 11:09:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jungelrbob you seem to have a problem with white folks, you should move out of your white neighborhood and move to the hood where you will feel more comfortable with like minded folks.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347646549130</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 14:15:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347653034780-23</Id><Title>Bachmann, doing the Talibornagain rag....</Title><Msg>Bachmann: Libya attack was effort to impose Sharia law on the U.S. By David Edwards Friday, September 14, 2012 11:39 EDT Print Share on facebookShare on redditShare on diggShare on twitterShare on farkShare on stumbleupon? Michele Bachmann speaks to Values Voter Summit Topics: michelle bachmann ♦ President Barack Obama ♦ President Obama Former Republican presidential candidate Michelle Bachmann on Friday asserted that the recent attacks on American embassies in Libya and Egypt were part of a plan to bring Sharia law to the United States. “The violence has come to us, the United States,” the Minnesota congresswoman warned in a speech at the Values Voter Summit. “And on the anniversary of 9-1-1, no less, our Libyan ambassador and his courageous staff lost their lives in Benghazi in Libya in a cruel, cold-blooded, gruesome, intentional terror attack.” “And all the while, the response of this administration has communicated both weakness and lack of resolve to the world,” she charged. “I want to be perfectly clear, this isn’t just about a movie. This is an intentional act that was done by radical Islamists who seek to impose their beliefs on the rest of the world and we will not stand for it!” “And what we’re watching develop before our eyes today are the direct consequences of this administration’s policy of apology and appeasement across the globe and the supposed success of the president’s foreign policy genius — hailed by the media, even last week — is now exposed for what it is.” Bachmann went on to explain President Barack Obama’s “relationship” with the Organization for Islamic Cooperation, which she claimed had a 10-year plan “to implement its Sharia-based speech code requirements worldwide.” “That, my friends, explains the story of this week,” she insisted. “Islamic-enforced speech codes. No one, not Muslims, not non-Muslims, not Americans are allowed to say anything Islamists see as insulting to their religion. They intend to force us to kiss our freedom of speech and religion goodbye. And that’s why we’re being forewarned today.” “President Obama needs to get his priorities straight,” Bachmann concluded. “What he needs to do is he needs to cancel his interview with David Letterman, cancel his meeting with Beyonce, cancel his meeting with Jay-Z, and instead, agree to meet with the prime minister of Israel, Benjamin Netanyahu!” Earlier this year, Sen. John McCain (R-AZ) accused Bachmann and four other Republican lawmakers of “specious and degrading attacks” after they called on inspectors general in the State, Homeland Security, Defense and Justice departments to investigate “potential Muslim Brotherhood infiltration” of the Obama administration by Huma Abedin, an aide to Secretary Clinton and wife of former Rep. Anthony Weiner (D-NY). Watch this video from CNN, broadcast Sept. 14, 2012.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347653034780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 16:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347654963422-24</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's tax policy is a sham</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney Tax Plan WASHINGTON -- Over the past few weeks, the Romney campaign has repeatedly pointed to five separate studies supporting the candidate's contention that a dramatic, across-the-board, reduction in tax rates can be paid for by economic growth and the elimination of deductions and exemptions for high-income earners. Romney himself referenced these five studies in an interview with Meet the Press on Sunday. His running mate, Rep. Paul Ryan (R-Wis.), said the same during his run through the Sunday show circuit. A closer examination, however, calls into question the fact that there are even five studies at all. Last week, the Romney campaign passed along the five documents that the candidate had referenced on NBC's Meet the Press. Three of the five are blog posts or op-eds (as opposed to academic literature), and two of those three are written by the same author: Harvard economist Martin Feldstein. Of the remaining two studies, one is the tax reform white paper authored by Romney-backing economists and paid for by Romney for President, Inc. (in an email to PolitiFact, the Romney campaign highlighted several Wall Street Journal editorials in place of the campaign white paper as the "fifth" study). The final study, produced by Princeton University's Harvey Rosen, backs the Romney campaign's assertions by arguing that people will work more, accumulate more income, pay more taxes, and seek out fewer loopholes if their tax rates are lowered. But even that report has several nuances that complicate the candidate's use of it. Romney is not without philosophical support with respect to his tax plan. The Wall Street Journal editorials that his campaign sent PolitiFact, for one, argue that sharp reductions in tax rates will spur economic growth, which, in turn, will allow for increases in tax revenues. Those pieces have helped the campaign push back on a critical study by the Tax Policy Center, which concluded that Romney would have to eliminate tax deductions on things like home mortgage interest payments, charitable donations, and employer-provided health insurance in order to have his plan be deficit-neutral. But even Feldstein has said that to make Romney's math work, some of those deductions would have to be eliminated on incomes over $100,000. In his August 28 Wall Street Journal piece, what Romney calls a "study," Feldstein writes that Romney could generate $191 billion by scrubbing these deductions, "more than enough to offset the revenue losses from the individual tax cuts proposed by Gov. Romney." In other words, the economist who has written two of the five studies that the Romney campaign highlights has conceded that Romney would have to eliminate tax preferences for people making over $100,000 per year in order to make his plan work. And yet, when asked in an interview with "Good Morning America" on Friday morning if he would remove those deductions and exemptions for incomes over $100,000, Romney said "no." "That’s not what I propose," he said. "And, of course, part of my plan is to stimulate economic growth. The biggest source of getting the country to a balanced budget is not by raising taxes or by cutting spending." The statement follows months of refusals from the Romney campaign to actually detail what kind of deductions and exemptions the candidate would seek to eliminate once in office. George Stephanopoulos, hosting GMA, pushed back, noting that Romney was now actually distancing himself from a study he routinely cites as supportive. Romney responded by saying he hadn't "seen [Feldstein's] precise study" but that there were five studies in total "that point out that we can get to a balanced budget without raising taxes on middle income people." Romney would define middle income as $200,000 to $250,000 per year and lower. With that measure of middle class, Princeton economist Rosen's study may still suffice. Rosen argued that Romney could get his tax plan to deficit neutrality by eliminating deductions for income over $200,000 a year. But in a separate interview with Reuters on Friday, he seemingly revised that figure downward to $100,000 per year "What the political system would find feasible, I don’t know,” Rosen said. “It’s mathematically possible." Even then, there are questions that surround the study's conclusions. Rosen depends on assumptions that he acknowledges are not made by the Treasury Department or the Congressional Joint Committee on Taxation about how high-income earners respond to changes in tax rates. Unlike those government bodies, he assumes that the wealthy will not seek to take advantage of as many tax loopholes if their overall tax rate is lower. More importantly, he assumes that Romney's tax plan will grow wage and capital income by at least three percent. This could be viewed as an aggressive assumption. Under President Bush, the entire economy (not just tax policy) resulted in total personal income growth that varied between 2.8 percent and 6.7 percent. Romney may agree with Rosen's data when it comes to wage growth. But he is now on record opposing the idea that certain exemptions and deductions would need to be eliminated above a $100,000-a-year threshold in order to make the plan work. The situation seems to leave the Romney campaign with supportive economists, but no purely supportive academic study. In addition to Rosen's work and Feldstein's two articles, the Romney campaign has highlighted a post by Matt Jensen of the American Enterprise Institute. But that post is primarily a rebuke of a small sliver of the Tax Policy Center analysis -- Jensen argues that, contrary the TPC, Romney could get tens of billions in revenue by eliminating the exclusion of interest on tax-exempt bonds and interest on life insurance savings. The Romney campaign's own white paper, authored by Romney-backing economists, doesn't attempt to lay out how mathematically his plan will work. Instead, it says that the former governor will "broaden the base to ensure that tax reform is revenue neutral."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347654963422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 16:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347655007559-25</Id><Title>Congradulations Mr. Obama</Title><Msg>Thank Mr. Obama and Mr. Bernanke for this... US Credit Rating Cut by Egan-Jones ... Again Ratings firm Egan-Jones cut its credit rating on the U.S. government to "AA-" from "AA," citing its opinion that quantitative easing from the Federal Reserve would hurt the U.S. economy and the country's credit quality. The Fed on Thursday said it would pump $40 billion into the U.S. economy each month until it saw a sustained upturn in the weak jobs market. In its downgrade, the firm said that issuing more currency and depressing interest rates through purchasing mortgage-backed securities does little to raise the U.S.'s real gross domestic product, but reduces the value of the dollar. In turn, this increases the cost of commodities, which will pressure the profitability of businesses and increase the costs of consumers thereby</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347655007559</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 16:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347659937887-26</Id><Title>Muslim hostility will ease</Title><Msg>Whoops not so fast! OBAMA FLASHBACK: The Day I'm Inaugurated Muslim Hostility Will Ease Then-Senator Barack Obama makes the case for an Obama Presidency on November 21, 2007 by saying he is uniquely qualified to bring stability to America's relationships in the Muslim world because he lived in an Islamic country during his youth and his half-sister is Muslim.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347659937887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347660945093-27</Id><Topic><Title>Muslim hostility will ease</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347659937887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, did he have 'Composite Mooo-sleem Gurlfriend' too??? Oh, the tall tales of Dumbo!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347660945093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 18:15:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347665239562-28</Id><Topic><Title>Muslim hostility will ease</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347659937887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 17:58:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OBAMA FLASHBACK: The Day I'm Inaugurated Muslim Hostility Will Ease" That's not what Obama said , is it? You slime on the right just invent stuff.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347665239562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 19:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347665945821-29</Id><Title>Labor gets a win in WI</Title><Msg>Judge Strikes Down Wis. Law Limiting Union Rights by The Associated Press text size A A A MADISON, Wis. September 14, 2012, 07:19 pm ET MADISON, Wis. (AP) — A Wisconsin judge on Friday struck down nearly all of the state law championed by Gov. Scott Walker that effectively ended collective bargaining rights for most public workers. Walker's administration immediately vowed to appeal, while unions, which have vigorously fought the law, declared victory. But what the ruling meant for existing public contracts was murky: Unions claimed the ruling meant they could negotiate again, but Walker could seek to keep the law in effect while the legal drama plays out. The law, a crowning achievement for Walker that made him a national conservative star, took away nearly all collective bargaining rights from most workers and has been in effect for more than a year. Dane County Circuit Judge Juan Colas ruled that the law violates both the state and U.S. Constitution and is null and void. In his 27-page ruling, the judge said sections of the law "single out and encumber the rights of those employees who choose union membership and representation solely because of that association and therefore infringe upon the rights of free speech and association guaranteed by both the Wisconsin and United States Constitutions." Colas also said the law violates the equal protection clause by creating separate classes of workers who are treated differently and unequally. The ruling applies to all local public workers affected by the law, including teachers and city and county government employees, but not those who work for the state. They were not a party to the lawsuit, which was brought by a Madison teachers union and a Milwaukee public workers union. Walker issued a statement accusing the judge of being a "liberal activist" who "wants to go backwards and take away the lawmaking responsibilities of the legislature and the governor. We are confident that the state will ultimately prevail in the appeals process." Wisconsin Department of Justice spokeswoman Dana Brueck said DOJ believes the law is constitutional. The ruling throws into question changes that have been made in pay, benefits and other work rules in place across the state for city, county and school district workers. Walker's law, passed in March 2011, only allowed for collective bargaining on wage increases no greater than the rate of inflation. All other issues, including workplace safety, vacation, health benefits, could no longer be bargained for. The ruling means that local government and schools now must once again bargain over those issues, said Lester Pines, an attorney for Madison Teachers Inc. that brought the case. "We're back to where we were before the law was enacted," he said. Pines predicted the case would ultimately be resolved by the state Supreme Court. "What's going to happen in the interim is unknown," he said. The state Supreme Court in June 2011 ruled that the law was constitutional after it had been blocked by a different Dane County judge on a challenge over its passage being a violation of open meetings law. Walker introduced the proposal in February 2011, six weeks after he took office. It resulted in a firestorm of opposition and led to huge protests at the state Capitol that lasted for weeks. All 14 Democratic state senators fled the state to Illinois for three weeks in an ultimately failed attempt to stop the law's passage from the Republican-controlled Legislature. The law required public workers to pay more for their health insurance and pension benefits at the same time it took away their ability to collectively bargain over those issues. Walker argued the changes were needed to help state and local governments save money at a time Wisconsin faced a $3 billion budget shortfall. Anger over the law's passage led to an effort to recall Walker from office. More than 930,000 signatures were collected triggering the June recall election. Walker won and became the first governor in U.S. history to survive a recall. Democrats and unions were ecstatic with Friday's ruling. "As we have said from day one, Scott Walker's attempt to silence the union men and women of Wisconsin's public sector was an immoral, unjust and illegal power grab," said Phil Neuenfeldt, president of the Wisconsin State AFL-CIO. The Democratic minority leader in the state Assembly called the ruling a huge victory for workers and free speech. "This decision will help re-establish the balance between employees and their employers," said Rep. Peter Barca. Republican Rep. Robin Vos, a staunch supporter of the law and the presumptive next speaker of the Assembly, called the ruling an example of the "arrogance of the judiciary." "I'm confident it's a single judge out of step with the mainstream," Vos said. He said the law is working "and we'll continue to implement it."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347665945821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 19:39:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347667300331-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot's tax policy is a sham</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347654963422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 16:36:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>September 13, 2012 THIS JUST IN: Tax Cuts for Rich Still Don't Drive Economic Growth When it comes to the subject of taxes, virtually article of faith held dear by Republicans has been proven false. For example, it's not true that "tax cuts pay for themselves" or that they increase revenue. Now, two new studies cut right to the heart of the bogus conservative claim that slashing tax rates for the richest Americans fuels job creation and economic growth. As these data are the just the latest to confirm, cutting taxes for "job creators" doesn't create jobs, but instead only produces a growing chasm of inequality and mountains of debt. As David Cay Johnston explained in Reuters, a new analysis by University of California graduate student and former staff economist on the Obama White House Council of Economic Advisers Owen M. Zidar undercuts a central argument of Mitt Romney and his GOP allies. (Ironically, Zidar once worked for an arm of Bain Capital.) Johnston summed up Zidar's findings about the top-down versus bottom up benefits of tax rate reductions at the state level: He reasoned that "if tax cuts for high income earners generate substantial economic activity, then states with a large share of high income taxpayers should grow faster following a tax cut for high income earners." The data show that tax cuts at the top, though, do not result in faster growth in states with more high-earners. "Almost all of the stimulative effect of tax cuts," Zidar found, "results from tax cuts for the bottom 90 percent. A one percent of GDP tax cut for the bottom 90 percent results in 2.7 percentage points of GDP growth over a two-year period. The corresponding estimate for the top 10 percent is 0.13 percentage points and is insignificant statistically." (Kansas Republican Governor Sam Brownback is about to learn that the hard way. Brownback recently signed a bill eliminating business taxes for 200,000 companies and slashing upper-income rates by 20 percent. The result isn't merely a dramatic shift of the tax burden onto less well-off Kansans, but will mean lost revenue "equivalent of 36 percent of the state budget within five years.") Meanwhile, a new report from the United States Census Bureau is just the latest evidence of the failure of the Bush tax cuts. While the poverty rate held steady at 15 percent in 2011, it increased throughout the previous decade even before the onset of the calamitous Bush recession in late 2007. (And as Sarah Kliff noted in the Washington Post, if not for policies including Social Security, unemployment benefits, food stamps and the Earned Income Tax Credit, the poverty rate would be 10.9 points higher and include 33.6 million more Americans.) But as the New York Times detailed, "The income gap between the wealthiest 20 percent of American households and the rest of the country grew sharply in 2011, the Census Bureau reported, as an overwhelming majority of Americans saw no gains from a weak economic recovery in its second full year." Fueled by a 5.3 percent jump in the income share of the top five percent of earners, the highest quintile enjoyed a 1.6 percent increase overall. (As explained here, the wealthiest Americans had already recovered from the Great Recession by 2010.) The other 80 percent of Americans either lost ground or made no progress at all. (See chart at top.) As McClatchy summed it up, "the earnings gap between rich and poor logged the largest annual increase since income inequality was first measured two decades ago." By 2010, the wealth of the richest one percent of households reached 288 times that of the median, a stratospheric rise from just three years earlier.) Those findings offer new support for President Obama's proposal to address the so-called "fiscal cliff" and refill the coffers of the United States Treasury by almost $1 trillion over the next decade by letting the Bush tax cuts for the top two percent of earners expire at the end of 2012. In contrast, Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney is offering a massive tax cut windfall for those he and his party call "job creators." Of course, there's only one problem with the Republican approach. The data are clear: lower taxes for America's so called job-creators don't mean either faster economic growth or more jobs for Americans. That dismal performance prompted David Leonhardt of the New York Times to ask, "Why should we believe that extending the Bush tax cuts will provide a big lift to growth?" His answer was unambiguous: Those tax cuts passed in 2001 amid big promises about what they would do for the economy. What followed? The decade with the slowest average annual growth since World War II. Amazingly, that statement is true even if you forget about the Great Recession and simply look at 2001-7... Is there good evidence the tax cuts persuaded more people to join the work force (because they would be able to keep more of their income)? Not really. The labor-force participation rate fell in the years after 2001 and has never again approached its record in the year 2000. Is there evidence that the tax cuts led to a lot of entrepreneurship and innovation? Again, no. The rate at which start-up businesses created jobs fell during the past decade. Asked by Johnston to respond to Zidar's study, Romney campaign spokesperson Andrea Saul "urged against publishing a story about Zidar's work because it is preliminary and because of Zidar's connection to the Obama Administration." Or to put it another way, when it comes to taxes, the truth will not set Republicans free.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347667300331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 20:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347668852592-31</Id><Title>You Didit Protect That!</Title><Msg>When the ignorant unwashed are scaling the walls, murdering our citizens and taking down our flag, somebody needs thrown out on his cowardly a(s)s.</Msg><Username>dropkickuuuuuu</Username><Timestamp>1347668852592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 20:27:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347672366709-32</Id><Topic><Title>Labor gets a win in WI</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347665945821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 19:39:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rowdy, slayer, pacifican, and biddermoon eat your hearts out!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1347672366709</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 21:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347679577460-33</Id><Topic><Title>Pig's rule,,,,</Title><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1347419411344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 23:10:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yoh, slayer,,, You sure has hell know I'm not Brak,,, don't even try it bro. Sweet dreams,,, p ,</Msg><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1347679577460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 23:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>