<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350014849136-1</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CNN has it 48-44 for Ryan</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350014849136</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350015039562-2</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both did well, but Ryan avoided facts. And he slid like a greased rat around his "budget"</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350015039562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350015580399-3</Id><Title>Austerity bites- GOP remains clueless</Title><Msg>IMF Agrees: Austerity Bites Posted: 10/11/2012 10:24 am Sen. Todd Akin calls for abortion on demand, and free distribution of condoms. The CEO of Exxon decries global warming and demands an end to oil company subsidies along with new public investment in renewable energy. Arizona Sheriff Joe Arpaio calls for amnesty for undocumented workers. Not likely, right? But the equivalent of these improbables just took place in international economics. The International Monetary Fund, for decades famed for inflicting harsh austerity policies on developing nations, now says, "never mind," essentially admitting it got it wrong. IMF Director Christine LaGarde is calling on European nations to ease austerity measures before they cause another global recession. "The fund warned earlier this week that governments around the world had systematically underestimated the damage done to growth by austerity," the Financial Times reports. This extraordinary recognition of reality by the IMF raises an obvious question: Will Romney and Republicans get a clue? The IMF's call is a direct repudiation of the harsh austerity policies it has been peddling. Just like the IMF, Romney is passionate about deep cuts in federal spending, as well as tax reforms that do not lower revenues (He claims now that he wants to lower rates across the board, but pay for them completely by closing loopholes). In addition, Romney and Ryan rail against the Federal Reserve for printing money, for taking extraordinary measures to keep long term interest rates low. They wax hysterical about the inflation ogre that is about to materialize at any moment and lay waste to the economy. Romney even sent out a fundraising email savaging the Fed, claiming its newest round of "quantitative easing" was "another bailout." That "Barack Obama is at it again -- spending your tax dollars to bail out his failed economic plan... money we can't afford for jobs we will never see." Now, all of this is simply nonsense. Barack Obama has nothing to do with the Fed policy. The Federal Reserve is notoriously independent of the administration and Congress (and its chairman, Ben Bernanke, is a Republican economist who is basically pursuing what conservative guru Milton Friedman advocated: an aggressive monetary policy to counter recessionary currents). And the Fed isn't "spending your tax dollars." In fact, the Fed has been paying billions in profits back into the Treasury, reducing deficits -- not adding to them. And we don't have to "afford the money" because the Fed is basically printing it. Romney's combination of slashing spending and hiking interest rates would drive up unemployment, spread poverty and probably end up adding to deficits, as the economy moves back towards recession. Romney argues that the "confidence" that would come from his election would counter these effects. Don't bet the store on that. (There are precious few businesses that will bet even a new salary on it). Getting it Right Last fall, Barack Obama called for passage of the American Jobs Act, which included investments in rebuilding schools and infrastructure, rehiring teachers and cops, and a jobs corps for veterans, among other things. It would be paid for by tax hikes on the wealthiest Americans. Independent analysts, such as Macroeconomic Advisers, estimated that it would create 2.1 million additional jobs. Republicans -- committed to slashing spending and austerity -- killed the bill in the House, and filibustered it in the Senate. The IMF turn is a big deal. If nothing else, it should be a wake-up call to governments and candidates across the world. The IMF is saying, essentially, that Obama got it right. Will Romney, Ryan and Republicans get it? Will the "Gang of Eight" Senators meeting with Alan Simpson and Erskine Bowles, the Archdruids of austerity, take another look? Will Democrats stop plotting a grand bargain and start talking once more about how to get people back to work and the economy moving? The Real Deal In its latest World Economic Outlook (PDF), the Fund explicitly warns against "excessive fiscal contraction in the short term," while reiterating calls for a plan -- including tax and entitlement reforms -- that places "government debt on a sustainable path in the medium term." Contrary to Romney and Republican's braying on deficits, the U.S. doesn't have a short-term deficit crisis. We aren't Greece, and won't ever be. The U.S. has to get the economy moving and then take sensible measures to makes its projected debt sustainable. That should involve progressive tax reform -- raising taxes on the wealthy to produce more revenue -- just the reverse of the Romney plan to lower rates, eliminate the estate tax and sustain the capital gains and carried interest tax loopholes that benefit the very wealthy (and enable him to pay a 14 percent tax rate). And it should involve reforms to get our health-care spending -- the driver of our long term debt problems -- under control. Here, too, Romney and Ryan just get it wrong. This isn't about gutting Medicare and Medicaid. It's about fixing health care. Ryan's budget slashes Medicaid and turns Medicare into a voucher, doing nothing to control rising costs, only pushing more and more of them onto the very people least able to afford them; seniors, the disabled, the poor, the dying. What we must address is reform of our broken health care system, which otherwise will bankrupt everything -- companies, governments and families. That requires continuing on the path begun with Obamacare, which started to change how we deliver health care and put limits on insurance company excesses. Eventually -- after exhausting all other alternatives -- we'll get to where every other industrial country has ended up, with exactly what Republicans go nuts about: a "government takeover" of health care. Either through far more extensive regulation (think negotiating bulk discounts for prescription drugs, for example ) or through extending a Medicare-like system across the population, we'll get there. If we spent what other industrial countries spend per capita on health care (with better public health results), we would RIGHT NOW be projecting surpluses as far as the eye can see. The bastion of high finance, the IMF, has come out against austerity. Can Mitt be far behind? Look forward to the next debate, when Romney's new "etching" will no doubt have him denouncing the president for his jobs program, while suddenly offering up his own version to get the economy going.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1350015580399</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:19:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016172270-4</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan: My CNN colleagues all seem to think it was a draw. I don't agree. Biden clearly the winner.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1350016172270</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016172503-5</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan: My CNN colleagues all seem to think it was a draw. I don't agree. Biden clearly the winner.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1350016172503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016503527-6</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Biden won 50-31 per CBS snap poll. Is that supposed to be a tie???</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350016503527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016611937-7</Id><Topic><Title>Everybody Ready for Bidens' As Kicking?...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349997134307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 19:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slayer thinking with his a.zz again ? Drunk #$%$ rednecks are pathological.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350016611937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016852388-8</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About the VP debate - Sen. John Thune in spin room with #CNN's Jim Acosta. Where does GOP get these guys? Is there some evil genetic lab making Ken-Doll pols?</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350016852388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350016852639-9</Id><Topic><Title>VP Joe Biden won the debate by a wide margin!!!</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350014191605</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 23:56:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About the VP debate - Sen. John Thune in spin room with #CNN's Jim Acosta. Where does GOP get these guys? Is there some evil genetic lab making Ken-Doll pols?</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350016852639</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 00:40:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350038801696-10</Id><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Msg>'Hope and Change' is NOT classy, Not smart and is pure DEMENTED HATE!!! Was Biden channeling his 'Inner Al Gore' (2000 Sighing campaign). And the funny thing is Biden is clearly a better debater than Dumbo..and WAY smarter too. President Romney will bring 'Class' back to the White house!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350041990226-11</Id><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Msg>Biden interrupting, laughing, smirking while Americans want to hear both sides to serious issues we all ponder is frightenly DISRESPECTFUL!!! This is Saul Alinsky Chicago thuggery!!! Verbal 'OCCUPYING"!! Complete failure of leadership Biden and that other Dumbo keep dishing out. NO CLASS!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350046484310-12</Id><Title>Mittens and Ryan promise to stay in Afganistan forever and a while longer</Title><Msg>they promise to repeal the plan to leave in 2014. .. plus ,they are thinking about going back to rebuild Iraq but even better and it will be "self-financed" and will lower our deficit.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350046484310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 08:54:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350046906420-13</Id><Title>Joe Biden - SMIRKY MALARKY</Title><Msg>Biden was tiring and insincere. Ryan came through as real and caring human being. I'm afraid this might damage our Communist Muslim Brotherhood agenda. Alla akbar.</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350046906420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350046917667-14</Id><Topic><Title>business genius Mitt says you don't need health insurance. The hospital will pay for you</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349989299427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:01:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens says healthcare in the USA is no problem, the hospital pays for it. "Instead you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital" (the hospital pays for it !!! that Mittens is a laugh!!)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350046917667</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350047139753-15</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I'm the billionaire with a 90,000 sq ft house ordering you to vote for the 1%</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349990084747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:14:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi. me again, the billionaire, ordering you to lick my rear end, or i swear, i will move to a 3rd world country!..... and also, if eddie munster says YOU are going to stay in Afghanistan forever and a few days, you better do it.... or i will move to a 3rd world country and you will lose your job since there is no competition and you are too stupid to start your own business .</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350047139753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350047245127-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Socio-path says you will pay for Healthcare for Illegals (FAIR!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349992786308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden's War on Women!! Obamascare will be The Department of Motor vehicles handling Women's Gyno-doctors exam!! Sick and un-sterile!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350047245127</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350047316902-17</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I am the rich, Chicago, Occupy-Loving, Facist Traitor Ordering Totalitarianism!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349990818606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:26:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden Chicago Thuggery! White House has lost it!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350047316902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350047580381-18</Id><Title>Mitt, Eddie Munster &amp; the billionaire from versailles volunteered you for afghanistan</Title><Msg>Mitt, Eddie Munster &amp; the billionaire from versailles said it is easy for them to volunteer you. and if you don't do it, they will move to a 3rd world country....... not afghanistan of course, somewhere nice.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350047580381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350047959190-19</Id><Title>Dumbo and his Idiot Voters</Title><Msg>Dumbo the Stupid Idiot and Biden LYING about Bengahzi-gate. Who will go to jail with Hillary??</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350047959190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:19:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350048243724-20</Id><Title>"you go to the hospital you get care it's paid for by the hospital" Mitt, the business genius</Title><Msg>healthcare in the USA is no problem, the hospital pays for it.! "Instead you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital"</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350048243724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350051158151-21</Id><Title>McSame's moment of clarity</Title><Msg>"Sen. John McCain (R-Ariz.) continued his harsh criticism of the Supreme Court's Citizens United ruling this week, calling it the bench's "worst decision ever." “They said money is free speech. Since when is money free speech?” McCain asked a crowd at an event put on by Oxford University, according to the Oxonian Globalist. “Money is money.” The Supreme Court's 2010 ruling, which allowed corporations, unions and individuals to pour unlimited amounts of money into elections through super PACs, has elicited a strong responses from McCain in the past. Earlier this year he predicted that the unfettered influx of money, often from undisclosed sources, would lead to "huge scandals" in upcoming elections. McCain has traditionally been one of Congress' most enthusiastic supporters of campaign finance reform, and he lamented the demise of such efforts in the wake of the Citizens United decision. At times, he's appeared to act as if he's willing to accept defeat. Congressional Democrats have since pushed the DISCLOSE Act, a response to Citizens United that sought to rein in the flow of secret and foreign money into elections. McCain first refused to support it in 2010 over his belief that it disproportionately favored unions. Democrats proposed another version of the bill this year, but McCain again demurred over the same concerns, despite guarantees that it treated corporations and unions fairly. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350051158151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350052083272-22</Id><Title>Joltin Joe the Big Winner</Title><Msg>Everybody sees it.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1350052083272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350052819118-23</Id><Title>Lyin' Ryan clicks off 24</Title><Msg>At The Vice Presidential Debate: Ryan Told 24 Myths In 40 Minutes By Igor Volsky on Oct 12, 2012 at 9:04 am Paul Ryan spoke for 40 of the 90 minutes during Thursday night’s vice presidential debate and managed to tell at least 24 myths during that time: 1) “It took the president two weeks to acknowledge that [the Libya attack] was a terrorist attack.” Obama used the word “terrorism” to describe the killing of Americans the very next day at the Rose Garden. “No acts of terror will ever shake the resolve of this great nation, alter that character, or eclipse the light of the values that we stand for,” Obama said in a Rose Garden statement on September 12. 2) “The administration was blocking us every step of the way. Only because we had strong bipartisan support for these tough [Iran] sanctions were we able to overrule their objections and put them in spite of the administration.” Even the Israeli President has effusively praised President Obama’s leadership on getting American and international sanctions on Iran, which have significantly slowed Iran’s progress. 3) “Medicare and Social Security are going bankrupt. These are indisputable facts.” [T]he possibility of Medicare going bankrupt is — and historically has been — greatly exaggerated. In fact, if no changes are made, Medicare would still be able to meet 88 percent of its obligations in 2085. Social Security is fully funded for another two decades and could pay 75 percent of its benefits thereafter. There is also an easy way to ensure the program’s long-term solvency without large changes or cuts to benefits. 4) “The vice president was in charge of overseeing this. $90 billion in green pork to campaign contributors and special interest groups.” Multiple reviews, including an independent review of all Department Of Energy loan programs by Herb Allison –- finance chair for McCain for President 2008 –- have found no “pork” in the stimulus’ funding of green projects, concluding that the loans were not steered to friends or family, as Ryan claims. 5) “Was it a good idea to spend taxpayer dollars on electric cars in Finland, or on windmills in China?” As PolitiFact has pointed out, the money for electric cars in Finland did not come from the stimulus. Rather, it originated with the Energy Department’s Advanced Technology Vehicles Manufacturing program, which predated the Obama administration. The claim about “windmills in China” is also inaccurate. 6) “When they see us putting – when they see us putting daylight between ourselves and our allies in Israel, that gives them encouragement.” The Israeli Deputy Prime Minister and Defense Minister, Ehud Barak, told CNN, “President Obama is doing … more than anything that I can remember in the past [in regard to our security].” 7) “You see, if you reform these programs for my generation, people 54 and below, you can guarantee they don’t change for people in or near retirement.” Here is how the Romney/Ryan Medicare plan will affect current seniors: 1) by repealing Obamacare, the 16 million seniors receiving preventive benefits without deductibles or co-pays and are saving $3.9 billion on prescription drugs will see a cost increase, 2) “premium support” will increase premiums for existing beneficiaries as private insurers lure healthier seniors out of the traditional Medicare program, 3) Romney/Ryan would also lower Medicaid spending significantly beginning next year, shifting federal spending to states and beneficiaries, and increasing costs for the 9 million Medicare recipients who are dependent on Medicaid. 8) “Obamacare takes $716 billion from Medicare to spend on Obamacare.” Ryan is claiming that Obamacare siphons off $716 billion from Medicare, to the detriment of Medicare beneficiaries. In actuality, that money is saved primarily through reducing over-payments to insurance companies under Medicare Advantage, cutting waste fraud and abuse, and eliminating inefficiencies in the system. Ryan’s budget plan keeps those same cuts, but directs them toward tax cuts for the rich and deficit reduction. 9) “And then they put this new Obamacare board in charge of cutting Medicare each and every year in ways that will lead to denied care for current seniors.” The Board, or IPAB is tasked with making binding recommendations to Congress for lowering health care spending, should Medicare costs exceed a target growth rate. Congress can accept the savings proposal or implement its own ideas through a super majority. The panel’s plan will modify payments to providers but it cannot “include any recommendation to ration health care, raise revenues or Medicare beneficiary premiums…increase Medicare beneficiary cost-sharing (including deductibles, coinsurance, and co- payments), or otherwise restrict benefits or modify eligibility criteria” (Section 3403 of the ACA). Relying on health care experts rather than politicians to control health care costs has previously attracted bipartisan support and even Ryan himself proposed two IPAB-like structures in a 2009 health plan. 10) “7.4 million seniors are projected to lose their current Medicare Advantage coverage they have. That’s a $3,200 benefit cut.” Enrollment is actually projected to increase by 11 percent in Medicare Advantage (MA) in 2013. Since the Affordable Care Act was enacted in 2010, Medicare Advantage premiums have decreased an average of 10 percent and enrollment in these plans has increased 28 percent. 11) “This [Medicare premium support] plan that’s bipartisan. It’s a plan I put together with a prominent Democrat senator from Oregon.” Wyden not only voted against Ryan’s budget, he also called the idea that he supported it “nonsense.” 12) “Eight out of 10 businesses, they file their taxes as individuals, not as corporations.” Far less than half of the people affected by the expiration of the upper income tax cuts get any of their income at all from a small businesses. And those people could very well be receiving speaking fees or book royalties, which qualify as “small business income” but don’t have a direct impact on job creation. It’s actually hard to find a small business who think that they will be hurt if the marginal tax rate on income earned above $250,000 per year is increased. 13) “[Unemployment is rising] all around America.” In August, the unemployment rate dropped from a year before in 325 of 372 metro areas surveyed by the U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. 14) “The average tax rate on businesses in the industrialized world is 25 percent, and the president wants the top effective tax rate on successful small businesses to go above 40 percent.” The U.S. is raising historically low amounts of revenue from the corporate income tax, and it already has the second lowest effective corporate tax rate in the world. U.S. corporations are taxed less than their foreign rivals, and the U.S. effective corporate tax rate is low compared to other developed economies. 15) “He’ll keep saying this $5 trillion plan, I suppose. It’s been discredited by six other studies.” The studies Ryan cites actually further prove that Romney/Ryan would, in fact, have to raise taxes on the middle class if he were to keep his promise not to lose revenue with his tax rate reduction. 16) “You can – you can cut tax rates by 20 percent and still preserve these important preferences for middle-class taxpayer. It is mathematically possible. It’s been done before. It’s precisely what we’re proposing.” If Romney/Ryan hope to provide tax relief to the middle class, then their $5 trillion tax cut would add to the deficit. There are not enough deductions in the tax code that primarily benefit rich people to make his math work. As the Tax Policy Center concluded, Romney’s plan can’t both exempt middle class families from tax cuts and remain revenue neutral. “He’s promised all these things and he can’t do them all. In order for him to cover the cost of his tax cut without adding to the deficit, he’d have to find a way to raise taxes on middle income people or people making less than $200,000 a year,” the Center found. 17) “So they proposed a $478 billion cut to defense to begin with. Now we have another $500 billion cut to defense that’s lurking on the horizon. They insisted upon that cut being involved in the debt negotiations, and so we have a $1 trillion cut.” Ryan has frequently gotten in hot water for criticizing President Obama for the very same defense cuts that he voted for in 2011. 18) “If these cuts go through, our Navy will be the smallest – the smallest it has been since before World War I.” PolitiFact rated this claim as “Pants on Fire,” noting that “a wide range of experts told us it’s wrong to assume that a decline in the number of ships or aircraft automatically means a weaker military.” 19) “Look at what they’re doing through Obamacare with respect to assaulting the religious liberties of this country. They’re infringing upon our first freedom, the freedom of religion, by infringing on Catholic charities, Catholic churches, Catholic hospitals.” Religious institutions haven’t been forced to “violate their conscience” by paying for contraception. Houses of worship and other religious nonprofits that primarily employ and serve people of the same faith will be exempt from offering birth control. 20) “If you like your health care plan, you can keep it. Try telling that to the 20 million people who are projected to lose their health insurance if Obamacare goes through or the 7-point million – 7.4 million seniors who are going to lose it.” The Affordable Care Act would actually expand health care coverage to 30 million Americans and all seniors will keep their guranteed Medicare benefits, despite Ryan’s fear mongering. The Congressional Budget Office estimates that very few people will have to enroll in new coverage. 21) “We should not have called Bashar Assad a reformer when he was turning his Russian-provided guns on his own people.” In March 2011, Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton noted that “many of the members of Congress of both parties who have gone to Syria in recent months have said they believe he’s a reformer.” However, she did not endorse their view. 22) “When Barack Obama was elected, they had enough fissile material — nuclear material to make one bomb. Now they have enough for five.” This is misleading and unproven. Iran now has enough fissile material, but has not yet enriched to the necessary level for a weapon. The Institute for Science and International Security says “it would take Iran more than two months to produce that amount if it started with 20%-grade uranium, and ‘several months’ to make enough for a bomb using low-enriched uranium. That would give the world community enough time to detect the operation and organize a response, ISIS noted in June.” 23) “[Iran is] racing toward a nuclear weapon.” Israeli and American intelligence officials aren’t so sure. 24) “We don’t want to do is give our allies reason to trust us less [by announcing a withdrawal timeline for Afghanistan].” It’s unclear how our allies would trust us less since they too agreed to the timeline. As Biden pointed outed, “That’s a bizarre statement. .. Forty-nine of our allies — hear me — 49 of our allies signed on to this position.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350052819118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350052851703-24</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOSER!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350052851703</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:40:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350052937654-25</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden - SMIRKY MALARKY</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350046906420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:01:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo's smarter half, that's the scary part!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350052937654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:42:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350053018477-26</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rubber room for Off-His-Meds LOSER dental bully!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350053018477</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 10:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350056239646-27</Id><Title>Vote smart before it's to late</Title><Msg>Biden's ugly teeth are like that of a hoarse.... the rest of him is a hoarse's rear end. Paul did an excellent job and his joke about Biden knowing what it's like to have slips from the mouth was original and the best one liner of the night yet the media ignores it? Obama continues to weaken the USA with military cut's yet the world still does not like the United States? China continues to build a first rate military and challenge everyone in the region including the friends of U.S. as does Iran... Muslim brotherhood more radical than the regimes they toppled. America like it or not has prevented a third world war using the peace through strength mentality. Lets hope America stays strong and we don't face a real war do to weakness from the left someday. Socialism on a large scale is the system of communism the difference between communism and the system in America today is we still are lucky enough to have one party that voices it's opposition to the the socialism. The problem is that party is becoming smaller as the party of the left grows with open boarders and the growing welfare state. One scary thing + Romney and Paul have talked about a means test for social security? The system is bad now thanks to the left however to punish those who saved and made money is making a bad system worse and a play book from the left. Wake up Conservatives take bad the republican party before we are just like them.</Msg><Username>nasdaqboil</Username><Timestamp>1350056239646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350056402819-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt, Eddie Munster &amp; the billionaire from versailles volunteered you for afghanistan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350047580381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:13:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>uncle mittens wants you in afghanistan forever.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350056402819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350056515660-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo and his Idiot Voters</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350047959190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:19:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rice, Biden and.....DUMBO!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350056515660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350056540458-30</Id><Title>Mr. Ed and Biden have the same smile? Mr. Ed was a talking hoarse for those to young to know</Title><Msg>Biden's ugly teeth are like that of a hoarse.... the rest of him is a hoarse's rear end. Paul did an excellent job and his joke about Biden knowing what it's like to have slips from the mouth was original and the best one liner of the night yet the media ignores it? Obama continues to weaken the USA with military cut's yet the world still does not like the United States? China continues to build a first rate military and challenge everyone in the region including the friends of U.S. as does Iran... Muslim brotherhood more radical than the regimes they toppled. America like it or not has prevented a third world war using the peace through strength mentality. Lets hope America stays strong and we don't face a real war do to weakness from the left someday. Socialism on a large scale is the system of communism the difference between communism and the system in America today is we still are lucky enough to have one party that voices it's opposition to the the socialism. The problem is that party is becoming smaller as the party of the left grows with open boarders and the growing welfare state. One scary thing is Romney and Paul are talking about a means test for social security? The system is bad now thanks to the left however to punish those who saved and made money is making a bad system worse and a play book from the left. Wake up Conservatives take bad the republican party before we are just like them.</Msg><Username>nasdaqboil</Username><Timestamp>1350056540458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350056554175-31</Id><Topic><Title>"you go to the hospital you get care it's paid for by the hospital" Mitt, the business genius</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350048243724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did i mention that Mitt, the business genuis said this: "...you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital"................? heck, who needs health insurance since "you get care, and it's paid for.......by the hospital" !!</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350056554175</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350056668122-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Socio-path says you will pay for Healthcare for Illegals (FAIR!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349992786308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lots of mooo=sleem Illegals. Friggin' #$%$ of all #$%$!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350056668122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350057425858-33</Id><Title>healthcare for all is free at the hospital say mittens!</Title><Msg>hospital pays for it!!!</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057425858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350057634152-34</Id><Title>Mittens promises a 600 ship Navy or whatever..jobs jobs jobs says mittens ,ship building jobs!</Title><Msg>gonna stay in afghanistan forever and build more ships too, all self financing and deficit reducing! "Do you actually have the specifics? Or are you still working on it, and that's why you won't tell voters?" RADDATZ:</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057634152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350058295413-35</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens promises a 600 ship Navy or whatever..jobs jobs jobs says mittens ,ship building jobs!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057634152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is already a shortage of skilled workers - ESPECIALLY welders skilled enough to weld a ships or a pipeline. Looks to me Romney wants to create more jobs ......overseas.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1350058295413</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:11:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350058505551-36</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens promises a 600 ship Navy or whatever..jobs jobs jobs says mittens ,ship building jobs!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057634152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear there is no shortage of plumbers - if Romney gets elected and flushes the country down the toilet - I guess they'll be busy....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1350058505551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350060533134-37</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I am the rich, Chicago, Occupy-Loving, Facist Traitor Ordering Totalitarianism!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349990818606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:26:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, You're out of control! Please seek mental help!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350060533134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350060533163-38</Id><Topic><Title>Hi, I am the rich, Chicago, Occupy-Loving, Facist Traitor Ordering Totalitarianism!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349990818606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:26:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, You're out of control! Please seek mental help!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350060533163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:48:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350061267068-39</Id><Title>Too few stalks are supporting the market.</Title><Msg>Time for a bigger correction but I could be wrong. Snapple stepped in quick sand. hehe mojo</Msg><Username>mojo_trade</Username><Timestamp>1350061267068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350061771907-40</Id><Topic><Title>Too few stalks are supporting the market.</Title><Username>mojo_trade</Username><Timestamp>1350061267068</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:01:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Snapple's market cap getting smaller like the iPAD. LMAO bobby</Msg><Username>unclefestersdonkey</Username><Timestamp>1350061771907</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350062387937-41</Id><Title>those whiny billionaires don't want to pay for a 600 ship navy, they threaten to leave town!</Title><Msg>those whiny billionaires don't want to pay for a 600 ship navy, they threaten to leave town! and you better do as they say or they will go to the 3rd world and you will be sorry they left.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350062387937</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350062483809-42</Id><Title>What was yesterday...a pump dump ?</Title><Msg>If you take out Thursdays spike, the price chart moves down from Monday. Volume above average today going down. Ken or another hedge pump it up and sell a couple hundred thousand shares.</Msg><Username>hatdean</Username><Timestamp>1350062483809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350062895880-43</Id><Topic><Title>What was yesterday...a pump dump ?</Title><Username>hatdean</Username><Timestamp>1350062483809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yesterday and the first half of today was a relief rally in a larger downturn that is only beginning but I could be wrong. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcorn</Username><Timestamp>1350062895880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350064240940-44</Id><Title>Market Stimulus!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Bernanke should start shorting Apple and Google. This would force the lazy institutions to get more creative and spread the wealth to the other unfortunate stalks that make up the market universe. Isn't that the current US theme? #$%$</Msg><Username>bileshooter</Username><Timestamp>1350064240940</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350064718239-45</Id><Title>Lyin' Ryan nabbed again</Title><Msg>"During Thursday evening's debate, vice presidential candidate Rep. Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) did not offer new details on the Romney campaign's promise to slash taxes without losing the government a ton of revenue. The centrist Tax Policy Center has analyzed the plan and concluded that it would create wide budget deficits unless the Romney administration hiked taxes on the middle class. The Romney campaign has insisted that it would not. "What we are saying is lower tax rates across the board and close loopholes, primarily to the higher-income people," Ryan said on Thursday. "We have three bottom lines: Don't raise the deficit, don't raise taxes on the middle class and don't lower the share of income that is borne by the high-income earners." Among other things, the plan would cut all individual income tax rates by 20 percent. "Let's talk about this 20 percent," debate moderator Martha Raddatz said to Ryan. "You have refused yet again to offer specifics on how you pay for that 20 percent across-the-board tax cut. Do you actually have the specifics, or are you still working on it, and that's why you won't tell voters?" Ryan said that his plan would deny loopholes and deductions for higher-income earners, but he didn't specify whether the plan might target deductions for mortgage interest or charitable giving, for instance. "We want to work with Congress on how best to achieve this," he said. Raddatz asked, "You guarantee this math will add up?" "Six studies have verified that this adds up," Ryan said, repeating a claim Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney made in last week's debate against President Obama. The claim is debatable. As HuffPost has reported, three of the studies are blog posts or op-eds, and one was paid for by Romney for President Inc. (And the author of two of the pieces highlighted by the Romney campaign suggested the tax plan only works by eliminating tax preferences for people making more than $100,000.) But the supporting research for Romney's plan argues that the Tax Policy Center ignores the way the Romney tax reform would boost the economy, resulting in additional revenue. The Tax Policy Center's William G. Gale responded that TPC's models accounted for potential economic growth. Gale stands by the original conclusion that the Romney proposal inevitably "would provide large tax cuts to high-income households, and increase the tax burdens on middle- and/or lower-income taxpayers."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350064718239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350065885275-46</Id><Topic><Title>Market Stimulus!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>bileshooter</Username><Timestamp>1350064240940</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:50:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The small guys can not pay $600 to $800 a share for an equity and hope to make any significant profit. That's why they are bailing on the stock market. Obama needs to fix this problem. I can't survive on one apple a month with dollar cost averaging. m</Msg><Username>mitosis1</Username><Timestamp>1350065885275</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:18:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350067221044-47</Id><Topic><Title>What was yesterday...a pump dump ?</Title><Username>hatdean</Username><Timestamp>1350062483809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what the h#ll is a relief rally ?</Msg><Username>hatdean</Username><Timestamp>1350067221044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350068291259-48</Id><Title>How's E*Bank doing with all its mortgage loans..</Title><Msg>I've read there's been big profits in the loan business...</Msg><Username>du_fonz</Username><Timestamp>1350068291259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350068435036-49</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens promises a 600 ship Navy or whatever..jobs jobs jobs says mittens ,ship building jobs!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057634152</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:00:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are we going to get a chance to look at those 10 years of tax returns.. C'mon Mitt.. You want the job, we want to vet you too..</Msg><Username>ohioracketeer</Username><Timestamp>1350068435036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350068679841-50</Id><Topic><Title>"you go to the hospital you get care it's paid for by the hospital" Mitt, the business genius</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350048243724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 09:24:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup he said that.. But that's not what he wanted to say.. what he wanted to say was.. "...you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital"................?</Msg><Username>greekislandtaverna</Username><Timestamp>1350068679841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350068696959-51</Id><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Msg>Rep. Jason Chaffetz (R-Utah) acknowledged on Wednesday that House Republicans had consciously voted to reduce the funds allocated to the State Department for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010. For the past two years, House Republicans have continued to deprioritize the security forces protecting State Department personnel around the world. In fiscal year 2011, lawmakers shaved $128 million off of the administration's request for embassy security funding. House Republicans drained off even more funds in fiscal year 2012 -- cutting back on the department's request by $331 million.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350068717061-52</Id><Topic><Title>What was yesterday...a pump dump ?</Title><Username>hatdean</Username><Timestamp>1350062483809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 13:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shorts covering to lock in profits too early and longs bottom fishing too early cause relief rallies. Both are net positives for the stock price but only briefly. Longs get one last chance to bail and get relief from their pain before the general market trend continues lower. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcorn</Username><Timestamp>1350068717061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350070176616-53</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's mystery tax plan</Title><Msg>Timeline of Romney’s tax proposals to see just how flexible he has been: 9/6/11: Romney’s First Tax Cut For The Rich Promising not to cut taxes for the rich, Romney proposes a plan that would extend the Bush tax cuts, eliminate capital gains taxes for those making under $200,000, cut corporate taxes, and eliminate the estate tax. In all, it adds up to a $6.6-trillion cut that would have little benefit for the middle class, which doesn’t enjoy the same benefits from a capital gains cut as the rich. 2/22/12: Romney Introduces A New Tax Plan Under pressure from conservatives, Romney scraps his first plan in favor of the current plan, which maintains the Bush tax cuts, provides another 20-percent rate reduction for all Americans, cuts corporate taxes, and eliminates the estate tax. Romney says he will eliminate unspecified tax loopholes and deductions to pay for the plan. Romney promises he won’t cut taxes for the rich. He also promises his plan won’t add to the deficit. 2/22/12: Romney Promises To Cut Taxes For The 1 Percent After criticism from fellow Republican presidential candidates, Romney asserts at a primary debate that “we’re going to cut taxes on everyone across the country by 20 percent, including the top 1 percent,” contradicting his previous assertion that he wouldn’t cut taxes for the rich. 3/1/12: Tax Plan Will Lead To $4.8 Trillion In Lost Revenue The nonpartisan Tax Policy Center scores Romney’s plan, finding that it would cost $4.8 trillion over the next 10 years. TPC does not take into account Romney’s plan to pay for his tax cuts, since he hasn’t yet proposed a specific way to do so. TPC found that Romney’s plan would give the average millionaire nearly $260,000 in tax cuts.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350070176616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350070825625-54</Id><Topic><Title>How's E*Bank doing with all its mortgage loans..</Title><Username>du_fonz</Username><Timestamp>1350068291259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 14:58:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand the bank no longer does mortgage loans..</Msg><Username>ohioracketeer</Username><Timestamp>1350070825625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350071788690-55</Id><Topic><Title>Why ETFC Could Make you Rich</Title><Username>davisdarius920</Username><Timestamp>1350045420324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 08:37:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, great help, and I did just this. sBest of luck, and many thanks guys!</Msg><Username>bonnercora469</Username><Timestamp>1350071788690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350075239119-56</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot's mystery tax plan</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350070176616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This what got your panties in a bunch? "The debate prompted 5 % of previously undecided voters and 2 % percent of Obama backers to move to Romney. Another 2 % of Obama supporters said they are now undecided because of the debate. "There's no question in my mind that debate made people stand up and pay attention, and it really wiped away any questions people had about Romney, whether they were undecided or soft for Obama," said Brad Coker of Mason-Dixon Polling and Research... "It's a very big shift since the debate, and where the shifts are taking place are very, very interesting: they are the types of shifts you see in Florida when something starts to break one way or another," said Coker, likening it to when Ronald Reagan shot past Jimmy Carter in 1980... Obama's once 11 point lead among likely independent voters had cascaded into a 13 point lead (Ed: = 24 pt. shift!) for Romney this week, 52 percent to 39 percent. The bottom line? Obama appears to be in serious trouble in America's biggest battleground state. He has two debates and 25 days to turn it around, but the poll points to a race that had been close and stable for months shifting significantly toward the Republican nominee..."</Msg><Username>spenditol98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350075239119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 16:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350076029786-57</Id><Title>I thought there was a strong buy on this today??</Title><Msg>I just bought today. Thought it would have bounced back, but i guess i have to wait for monday.</Msg><Username>nedelkay</Username><Timestamp>1350076029786</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 17:07:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350079356763-58</Id><Title>ETFC will fall under $8 next week! AH is dropping big now!!</Title><Msg>ETFC will fall under $8 next week! AH is dropping big now to $8.95. ETFC will retest $7.50 very soon!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350079356763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350081947351-59</Id><Title>Biden performance</Title><Msg>Was more like a obnoxious drunk relative at a family holiday gathering. What a class act...and this hyena is a sitting Vice President a heartbeat away from the oval office. Maybe he can explain to the 23 million Americans out of work or the families of the dead four Americans what was so funny! You Democrats sure can pick-um. Win, lose, or draw that was the worst display of buffoonery in a Vice Presidential debate ever.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350081947351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350083487969-60</Id><Topic><Title>Biden performance</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350081947351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the funny thing is Biden is a much better debater than Dumbo...AND way smarter than Dumbo..THAT IS SCAREY!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350083487969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350083595128-61</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No CLASS!! #$%$S</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350083595128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350083674081-62</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden plagerized in 1988 and had to drop his Presidential bid because of it.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350083674081</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085650119-63</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, Are you a sick idiot? Rumney did the same thing at the prez debate! Stop crying you wienie!!!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350085650119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:47:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085773142-64</Id><Topic><Title>Biden performance</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350081947351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 18:45:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden the clown-- Bozo Biden-- bears a strong resemblance in appearance to Jerry Sandusky. Furthermore, his facial expression he carried throughout most of the debate seemed eerily similar to that of Holmes the Colorado movie theatre shooter's mugshot.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350085773142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085791679-65</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, The rubber room has been reserved for you! Have fun!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350085791679</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085792429-66</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, The rubber room has been reserved for you! Have fun!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350085792429</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085792456-67</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike, The rubber room has been reserved for you! Have fun!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350085792456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350085958301-68</Id><Topic><Title>Biden enters Mental Institution!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350038801696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 06:46:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bike4q, VP Joe Biden won the debate - get over it momy's boy.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1350085958301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350091703367-69</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Paul Ryan was one of those who cut funding for embassy security around the world.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350091703367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 21:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350094674371-70</Id><Title>Rep. Jesse Jackson Jr. under federal investigation over alleged financial improprieties</Title><Msg>hmmmmmm</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350094674371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350095027556-71</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And now the sob's are so concerned about security of our embassies.. Hypocrites all! You can't trust Romney and his gang of liars.. Let's hope America doesn't get hoodwinked as in 2004..</Msg><Username>greekislandtaverna</Username><Timestamp>1350095027556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:23:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350095083414-72</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the buck stops at the pubs... Sad!</Msg><Username>ohioracketeer</Username><Timestamp>1350095083414</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350095531138-73</Id><Title>Walker appointee found guilty</Title><Msg>Ex-Walker appointee convicted of stealing $51,000 from veterans Kevin Kavanaugh skimmed Purple Heart funds, jury finds By Steve Schultze of the Journal Sentinel Oct. 12, 2012 5:10 p.m. A Milwaukee County jury Friday convicted Kevin Kavanaugh of stealing more than $51,000 from money donated to help veterans and their families. Prosecutors said the 62-year-old Kavanaugh had skimmed the money from bank deposits and phony withdrawals from accounts for the local chapter of the Military Order of the Purple Heart, a veterans service organization. Kavanaugh, of Cudahy, was treasurer of the group. He didn't testify at the trial and said nothing following the verdict. Sentencing on the felony conviction was sent for Dec. 7. Kavanaugh, who had no prior criminal record, faces up to 10 years in prison and a $25,000 fine. Kavanaugh's attorney Christopher Hartley said circumstantial evidence in the form of many checks Kavanaugh cashed from Purple Heart funds were difficult to overcome with jurors. No direct evidence was presented showing that Kavanaugh spent the missing money or salted it away for himself, Hartley said. He argued to jurors that Kavanaugh regularly gave money - a few hundred dollars at a time - to needy veterans. The biggest source of money Kavanaugh was accused of tapping was donations made for Operation Freedom, an annual picnic and veterans event at the zoo that Gov. Scott Walker hosted while he was Milwaukee County executive. In 2006, Walker's county office arranged to have the Operation Freedom donations and expenses run through the Purple Heart chapter after being advised by county lawyers to have a separate nonprofit handle the books rather than continue to have Walker aides do so. Kavanaugh, who also worked as a counselor at the Zablocki Veterans Administration Medical Center, had been named by Walker to the county Veterans Service Commission. Prosecutors said Kavanaugh went to elaborate lengths to conceal his transactions and had witnesses testify they never received money purportedly donated to them, as listed in his Purple Heart records. "Why did he falsify the check stubs" to say money was going to children of veterans killed in the Iraq and Afghanistan wars, asked Assistant District Attorney Hanna Kolberg in her closing statement to jurors. "Why did he refuse to open his books when asked" by a Purple Heart auditor, Walker's chief of staff at the county and others, she said. "Why did he purposely commingle" the Purple Heart money with his money? "Because the defendant is a thief," Kolberg told jurors. Hartley said Kavanaugh was just a terrible bookkeeper. "Where is the proof?" he said. Kavanaugh "is not on trial for being a very bad bookkeeper." It was the second conviction from cases that grew from that probe this week. Former Walker aide Kelly Rindfleisch pleaded guilty Thursday to felony misconduct in office for doing campaign work while at her taxpayer-paid county job as Walker's deputy chief of staff.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1350095531138</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350095729082-74</Id><Title>Did Lyin' Ryan plagiarize dead rocker?</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's running partner Paul Ryan accused of stealing 'Bean' story from Kurt Cobain Source: NME Mitt Romney's running partner in the US election, Paul Ryan, has been accused of stealing an anecdote from the late Nirvana frontman, Kurt Cobain. In last night's Vice Presidential debate (October 11), Republican congressman Ryan told a story about how his daughter Liza got the nickname Bean, when answering a question about abortion. Gawker reports that it was quickly pointed out by Twitter users that Ryan's story was similar to Cobain's, who said he gave his daughter, Frances Bean Cobain, her unique middle name because she looked like a kidney bean on his wife Courtney Love's ultrasound scan. Ryan has stated that he is a big fan of Nirvana, as well as Rage Against The Machine. In the debate, Ryan said: "You know, I think about ten and a half years ago, my wife Janna and I went to Mercy hospital in Janesville where I was born for our seven week ultrasound for our first born child. And we saw that heartbeat. Our little baby was in the shape of a bean, and to this day we have nicknamed our first born, Liza, 'Bean'."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1350095729082</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350096124248-75</Id><Title>Dipshidiot accused of plagiarism</Title><Msg>"Peter Berg, the creator of the "Friday Night Lights" television series and movie, has sent Mitt Romney a scathing letter demanding the Republican candidate cease use of the show's "Clear Eyes, Full Hearts, Can't Lose" slogan. In the letter, which was obtained exclusively by The Hollywood Reporter, Berg writes that "the only relevant comparison I see between your campaign and 'Friday Night Lights' is in the character of Buddy Garrity -- who turned his back on American car manufacturers selling imported cars from Japan." In noting that the "politics and campaign" of the Romney ticket "are clearly not aligned with the themes we portrayed in our series," Berg echoed a similar rebuke aimed at Paul Ryan by Tom Morello of Rage Against the Machine. In August, Morello wrote an op-ed denouncing Ryan, who he cited as "the embodiment of the machine our music rages against." Mitt Romney has been using the "Friday Night Lights" slogan in speeches. Ann Romney has also made use of the inspirational motto, which figures prominently in the series. The Huffington Post has reached out to Romney's campaign and will update this post if we receive comment."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1350096124248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350098425343-76</Id><Title>Looks Like Biden Won !!!!!</Title><Msg>You can see by the peter meter, here with all the Log Cabin Queeens whining about Joe.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350098425343</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350099401813-77</Id><Title>Lindsey Lohan Endorses Romney</Title><Msg>Lindsay Lohan has joined the likes of Stacey Dash and Hulk Hogan by telling the press she's voting for Mitt Romney................... I know. It reads like a joke. But it's true. This is the republican base.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350099401813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350099604931-78</Id><Topic><Title>Lindsey Lohan Endorses Romney</Title><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350099401813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:36:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Limbots and Hannities are defending the felon and parole violator, with 16 identities, who was jailed for fraud ............. These are today's republicans</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1350099604931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>