<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348318328337-1</Id><Title>Another Round of Golf For Our Lazy President</Title><Msg>He never worked a day in his life, but he loves him some golf.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1348318328337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348318589939-2</Id><Title>Romulus and Ryannus: just say what you mean</Title><Msg>in private you denouce social security and medicare as "collectivist" &amp; "socialist"...... but in public you say you want to save these "important" programs....... that you say in private are part of the moocher entitlement system of those it's not your job to represent..... so, just say it you want to kill social security and medicare right? why do you have to be such weasels?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348318589939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 08:56:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348325511216-3</Id><Title>Scott Walker trashes Dipshidiot</Title><Msg>Wisconsin Gov. Scott Walker, one of the Republican Party's rising stars, has repeatedly criticized Mitt Romney for being too cautious. He hoped that would change when the GOP presidential nominee chose a Wisconsin boy, Rep. Paul Ryan, as his running mate. But in an interview with conservative radio host Charlie Sykes on Friday, Walker said he is still disappointed. "They not only need to use [Ryan] out on the trail more effectively; they need to have more of him rub off on Mitt, because I think Mitt thinks that way but he's gotta be able to articulate that," said Walker. More from the interview: I was enthused when Mitt Romney picked Paul Ryan because I thought that was a signal that this guy [Romney] was getting serious, he's getting bold. It's not even necessarily even a frustration over the way Paul Ryan's been used, but rather in the larger context, I just haven't seen that kind of passion that I know Paul has transferred over to our nominee. I think it's a little bit of some pushback from the folks in the national campaign. But I think for him to win, he's got to [do] that. The Sunday after Paul Ryan was picked ... I could sense the enthusiasm, the excitement, the adrenaline that Mitt Romney had -- not just Paul Ryan, [but what] he had about this ticket and about being bold and exciting. I haven't seen that as much lately. I think they need to get back to that if they're going to win that election. People want bold leadership. Listen: Also on Friday, in an interview with the Dallas Morning News, Walker said Romney needs to be more forceful in talking about the economy. "In the end, at least in my state, what most voters need to know, more than anything else, is what are you going to do to fix things," Walker said. "Gov. Romney needs to do more to articulate and address those issues. He needs to be bold and specific on the budget debate."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348325511216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 10:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348328889565-4</Id><Title>Lyin' Ryan nabbed again</Title><Msg>Sat Sep 22, 2012 at 01:52 AM PDT Ryan's latest whopper: Oops, I 'overlooked' 20% of my income by kenm From the NYT article on Romney's newest tax info release: In an amended return also released Friday, Representative Paul D. Ryan, Mr. Romney’s running mate, disclosed that he and his wife had initially failed to report $61,122 in income from 2011. He said the failure was inadvertent. The change raised their total income to $323,416 and increased their taxes by $19,917 to $64,674, or 20 percent of adjusted gross income. They owed a penalty of $59 for the original underpayment. The Ryans explained that they had overlooked their income from the Prudence Little Living Trust. Mrs. Little, who died in 2010, was Mrs. Ryan’s mother. Yup. I overlooked that $60K, almost 20% of my income. $60K here, $60K there, how am I supposed to keep track of it? Who can remember every penny? Besides it came from some obscure source I'd never remember ... what was it again? ... oh yeah, your Mom's trust. Or maybe, just maybe, what I overlooked was the fact that I would be the vice-presidential candidate and wouldn't be able to count on the trust income going unnoticed and unreported. Sorry, no time for questions, got to run another sub-3-hour marathon. (As Paul Krugman has always called him: the flim-flam man.)</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348328889565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348335910070-5</Id><Topic><Title>Can't you liberal fks ever say what you're tryin to say</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348270687655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm trying to say, that you "returnusmaximusignoramus" are NUTS!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348335910070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348335910221-6</Id><Topic><Title>Can't you liberal fks ever say what you're tryin to say</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348270687655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm trying to say, that you "returnusmaximusignoramus" are NUTS!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348335910221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 13:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348340743951-7</Id><Title>Brandish_now returns!</Title><Msg>I have returned. Just as the Great Douglas MacArthur said and did. I have Returned with an entirely new line-up and a pocket full of tricks.</Msg><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348340743951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348341445138-8</Id><Title>Bronzed Dipshidiot unraveling</Title><Msg>Things are unraveling at the Romney campaign. Univision says that during his townhall with them, not only did the Romney campaign packed the hall with non-students because they couldn’t find enough supporters on campus, but when the anchor gave an introduction to Mitt that he didn’t like, he refused to go on until they re-taped it. A Republican present called it a “temper tantrum”. Buzzfeed reports: That wouldn’t be the last demand from the campaign: Romney himself almost pulled the plug on the whole thing minutes before the broadcast, Salinas said. While introducing Romney at the top of the broadcast, Salinas’s co-anchor, Jorge Ramos, noted that the Republican candidate had agreed to give the network 35 minutes, and that Obama had agreed to a full hour the next night. Ramos then invited the audience to welcome Romney to the stage — but the candidate didn’t materialize. “It was a very awkward moment, believe me,” Salinas said. Apparently, Romney took issue with the anchors beginning the broadcast that way, said Salinas, and he refused to go on stage until they re-taped the introduction. (One Republican present at the taping said Romney “threw a tantrum.”) Making last minute “demands” that would ensure his success, indeed threatening to “reschedule” if he wasn’t allowed an exemption to the student only rule and then packing the forum with rowdy, bused-in supporters who ignored the rules not to applaud, the Romney campaign later gloated that the Hispanic forum was more “excited” for Mitt than for Obama, whose also partisan crowd did not ignore the rules. The image of “excitement” was apparently nothing but a carefully constructed mirage, propped up backstage manipulations and string pulling. The Univision host seemed put out by the disrespect shown by the bused-in Romney crowd, who booed questions while cheering the candidate as if the forum were a rally. All the worlds a stage. This behavior is reminiscent of Mitt Romney’s temper tantrum as Governor after his party lost the midterms. He reportedly was hardly ever seen after that, spending 212 days out of the state campaigning for the presidency in his last year on office. In 2006, “his disapproval ratings hit a new low with 65 percent of residents disapproving of his job performance, as residents grumbled that he was never around.” Mitt Romney’s Republican opponents during the primaries also observed this sort of behavior, saying he was cold and aloof, and came after them with unnecessarily negative ads. Mitt has been telling reporters that he is not his campaign and therefor his comments about the 47 percent of Americans can’t be held against him. Meanwhile, his wife Ann (his “secret weapon”) canceled her interviews with reporters after her “stop it” debacle. If Mitt is out of his campaign as a person and Ann is being hidden in a time out until she can stop ordering Republicans around, you have to wonder just who will carry the mantle for the tax the poor ruse. Paul Ryan? The architect of turn Medicare into a voucher program and kill Social Security Paul Ryan, who was booed even though he brought his mother with him to the AARP townhall? “Look at those clouds. It’s beautiful.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348341445138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348341815259-9</Id><Title>Topic #1: Why is it taking this company so long to find a new CEO?</Title><Msg>With all the recently laid off blood on wall street, plus all the freindly suggestions from Citadel and a number of other institutions that hold this company, one would think that finding a candidate would be sort of easy. Taint so. Freebird must have left the coop in one hell of a hurry. The Jamokes on the board never had anyone lined up ahead of time. Just VAMOOOSE with Steve. Must have been a heck of a lastminute dust-up between Steve and the board. Hmmmmm Makes one wonder, doesn't it? The board of directors took special effort to mention that steve wasn't being a strong advocate for selling the company. It was probably sort of like putting a corpse in a car to be sold on a dealer lot. So, with the recent DART dearth at AMTD and SCHW and maybe even Scottrade, one would think that the need for scale just gunned up the compunction to try to snatch an asset. Maybe steve was a strong advocate for a sale and the board was saying NO? Someone has to see the handwriting on the wall - the economics are pushing consolidation. There a re banks out there that would buy etfc for fee income. Will we soon find out? The call date appraoches on the springers and my guess tends tothink that a buyout will take place almost simaultaneously with the call of the 12 1/2% notes. These Jacks can't keep this up. What, Four CEOs in four years. First it was Dandy Don wasn't it? I think he was the guy that #$%$ the bed on TV - or maybe i t was Stevie. Then the economy tanks and DARTS crap out, and NIM starts to implode. What more do they need for a signal to sell? Do they want a ferry to come along and lop off their DIKKS?</Msg><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348341815259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348345253198-10</Id><Topic><Title>I'd be embarassed to be a Pub</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348262227173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:17:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**I want to see others do well** That is a contradition in terms. By ensconcing this socialist in the Whitehouse for four more years the only folks who will do well is the 47%. Of cource unless in your in one of the Presidents favored disciplines like alternative energy, or healthcare. BTW, just curious, what line of work is doing so well in this economy?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348345253198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348345687739-11</Id><Topic><Title>Can't you liberal fks ever say what you're tryin to say</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348270687655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**This proves that you have all of your own alias's on ignore, doofus** Thanks for proving my point.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348345687739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:28:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348346039967-12</Id><Topic><Title>Topic #1: Why is it taking this company so long to find a new CEO?</Title><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348341815259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe no one wants to become a CEO of a business that won't exsist as a seperate company in six months.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348346039967</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348346945707-13</Id><Title>Mitten's windowdressed tax return is a joke</Title><Msg>"Mitt Romney says that tax rates are too high—so high that he wants to cut them. So why did he deliberately avoid deducting charitable contributions in his 2011 tax return in order to pay a higher effective tax rate?" not long ago he said anyone who paid more than they were required should be disqualified from running for prez, but that is what he did....... and he did it because recently he said he never paid less than 14% but his 2011 return would have had a tax of 13%..... so he didn't write off all of his deductions so that his rate was 14%......jeez.....what a phony and a putz romney is...... plus who cares about his returns from AFTER he knew he was running.... he still has to hide the ones from before he could windowdress them.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348346945707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348352252690-14</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's windowdressed tax return is a joke</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348346945707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are 47%er, who doesn't pay any income taxes. Yet, quick to whine about other people not paying enough. Mitt paid enough taxes to pay for entitlements of thousands of leeches like you. Yet, you scream it isn’t enough. Creep, it must be very frustrating for you to watch your neighbor’s pocket all you life instead of making your own money. PUBLIC DISCLOSURE: “The Romneys have provided extensive information about their personal finances, including over 1,200 pages of federal tax returns that are now public on this website. Also posted is a letter from the Romneys' tax preparer, PricewaterhouseCoopers, LLP, which gives an overview of the Romneys' tax returns covering an additional 20 years, from 1990-2009. Governor Romney's tax returns show: First, as a successful businessman, Governor Romney has not only added value to our economy through his investment and business activity, but he has paid millions in taxes every year to the U.S. government. Second, the Romneys take to heart "to whom much is given, of him shall much be required." Accordingly, they have been generous in their charitable giving, donating over $7 million between 2010-2011 – donating more to charity than they paid in federal income taxes. Third, Mitt Romney has scrupulously complied with the U.S. tax code, and his income is reported and taxed at the applicable rates, and he has paid 100 percent of what he has owed. In addition, Gov. Romney has released nine financial disclosures since 2002, which are also posted on this site. There are 3 federal Public Financial Disclosures (from 2007, 2011, and 2012), and 6 Massachusetts Statements of Financial Interests (from 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, and 2007). With a decade's worth of financial disclosure documents and the Romneys' recent tax returns, the American people have extensive information about their personal finances, above and beyond what is required by the law.”</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348352252690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 18:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348356814176-15</Id><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Msg>The idiot got caught lying again.</Msg><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348364736189-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was Obama lying about? I think you are the idiot!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348364736189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348365427647-17</Id><Topic><Title>Waasssssup you little liberal puntas</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348268225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maximusignoramusreturnus, It won't be long now and you'll be crying a river over Mitten's lost presidential raise. In fact you will diappear just like bigmouth Rowdy.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1348365427647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348365428329-18</Id><Topic><Title>Waasssssup you little liberal puntas</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348268225316</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maximusignoramusreturnus, It won't be long now and you'll be crying a river over Mitten's lost presidential raise. In fact you will diappear just like bigmouth Rowdy.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1348365428329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 21:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348367012134-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brak has an attorney general who is a criminal, seems Brak didn't want to be left out.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348367012134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 22:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348367531445-20</Id><Title>Admin puts the UP in Cover-up</Title><Msg>20 September 2012Libyan Consulate Protected by British Firm Not Among the 8 Approved State Dept Firms A badly wounded 27-year-old Libyan man says he was hired by a British group to guard the exterior of the Libyan consulate on the night Ambassador Christopher Stevens and three other Americans were murdered. He says there were a total of 8 guards. There were no protests – “there wasn’t a single ant outside.” “The attack “was immediate and bold…” The State Department sent Victoria Nuland to a microphone to say “at no time did we contract with a private security firm in Libya.” Contrary to Friday’s claim by State Department spokeswoman Victoria Nuland that “at no time did we contract with a private security firm in Libya,” the department inked a contract for “security guards and patrol services” on May 3 for $387,413.68. An extension option brought the tab for protecting the consulate to $783,000. The contract lists only “foreign security awardees” as its recipient. The State Department frequently hires security companies to protect diplomats in conflict zones. It usually is done through what’s known as the Worldwide Protective Services contract, in which a handful of approved firms compete to safeguard specific diplomatic installations. In 2010, State selected eight firms for the most recent contract. Blue Mountain wasn’t among them, and the State Department did not explain why the Benghazi consulate contract did not go to one of those eight firms. Source: The Danger Room Maybe a “no bullets” policy was acceptable only to Blue Mountain? The guard said he had been hired by a British company seven months ago to protect the compound, and that the first explosion knocked him to the ground, leaving him unable to fire his weapon. Four other contracted guards, and three members of Libya’s 17th of February Brigade, a group that was formed at the start of the uprising that ousted Libya’s former military dictator, Col. Muammar Gaddafi, and integrated into the Libyan security forces, made up the security force protecting the outer perimeter of the consulate grounds; along with the eyewitness. According to this witness, that meant that the total security team guarding the perimeter of the compound were eight guards. After the men stormed the main gate, the men rushed into one of the buildings within the compound, and there was no resistance from inside the building. Source: The Eaminer Breitbart reported that the British company, Blue Mountain Group, was hired because it agreed to Hillary Clinton’s “no bullets” Rules of Engagement policy. Breitbart News has filed a Freedom of Information Act request for a copy of the Rules of Engagement (ROE). This guard, however, indicates that he could have fired his weapon but was knocked to the ground. Note that according to the him, no gunfire appears to come from inside the Consulate in self-defense. The Examiner story repeats that former SEALs Doherty and Woods were there that night as security, but NBC and ABC say they were in Libyan to track down and destroy “dangerous weapons in the area.” ABC claims that Doherty personally gave that information to its reporter.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348367531445</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 22:32:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348370168222-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Contrary to Friday’s claim by State Department spokeswoman Victoria Nuland that “at no time did we contract with a private security firm in Libya,” the department inked a contract for “security guards and patrol services” on May 3 for $387,413.68. An extension option brought the tab for protecting the consulate to $783,000. The contract lists only “foreign security awardees” as its recipient." - Security was never provided; - Spokeswomen lies that contract ever existed; Who could even think about any precautinary measures on anniversary of 9/11 in islamic country? The attack was well organized. Perpetrator is released Guantanamo detainee. The President still blames the MOVIE. Despite all evidence. The media, of course, whiping his butt. Can't wait till November to cast my vote against this insanity.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348370168222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348370595333-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you Democrats all that lazy? Get off NBC channel just for couple of minutes.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348370595333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>