<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348553290679-1</Id><Topic><Title>A major pullback is due and coming soon as Q3 eps disappoints investors!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348515141494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:32:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the last 24 hours, the Reuters Research Mean Recommendation Changed from 2.73 to 2.80.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553290679</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348553377188-2</Id><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Msg>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348578799934-3</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney a bush rerun..... bushalloveragain....</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348535975765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt: trust me!!! i have fixed medicare and you get a taxcut!!!! medicare stays just the same as it is out to the 2040s for most of the boomers, no change at all!! details later!!!</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348578799934</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348578886795-4</Id><Title>Unemployment numbers HIGH ?</Title><Msg>and you thought that Prezidunce Obomba Husseini will reduce the unemployment numbers, thereby destrying his voter base and his main constituency ? LMAO ! Good luck and remember, vote Obomba ! Allahu akbar.</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348578886795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348578971605-5</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>."It makes sense for the 99 percent of Americans to find new ways to pay their debt to the 1 percent who serve in uniform"......... does it not? (not to the gop)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348578971605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348581040758-6</Id><Title>Weeee, Over the Financial Cliff...</Title><Msg>Lets just all hold hands and do it. There aint no other way. Dems get what they want. Pubs don't have to answer to Norquist and his henchmen and the deficit gets cut in half. Reduce a few more expenses, sell a few federal treasures then suffer the pain for a while. Eventually we will all be better off. Plus, gonna be a lot of good bargains in the equities dept in the meantime. Just don't cut food stamps. Everybodys gotta eat. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348581040758</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348581507411-7</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't a jobs bill that created permanent jobs. Give us something that isn't a one year gig that provides jobs that people can earn a living at. One years funding for a program that is in effect another exercise in transfer payments just isn't going to do it. Permanent private sector jobs are what is needed, not further expansion of government transfer payments. Create wealth, not just more spending. If it "It makes sense for the 99 percent of Americans to find new ways to pay their debt to the 1 percent who serve in uniform" then get the government to fix the VA Hell Care system. I'm a 100%+ service connected disabled vet and I can't even see a doctor with any kind of reliability, much less any other services, because the VA is too busy being used to prop up social services like Medicare and Medicaid.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348581507411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 09:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348583037853-8</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fubar - I'm not sure there is enough lipstick that will make this piggy look good. I mean - your attempt at explaining it is very cure - full of crap, but cute.... - but quite frankly if I was you - I would be embarrassed to have to even look for twists and turns to defend that pile of turd..... I think that action, combined with the Romney 47% comment (which includes a LARGE portion of the military and veterans) may finally allow our military men and women to see the truth - GOP likes military NOT for the soldiers, but for the weapons program that make sooooo many rich people much much richer.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348583037853</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348583109316-9</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it was most definately a bill that would have led to thousands of permanent jobs. fyi "Republican Senators Mike Johanns from Nebraska, Richard Burr from North Carolina, Pat Toomey from Pennsylvania, and John Boozman from Arkansas actually co-wrote this piece of legislation to help our veterans only to turn around and vote to kill it. Just following orders, I suppose, and doing what is required…putting the Republican Party first."</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348583109316</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 10:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348587439710-10</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you READ the bill? If the government wants to use that money to boost employment then just contract out the infrastructure jobs to regular construction companies, who'll then have to hire new workers, a large number of whom you'll find are veterans. That alone will have an effect. Instead the bill was going to restrict bidders to veteran owned (often a scam with the veteran owning the business only on paper) companies, or companies that employ large numbers of veterans in proportion to non-veterans; also including reporting and verification requirements, etc etc etc . . . . The costs of administering the program reduce the effectiveness of the government dollars spent on any given project by almost 50%. On the other hand reducing the VA's coverage to Priority 4 or less and eliminating the areas of coverage that are determined by income (making them not a veterans program but a wealth transfer program) rather than service status. That alone will undo most of the damage President Clinton did when he briefly opened up the VA system to everyone regardless of length or service or discharge status, and tripled the case load in less than 2 years. AFTER promising there would be a concomitant bill to transfer the balancing funds from Medicare, which of course never happened, since any bill touching Medicare funding wasn't EVER going to get any political support, something of which he was well aware when he gave the VA the order to start taking people based on income. Democratic Presidents tend to use their authority as Federal Executives to abuse agency law for the purpose of pursuing political agendas. Then again, Republicans aren't entirely immune from this either, they just usually wait and get Congress to do as they wish instead of signing an executive fiat that has a HUGE impact on an agencies ability to do its job. It would be like a Republican President signing an order requiring HUD housing to be changed from rental assistance and public housing to work houses and barracks.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348587439710</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348587751841-11</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess you missed that gop senators coauthored the bill and a few voted for it , and of course the veterans thought it was a good idea, but you and the gop first crowd only think about the 1%........... typical of your type , you are all for TRILLIONS UNFUNDED to send the troops to war but when it comes to $5 billion over 5 years for a vets jobs bill that is FUNDED, you screww the vets to kiss gop party line rear end.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348587751841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348588329879-12</Id><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Msg>elect Mitt and medicare goes from near broke to GOOD to GO , AS IS, NO CHANGE, for most of the boomers who will be on it out into the 2040s......... and we all get tax cuts ! and defense spending will be increased! and the deficit will be reduced! don't ask how all THAT works, you just have to "trust Mitt".</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348589032517-13</Id><Title>Obama’s policies are actually bad for the underdogs and minorities.</Title><Msg>" The notion that big government helps the poor is a false one. Some government programs may help some poor people in the moment, but the long-term effect of such programs is well proven to be disastrous. Look at Detroit, New Orleans, and Chicago — all Democrat strongholds since forever. Why do you think blacks are moving out of the northern cities and back to the south ? " - Andrew Klavan</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348589032517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348589136931-14</Id><Title>NetSol Technologies, Inc. (NTWK) Don' t miss it</Title><Msg>read up on it</Msg><Username>god_is_great_2013</Username><Timestamp>1348589136931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348592578730-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama’s policies are actually bad for the underdogs and minorities.</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348589032517</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 12:03:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow - you truly went after a powerhouse quote !!! How long did it take you to find it??? ----------------- From Wikipedia: "Andrew Klavan, (born 1954), known also by his pen name Keith Peterson, is an American writer of mystery novels, psychological thrillers, and screenplays" ----------------- And where exactly is that quote from? one of his books ? where - let's say - an imaginary self-absorbed GOP psychopath is trying to convince his soul that Jesus also hated compassion, charity and kind hearth?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348592578730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348592902238-16</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As I said before - shame on you Fubar for even attempting to defend it.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348592902238</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348593132107-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't miss it at all, as I said, some bills come with political baggage, and voting to reduce medicare funding is, as I said, one of these. Another is failing to vote FOR a veterans appropriations bill no matter HOW inefficient it might be. Thanks, as much as that program might have helped me as the new straw owner of a number of local construction companies, I would rather the government spent the money more efficiently all around rather than inefficiently to my benefit. There are already plenty of other veterans preferences in government contracts. As well as tax breaks for businesses hiring recently discharged veterans, the modern educational assistance program is MUCH more generous than when I was active duty, and now they actually recognize PTSD rather than writing it off as a failure to adjust to civilian life . . . so we've got a few advantages already. An unemployed veterans is either, like me, too disabled to be employed in anything but a high executive position where mostly what he does is think, scheme, and plot; or he simply doesn't want to work, or he is so messed up no employers will have him. Now, if he's so messed up others won't have him but shows an exemplary service record followed by, in particular, multiple traumatic combat experiences, or simply one horrifying one, followed by a period of dysfunction in military life, that's a clear cut case for PTSD that if documented would result in 100% disability due to being unemployable, and that's on top of any other PTSD related disability levels (disability levels are semi logarithmically calculated using a table and rounding system rather than an equation most people wouldn't understand, me probably included). That means a minimum of around $2500 a month tax free. Don't think that if we get screwed up, mentally or physically, the government fails to see to our economic needs. Writing a check is, after all, fairly easy. Where the VA falls short is in the quality and availability of health services, and that's LARGELY because almost two thirds of the health budget is wasted on veterans who before Clinton wouldn't have even been eligible for VA care in most circumstances, as well as non-veterans who have become covered under some of the lower categories (5-8) rather than the higher ones (1-4) which were, when I entered the VA system, the ONLY categories of veterans the VA would treat. Clinton signed his order (since rescinded but veterans already admitted to the program were allowed to continue on it) because he felt the declining World War II population would ease the demand on resources, and to an extent he was right. However that overcapacity was designed into the system as a matter of prior policy in case we become involved in another war (wars often happen unexpectedly, certainly without enough warning to build a network of hospital and rehab facilities it will require), which we did . . . and now that used up overcapacity has a demand on it that requires a GREAT expansion of the VA healthcare system. If you want to stimulate the economy via government spending, do that, and they WILL hire veterans, most VA regional centers far prefer them to civilians. In addition there would be construction of new facilities, new PERMANENT employees in the VA. And; Bonus, a need currently unaddressed will be met, without having to kick the category 1-8 servicemen and women out of the system.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348593132107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348593274331-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes - trust Mitt - he has nothing to hide.......... - well..... maybe few tax shenanigans, few foreign tax-heaven accounts.... few uncool business transactions..... a couple of misstated fillings..... his family history..... his magic underwear..... but other than that - honestly - you can trust Mitt ................... to have several opinions (two completely opposing) on every topic ever raised....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348593274331</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:14:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348593920763-19</Id><Title>$9.30+++ is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Msg>You know how much ETFC is worth!! NO GUTS NO GLORY!!</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1348593920763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348594158270-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney a bush rerun..... bushalloveragain....</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348535975765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:19:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Facts?? Details??? That's for those silly Liberals....... we here in the GOP run faith based economy.... :)</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348594158270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:29:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348594488184-21</Id><Title>ETFC is falling and falling!! 1-year target price dropped as well...</Title><Msg>We will soon see $8..... maybe $7.50......</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348594488184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348598565038-22</Id><Topic><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like what I said.... I am glad that I sold out at the last peak!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348598565038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:42:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348598874754-23</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is falling and falling!! 1-year target price dropped as well...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348594488184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm hoping for sub $9 as an accumulation point. Sub $8 isn't likely. Current valuations of the company are WAY too low. Particularly if you're looking at the Treflis (?) reports. Their so called model changed ETFC so much during one quarter they made a significant chop in their reported price without any change in the forecast numbers from eTrade, just off their own guesses. So, I guess it comes down to whose guesses I trust, some guy who may, or may not, have a nose for businesses and how they work who has, at least, a slightly above average IQ, but who has to cover multiple companies churning out reports on each so often he doesn't have time to examine the nuances, or me, who, in reverse order spends more time researching, has been intimately involved in two start ups, created an accounting system for the largest lab at MIT, and was offered assistance-ships by my matriculating University by three different graduate programs, and has an IQ high enough that in one sample of about 1000 people only ONE out scored me on a general aptitude test, and that only by a small margin. (I had access briefly to the TO&amp;E records for my Cavalry Squadron). I've held two primary combat MOS's, one secondary combat MOS, and one secondary non-combat MOS in my short military career because I train incredibly quickly and could be slotted into ANY role within the squadron where a body was needed. As an E3 I held positions usually calling for anything from an E4, a rank I eventually attained after graduating from advanced demo school, to E6 as commander of a main battle tank. Of course I was bench warming so when a qualified NCO become available I gave my tank up, but they trusted me with it (they moved me to an E5 slot at HQ as an attaboy), which was rather flattering (I did so much better in the job than the E5 who was actually army trained for it that I won one of the first Army Achievement Awards, downgraded from an Army Commendation Medal because the Army wanted some of the new awards out there quickly so people would get used to seeing them). The point is I learn bloody fast and I've been trading since before the turn of the century. I don't see much downside in this company absent conditions that would be disastrous for the economy as a whole. The ONE thing that the market is reacting too , and eTrade and other financials along with it, is the election cycle and the possibility of the re-election of President Obama. If he stays in office then the market will tank for awhile. If he manages to improve the economy then we'll have a gradual recovery of our market cap. If he over-regulates the industry, then $8 may be overpriced, but I'm hoping he won't be that dumb. If Romney is elected we'll see an IMMEDIATE pump in the stock market, but, as he WILL fail to produce instant results, it will be a temporary boost followed by a trail-off selling period until the real recovery starts. Admittedly it may start sooner under Romney and not be in as much danger of being snuffed out by government insanities, but no matter who gets elected we will either have a recovery, or chaos, and if its chaos I have an entirely different portfolio.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348598874754</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348599163082-24</Id><Topic><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hold a core position then swing trade around the rest. My swing shares are also gone on the last pop, and I'm looking for a $8.60ish buy point. How long do you think I have to wait? My buy limit order is already in the system. (#1642 for my account, though not all those executed).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348599163082</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:52:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348599338969-25</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kinda like the Pres who swore his first act would be to close Gitmo in one year?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348599338969</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348599613948-26</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well not really. gitmo does not effect million of Americans lives and that's was a bush creation and who cares.......... are you saying who cares if Mitt can't deliver his promises on medicare and the deficit reduction.?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348599613948</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348599639895-27</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is falling and falling!! 1-year target price dropped as well...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348594488184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sheeesh.... you ARE GREAT!</Msg><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1348599639895</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348600141038-28</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is falling and falling!! 1-year target price dropped as well...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348594488184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks</Msg><Username>doubledown</Username><Timestamp>1348600141038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348600148858-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm saying that if you're going to mortar your arguments with mud it would be best to spread the mud evenly about the surface. Lets compare the economic results in MA as after 4 years of Romney as Governor versus the economic results in the US after 4 years of Obama. The ONLY significant areas of growth in our economy over the last 4 years have been generated either by Apple Computer or massive government spending. That spending cannot continue, so those jobs WILL go away, hence they really don't count. Romney OTOH attracted business to MA by lowering businesses tax burden, which in turn increased local tax bases, which increased net revenues which allowed the state to keep its head above water despite recent overspending. It's called "trickle down" economics, and it really DOES work, but only if what you're producing with your economic activity generates wealth. Government spending dissipates wealth rather than creating it, which is why Obama's world is flawed by one of his most basic assumptions, that more government is better government.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348600148858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348600478599-30</Id><Topic><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heh, that sucker may execute before the end of trading, and if not I may bump my bid up to buy at market on close if its reasonably close. Someone flushed their eTrade stock down the market. Ahhh darn, the nose dive stopped and recovered after getting to within pennies of my bid. Maybe later today? :-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348600478599</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:14:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348600905038-31</Id><Topic><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hmm think I'll bump my bid down a bit if people are being this doom and gloom.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348600905038</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348601044315-32</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are out of your frigging mind! You need mental help!!!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1348601044315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348601668315-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG, You parasite belong in a home for the underdeveloped!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348601668315</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:34:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348601985058-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This board used to be for normal posters until the crazy children went besirk.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348601985058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348602028150-35</Id><Title>Romney's campaign says he might have to "give on his tax cuts"</Title><Msg>people have figured out Mitt's tax plan doesn't don't add up: "Romney adviser: If Romney can’t broaden the base enough, he’ll give on his tax cuts" people have figured out that INCREASES to the taxes of the poor and middle class won't make up for the tax cuts to the rich......... AND pay for the increased military spending, and pay for the full as is medicare for most boomers out to 2040 or so, and reduce the deficits..... and now the Romney campaign says Romney will " give on his tax cuts"....... how about NO more tax cuts, and in fact , get rid of the bush tax cuts for the rich NOW, and when the economy is better , and it is getting better, then get rid of the bush tax cuts entirely. and then use a combination of spending cuts and tax hikes to fix medicare?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348602028150</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348602243114-36</Id><Title>Romney = Palin</Title><Msg>College cheerleader and Viet Nam chicken Romney just needs a skirt.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1348602243114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348602626050-37</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fubar's admission: "Thanks, as much as that program might have helped me as the new straw owner of a number of local construction companies, I would rather the government spent the money more efficiently all around rather than inefficiently to my benefit." clgl_fubar seems oblivious to his contribution to the problem. Are we sure someone who is essentially defrauding we taxpayers should be given credibility. In fact, aren't we honor bound to rat him out ? A citizenry that just shrugs off abuse of well intentioned Gv't programs is complicit in the fraud. And it leads to a bigger concept, Gv't can't succeed if the citizenry insists on treating it as the enemy. Look no farther than Italy,Greece, Spain and Portugal whose populations for generations treated "dodge the taxman ' as the national sport. The "piper" is asking to be paid.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1348602626050</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348602686663-38</Id><Topic><Title>Calipornia is turning in to a New Jersey ?</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348525874553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason is that these brain dead liberals are moving because they don't want to sleep where they sheet, and taking their bloated pensions with them draining the states of that income. Now they want to pollute the red states with their mental disorder. Reminds me of the Mexicans that come here and can't wait to reproduce the squalor they left in Mexico. Same story with these blue state Democrats.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348602686663</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348604130160-39</Id><Topic><Title>$8.86 is coming tomorrow... EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348553377188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 02:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wouldn't even put the buy order at this time knowing that ETFC will further sink with poor Q3 eps. I will wait till end of October before even thinking about adding or not. ETFC will may fall under $7 in any bad situation.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348604130160</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348604261063-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Cheney/Bush lied - Americans died** You forgot Haliburton. Look Hussein Obama dose not need Bush to pile up bodies in that hell hole Afghanistan which is the war of his choice...and pointing to other bad behavior does not justify his.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348604261063</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:17:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348604644613-41</Id><Title>TOPIC #2: What costs are stripped out on an AMTD transaction?</Title><Msg>Comp and benefit savings. 40MM per quarter Clearing and Svc 5MM per quarter Advertising &amp; mktg 40MM per quarter FDIC prems 14MM per quarter Prof Svcs 10MM per quarter Occ &amp; Eqmt 5MM per quarter Communications 10MM per quarter Interest corp 40MM per quarter Total savings per quarter $164MM or $656MM per year. OR $6B in market cap at a 10PE. Etrade Management holding out for the highest price. There is too much hidden value here for a transaction not to take place in this tight market.</Msg><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348604644613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348605614502-42</Id><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Msg>Just curious, been with them 3 yrs</Msg><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348606154004-43</Id><Topic><Title>Romney = Palin</Title><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1348602243114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ! So true !</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1348606154004</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:49:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348609333844-44</Id><Title>ETFC will hit $8.20~8.30 this week and $7.70~7.80 by next week!</Title><Msg>Fasten your seat belt because it will fall like a rollercoaster!!! Looking to add around at $7s again!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348609333844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348610356477-45</Id><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Msg>There was time to save Glen Doherty, Sean Smith, Tyrone Woods and Christopher Stevens. their lives. Obama did not attempt to protect them. He says there is always time until there is no time and then he still does nothing because he is waiting for the next time.</Msg><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348611795667-46</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The junior senator and community organizer wants us to believe "it was the movie stupid". Unfortunetely there will be a next time. You are witnessing Jimmy(I'll never lie to you)Carters second term.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348611795667</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:23:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348612046079-47</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt wants to lower taxes for all terrorists. He says if they have more $$$, it will trickle down.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1348612046079</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348612524877-48</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's miracle medicare remedy &amp; all purpose snake oil</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348588329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 11:52:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why don't you just spell out the details of how more tax cuts for the rich pays for increased military spending, no changes to medicare for most boomers who will be on it out to the 2040's, and of course, deficit reduction........ did you notice that the medicare is near broke , but somehow the day after Mitt is elected it is good to go as is no changes for most boomers? plus we get tax cuts, and all the rest.. I want to believe in Mitt's easy as pie , no pain fix ....... plus a big tax cut..... wow! but it doesn't add up you true believers are just stampeding off the cliff on blind faith just like you did with the previous Romney: Bush....... you fell for the wmd and the trickle down road to riches and the whole 9 yards..</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348612524877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:35:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348613246237-49</Id><Title>supply side spin</Title><Msg>(what republicans fail to mention is that tax revenues would have been higher without the tax cuts) Supply-side Spin June 11, 2007 Sen. John McCain has said President Bush's tax cuts have increased federal revenues. But revenues would have been even higher without them. Summary Republican presidential candidate Sen. John McCain has said that the major tax cuts passed in 2001 and 2003 have "increased revenues." He also said that tax cuts in general increase revenues. That’s highly misleading. In fact, the last half-dozen years have shown us that we can't have both lower taxes and fatter government coffers. The Congressional Budget Office, the Treasury Department, the Joint Committee on Taxation, the White House’s Council of Economic Advisers and a former Bush administration economist all say that tax cuts lead to revenues that are lower than they otherwise would have been – even if they spur some economic growth. And federal revenues actually declined at the beginning of this decade before rebounding. The growth in the past three years that McCain refers to brings revenues back in line with the 40-year historical average as a percentage of gross domestic product. fact check</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348613246237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 18:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348614602017-50</Id><Title>Fire some more dead weight</Title><Msg>Get rid of more of the dead weight management! I'm sure there is a couple of board members that are still in a coma! Imho</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1348614602017</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348615082305-51</Id><Title>Our Supreme Leader - Pzidunce Obongo Husseini</Title><Msg>shall not be compared to Carter. Obongo thinks BIG. Allahu akbar !</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348615082305</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348616224576-52</Id><Title>i want to believe in the miracle that more tax cuts solves all our problems</Title><Msg>who could be against an such an easy as pie cure to our economic ills.... tax cuts will cure them all! no pain, cash back! believe me i would love it if it were true. but it just does not add up to deficit reduction and how could it? people are beginning to see through the gop manure of "broadening the base" .... taxing the poor and the middleclass more to pay for more tax cuts to the rich......... which they promose will lower the deficit, pay for increased defense spending, pay for keeping medicare AS IS for most of the boomers....... but it does not add up....... and a Romney advisor said " If Romney can’t broaden the base enough, he’ll give on his tax cuts" so there you go..</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348616224576</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348617235457-53</Id><Topic><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Thanks, as much as that program might have helped me as the new straw owner of a number of local construction companies, I would rather the government spent the money more efficiently all around rather than inefficiently to my benefit." clgl_fubar admits to possible felonious behavior but all his GOP buddies look the other way. Ah, the party of law and order, personal responsibility and Jack Abramoff.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1348617235457</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348617466680-54</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama will not be pushed into a war with any country! We don't need another Iraq.! Let Mitten's friend Bibi handle it. There will be no war as long as Obama is President - 4 more years! No, there was no time to safe anyone at the consulate.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348617466680</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348617466733-55</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama will not be pushed into a war with any country! We don't need another Iraq.! Let Mitten's friend Bibi handle it. There will be no war as long as Obama is President - 4 more years! No, there was no time to safe anyone at the consulate.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348617466733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 19:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348619996548-56</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only when your momma is sitting on my lap.</Msg><Username>irush59</Username><Timestamp>1348619996548</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 20:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348626568188-57</Id><Title>The value of Unions</Title><Msg>by louis c. Hey, Wisconsin, What Do You Think of Union-Busting Now? Last edited Tue Sep 25, 2012, 03:37 PM USA/ET - Edit history (4) Scott Walker is a union buster. So are the owners in the NFL. Let's just review what this job action is about. The NFL Refs are not on strike, they are locked out. That's a big difference. They don't want anything more than they have, they just don't want to lose what they already have and have been promised through the years. The NFL makes billions and their brand hinges on the integrity of the game. The Refs safe guard that integrity, and a pension is a small item in securing that integrity. Now you can see how important experience and competence is at such a high level, pressure job. Last night's game was just an example of what football fans from all over America are going through. Sunday night, we here in Boston went through a similar evening. Our owner, Bob Kraft, is one of the biggest culprits in all of this. He's been an anti-union maggot in everything he does (he built "Patriot Place" with non-union labor). His son, Jonathan, is worse than he is. Now, I know that 35% of my union brothers and sisters voted for Scott Walker in his recall. I know that was more than the margin of victory. I also know that if Scott Walker was removed from office, it would have had no baring on last night's game. However, the dispute between the NFL owners and the NFL Refs is a perfect example of a very rich corporation that makes billions doesn't want to share a small portion of that profit with some of those that are responsible for helping to create that profit. Last night, that point was brought home, vividly, to the people of Wisconsin, and the irony should not be lost on anyone.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348626568188</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348627574869-58</Id><Title>There is no evidence that Obama stimulates economic growth</Title><Msg>The people grow tired of empty promises.</Msg><Username>redistribute_this</Username><Timestamp>1348627574869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629160685-59</Id><Topic><Title>There is no evidence that Obama stimulates economic growth</Title><Username>redistribute_this</Username><Timestamp>1348627574869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But his poll ratings are getting better and better. Corporations are reporting biggest profit margins in history. Stock market at all time high. Housing prices are recovering. And middle class taxes are the lowest in 45 years.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348629160685</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629439451-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you know, you worthless, uneducated Puke??? The war in Afghanistan was also started by the Bush administration and it was left to Obama to finish it. Republicans want to prolomg this war and generals say, this is not the time to end this war. But by 2014 Obama will have all of the troops out of Afghanistan. moonman,You have alot to learn yet! I wonder how old you are?</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348629439451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629439918-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What do you know, you worthless, uneducated Puke??? The war in Afghanistan was also started by the Bush administration and it was left to Obama to finish it. Republicans want to prolomg this war and generals say, this is not the time to end this war. But by 2014 Obama will have all of the troops out of Afghanistan. moonman,You have alot to learn yet! I wonder how old you are?</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348629439918</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629490370-62</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not at all. They just need to tell me when to buy and sell. Then again, I have American Bull for that. Darn thing works when I listen to it.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1348629490370</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629619480-63</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, I have never had any trouble with E-Trade since they took over my account when they bought Brownco, but I have had trouble a few times with Scottrade.</Msg><Username>tmcg1367</Username><Timestamp>1348629619480</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348629862351-64</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is falling and falling!! 1-year target price dropped as well...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348594488184</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 13:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All those words to say, " I have no idea what will happen in the market". Yep, real bright.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1348629862351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 23:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>