<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345435365000-1</Id><Topic><Title>OMG!!! Fox rakes Ryan tax plan</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344971005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey JB, I gotsa bone to pick with y'all. First, don't never use OM[G], since Commie Pinko's don't believe in that stuff, okay. You should consider OMC (Oh, My Commrade) instead, okay? Also, Ms Helmsly once commented: "Only da little people pay taxes." Gawd, weren't those hotels-she didn't build em- wonderful, huh? JB, are you a, you know, little person, huh? C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( JB, yer not poor, so cut da empathy gig, okay? Yer a GD wealth SOB and probably never put a buck in a homeless dude's cup or invited a stinky homeless wineo to sleep on yer deck during a zero degree snow storm. Yea, ya may have fed a stray dog-before ya called da dog catcher-but, ya never gave da dog a bone. You should be ashamed, JB. I'm leaving a loaded 45 here for ya. I trust y'all will do da right thing. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1345435365000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345435592000-2</Id><Topic><Title>5-Day Forecast on ETFC</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345406626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish to have your gift. I will quit my job instantly. :)</Msg><Username>million_shares</Username><Timestamp>1345435592000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345436347000-3</Id><Title>Republican Male Defends R.APE</Title><Msg>Now we know that right wing nutz hate women. "Rep. Todd Akin (R-Mo.) justified his extreme opposition to abortion by claiming that victims of "legitimate rape" rarely get pregnant. In an interview with KTVI-TV on Sunday, the GOP Senate nominee was asked if he supported abortion in the case of rape. "From what I understand from doctors, that's really rare," said Akin said of pregnancy caused by rape. "If it's a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down." Of course, the Log Cabin Boys here will agree with the Pub. You will see by the one stars of this message.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1345436347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345437140000-4</Id><Title>Grover Norquist Says Bush is a Liar !</Title><Msg>“When George Herbert Walker Bush ran for president, he promised the American people he wouldn’t raise their taxes,” Norquist said on ABC's 'This Week'. “He lied to them. He broke his commitment to them and they threw him out of office four years later.”............... Looks like it runs in the fambly. Junior lied us into wars. And then said America's economy is healthy.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1345437140000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345438081000-5</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney!!! (Done!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1345413053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now we know you read gay blogs. No surprise, really.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1345438081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345466991000-6</Id><Topic><Title>OMG!!! Fox rakes Ryan tax plan</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344971005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what's not to like? as part of the deficit reduction boomers like me will get a huge tax cut , plus full AS IS social security and medicare, plus increased military spending! there may be some spending cuts in the FUTURE, but you know, it for the best for those people of 2050 and they will thank us for our sacrifices now and for being responsible.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345466991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:49:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345468059000-7</Id><Title>gop congressman swam naked with jesus?</Title><Msg>Republican Congressman Scolded After Drinking and Nudity in Israel A group of House Republicans visiting Israel as part of an official Congressional delegation last summer enjoyed a late night of drinking at the Sea of Galilee that included swimming and, in the case of one member, a little skinny dipping in the place where the Bible says Jesus walked on water. ( the gop should have been ashamed of their shameless junket to israel and all the pandering and war mongering they did. Why whine about a little skinny dipping, it didn't bother the locals and after all they are not fans of the jesus stuff anyway..... you know being socialists with universal healthcare and a religion that regards jesus about the same way Thomas Jefferson did, as just another another human being like the rest of us, and sure a great moral teacher but no better than buddha or pythagagoras)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345468059000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345469794000-8</Id><Title>get rid of more dead weight</Title><Msg>get rid of all the extra people the EX-ceo hired not needed in this market!!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1345469794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345472207000-9</Id><Topic><Title>get rid of more dead weight</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1345469794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:36:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can agree with that. Although the effort ignores the reality that the business model is out-moded and ETFC is swimming upstream. No reasonable amount of expense cuts can get he earnings to where they should be. This company should be sold off before they cause another 50% decline in shareholder value. The current management is doing a dis-service to shareholders by ignoring the realities of the situation. The management and board need to work in the best interest of shareholders. The firing of the CEO was perhaps a pacifying move by the board. They may also have elected to use the CEO as a goat. Fact of the matter is, the bank has been running itself, and the brokerage has been running under the direction of Petrelli. The CEO was just filler material.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345472207000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:16:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345473422000-10</Id><Title>Management must be held accountable</Title><Msg>Shareholders lost over three billion in market value since the rejection of sale process. It is time for the directors to feel the heat for what they have done.</Msg><Username>commitee_to_elect</Username><Timestamp>1345473422000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473507000-11</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting that the VA hospitals single payer model delivers higher quality care than any other system. Completely destroys the long held assumptions that Veterans suffered from inferior care.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345473507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473717000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted LF @ 10.96</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1344534312000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 13:45:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Covered LF @ 10.88 tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1345473717000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345473996000-13</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're wrong on so many levels here, junglebob. Not the least of which is your assumption that it's interesting.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345473996000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345474016000-14</Id><Topic><Title>$3.00 dollar value, old platform,same old hype</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345122205000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-16 09:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing changed , still $3.00 to $3.50 Griffin's Empire down to the pink sheets on his bed and for Etrade</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345474016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:46:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345474286000-15</Id><Title>What is next? Who is playing games?</Title><Msg>The w-hores of the market have had their way with the etrade company. When will there be some direction here? Shorts thrive on uncertainty, the customer base is not thrilled with uncertainty, and look at the stock price.</Msg><Username>commitee_to_elect</Username><Timestamp>1345474286000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 10:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345475217000-16</Id><Title>Look@Volume20to30kshrmovement:manipulation</Title><Msg>so sad that such a small amount of trading can bump this up falsely. seems like 300k opens this thing where ever the market maker wants as he must have a ton and a half of booked shares on his side of the tally sheet. silly is nown else seems to see the silly shift, who wants to buy at the top here. taking mine off the table plain and simple. thx</Msg><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345475217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475330000-17</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2005 "Quick. When you read "veterans hospital," what comes to mind? Maybe you recall the headlines from a dozen years ago about the three decomposed bodies found near a veterans medical center in Salem, Va. Two turned out to be the remains of patients who had wandered months before. The other body had been resting in place for more than 15 years. The Veterans Health Administration (VHA) admitted that its search for the missing patients had been "cursory." Or maybe you recall images from movies like Born on the Fourth of July, in which Tom Cruise plays a wounded Vietnam vet who becomes radicalized by his shabby treatment in a crumbling, rat-infested veterans hospital in the Bronx. Sample dialogue: "This place is a fuckin' slum!" By the mid-1990s, the reputation of veterans hospitals had sunk so low that conservatives routinely used their example as a kind of reductio ad absurdum critique of any move toward "socialized medicine." Here, for instance, is Jarret B. Wollstein, a right-wing activist/author, railing against the Clinton health-care plan in 1994: "To see the future of health care in America for you and your children under Clinton's plan," Wollstein warned, "just visit any Veterans Administration hospital. You'll find filthy conditions, shortages of everything, and treatment bordering on barbarism." And so it goes today. If the debate is over health-care reform, it won't be long before some free-market conservative will jump up and say that the sorry shape of the nation's veterans hospitals just proves what happens when government gets into the health-care business. And if he's a true believer, he'll then probably go on to suggest, quoting William Safire and other free marketers, that the government should just shut down the whole miserable system and provide veterans with health-care vouchers. Yet here's a curious fact that few conservatives or liberals know. Who do you think receives higher-quality health care. Medicare patients who are free to pick their own doctors and specialists? Or aging veterans stuck in those presumably filthy VA hospitals with their antiquated equipment, uncaring administrators, and incompetent staff? An answer came in 2003, when the prestigious New England Journal of Medicine published a study that compared veterans health facilities on 11 measures of quality with fee-for-service Medicare. On all 11 measures, the quality of care in veterans facilities proved to be "significantly better."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345475330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:08:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475362000-18</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's another curious fact. The Annals of Internal Medicine recently published a study that compared veterans health facilities with commercial managed-care systems in their treatment of diabetes patients. In seven out of seven measures of quality, the VA provided better care. It gets stranger. Pushed by large employers who are eager to know what they are buying when they purchase health care for their employees, an outfit called the National Committee for Quality Assurance today ranks health-care plans on 17 different performance measures. These include how well the plans manage high blood pressure or how precisely they adhere to standard protocols of evidence-based medicine such as prescribing beta blockers for patients recovering from a heart attack. Winning NCQA's seal of approval is the gold standard in the health-care industry. And who do you suppose this year's winner is: Johns Hopkins? Mayo Clinic? Massachusetts General? Nope. In every single category, the VHA system outperforms the highest rated non-VHA hospitals. Not convinced? Consider what vets themselves think. Sure, it's not hard to find vets who complain about difficulties in establishing eligibility. Many are outraged that the Bush administration has decided to deny previously promised health-care benefits to veterans who don't have service-related illnesses or who can't meet a strict means test. Yet these grievances are about access to the system, not about the quality of care received by those who get in. Veterans groups tenaciously defend the VHA and applaud its turnaround. "The quality of care is outstanding," says Peter Gayton, deputy director for veterans affairs and rehabilitation at the American Legion. In the latest independent survey, 81 percent of VHA hospital patients express satisfaction with the care they receive, compared to 77 percent of Medicare and Medicaid patients. Outside experts agree that the VHA has become an industry leader in its safety and quality measures. Dr. Donald M. Berwick, president of the Institute for Health Care Improvement and one of the nation's top health-care quality experts, praises the VHA's information technology as "spectacular." The venerable Institute of Medicine notes that the VHA's "integrated health information system, including its framework for using performance measures to improve quality, is considered one of the best in the nation."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345475362000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345475821000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Look@Volume20to30kshrmovement:manipulation</Title><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345475217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:06:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the shares are gonna take a dump, the market maker can't prop it up for ever. very low low volume so when it dumps there goes all your top cream down the drain as if you spilled the milking can by leaving it to close to the back of the cow big milkers get milked always as do pigs getting slaughtered. old rules that are repeated over and over every year this exchange has been in business</Msg><Username>pabst_ifyouplease</Username><Timestamp>1345475821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476698000-20</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bethesda naval hospital saved cheney many times. mccain was born on US government healthcare and has been on it his entire life. He never complained about it.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345476698000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476785000-21</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess socialized health care under the supervision of GOP sucks and under the DEMS turns into the best health care program in the country..... why am I NOT surprised?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345476785000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:33:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345476823000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Male Defends R.APE</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1345436347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs are really disgusting low life morons.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1345476823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477234000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Male Defends R.APE</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1345436347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're just gullible - you got to be, to believe a word a MORMON has to say - they will SAY absolutely anything to advance their religion. And Romney was their bishop! Magic underwear, bigamy, baptizing the dead (J.ewish, M.uslim and C.hristians alike) and all the other crazy stuff that comes with that cult...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345477234000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477396000-24</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The study was conducted in 2003 after a revitalization of the VHS begun in 1994 had a chance to take full effect. Probably should do another study soon, it's been 10 years and the monumentally inept Bush administration had a chance to screw things up.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345477396000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:43:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345477742000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Male Defends R.APE</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1345436347000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 00:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Republican Taliban. They share so much with al Queda. Their hate for women, especially.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1345477742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 11:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345478727000-26</Id><Topic><Title>gop congressman swam naked with jesus?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345468059000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 09:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Both Jefferson and the Juice knew that Jesus was gay. He hung out only with men. He had no kids. He used a hooker as arm candy.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1345478727000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345479364000-27</Id><Topic><Title>OMG!!! Fox rakes Ryan tax plan</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344971005000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:03:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;s part of the deficit reduction boomers like me will get a huge tax cut&gt;&gt; The typical GOP selfish approach. the GOP "boomers" milked this country dry and think they're invincible. The tide is changing...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345479364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345479520000-28</Id><Title>boys buy them shares from the old CEO</Title><Msg>he'll love to sell them shares he bought a few weeks back for 7 dollars and change. he'll love you all the way to his bank acct. there will not be a sale this year or next silly boys</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345479520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345480227000-29</Id><Topic><Title>E*TRADE Financial Best thing Since Sliced Bread...</Title><Username>debbiehouse850</Username><Timestamp>1345466872000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you for the good,meaningful article..</Msg><Username>edwards_gerry</Username><Timestamp>1345480227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:30:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345480240000-30</Id><Topic><Title>boys buy them shares from the old CEO</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345479520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:18:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Short position getting alittle tight?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345480240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345482739000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Wimp is stonewalling</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345419392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Kristol: Mitt Romney's Low Tax Rate Is 'Kinda Weird' Source: Huffington Post Weekly Standard editor Bill Kristol said Monday that he thinks Mitt Romney should pay a higher tax rate, calling the rate he pays on his investments "weird." "I personally -- if I were designing the tax code -- would have a tax code in which Mitt Romney paid more than 13 percent, given what I know about the kind of investments he made money from," Kristol said Monday on C-Span. The prominent conservative commentator added that he thought there would be no "economic detriment" to Romney if he paid more. "I think it just seems kinda weird that he pays a lower rate than an awful lot of middle-class people," Kristol said.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345482739000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345483771000-32</Id><Title>AAPL Hits All Time High</Title><Msg>Could go to $900. The board morons here said AAPL would crash the market. Leg of bear and Project are always wrong about AAPL.</Msg><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1345483771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345483832000-33</Id><Title>Nurse26 goes short.</Title><Msg>Nurse 26 bent over the short position to far and got her t;t stuck in the wringer. This nurse 26 has got all the imagination, eh?</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345483832000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345484482000-34</Id><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Msg>ETFC will skyrocket to $9 with a major market rally soon!!! Hold or increase your shares!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485330000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Nurse26 goes short.</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345483832000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fore thought boys fore thought not foreskin blinders forethought, if it was worthy it would have been bought along time ago</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345485330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345485419000-36</Id><Title>Romneyann support abortion now</Title><Msg>rape...... at least ryan has flipped on abortion for rape victims: now "Romney and Paul Ryan support abortion access for rape victims -- something Ryan, for one, has opposed in the past. " They may have to get approval on that from an all male Issa committee of mullahs who last ruled that sperm are human beings and that women are "sluts" and "prostitutes".</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345485419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485598000-37</Id><Topic><Title>boys buy them shares from the old CEO</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345479520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:18:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>always does when a dump truck is backing up to find a dumpflag. CEO buying a mil an a hlf and then getting fired for 13 plus million. boldest blantant inside in your face Fu*k trade and management ploy i have seen since the saving's and loan scams &amp; B.K's WOW i love this exchange love it!</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345485598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345485747000-38</Id><Topic><Title>boys buy them shares from the old CEO</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345479520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:18:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you boys remember the saving's and loan schemes from the late 70's and mid 80's WOW, see what I mean, and I am not a mean spirited person by nature, just watching all the other people go by !</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345485747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345486066000-39</Id><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Msg>...can't get a woman pregnant. Pubs got some strange notions. Get the slope out of your forehead and step into the twenty-first century. Pitiful! ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345486480000-40</Id><Title>Making money is now a piece of cake using this strategy!</Title><Msg>Dont waste time on other websites that promise trading tips! Check out this system that made me thousands! HTTP://WWW.MYPENNYBIDSSTOCKSPROFITS.INFO</Msg><Username>loughnansifc30745</Username><Timestamp>1345486480000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345486682000-41</Id><Title>26,000 votes cast in presidential poll</Title><Msg>See who's ahead and by how much Hint: Map --&gt; BLOOD RED &lt;-- http://www.topix.com/issue/election-poll-june-2012</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345486682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:18:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345486742000-42</Id><Title>After further consideration, Wimp is offended</Title><Msg>Mon Aug 20, 2012 at 07:30 AM PDT Mitt Romney sleeps on it, decides to be offended by Kaili Joy Gray Mitt Romney - 08/20/2012 Hold on, hold on, just give me enough time to figure out whether I should be offended. After Mitt Romney's campaign issued the mildest statement possible to "disagree" with Republican Rep. Todd Akin's statement that women have magical rape sperm protection shields in their ladyparts, Mitt Romney slept on it and decided to clarify his disagreement further with the National Review. (Yeah, the National freakin' Review.) “Congressman’s Akin comments on rape are insulting, inexcusable, and, frankly, wrong,” Romney said. “Like millions of other Americans, we found them to be offensive.” [...] “I have an entirely different view,” Romney said. “What he said is entirely without merit and he should correct it.” Holy crap! Mitt Romney doesn't just disagree; he has an entirely different view! Those are some fightin' words. And it only took him 12 hours to think about it, watch the entire country—including his own party—condemn Akin's statement, and then decide he was offended. By the way, Mitt still hasn't explained how his view is "entirely different." Todd Akin wants to outlaw abortion in all circumstances; Mitt Romney does too, at least in his current incarnation as Republican presidential candidate in the year 2012. He has a tendency to change his mind on this issue. But at least Mitt has worked up enough anger to go from disagreement to entirely different view, with some "I'm offended" thrown in. Way to go, Mitt. Maybe a week from now you might even be able to explain why.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345486742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345486815000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Romneyann support abortion now</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345485419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ryan's flipflop may not be sincere and he could very well flipflop back. He does hold the view that any but Pope approved birthcontrol is murder.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345486815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345486937000-44</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As market turns positive this afternoon, ETFC will go into $8.70s!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345486937000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:22:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487316000-45</Id><Topic><Title>26,000 votes cast in presidential poll</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345486682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:18:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wowee berkins that map is RED</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345487316000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345487332000-46</Id><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Msg>Dear Todd Posted on August 20, 2012 by ReneeDavis I am a woman, a survivor of rape, and a registered Republican. You have issued an apology for the uneducated “off the cuff” remark you made where you stated “from what I understand from doctors, pregnancy [ as a result of rape] is really rare. If it is a legitimate rape, the female body has a ways to try shut that whole thing down.” Todd, I do not accept your apology! The problem that goes to the core of this issue is that no matter what your apology says, you and your friends have left most of your more moderate members behind and traded us in for a very extreme view. Number one, women have the right to determine what happens to their body and to not be raped, assaulted, or molested whether that is by a rapist or an elected official who thinks they have the right to dictate what she should do. You and your friends do not want government intrusion into your lives ONLY when it suits your beliefs – period! You and your like-minded friends, who do not agree with the Affordable Care Act yell from the roof tops that personal religious freedoms are being infringed upon because it requires women to have access to birth control. What I find so interesting is those same people have no problem creating legislation that does just that to the women of this country. For example, have you forgotten Todd that little piece of legislation that you and GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan co-sponsored a bill called “No Taxpayer Funding for Abortion Act,” a bill which, among other things, introduced the country to this bizarre term “forcible rape,” as if there is some other form of rape?</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345487332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345487419000-47</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345487332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:28:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The constitution says the Freedom OF religion which means that the American people are free to choose whatever religion they want to practice, no religion at all and our government cannot not dictate what religion or religious beliefs we should have. • It DOES NOT mean that elected officials get to instill their religion into our government and impose the government into the most intimate parts of a woman. • It DOES NOT mean that our federal or state government gets to FORCE women to undergo unnecessary medical procedures, by inserting probes into our vaginas against our will or by forcing us to have regular ultrasounds and then actually writing in the legislation THAT WE HAVE YOUR PERMISSION TO TURN OUR EYES AWAY WHEN YOU VIOLATE US!! • It DOES NOT mean that elected officials get to limit women’s access to birth control and legal medical procedures the U.S. Supreme Court has upheld. • It DOES NOT mean that you get to distort and flat out lie in biology, science, sex education, and history classes that are being taught to our children. If you and your pals are so concerned with jobs and the economy then how come there have been over 1100 pieces of anti-women legislation brought up across the country in 2011 and over 900 pieces so far this year and NOT ONE SINGLE TIME has a JOB bill been voted on in the U.S. House! How many times has a vote against women and our right to autonomy been voted on? Oh and by the way didn’t the U.S. House also vote 33 TIMES to repeal the Affordable Care Act? You and your friends have now attacked every single group of people in this country except the religious right. Do you seriously think that the Republicans are going to be able to win in this country when you marginalize and alienate voters who don’t think like you? Oh, wait, I apologize I forgot you’re also taking care of that as well through various “Voter ID” laws that have the sole purpose of eliminating voters who are American citizens the right to vote. So you see Todd, and let your friends Paul and Eric know too, it doesn’t matter what apology your PR person comes up with for you…the fact is when you speak “off-the-cuff”, when your words aren’t rehearsed, when you don’t have time for someone to tell you what to say – that is when the voters get to see you and the rest of your friends like you for who you truly are. When you write, sponsor, and vote on bills that are being used to attack the citizens of this country – that is when the voters get to see all of you for who you truly are. Oh one more thing Todd we have had enough and we aren’t taking it anymore. The women of this country have had ENOUGH! This country has more of us “others” and we are going to make sure that every single person regardless of their gender, race, religion, etc. gets out to vote and sends you and your pals back to where you belong – the Stone Age!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345487419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:30:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345487568000-48</Id><Title>Garbage Posts in Overdrive. Wonder why?</Title><Msg>I wonder too. Unsolicited posts on Politics.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345487568000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345488080000-49</Id><Title>Insider Buying over $1M.</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial (ETFC): Chairman Frank Petrilli and one other director purchased more than more than 126,000 shares of this financial services company last week. That was worth more than $1 million. The board of this New York-based company recently ousted the CEO. The company's market cap is about $2.4 billion and its long-term EPS growth forecast is 12.2%. Short interest is less than 2% of the float. Read more: http://www.minyanville.com/trading-and-investing/stocks/articles/AGN-AMTD-CAKE-DRI-EAT-ETFC/8/20/2012/id/43343#ixzz2474n1EEp</Msg><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345488080000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488629000-50</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"ETFC will skyrocket to $9 with a major market rally soon" The S&amp;P is sitting at 1416 and this stock is sitting at .86 cents. This stock was trading at $1.50 back when the S&amp;P was 1100. Can you explain that you market guru? Besides, there are about 80k shares just sitting on the ask at $8.65 like a sumo wrestler.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345488629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:50:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345488802000-51</Id><Topic><Title>E*TRADE Financial Best thing Since Sliced Bread...</Title><Username>debbiehouse850</Username><Timestamp>1345466872000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Continue sharing this to us please. Thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>parkmorton10</Username><Timestamp>1345488802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:53:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345488854000-52</Id><Title>This stock capitalizes on a strong Dollar &amp; weak Euro, ETFC</Title><Msg>Best to E*Trade; FLKI just reported blowout earnings: operating margins increased from 17 pct to 45 pct, with net operating revenues up 34 pct on rising product demand. It is not every day investors have the opportunity to get the best of the Old and New Worlds: capitalize on a strong U.S. Dollar by buying a Euro-based multinational company with impressive financials. Falken Industries Ltd. (FLKI) is a leading global manufacturer and commercialization of high-end specialty cleaning products for industrial, professional and consumer uses. Under its brand name Clean Plus, Falken Industries has successfully launched more than 160 professional and consumer auto care products which are sold in over a dozen international markets, including recently signed Australia and Russia. Clean Plus products are available in over 1000 petrol stations and other outlets throughout Europe. Key Investor Points Falken Industries sales volumes more than doubled over the past two years, with continued record growth. Q1 2012 revenues increased 30% over Q4 2011 along with record profits. Q2 is even more remarkable: net operating revenues even after unfavorable net currency adjustments to the strong dollar increased 34% from the year-ago quarter while net operating margins were up 17% to 45% Profits (PPS) were a solid 2 cents per share on an annualized basis. The company is experiencing impressive expansion, including recent signed agreements with distributors in Norway, Australia, and Russia. Falken Industries supplies the global markets of major petrol distributors, including Shell, BP, Esso, Q8, Statoil, Hydro-Texaco, Olis, Cepsa, and Agip. Why Now? Despite record impressive performance and profits, Falcon Industries is trading at a heavy discount: 30% of its book value. This anomaly is largely due to the current economic downturn in Europe, which has affected exchange rates between the Dollar and Despite record impressive performance and profits, Falcon Industries is trading at a heavy discount: 30% of its book value. This anomaly is largely due to the current economic downturn in Europe, which has affected exchange rates between the Dollar and the Euro. Since the company’s financial reports are primarily denominated in Euro, the monetary figures are artificially diminished as a consequence of U.S. Dollar reporting. This has resulted in exaggerated fears resulting in a heavily-discounted PPS, despite strong fundamentals. This temporary fluctuation is expected to be corrected as the currency markets stabilize. In the meantime, Falken management has responded with initiatives designed to capitalize on the weaker Euro and stronger Dollar by expanding into U.S. and Canadian markets. The trade-off is huge, offsetting by far any currency conversion loss. It is only a matter of time before the stock begins to reflect the fact that its products have up to a 50% price advantage over competitors. All this presents a unique opportunity for investors to buy at an artificially low PPS before the inevitable adjustment of the currency exchange rates reveals the true strengths of this rapidly growing company.</Msg><Username>luvr_n</Username><Timestamp>1345488854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345490894000-53</Id><Topic><Title>26,000 votes cast in presidential poll</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345486682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:18:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that site is dedicated to and used only by farmers and hillbillies.... it would show red even if there was just 2 hillbillies in a city of 6 million - no one else knows about it. Slayer is good at tracking those kind of sites. If there was a site dedicated to "man/goat friendship" we would never hear the end of it.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345490894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345491398000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Romneyann support abortion now</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345485419000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:56:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pope approved birthcontrol" Isn't that just the aspirin between the knees method? And the Pope probably thinks you would be depriving someone the cure for their headache. The popes just want to make more catholics to load up the offering plate. My kid went to a Catholic school for a while at a reduced rate. We got a notice that said if we did not contribute more to the church, we would have to pay the full tuition. The whole thing was just a tax dodge scam for the parents. We could deduct the "gift" to the church but not the tuition. I ignored the letter b/c I just didn't have the money to give. A little after that he got kicked out for being "bad". Then, few months later a jock got caught for the same thing and was allowed to stay in school. Priests must have to take the hypocratic oath before they are ordained. Much against there wishes, I did get the month-in-advance tution payment returned. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345491398000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345492326000-55</Id><Topic><Title>gop dreamland fantasia tax plan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345324972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, wait: http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2012/04/23/finance-reports-to-reveal-how-aging-workforce-straining-social-security/ http://www.ssa.gov/oact/trsum/index.html “The retirement fund is projected to run out of money in 2035 while the disability fund is projected to run dry in 2016.“ "This year's trustees report contains troubling but not unexpected projections about Social Security's finances," said Social Security Commissioner Michael J. Astrue. "It once again emphasizes that Congress needs to act to ensure the long-term solvency of this important program, and needs to act within four years to avoid automatic cuts to people receiving disability benefits." It is our retirement, doofus. For most normal people it is sacred cow. Taking money out of it without any plan to return it back is a felony risen to the government level. Although, it wasn’t the point I was making at all with previous post, but but still worth stressing out.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345492326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345492412000-56</Id><Title>What is this? No options sold?</Title><Msg>Sure? Why no sellerz?</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345492412000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345492475000-57</Id><Topic><Title>gop dreamland fantasia tax plan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345324972000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 17:22:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmmm, what presidential candidate talked about a 'lox box' on the SS funds?? Now who was that???</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1345492475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 15:54:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345492823000-58</Id><Topic><Title>E*TRADE Financial Best thing Since Sliced Bread...</Title><Username>debbiehouse850</Username><Timestamp>1345466872000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 08:47:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is by far and away the strongest stock I have ever bet against. Remarkable comeback</Msg><Username>frankl31</Username><Timestamp>1345492823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493483000-59</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Interesting that the VA hospitals single payer model delivers higher quality care than any other system. Completely destroys the long held assumptions that Veterans suffered from inferior care&gt;&gt; So I quess we on this MB can count on you heading over to your local military recruitment center and you joining up. The only thing wrong with this assumption is that this care is only afforded you if you don't get dead.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345493483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345493607000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Get the slope out of your forehead and step into the twenty-first century&gt;&gt; You need to tell that to Joe(Y'all)Biben.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345493607000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345493770000-61</Id><Title>Willard's taxes</Title><Msg>The only logical reason he's hiding them is they contain some embarrassing revelations. Probably not illegalities, his lawyers and tax accountants are too smart, but things that skirt the line close enough to disgust Joe Sixpak. Absent disclosure, speculation is fair game now for the Dems.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345493770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345493863000-62</Id><Title>$8.88, Repeat After Me!! $8.88, $8.88!!</Title><Msg>$8.88, Repeat After Me!! $8.88, $8.88!! Coming soon!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345493863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:17:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494079000-63</Id><Topic><Title>$8.88, Repeat After Me!! $8.88, $8.88!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345493863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ate a-t ate</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345494079000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494204000-64</Id><Topic><Title>For fans of socialized medicine</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345428323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is you have a handy, documentable and measurable example of single payer healthcare delivering a higher quality product than the private sector. A fact never cited by the GOP. It's something they affirm is impossible.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345494204000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494285000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey shineola. Appreciate your comments. I am wondering if you know what many abused women have in common.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345494285000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:24:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494323000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Willard's taxes</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345493770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am no Romney fan, but he has fully complied with the income tax disclosure laws. This is a diversion tactic by the Obama campaign...trying to make this election about anything and everything EXCEPT his economic record during his first term. GK Full disclosure: I am voting for Gary Johnson: end all foreign wars, balance the budget, end the fruitless war on drugs, eliminate the Patriot Act and similar restrictions on individual liberty</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1345494323000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:25:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345494576000-67</Id><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Msg>god this man has the midas touch...don't he! &lt;&lt;That's the highest price ever on this date, according to auto club AAA&gt;&gt; Summertime blues for drivers U.S. drivers paid an average of $3.72 per gallon on Monday. That's the highest price ever on this date, according to auto club AAA, a shade above the $3.717 average on Aug. 20, 2008. A year ago, the average was $3.578. More daily records are likely over the next few weeks. The national average could increase to $3.75 per gallon by Labor Day, said Tom Kloza, chief oil analyst at Oil Price Information Service. By comparison, gas prices stayed below $3.70 in late August and early September in both 2008 and 2011.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345494725000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Willard's taxes</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345493770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A major issue of this campaign is whether the rich are paying their fair share. Willard says the rich are overburdened but won't use his own taxes to demonstrate just how. It smells bad, really bad.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345494725000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345494978000-69</Id><Title>You have to pass it , so know whats in it</Title><Msg>This ought to drive down healthcare costs...pensions for as far as the eye can see. &lt;&lt;a union-driven effort to organize 21 million health care workers&gt;&gt; In a book set for publication Tuesday, a politics and government professor at The Citadel claims President Obama’s 2009 health care reform law was, in part, a union-driven effort to organize 21 million health care workers. In ”Shadowbosses: Government Unions Control America and Rob Taxpayers Blind,” Mallory Factor describes a December 9, 2008 memo from Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Healthcare president Dennis Rivera to the Obama-Biden transition team. That memo outlined a legislative proposal calling for “increasing the capacity of the health care workforce” as part of a larger health care reform initiative. The SEIU and the Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Factor writes, later coordinated with other public-sector unions to spend “literally hundreds of millions of dollars promoting Obamacare.” The Daily Caller requested comments for this article from the SEIU, AFSCME and a White House spokesman. None of them responded. A booklet published by SEIU during the 2008 election season called for “building a new American health care system,” in part by “organizing workers.” The publication argued for outcomes nearly identical to those later adopted in the Obamacare legislation.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494978000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:36:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495132000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thatsucks and so does the .716 trillion he stole from seniors to give out free to the illegals for their votes.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345495132000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345495465000-71</Id><Title>Donald knows best</Title><Msg>Another old white guy telling women what's best for them. Clueless!! -- Donald Trump says women's liking for Obama shows they 'don't get what's going on' politically [View all] Source: ANI Washington, Aug. 20 (ANI): American business mogul Donald Trump has said that President Barack Obama's high popularity among women shows that female voters 'don't get what's going on', politically. Trump also said that women liked him because they don't know him and that ignorance prevented them from seeing things the way he does. "Well, maybe they don't know him . Maybe they don't get what's going on, the New York Daily News quoted Trump, as saying. According to the report, Trump asserted that Obama is "somebody that will say some very nasty things. is a person that is not the nice person that some people think. And his popularity rating, while high, I think if people knew the facts, the rating would actually be extremely low".</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345495465000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495741000-72</Id><Topic><Title>$8.88, Repeat After Me!! $8.88, $8.88!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345493863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>choo choo.....!! choo choo.....!! 888-888-888-888-888-888-888-888-888-888-!! choo choo....!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345495741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:49:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495753000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Willard's taxes</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345493770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Taxes WASHINGTON -- Mitt Romney sought and received $787,455 in foreign tax credits from the U.S. Treasury to cover his tax payments to other nations in 2008. While there is no evidence that his actions violated the law, abuse of the foreign tax credit has been a problem for the Internal Revenue Service. The agency has prosecuted a number of international fraud cases in the last few years involving such credits. And the size of Romney's claim in 2008 raises questions about the sources of his foreign income. "This could definitely be a contributing reason for Romney's unwillingness to disclose prior years' returns," said New York University School of Law professor Daniel Shaviro, a tax expert. The U.S. government provides tax credits to Americans who also pay taxes abroad, so that foreign income is not taxed twice by different governments. While these credits do not save U.S. residents from paying taxes -- they still have to pay the foreign governments -- they do put a dent in the U.S. Treasury's collections. "In the plain-vanilla case, the taxpayer is hurting the U.S. Treasury to the benefit of the foreign treasury, but isn't benefiting himself," Shaviro said. The Huffington Post had previously reported that Romney received more than $25 million in foreign income between 2005 and 2010. At the time, he was governor of Massachusetts. His 2010 return also lists foreign tax payments that Romney made dating back to 2000. Through 2004, the payments were tiny -- for Romney -- averaging $37,000 a year. In 2005, however, his foreign tax bill shot up to $333,149 and stayed high for the next three years, prior to the Great Recession. "Romney had a significant amount of foreign income," observed Rebecca J. Wilkins, senior counsel for federal tax policy with the nonpartisan Citizens for Tax Justice. "We don't know what the source of his foreign income is." The Romney campaign declined to comment for this article, and there is no way to determine where Romney's foreign income came from without additional disclosures. HuffPost recently pointed out the circumstantial evidence showing that he may have used offshore corporations to avoid paying taxes.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345495753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345495786000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Willard's taxes</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345493770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:16:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The total $787,455 credit covers both "passive income" -- dividends and investment gains -- and "general income" -- foreign wages and business revenue. Some money from Romney's Bermuda-based corporation, Sankaty High Yield Asset Investors Ltd., could qualify as general income. While there is no evidence that Romney broke the law, American taxpayers have set up illegal sham transactions involving foreign taxes in recent years to dupe the IRS. Such transactions can involve multiple taxpayers claiming the credit for the same foreign income or one taxpayer claiming multiple tax credits for the same foreign income. Individual taxpayers have also claimed credits for foreign taxes that they never actually paid. Much of Romney's foreign banking activity is also shrouded in secrecy. He has not released a 2010 tax form that details his foreign bank account holdings. He has, however, disclosed the existence of a Swiss bank account. Such accounts are prized by global elites for Swiss banks' extreme levels of secrecy, which has allowed thousands of American taxpayers to shield offshore income from the IRS by stashing it in Swiss accounts. There is no evidence that Romney broke the law with his Swiss account. But Romney's large foreign tax credit in 2008 was unusual. Many wealthy individuals who engage in aggressive tax planning choose to park foreign income in tax-free jurisdictions. Romney and Bain Capital, for instance, made extensive use of Cayman Island accounts. The U.S. Treasury, moreover, caps the foreign tax credit at whatever the U.S. tax rate would be on the income in question. Any additional foreign taxes can be "carried forward" and receive a tax credit in future years. Because Romney exceeded the foreign tax credit limit in 2008, he received additional credits based on his 2008 income in 2009 and 2010. "What does he have that's generating all that foreign income?" Wilkins asked."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345495786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496293000-75</Id><Topic><Title>$8.88, Repeat After Me!! $8.88, $8.88!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345493863000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To da moon!!!!!!! Soon!!!!!!</Msg><Username>strnoon2ooo</Username><Timestamp>1345496293000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345496409000-76</Id><Title>GOP trainwreck looms</Title><Msg>Robert Reich 5 Reasons Why the Ryan-Romney Economic Plan Would Be A Disaster for America Posted: 08/20/2012 2:54 pm Mitt Romney hasn't provided details so we should be grateful he's selected as vice president a man with a detailed plan Romney says is "marvelous," "bold and exciting," "excellent," "much needed," and "consistent with" what he's put out. So let's look at the five basic features of this "marvelous" Ryan plan. FIRST: It would boost unemployment because it slashes public spending next year and the year after, when the economy is still likely to need a boost, not a fiscal drag. It would be the same austerity trap now throwing Europe into recession. According to the Economic Policy Institute, Ryan's plan would mean 1.3 million fewer jobs next year than otherwise, and 2.8 million fewer the year after. SECOND: Ryan would take from lower-income Americans and give to the rich -- who already have the biggest share of America's total income and wealth in almost a century. His plan would raise taxes on families earning between 30 and 40 thousand dollars by almost $500 a year, and slash programs like Medicare, food stamps, and children's health What would Ryan do with these savings? Reduce taxes on millionaires by an average of over $500,000 a year. THIRD: Ryan wants to turn Medicare into vouchers that won't keep up with the rising costs of health care -- thereby shifting the burden onto seniors. By contrast, Obama's Affordable Care Act saves money on Medicare by reducing payments to medical providers like hospitals and drug companies. FOURTH: He wants to add money to defense while cutting spending on education, infrastructure, and basic research and development. America already spends more on defense than the next five biggest military spenders put together. Our future productivity depends on the public investments Ryan wants to cut. FIFTH AND Finally, Ryan's budget doesn't even reduce the federal budget deficit -- not for decades. Remember: He's adding to military spending, giving huge additional tax cuts to the very rich, and stifling economic growth by cutting spending too early. The Center for Budget and Policy Priorities estimates Ryan's Roadmap would push public debt to over 175 percent of GDP by 2050. So there you have it. The Ryan -- Ryan-ROMNEY -- economic plan. And the five reasons why it would be a disaster for America.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345496409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496578000-77</Id><Topic><Title>GOP trainwreck looms</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345496409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It could be curtains for the fool in his home state. That's if you feel comfortable calling Illinois Brak's "home" state. http://hotair.com/archives/2012/08/20/too-good-to-check-could-obama-lose-illinois/</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345496578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345496844000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many years ago, the National Organization for Women, a liberal Democrat base group, declared all sex with/by a man as rape. "Women are oppressed by rapist men." Therefore there is no abortion distinction for rape in the Democratic platform -- any pregnancy can be aborted if the woman so chooses. He was only trying to distinguish between actual violent, non-consenting rape and what Democrats believe-sex without consequence or personal responsibility and abortions anytime at taxpayer expense. The Dems who would kill babies so they can continue their selfish ways are the real problem.</Msg><Username>gretchn5867</Username><Timestamp>1345496844000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497421000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And to think that Europeans are paying over 6$ a gallon... Count your blessings. America compared to the rest of the FREE world is doing great. Euro unemployment, above 12% some countries like Greece are at 22%. ( Yea austerity cuts, really working..NOT!) America would even be in better shape if the gop would not block every incentive Obamy wants to put in place. Thank you Obamy! Where would we be if the GOP was in charge today.</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1345497421000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:17:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497638000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the end of the day, abortion is the decision of the woman not a bunch of pompous old white guys who've never carried, birthed or raised a child as a responsible mother. GOP needs to stay out women's issues.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345497638000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345497866000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Lying for the Lord</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345262552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 00:02:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..They are JUST LIKE US.." Close but no cigar! "...the ultimate goal of the church, as stated publicly by its early leaders Joseph Smith and Brigham Young (but not mentioned so publicly by more recent Mormon leaders), is to establish the Mormon Kingdom of God in America,and to govern the world as God's appointed representatives. The church is already influential in the making of secular policy, as was proven not so long ago when the Equal Rights Amendment was defeated with decisive help from the Mormon church. To me, the possibility that the Mormon church might control America is a frightening prospect. Those are some of the more important reasons why I am still vitally interested in Mormonism and the LDS church..." http://www.infidels.org/library/modern/richard_packham/why.html http://www.infidels.org/ library/modern/richard_packham/why.html</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1345497866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345498061000-82</Id><Title>Hit The Road!</Title><Msg>Amateur hour is ending.</Msg><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1345498061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345498182000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you will find out very soon...</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1345498182000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345498287000-84</Id><Title>The Mormon Kingdom of God in America</Title><Msg>&lt;&lt;&lt;... "...the ultimate goal of the church, as stated publicly by its early leaders Joseph Smith and Brigham Young (but not mentioned so publicly by more recent Mormon leaders), is to establish the Mormon Kingdom of God in America,and to govern the world as God's appointed representatives. The church is already influential in the making of secular policy, as was proven not so long ago when the Equal Rights Amendment was defeated with decisive help from the Mormon church. To me, the possibility that the Mormon church might control America is a frightening prospect. Those are some of the more important reasons why I am still vitally interested in Mormonism and the LDS church..." ....&gt; &lt;&lt;&lt;... http://www.infidels.org/library/modern/richard_packham/why.html ....&gt; &lt;&lt;&lt;... http://www.infidels.org/ library/modern/richard_packham/why.html ....&gt;</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1345498287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345498536000-85</Id><Topic><Title>boys buy them shares from the old CEO</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345479520000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 12:18:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a bit harder to do with a publicly traded company, and eventually the shareholders, almost all institutions, will either sue you or have you killed. So what's to gain outside the normal insider sweetheart deals that pervade today's business atmosphere (almost always ended in some politicians Cayman accounts)?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345498536000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:35:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345498881000-86</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And how does that, in your mind, legitimize the act itself? He never said it did, its your subject line, so explain YOUR self. And, by the way, there is a measurable statistical difference between the two, it's just not politically correct to say that if the woman isn't turned on she doesn't lubricate and that really screws with the odds it and of itself. Further most women showing up for an SAE kit also request a morning after pill if not already on birth control. Not excusing the rather blunt and non-detailed way he said it, but lets face it, anything nay prominent Republican says for the next few months will be turned into a 5 second soundbite and repeated out of context. The people have grown SO used to it that it would take an outright blatant statement of endorsement, like, say, yours, to create a real scandal. I hate the way liberals wear ear filters that discard "inconvenient truths".</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345498881000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499178000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, votes are expensive, particularly if you're a radical Marxist thinly disguised as a liberal democrat. Afterall, if he destroys ALL the nations wealth, then EVERYONE will be equal . . . except of course our enlightened Chinese masters who will be just alittle more equal than the others.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345499178000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:46:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499353000-88</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;At the end of the day, abortion is the decision of the woman not a bunch of pompous old white guys who've never carried, birthed or raised a child as a responsible mother. GOP needs to stay out women's issues&gt;&gt; First, why limit it to just old white guys. Second, I agree it is a womans issue, and the Democrats should butt out as well with all their interfeance in birth control etc. Someone needs to tell the cropped hair NOW crowd to quit being so hysterical over the issue.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345499353000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499548000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;America would even be in better shape if the gop would not block every incentive Obamy wants to put in place&gt;&gt; I know it is summer, but you need to come in out of the heat, it's effecting your brain.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345499548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499558000-90</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sumo wrestler was killed..... and I am not a part of it.... sh$t !!!!</Msg><Username>seniortrader213</Username><Timestamp>1345499558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499641000-91</Id><Topic><Title>5-Day Forecast on ETFC</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345406626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:03:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You were 6c short today.....</Msg><Username>seniortrader213</Username><Timestamp>1345499641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499742000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm guessing you're a Mormon fanatic, waiting for the kingdom of god.. (exclusively yours) ".. It may be asked, How can we live under the dominion and laws of the United States and be subjects of another kingdom? Because the kingdom of God is higher, and its laws are so much more exalted than those of any other nation, that it is the easiest thing in life for a servant of God to keep any of their laws’..." http://mormongandhi.com/a-house-of-fasting/the-kingdom-of-god-or-nothing-mormon-civil-disobedience/ http://mormongandhi.com/ a-house-of-fasting/the-kingdom-of-god-or-nothing-mormon-civil-disobedience/ Be afraid bro! Be very afraid, of what you wish.</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1345499742000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499786000-93</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying over $1M.</Title><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345488080000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but FB insiders sell FB.</Msg><Username>seniortrader213</Username><Timestamp>1345499786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345499883000-94</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Europeans don't have to go across a continent to go see Grandma. . . Even their largest nation, Germany, is smaller than Texas. Germany, 134k sq miles. Texas 268k sq miles. In fact Texas may be larger than the primary European land mass. Alaska almost certainly is. And that's just one state that occupies about 20% of the width of the country (ballpark guess, I didn't look that one up). Most of what Europeans pay for gas is TAXES. Total European tax burden, including fuel taxes, is still less than total US tax burden, further the number of people on public assistance in Germany is a mere fraction of what it is in the United States. And don't tell me there aren't any jobs. You have no idea how long it took me to find even a part time nurses aide, a job that requires nothing more than a high school diploma and some training time in a nursing facility. It's not that the jobs aren't there, it's that there aren't enough competent people filling them. Most Americans who work now either do it because they enjoy it, or because they don't know how to fill out government forms. Free rides are entirely too easy to get with a presumption of need at every turn, whereas in Germany the TOTAL focus is to return the person as a functioning member of society. Even if that function is being a bus boy. It's tough, but people should have thought about things like employability before deciding to major in the "liberal arts" or blowing off high school or dismissing the value of post high school trade school for those not intending to go to a 4 year school. Heck when I was in high school we had vocational high schools you could go to your last two years to learn a skill, but today's required curricula doesn't leave room for people to learn practical skills before their 18 unless they seek the training out themselves, and frequently in violation of OSHA laws regarding "children" handling "dangerous equipment". Something that in and of itself shut down practical education at the high school level in ANY heavy industry. If you can't compete, don't show up for the game, or vote for President Obama. He'll treat you like you were his own brother. That is, block your entry into the United States and ignore the plight of your sick child.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345499883000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500052000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Hit The Road!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1345498061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for the big cheese to stink up the place</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345500052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500177000-96</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying over $1M.</Title><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345488080000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd be buying this like mad if I was on the inside as well, in fact it'd almost be worth resigning to be able to avoid insider restrictions, though of course then you can't influence the outcome. This is WAY undervalued as compared to assets on hand, and I'm wondering how long it'll take the market to figure that out.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345500177000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500248000-97</Id><Topic><Title>The Mormon Kingdom of God in America</Title><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1345498287000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:31:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a sort of pragmatism that is non-pragmatic in a John Taylor’s sermon. The Saints must do what the servants of God would tell them, be it to go to war or not to resist the attacks of the enemy. For what was of most importance for the Saints was the establishment of God’s Kingdom on Earth, and in order to do so, they would have to listen and obey the words of the Prophet – scrupulously: ‘If there cannot be a people anywhere found that will listen to the word of God and receive instructions from him, how can his kingdom ever be established? It is impossible. What is the first thing necessary to the establishment of his kingdom? It is to raise up a Prophet and have him declare the will of God; the next is to have people yield obedience to the word of the Lord through that Prophet. If you cannot have these, you never can establish the kingdom of God upon the earth. What is the kingdom of God? It is God’s government upon the earth and in heaven’.</Msg><Username>cozined</Username><Timestamp>1345500248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500289000-98</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying over $1M.</Title><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345488080000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think it is because of the value of because they know about a buyout?</Msg><Username>seniortrader213</Username><Timestamp>1345500289000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500458000-99</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what would the republicans do?</Msg><Username>cozined</Username><Timestamp>1345500458000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500682000-100</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't fret. The market will correct and this stock will get hit harder than others. Just sit back and wait for a pullback. My guess is this stock sees the 7's again before $10.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345500682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345500763000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Insider Buying over $1M.</Title><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345488080000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senior.... Surely you know that would be insider trading? You just can't do it, which means there is no buyout on the table as of that stock purchase.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345500763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345501120000-102</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Billwilliselkins are you a manic-depressive?</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345501120000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345501404000-103</Id><Title>$8.89. ! $8.89 ! $8.89. Go go go etrade!</Title><Msg>Tomorrow big news</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345501404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345501566000-104</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for since early July and I made nothing on it yet. I hope you are right. I am ready to buy 10,000 etfc shares if I see any major pullback. We may see this stock going higher and higher also and then what? Buy at $15-$18? I have to do something soon. It is not normal to go up that quick without that something that insiders know about it already.</Msg><Username>seniortrader213</Username><Timestamp>1345501566000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:26:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345501686000-105</Id><Title>$9.11 $9.11 $9.11 go go go etrade!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Bidding up for tomorrow. -Morton Drexler</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345501686000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345502052000-106</Id><Title>Happy Dayz are Here Again</Title><Msg>Go, go go</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345502052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345502553000-107</Id><Title>Another Fisker Goes Flambe'!...</Title><Msg>Hot Dogs when you buy one?... http://abcnews.go.com/Blotter/fisker-recalls-electric-cars/story?id=17044981#.UDK8rd2PWpg</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345502553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345503757000-108</Id><Topic><Title>About to Skyrocket!!!! Strong Support Being Built at $8.60!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345484482000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 13:41:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're way off. We're never going to see $7 anymore.</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1345503757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345505329000-109</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama accomplishment</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345494576000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that why he don't give money to his brother in Kenya to help with his nephews surgery.....brack yo pos.....help your auntie buy some new teeth...dam</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1345505329000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345505379000-110</Id><Title>Just making stuff up!</Title><Msg>Obama Welfare WASHINGTON -- During a surprise appearance in the White House Briefing Room on Monday, President Barack Obama responded to Republican challenger Mitt Romney's claim that Obama has "gutted" work requirements for welfare recipients. Obama called the charge "absolutely wrong." A reporter asked Obama if he was comfortable with the tone of his campaign, pointing to an ad by an Obama-supporting super PAC that implied Romney bore responsibility for a woman's cancer death after her husband lost his job following a buyout by Romney's former company. "I don't think that Gov. Romney is somehow responsible for the death of the woman that was portrayed in that ad," Obama said. "But keep in mind this is an ad that I didn't approve, I did not produce, and as far as I can tell, has barely run." The president then pointed out that Romney himself has endorsed attack ads rated false by a plethora of newspapers and fact-checkers. (The Romney camp released the latest such ad earlier on Monday.) "Now, in contrast you've got Gov. Romney creating as a centerpiece of his campaign this notion that we're taking the work requirement out of welfare, which every single person here who's looked at it says is patently false," Obama said. "What he's arguing is somehow we have changed the welfare requirement, the work requirement in our welfare laws. And, in fact, what's happened was that my administration, responding to the requests of five governors, including two Republican governors, agreed to approve giving them, those states, some flexibility in how they manage their welfare rolls as long as it produced 20 percent increases in the number of people who are getting work." Nevada and Utah were among the states interested in greater flexibility in the Temporary Assistance for Needy Families program, better known as welfare. The Obama administration has not announced that any waivers have gone out. "Everybody who's looked at this says what Gov. Romney's saying is absolutely wrong," Obama continued. "Not only are his super PACs running millions of dollars worth of ads making this claim, Gov. Romney himself is approving this and saying it on the stump. So the contrast, I think, is pretty stark. They can run the campaign that they want, but the truth of the matter is you can't just make stuff up."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345505379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345507113000-111</Id><Title>Common Sense Seeping Back into the Courts?...</Title><Msg>Maybe.... http://www.wsbtv.com/ap/ap/social-issues/court-ga-police-may-verify-immigration-status/nRF9P/</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345507113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345507318000-112</Id><Title>Willard defrauded Medicare</Title><Msg>Sun Aug 19, 2012, 12:48 AM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Romney and Bain profited from massive Medicare Fraud From the delightful gift that is John McCain’s opposition research on Mitt (courtesy of namelessgenxer) comes the sordid tale of Mitt’s tenure on the board of Damon Clinical Laboratories, which plead guilty to charges of defrauding Medicare and agreed to pay what was at the time the largest health care criminal fraud fine in history – $35,300,000. They also agreed to larger civil fines which totaled $83,700,000. I originally published this back in January, but given the recent focus on Bain it’s worth a revisit. Also, I’m republishing this to The Bain Files to add to that archive of Mitty evildoings. The time line goes as follows. 1988: Damon begins a systemic practice of fraud. The government estimates later that the total cost to taxpayers of this fraud is around $40,000,000 1990: Bain Capital (CEO Mitt Romney) buys a minority stake in Damon. Mitt takes a seat on the board of directors 1990 to 1993: Mitt serves on the board of directors, earning ~$10,000 per year for doing so. He is on the company’s “Strategic Planning” committee 1992: Romney said that Rosen told the board in about 1992 ‘that all current practices at the company were now in conformity with government regulations and that in the past there may have been practices which would not be deemed appropriate. 1993: Damon is taken over by Corning, with Mitt Romney voting in favor of the acquisition 1993: Corning immediately closes Damon’s Massachusetts plant and lays off 115 workers 1993: Corning uncovers the fraud and alerts authorities. The SEC filings made by Damon prior to the acquisition make no mention of any potential earnings write-downs or legal problems 1993: Mitt Romney’s share of Bain’s profit from the Damon investment: $473,000 1993: Bain’s profit from its investment in Damon: $7,400,000, which represented a tripling of the initial investment 1994: Running for Senator, Mitt Romney says: I’m proud of the small part I played in the growth of Damon,’ Romney said yesterday. ‘It’s something that Ted Kennedy doesn’t have a clue about – creating real jobs in the private sector. 2002: While running for governor, Romney claims that he helped uncover the fraud by starting an investigation. This version of events is disputed by Corning and by the Federal Prosecutors. Mitt also says he never alerted the authorities, which no one disputes. (read the rest) http://www.balloon-juice.com/2012/08/18/mitt-romney-profited-from-massive-medicare-fraud-while-at-bain-capital/ So - Bain invests in a company. Mitt gets personally involved with managing said company. Company profits are significantly based upon Medicare Fraud. Bain &amp; Romney never uncover the fraud in 4 years, Corning uncovers it immediately upon buying Damon. Despite the fraud, Bain triples its investment, and Romney's share of that profit is a cool half a million.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345507318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345507340000-113</Id><Title>If it is sooo goood insiders would do buy-out?</Title><Msg>the question and the answer are the same! if it is so good then the insiders (all of them not just 2 smart guys????? but all would see the true value and buy it for themselves and still have a job to go to each morning) it's not and they will not buy it.....or ask your self , (why do only these two guys know something and all the others don't?) there is your answer it is imagined sell til the 3's</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345507340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345507369000-114</Id><Topic><Title>Common Sense Seeping Back into the Courts?...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345507113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:58:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously it will be a Very Slow process!... "The panel did leave in place a part of the injunction blocking the prosecution of people who knowingly harbor or transport an illegal immigrant during the commission of a crime."</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345507369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345508422000-115</Id><Topic><Title>Just making stuff up!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345505379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 19:29:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;"but the truth of the matter is you can't just make stuff up"&gt;&gt; This sharlatin has made a carrer of doing exactly that... lying through his piano teeth.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345508422000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345510082000-116</Id><Topic><Title>If it is sooo goood insiders would do buy-out?</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345507340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:02:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look at the ownership, dummie.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1345510082000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 20:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345511233000-117</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney!!! (Done!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1345413053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Hit the Road, Barack,” This thread isn't getting enough play. Er'body know nobody read Newsweek anymore. The author nailed brak's ears to the wall on this one-- great job! "Hit the road 'Brak" &lt;-- fits better (How neat would that have been to just replace the j wif the b? and on the cover too-- I have to admit, I would've been BEAMING wif pride.) Perhaps they might have thought I copyrighted, trademarked or registered "Brak".. But nope, as far as things on my end go, they could have legally used it.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345511233000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345512600000-118</Id><Topic><Title>GOP trainwreck looms</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345496409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 17:00:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whot we got here? A newly minted swing state?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345512600000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345513228000-119</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney!!! (Done!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1345413053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wot have we here? Because of the newsweek story msm now has cover to tell the troof about brak? That's one story that'll have to be seen to be believed. http://www.newsmax.com/Newsfront/newsweek-barack-obama-wright/2012/08/20/id/449085</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345513228000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 21:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345514428000-120</Id><Title>I never expected it to get this big</Title><Msg>After plugging my digits into it, when I looked down it had grown bigger than I thought. http://www.politico.com/blogs/burns-haberman/2012/08/romney-leads-in-cash-on-hand-by-m-132619.html</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345514428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514534000-121</Id><Topic><Title>I never expected it to get this big</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345514428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what Adam said in the garden. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345514534000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345514639000-122</Id><Topic><Title>I never expected it to get this big</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345514428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, wait, Adam said, "Stand back Eve, I don't know how big this thing gets!".</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345514639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:03:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515171000-123</Id><Topic><Title>I never expected it to get this big</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345514428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:00:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ha ha ha. Now make funny about mohammed</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345515171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345515415000-124</Id><Topic><Title>Another Fisker Goes Flambe'!...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345502553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:42:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear that the buddhist munks are buying these cars. Something about making a statement.</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1345515415000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345516899000-125</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Akin said when asked whether he believes abortion is justified in cases of rape and replies that rape does not result in pregnancy. He said, “It seems to be, first of all, from what I understand from doctors, it’s really rare. If it’s a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut the whole thing down.” That is what he said. There isn't any "repeated out of context" about it. That is what he said. Let me tell you, there is no such thing as a legitimate rape. There is only rape. Rape is never legal or allowed or proper. Akin could have said not said "legitimate" at all and the statement would have conveyed _his_ meaning better for his purposes: If it’s rape, the female body has ways to try to shut the whole thing down.” That statement is pure BS but not mean spirited BS. Adding the word "legitimate" questions the womans honesty, which is what the defense lawyers have done for years and why Akin is such a cur dog. Woman: He raped me. Lawyer: Are you trying to tell me that you didn't enjoy it just a little bit? I can't imagine that you wouldn't. Women have conceived children from men they did not even know from semen in swimming pools. Not rape, just an excited stranger who got too close waiting in line to go up the ladder. Think about that for awhile. Doesn't happen very often. I have a friend who got pregnant the fist time she had sex. And yet that was a thing that guys said long ago. Can't get pregnant the first time. BS. Don't imagine that a raped woman's body has defenses. It doesn't. If I were a woman and had to bear a child from rape, I'd hate that child every second of the day. I can't imagine anything more cruel than to make a woman bear a child conceived in rape. I hate the way conservatives wear mind filters that discard "inconvenient truths". ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345516899000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 22:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345520556000-126</Id><Topic><Title>Legitimate R ape...</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1345486066000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:07:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mon Aug 20, 2012, 12:10 AM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Earlier today, Missouri U.S. Senate candidate Rep. Todd Akin (R-MO) claimed that “legitimate rape” does not often lead to pregnancy because “the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down.” This is not the first time the biologically challenged senate candidate tried to minimize the impact of rape. Last year, Akin joined with GOP vice presidential candidate Rep. Paul Ryan (R-WI) as two of the original co-sponsors of the “No Taxpayer Funding for Abortion Act,” a bill which, among other things, introduced the country to the bizarre term “forcible rape.” Federal law prevents federal Medicaid funds and similar programs from paying for abortions. Yet the law also contains an exception for women who are raped. The bill Akin and Ryan cosponsored would have narrowed this exception, providing that only pregnancies arising from “forcible rape” may be terminated. Because the primary target of Akin and Ryan’s effort are Medicaid recipients — patients who are unlikely to be able to afford an abortion absent Medicaid funding — the likely impact of this bill would have been forcing many rape survivors to carry their rapist’s baby to term. Michelle Goldberg explains who Akin and Ryan would likely target: Under H.R. 3, only victims of “forcible rape” would qualify for federally funded abortions. Victims of statutory rape—say, a 13-year-old girl impregnated by a 30-year-old man—would be on their own. So would victims of incest if they’re over 18. And while “forcible rape” isn’t defined in the criminal code, the addition of the adjective seems certain to exclude acts of rape that don’t involve overt violence—say, cases where a woman is drugged or has a limited mental capacity. “It’s basically putting more restrictions on what was defined historically as rape,” says Keenan. Although a version of this bill passed the GOP-controlled House, the “forcible rape” language was eventually removed due to widespread public outcry. Paul Ryan, however, believes that the “forcible rape” language does not actually go far enough to force women to carry their rapist’s baby. Ryan believes that abortion should be illegal in all cases except for “cases in which a doctor deems an abortion necessary to save the mother’s life.” So rape survivors are out of luck.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1345520556000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345521326000-127</Id><Topic><Title>Another Fisker Goes Flambe'!...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345502553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 18:42:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hope yer doin well with yer buggy whip business. You hate progress as much as you hate America.</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1345521326000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 23:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>