<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345954620000-1</Id><Topic><Title>The " Birther Ball"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345921554000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 15:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget the various witches and whackos, gun nutz, para military govt haters, and morons who hate anyone who isn't fat and white.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbie</Username><Timestamp>1345954620000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345954789000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Brak wins in likeability poll</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345915146000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:19:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sweetie, with that gay hippie look you have, it looks like you have shitzsandwich every day. And love it.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbie</Username><Timestamp>1345954789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345955146000-3</Id><Title>Pat Robertson Says Hurricanes are Caused by Gays</Title><Msg>So Tampa must be a very gay convention.</Msg><Username>mitt_da_szit</Username><Timestamp>1345955146000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:25:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345956960000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Robertson Says Hurricanes are Caused by Gays</Title><Username>mitt_da_szit</Username><Timestamp>1345955146000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:25:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a gay hooker convention. For a short time, the gays will be the 1 %.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1345956960000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:56:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345965028449-5</Id><Topic><Title>Top 1% takes in more income than the entire bottom 50%</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345765393035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>non-greedy, I moved to United States from places not far from those Scandinavians and would't reconsider my decision unless people like you screw this country beyond recognition. If I don't meet my legal obligations to pay established $$$ amount to IRS, I end up in prison. Your option to move to my own island is rather idiotic. I am not tax evader, I pay exact amount required by tax law. If I think my tax is too high, the only option is to change it constitutional way. As far as my moral obligations go, there are plenty of ways to meet them without sending a penny to the government. It is rather disingenuous to pass your personal moral obligation to government, than blame others for non compliance. Do you send your non tax money to help the needy? If not, go F yourself.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345965028449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 03:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345981673296-6</Id><Topic><Title>Now we know why yapoop was one of the first and sucks hind tit now</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1345942146202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 20:49:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rampant rump rider..,, you still forgetting to put on your filtration mask in your meth lab???</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1345981673296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 07:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345984581545-7</Id><Topic><Title>Top 1% takes in more income than the entire bottom 50%</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345765393035</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 19:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only the brainless gop would demand to lower the taxes for those with money and and raise them on people with none.. But that is in keeping with a long tradition of gop stupidity: the bush taxcuts eliminated a $5.6 trillion projected budget surplus and now the Romney tax cuts are promised to end the budget deficits. Amazing how tax cuts can both reduce a suplus and a deficit! Gop deficit reduction = giving a huge new tax cut, giving most boomers full AS IS medicare and social security, and as a big cherry on top for the neocons the gift of increased military spending.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345984581545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345987935000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Calls</Title><Username>sivretaywg72353</Username><Timestamp>1345983457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:17:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just joined too.</Msg><Username>liscanoido5388</Username><Timestamp>1345987935000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345992429000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Buy Calls</Title><Username>sivretaywg72353</Username><Timestamp>1345983457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:17:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>pingreeodia63605</Username><Timestamp>1345992429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 10:47:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993340000-10</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Robertson Says Hurricanes are Caused by Gays</Title><Username>mitt_da_szit</Username><Timestamp>1345955146000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:25:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every little boy in Florida is hiding at home.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1345993340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345993858000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Losing Hard?</Title><Username>paul_alana22</Username><Timestamp>1345983434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>dedra_avis12</Username><Timestamp>1345993858000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345994847489-12</Id><Title>FLA Gov. endorses BO</Title><Msg>Former Gov. Charlie Crist: Here's why I'm backing Barack Obama By Charlie Crist, Special to the Times In Print: Sunday, August 26, 2012 Facebook 1K Email Share 3K ADVERTISEMENT ADVERTISEMENT Story Tools Print this story Purchase reprints Contact the editor Email Newsletters I’ve studied, admired and gotten to know a lot of leaders in my life. Across Florida, in Washington and around the country, I've watched the failure of those who favor extreme rhetoric over sensible compromise, and I've seen how those who never lose sight of solutions sow the greatest successes. As America prepares to pick our president for the next four years — and as Florida prepares once again to play a decisive role — I'm confident that President Barack Obama is the right leader for our state and the nation. I applaud and share his vision of a future built by a strong and confident middle class in an economy that gives us the opportunity to reap prosperity through hard work and personal responsibility. It is a vision of the future proven right by our history. We often remind ourselves to learn the lessons of the past, lest we risk repeating its mistakes. Yet nearly as often, our short-term memory fails us. Many have already forgotten how deep and daunting our shared crisis was in the winter of 2009, as President Obama was inaugurated. It was no ordinary challenge, and the president served as the nation's calm through a historically turbulent storm. The president's response was swift, smart and farsighted. He kept his compass pointed due north and relentlessly focused on saving jobs, creating more and helping the many who felt trapped beneath the house of cards that had collapsed upon them. He knew we had to get people back to work as quickly as possible — but he also knew that the value of a recovery lies in its durability. Short-term healing had to be paired with an economy that would stay healthy over the long run. And he knew that happens best by investing in the right places. President Obama invested in our children's schools because he believes a good education is a necessity, not a luxury, if we're going to create an economy built to last. He supported more than 400,000 K-12 teachers' jobs, and he is making college more affordable and making student loans, like the ones he took out, easier to pay back. He invested in our runways, railways and roads. President Obama knows a reliable infrastructure that helps move people to work and helps businesses move goods to market is a foundation of growth. And the president invested in our retirement security by strengthening Medicare. The $716 billion in savings his opponents decry today extended the life of the program by nearly a decade and are making sure taxpayer dollars aren't wasted in excessive payments to insurance companies or fraud and abuse. His opponents would end the Medicare guarantee by creating a voucher that would raise seniors' costs by thousands of dollars and bankrupt the program. We have more work to do, more investments to make and more waste to cut. But only one candidate in this race has proven a willingness to navigate a realistic path to prosperity. As Republicans gather in Tampa to nominate Mitt Romney, Americans can expect to hear tales of how President Obama has failed to work with their party or turn the economy around. But an element of their party has pitched so far to the extreme right on issues important to women, immigrants, seniors and students that they've proven incapable of governing for the people. Look no further than the inclusion of the Akin amendment in the Republican Party platform, which bans abortion, even for rape victims. The truth is that the party has failed to demonstrate the kind of leadership or seriousness voters deserve. Pundits looking to reduce something as big as a statewide election to a single photograph have blamed the result of my 2010 campaign for U.S. Senate on my greeting of President Obama. I didn't stand with our president because of what it could mean politically; I did it because uniting to recover from the worst financial crisis of our lifetimes was more important than party affiliation. I stood with our nation's leader because it was right for my state. President Obama has a strong record of doing what is best for America and Florida, and he built it by spending more time worrying about what his decisions would mean for the people than for his political fortunes. That's what makes him the right leader for our times, and that's why I'm proud to stand with him today. Charlie Crist is the former Republican governor of Florida and previously was elected as a state senator, education commissioner and attorney general. He currently is registered as no party affiliation. Crist wrote this column exclusively for the Tampa Bay Times.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345994847489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345995068000-13</Id><Title>Former GOP Gov. endorses BO</Title><Msg>Former Gov. Charlie Crist: Here's why I'm backing Barack Obama By Charlie Crist, Special to the Times In Print: Sunday, August 26, 2012 I’ve studied, admired and gotten to know a lot of leaders in my life. Across Florida, in Washington and around the country, I've watched the failure of those who favor extreme rhetoric over sensible compromise, and I've seen how those who never lose sight of solutions sow the greatest successes. As America prepares to pick our president for the next four years — and as Florida prepares once again to play a decisive role — I'm confident that President Barack Obama is the right leader for our state and the nation. I applaud and share his vision of a future built by a strong and confident middle class in an economy that gives us the opportunity to reap prosperity through hard work and personal responsibility. It is a vision of the future proven right by our history. We often remind ourselves to learn the lessons of the past, lest we risk repeating its mistakes. Yet nearly as often, our short-term memory fails us. Many have already forgotten how deep and daunting our shared crisis was in the winter of 2009, as President Obama was inaugurated. It was no ordinary challenge, and the president served as the nation's calm through a historically turbulent storm. The president's response was swift, smart and farsighted. He kept his compass pointed due north and relentlessly focused on saving jobs, creating more and helping the many who felt trapped beneath the house of cards that had collapsed upon them. He knew we had to get people back to work as quickly as possible — but he also knew that the value of a recovery lies in its durability. Short-term healing had to be paired with an economy that would stay healthy over the long run. And he knew that happens best by investing in the right places. President Obama invested in our children's schools because he believes a good education is a necessity, not a luxury, if we're going to create an economy built to last. He supported more than 400,000 K-12 teachers' jobs, and he is making college more affordable and making student loans, like the ones he took out, easier to pay back. He invested in our runways, railways and roads. President Obama knows a reliable infrastructure that helps move people to work and helps businesses move goods to market is a foundation of growth. And the president invested in our retirement security by strengthening Medicare. The $716 billion in savings his opponents decry today extended the life of the program by nearly a decade and are making sure taxpayer dollars aren't wasted in excessive payments to insurance companies or fraud and abuse. His opponents would end the Medicare guarantee by creating a voucher that would raise seniors' costs by thousands of dollars and bankrupt the program.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345995068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345995098000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Former GOP Gov. endorses BO</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345995068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have more work to do, more investments to make and more waste to cut. But only one candidate in this race has proven a willingness to navigate a realistic path to prosperity. As Republicans gather in Tampa to nominate Mitt Romney, Americans can expect to hear tales of how President Obama has failed to work with their party or turn the economy around. But an element of their party has pitched so far to the extreme right on issues important to women, immigrants, seniors and students that they've proven incapable of governing for the people. Look no further than the inclusion of the Akin amendment in the Republican Party platform, which bans abortion, even for rape victims. The truth is that the party has failed to demonstrate the kind of leadership or seriousness voters deserve. Pundits looking to reduce something as big as a statewide election to a single photograph have blamed the result of my 2010 campaign for U.S. Senate on my greeting of President Obama. I didn't stand with our president because of what it could mean politically; I did it because uniting to recover from the worst financial crisis of our lifetimes was more important than party affiliation. I stood with our nation's leader because it was right for my state. President Obama has a strong record of doing what is best for America and Florida, and he built it by spending more time worrying about what his decisions would mean for the people than for his political fortunes. That's what makes him the right leader for our times, and that's why I'm proud to stand with him today. Charlie Crist is the former Republican governor of Florida and previously was elected as a state senator, education commissioner and attorney general. He currently is registered as no party affiliation. Crist wrote this column exclusively for the Tampa Bay Times.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345995098000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345995883176-15</Id><Title>Tax weasel 101</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney Reaped Huge Tax Benefits Based On 'Active' Role At Bain Capital Posted: 08/26/2012 12:45 am Romney Taxes WASHINGTON -- Mitt Romney has repeatedly insisted during the presidential campaign that layoffs and other controversy surrounding Bain Capital companies for the past decade are not his responsibility, because he retired in 1999. When tax experts charged that he benefited from legally dubious tax avoidance strategies employed by Bain, his campaign noted that the investments are kept in a blind trust completely out of his control. "As we have said many times before, Governor and Mrs. Romney's assets are managed on a blind basis. They do not control the investment of these assets. The investment decisions are made by a trustee," spokeswoman Michele Davis said. But according to his 2010 tax return, when the Internal Revenue Service comes calling in April, Romney has a different answer: The presumptive GOP nominee reaps lucrative tax breaks for "active" participation in the private equity firm he founded, as well as a host of other investments. As David Kautter, a tax expert at American University, explains, the concept of active investment has different meanings for the IRS and for regular people. "When you say you're actively involved in all these businesses, people do think, OK, you're actively involved. But the tax law has its own definition," he said. That still leaves Romney in a rhetorical jam: For tax purposes, he claims an active status; for political purposes, he claims to have zero to do with the investments. The distinction is valuable, for the IRS treats passive and active income and losses differently. If a passive investment loses money, the taxpayer can only write off that loss if passive gains have also been made and only at a 15 percent rate. But active losses can be written off at a 35 percent rate and deducted from the taxpayer's ordinary income. In other words, a taxpayer wants active losses, not passive losses. So by describing many of his investments as active, Romney saves himself millions of dollars in taxes. With those active investments, he is also securing a tax break few Americans enjoy: When he wins, he's paying a 15 percent rate on the gain. When he loses, he's writing it off at 35 percent, meaning that tax policy is subsidizing Romney's risk in his Bain investments. In other words, Romney didn't build that, at least not without taxpayer backing. Federal rules allow many of these tax loopholes. But under the technical terms of the retirement package that Romney negotiated for himself, he has borne a lighter tax load than most other retired financial professionals. And the unusually large scope of his deductions and the generous rate at which they are recognized have some tax experts questioning their validity. Romney's 2010 tax return lists $301,630 in "trade or business interest" deductions and $503,737 in "trade or business expense" deductions -- all of it described as expenses from his business partnerships, including Bain. Specifically from his various Bain-related activities, Romney scored a total of $547,525 in such deductions. These kinds of deductions are only available to "active" participants in business partnerships. While Romney filed as an active participant for tax purposes, there is no evidence that he took part in Bain management decisions in 2010, and he has denied doing so. The sophistication with which Romney used Bain's later efforts to boost his own income could serve as fodder for political campaign advertisements. Since Romney has been willing to profit from Bain's later activity, the Obama campaign may well argue that such practices are fair game for attack ads. Some Democrats are already on the attack. "Governor Romney appears to be saying one thing to the American people and one thing to the Internal Revenue Service," Rep. Brad Miller (D-N.C.) said to The Huffington Post. "Right now we are just seeing inconsistent statements. The American people are entitled to know more than that. If there's a legalistic distinction, we are entitled to know what that is. ... Has he played too close to the line or over the line?" It is also possible that these deductions are all legitimate expenses for Bain and the handful of Goldman Sachs subsidiaries in which Romney is a partner. But they all appear on a tax document where individuals usually list personal expenses, known as Schedule E. And listing personal expenses as business expenses is not allowed. In addition, some tax experts are surprised by the size of the deductions he takes as business expenses and the aggressive nature of the deductions. "One question is just the amount of the expenses," said Rebecca Wilkins, senior tax policy counsel at Citizens for Tax Justice. "At half a million dollars, you have to wonder what all of that is." Romney's income can basically be divided into two parts. His "ordinary" income triggers the top 35 percent tax rate to which America's wealthiest earners are subject. But most of his income comes in the form of capital gains, which are taxed at only 15 percent. According to the Washington Post, 50 percent of all capital gains in the United States flow to the top 0.1 percent of taxpayers. These two different tax rates present a tempting opportunity: By applying deductions to the pool of money taxed at 35 percent, rather than the pool of money taxed at 15 percent, Romney can reduce his overall tax bill. The $805,367 in deductions from his partnerships all receive exactly this useful treatment -- which may or may not be appropriate, depending on the nature of the expenses incurred. "What's problematic is that these expenses are being deducted at the ordinary income tax rate of 35 percent, while the related income is mostly subject to the preferential long-term capital gain tax rate of 15 percent," Wilkins said. Whether these expenses rightly apply to the pool of money taxed at 35 percent can only be determined by accessing the tax returns of Romney's Bain partnerships, which are not public documents. But many investment partnerships recognize stock losses that could not receive this favorable treatment. In the years after Romney insists that he ended any active role at the firm, Bain Capital companies suffered huge job losses, plant closures and bankruptcies. KB Toys may be the saddest example. The New York Times has reported that after Bain bought the toy company in 2000, KB Toys filed for bankruptcy, laying off more than 3,000 workers. Bain's aggressive financial maneuvering, however, scored a 370 percent return on its investment. Romney's own testimony and Securities and Exchange Commission filings demonstrate that he might not have been as hands off decision-making during those later years as he's suggested. Either way, his sophisticated tax practices show that he continued to benefit not only from Bain's profits but, at least in his tax bill, from Bain's losses.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345995883176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345996014000-16</Id><Title>Sounds like a tax cheat to me</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney Reaped Huge Tax Benefits Based On 'Active' Role At Bain Capital Posted: 08/26/2012 12:45 am Romney Taxes WASHINGTON -- Mitt Romney has repeatedly insisted during the presidential campaign that layoffs and other controversy surrounding Bain Capital companies for the past decade are not his responsibility, because he retired in 1999. When tax experts charged that he benefited from legally dubious tax avoidance strategies employed by Bain, his campaign noted that the investments are kept in a blind trust completely out of his control. "As we have said many times before, Governor and Mrs. Romney's assets are managed on a blind basis. They do not control the investment of these assets. The investment decisions are made by a trustee," spokeswoman Michele Davis said. But according to his 2010 tax return, when the Internal Revenue Service comes calling in April, Romney has a different answer: The presumptive GOP nominee reaps lucrative tax breaks for "active" participation in the private equity firm he founded, as well as a host of other investments. As David Kautter, a tax expert at American University, explains, the concept of active investment has different meanings for the IRS and for regular people. "When you say you're actively involved in all these businesses, people do think, OK, you're actively involved. But the tax law has its own definition," he said. That still leaves Romney in a rhetorical jam: For tax purposes, he claims an active status; for political purposes, he claims to have zero to do with the investments. The distinction is valuable, for the IRS treats passive and active income and losses differently. If a passive investment loses money, the taxpayer can only write off that loss if passive gains have also been made and only at a 15 percent rate. But active losses can be written off at a 35 percent rate and deducted from the taxpayer's ordinary income. In other words, a taxpayer wants active losses, not passive losses. So by describing many of his investments as active, Romney saves himself millions of dollars in taxes. With those active investments, he is also securing a tax break few Americans enjoy: When he wins, he's paying a 15 percent rate on the gain. When he loses, he's writing it off at 35 percent, meaning that tax policy is subsidizing Romney's risk in his Bain investments. In other words, Romney didn't build that, at least not without taxpayer backing. Federal rules allow many of these tax loopholes. But under the technical terms of the retirement package that Romney negotiated for himself, he has borne a lighter tax load than most other retired financial professionals. And the unusually large scope of his deductions and the generous rate at which they are recognized have some tax experts questioning their validity. Romney's 2010 tax return lists $301,630 in "trade or business interest" deductions and $503,737 in "trade or business expense" deductions -- all of it described as expenses from his business partnerships, including Bain. Specifically from his various Bain-related activities, Romney scored a total of $547,525 in such deductions.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345996014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:46:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345996065000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Sounds like a tax cheat to me</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345996014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:46:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These kinds of deductions are only available to "active" participants in business partnerships. While Romney filed as an active participant for tax purposes, there is no evidence that he took part in Bain management decisions in 2010, and he has denied doing so. The sophistication with which Romney used Bain's later efforts to boost his own income could serve as fodder for political campaign advertisements. Since Romney has been willing to profit from Bain's later activity, the Obama campaign may well argue that such practices are fair game for attack ads. Some Democrats are already on the attack. "Governor Romney appears to be saying one thing to the American people and one thing to the Internal Revenue Service," Rep. Brad Miller (D-N.C.) said to The Huffington Post. "Right now we are just seeing inconsistent statements. The American people are entitled to know more than that. If there's a legalistic distinction, we are entitled to know what that is. ... Has he played too close to the line or over the line?" It is also possible that these deductions are all legitimate expenses for Bain and the handful of Goldman Sachs subsidiaries in which Romney is a partner. But they all appear on a tax document where individuals usually list personal expenses, known as Schedule E. And listing personal expenses as business expenses is not allowed. In addition, some tax experts are surprised by the size of the deductions he takes as business expenses and the aggressive nature of the deductions. "One question is just the amount of the expenses," said Rebecca Wilkins, senior tax policy counsel at Citizens for Tax Justice. "At half a million dollars, you have to wonder what all of that is." Romney's income can basically be divided into two parts. His "ordinary" income triggers the top 35 percent tax rate to which America's wealthiest earners are subject. But most of his income comes in the form of capital gains, which are taxed at only 15 percent. According to the Washington Post, 50 percent of all capital gains in the United States flow to the top 0.1 percent of taxpayers. These two different tax rates present a tempting opportunity: By applying deductions to the pool of money taxed at 35 percent, rather than the pool of money taxed at 15 percent, Romney can reduce his overall tax bill. The $805,367 in deductions from his partnerships all receive exactly this useful treatment -- which may or may not be appropriate, depending on the nature of the expenses incurred. "What's problematic is that these expenses are being deducted at the ordinary income tax rate of 35 percent, while the related income is mostly subject to the preferential long-term capital gain tax rate of 15 percent," Wilkins said. Whether these expenses rightly apply to the pool of money taxed at 35 percent can only be determined by accessing the tax returns of Romney's Bain partnerships, which are not public documents. But many investment partnerships recognize stock losses that could not receive this favorable treatment. In the years after Romney insists that he ended any active role at the firm, Bain Capital companies suffered huge job losses, plant closures and bankruptcies. KB Toys may be the saddest example. The New York Times has reported that after Bain bought the toy company in 2000, KB Toys filed for bankruptcy, laying off more than 3,000 workers. Bain's aggressive financial maneuvering, however, scored a 370 percent return on its investment. Romney's own testimony and Securities and Exchange Commission filings demonstrate that he might not have been as hands off decision-making during those later years as he's suggested. Either way, his sophisticated tax practices show that he continued to benefit not only from Bain's profits but, at least in his tax bill, from Bain's losses.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345996065000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:47:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345999471469-18</Id><Title>Your "Akin" heart</Title><Msg>Why Does Akin Have To Go, But Paul Ryan Gets To Stay? Posted: 08/22/2012 1:04 pm Seriously Republicans: why does Todd Akin have to go, but Paul Ryan gets to stay? A tip of my hat to Christine Pelosi for asking this great question on Politico yesterday. In fact, Congressman Akin has got to be scratching his head at the recent turn of events. Why are the Republicans so breathlessly chasing him from the field when they all - and especially Paul Ryan - have advocated essentially the same thing? It's about the policy - there should be no rape exception to abortion. It's got to be confusing, especially since the Republicans put that in their party platform yesterday. Congressman Akin has apologized for his dumb remarks about rape biologically preventing pregnancy. Repeatedly. But the Republicans are still professing to be "outraged" - shocked and stunned by Akin's comments. "There's no excuse" for such caveman-like statements, they are saying. He's a Neanderthal, they claim. Virginia Governor Bob McDonnell says Akin's a "lost cause." The National Review says his views are "abhorrent." Check out these statements from Republicans in the video below: Surely these same Republicans were equally outraged when Paul Ryan joined Akin to sponsor a bill, HR-3 -- which shows it was a top priority among House Republicans -- defining "forcible" rape. After all, even Akin himself admits that when he said "legitimate," he meant to say, "forcible." So were all the Republicans equally outraged by that bill? Of course not -- 177 of them actually signed on to the bill. After lots of outcry the word "forcible" was removed, but the point was made. What they're saying is that "real" rape is only when the woman is hurt. If she doesn't get hurt, she must have enjoyed it, so it obviously wasn't rape. The women who are drugged and raped, they're not conscious so what's the harm? The women who don't fight back, who succumb in order to save themselves from further harm? Well, they obviously must secretly want it. Yes, the whole Republican Party is now aligned against Akin in name, but solidly behind his ideas. With no exceptions for rape or Romney. The party platform - what they stand for - matches Akin and Ryan's no-exemption-for-rape position, and it's their governing document. But none of the Republican establishment is jumping up and down about that, are they? So why are all these Republicans so quick to banish Akin from their ticket? Because he said out loud what they're all thinking and what they're all legislating, but hope we don't notice. If you're outraged about Akin's comments, you should be outraged by the entire Republican establishment. But let's just start here and go one man at a time: if Akin is drummed from the Senate race, Ryan should go, too.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345999471469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346002974238-19</Id><Topic><Title>Your "Akin" heart</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345999471469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 12:44:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>akin could be the gop presidential candidate running with rand paul as vp...and still kick the dufus bammy o into oblivion.........................we havent had a president in almost 4 years....just a garden party sports fanatic...maybe odufus should run under the garden party</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346002974238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 13:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346010627000-20</Id><Title>No, It aint right.</Title><Msg>Brak's own words come back to haunt him. A bountiful harvest of low hanging froot to pick from here. What wif all the instances where he says one thing and winds up doing the opposite. http://townhall.com/tipsheet/guybenson/2012/08/26/new_romney_ad_obamas_medicare_cuts_slammed_byobama</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346010627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346011121644-21</Id><Title>Paul censored, slams dipshidiot</Title><Msg>Ron Paul declines a speaking spot at GOP convention after Romney demands to review remarks Last edited Sun Aug 26, 2012, 02:38 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Source: Houston Chronicle The libertarian Republican presidential candidate says he’s declined an opportunity to speak at the Republican National Convention in Tampa because Mitt Romney’s campaign imposed two conditions on any Paul speech — that it be reviewed by the nominee-to-be’s team and that it include an endorsement without hesitation or reservation. “It wouldn’t be my speech,” the Texas congressman told the New York Times. “That would undo everything I’ve done in the last 30 years. I don’t fully endorse him for president.” Pundits noted that the uncompromising attitude that has won Paul a national following also limits his clout within the GOP. “Uncompromising and perfectly willing to operate on the margins of mainstream politics for decades, Ron Paul proved unable to take his liberty message to a broader audience,” Charlie Mahtesian wrote today in Politico. “Even this year, at the height of his national influence and popularity, the Texas congressman failed to win the popular vote in a single state and never seriously threatened to win the GOP nomination.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346011121644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346015142056-22</Id><Title>How in the f is odufus going to defend</Title><Msg>15% unemployment. Other than not talking about it. Friggin jimmy carter in a wheel chair and alzheimers would wax him at the polls</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346015142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346015569140-23</Id><Topic><Title>FLA Gov. endorses BO</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345994847489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Charlie. So wildly popular in Florida, couldn't win more than 30% of the votes to gain US Senate seat. Most of Floridians know him as pure political snake with no core. Is that Obama's last hope to gain some traction in Sunshine state?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346015569140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:12:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346015686946-24</Id><Topic><Title>FLA Gov. endorses BO</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345994847489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now you know why he is the X governor, nothing worst than a soar loser.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346015686946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346018153833-25</Id><Topic><Title>FLA Gov. endorses BO</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1345994847489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 11:27:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that was the longest line of chit ive seen since the million man march...hehehehe</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346018153833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346019414408-26</Id><Topic><Title>How in the f is odufus going to defend</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346015142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frigging returnusignoramus, This President has created plenty of jobs! The U.S. auto industry is thriving again! U.S. naval bases will run partly on solar power and that means jobs!!! There will not be an overall recovery rather it will occur by region in the U.S.. Many states are doing well!!!</Msg><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1346019414408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 18:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346023552000-27</Id><Title>Jb's, shiny's and clowny's fault</Title><Msg>You kids need to dust off that wallet and send your hero his 3 bucks-- immediately, if not sooner. If you don't, be ready to take the blame for his loss in Nov. Don't think for a second he won't hesitate to blame his army of useful idiots &lt;-- consider yourselves blamed. He gots you cheapskates already penciled in as fall-guys in the event he screws up this reelect bid. This is getting more hilariouser by the day. http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/08/26/Obama-email-if-I-lose-your-fault</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346023552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 19:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026073000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Pat Robertson Says Hurricanes are Caused by Gays</Title><Username>mitt_da_szit</Username><Timestamp>1345955146000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 00:25:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm so glad we dont have a ocean near Traverse City otherwise Side Traxx wood be gone and where would I go to find other gays, I mean guys to play choo choo train wiff me!!! hohobo...heehee</Msg><Username>the_kissimmee_butt_pirate</Username><Timestamp>1346026073000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:07:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026432000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Losing Hard?</Title><Username>paul_alana22</Username><Timestamp>1345983434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 08:17:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Losing Hard? Maybe I can help!!! RU into toy choo choo trains? I have a big caboose and all the Side Traxx guys say I'm loose!!! HeeHee...HoHo!!!</Msg><Username>the_kissimmee_butt_pirate</Username><Timestamp>1346026432000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:13:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346026794402-30</Id><Topic><Title>How in the f is odufus going to defend</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346015142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP whining BO isn't cleaning up their humongus mess fast enough. Not a good enough excuse to let them create another mess with their failed policies.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346026794402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:19:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346028117791-31</Id><Topic><Title>How in the f is odufus going to defend</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346015142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I understand ya senile old bass turd, truth hurts don't it, Imagine if there weren't 10 k boomers retiring daily....maybe Odumbo can pull solyndra back out of bk for those solar jobs. Continuously lickin bammys nuts won't make things any better. Keep believing in the auto thing too.</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346028117791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 20:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346033001032-32</Id><Topic><Title>How in the f is odufus going to defend</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346015142056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 17:05:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong! Wrong! Wrong!</Msg><Username>returnuspompus</Username><Timestamp>1346033001032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 22:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346038373000-33</Id><Title>Hurricanes and Ron Paul Block GOP Con Vention</Title><Msg>God hates the GOP. That's obvious. Now Ron Paul is standing in the way. And stupid right wing christians end up with an anti christian Mormon cultist. Too stupid for words.. Hehe. Any vote for a Pub is a vote for oblivion.</Msg><Username>borderxingbeaner</Username><Timestamp>1346038373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 23:32:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>