<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347164567709-1</Id><Topic><Title>Ms. Dipshidiot covers up</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347141496422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repubs cannot answer questions They have no answers Just a rehash of what failed last time. Republicans feel no shame. Although no one mentions Bush. hehe</Msg><Username>chuckiedamanson</Username><Timestamp>1347164567709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347165760847-2</Id><Title>Does anybuddy really care about Da Poor, huh? ...learn more...</Title><Msg>All this Clinton crap and Obama speak complain that Pubs wanna balance da budget on da poor, middle class and seniors. Okay, sumbuddy has to pay-this is a zero sum game here-so, why not Da Poor, Middle Class and Seniors, huh? Look, most likely none of Yinz on this here board are poor, probably not even middle class either. So, why give a flying #$%$ if poor, old people starve homeless in da street, huh? Let em starve, that's less SS and medicare we have to fund, right. Also, when granny and grandpa kick off, err actuarilly matrure, they're gonna leave da grand kids a bundle, which they can blow on hot cars, women, i-phones and tables. JB's bleeding heart poor peoples post doesn't quite work when y'all know JB. JB's a rich SOB. He's sitting on a couple or three million in investments plus over a million in property, and that's what I know about. He's probably hiding stuff, like Romney, and taking advantage of every legal trick for his family and thems that his family manages. Yea, JB &amp;/or spouse do some financial advising sort of stuff. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( JB posts empathy about da poor, but, wouldn't give em da scraps in his garbage can if they were starving. He can vote for Obama simpy because he can aford it. Can YOU, huh? )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1347165760847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 00:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347172772665-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's recovery</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347130923444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still dont quite grasp what -8.9% gdp means I see. Here is another area to study up on, see what percent of GDP is housing related, and how that area is doing after it was raped by republican policies?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1347172772665</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 02:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347190190349-4</Id><Topic><Title>Next Week = $9.20~9.70 price range!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1347048146921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 16:02:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree and it was my reason to buy more than 8,000 etfc shares to sell quickly at 9.50 this week. My stop loss is 8.80 Good luck to all longs. Rebound</Msg><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1347190190349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 07:29:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347190473021-5</Id><Title>Yahoo new format sucks. It is slow like Hell</Title><Msg>I cannot post here like I used to, because I have no hours to be wasted waiting for Yahoo to display messages. Do you agree that they suck? They will ignore our feedback anyway. This new format everybody hates will stay. Good luck with that. Good buy</Msg><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1347190473021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 07:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347193839513-6</Id><Topic><Title>How can the GOP even claim to be christians?</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347156697819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop "cuts to Medicaid "start immediately and cut the program 35 percent by 2022 -- a loss of $810 billion over that time period" and still that doesn't pay for their new tax cuts on top of the bush tax cuts let alone the increased military spending and full medicare and social security for most of the boomers. and since the romney types will be paying even less a percent incomet tax, maybe even zero peercent, who will be making up the difference...........another blind faith gop road to disaster everthing W did.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347193839513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 08:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347197857470-7</Id><Title>Mitt says he will keep a lot of Obamacare</Title><Msg>yep, now Mitt promises to keep a lot of Obamacare, like the end of dumping people with pre-existing conditions by insurers. But does Mitt know that in exchange for ending preexisting condition exclusion the insurers demanded the mandate.?.... you know, the way to PAY for the change...... so now add keeping a lot of the ACA to the list of Romney promises: full medicare and full social security for most of the boomers , and increased military spending , plus more tax cuts on top of the bush tax cuts and this is all deficit reduction?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347197857470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 09:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347211019894-8</Id><Title>I'm still looking for ROWDYRODENT</Title><Msg>There are two possibilities, either Rowdy is absent from this board, or he changed his handle and is hiding behind it. In regard to his 'Obama is toast' I want to make him a bet of $500. I'm betting that President Obama will be reelected. So, Rowdy come out where ever you are.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1347211019894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347211428556-9</Id><Topic><Title>I'm still looking for ROWDYRODENT</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1347211019894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a coward. And he'd never pay up.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1347211428556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:23:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347214235713-10</Id><Topic><Title>I'm still looking for ROWDYRODENT</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1347211019894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 13:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lose your Rodent? Check up yourass</Msg><Username>marthamccallums_bathwater</Username><Timestamp>1347214235713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 14:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347218748727-11</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt says he will keep a lot of Obamacare</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347197857470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 09:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney would say or do anything to get elected...anything. JMO, ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1347218748727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347219979200-12</Id><Title>a republican women speaks up on women and democracy</Title><Msg>"take away women's right to vote..........It's a personal fantasy of mine.' ann coulter "I think women should should not vote " ann coulter "It would be a much better country if women did not vote. That is simply a fact" ann coulter</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347219979200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347222208277-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's recovery</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347130923444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I get is that you can't comperhend that your boys policies have failed to do what he promised...period.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347222208277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347222844421-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's recovery</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347130923444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What was the 'promise' exactly, and while you are at it, look up the date of the 'promise' Then get back to me.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1347222844421</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 16:34:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347224536677-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's recovery</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347130923444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here I will give you a clue, not that it will help you much as you have no grasp of what -8.9% GDP means Q4 2008 GDP: -8.9% (-6.8%, -5.4%)</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1347224536677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225294015-16</Id><Topic><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unimpressive rant filled with baseless statements. Not even a single reference to support your point? Just regurgitating talking points. What’s the use for those 85% number? It isn’t about who released “subprimes” the most, but why. Great number if not most from this 85% ended up in the hands of Fannie &amp; Freddie anyway! And they gladly accepted them. Profit making? Greed? It has been there for centuries. Yet, most of the bankers where doing responsible, reasonable things to keep business going on the long term. Were they greedy? No more than any other time in history. The triggers which made banks to take unreasonable risks cannot be explained by simple desire of obscene profit making. Desire to make more money is always there but it doesn’t push for common practice to take unreasonable risks. Besides, small banks involved in making “subprimes” didn’t make much at all, they were getting rid of them ASAP by solling to large institutions. So, now you blame it on CDO and CDS. But those where only tools to address the problem, making a patch, but not a fix. By no means were they motivating factor. Large financial institutions saw “subprimes” flooding the pool, so they had to do something to make it at least look like a decent product. So, here are undeniable facts: - Fannie &amp; Freddie lowered their loan requirements in the mid 90s, even before Glass-Steagall act was repealed. They started the mess by re-defining standards. It was an affirmative action program in effect only in mortgage business. - Unregulated banks were pressured to give loans to minorities. How? Banks which didn’t comply were sued for discrimination. Even a few of those cases won by ACORN (YES!) sent intimidating message to many other mortgage banks. Small banks couldn’t merge without CRA compliance. Many banks were allowed to issue mortgages only in minority districts. Wells Fargo is a very large “unregulated” bank. In mortgage business for more than a decade. But didn’t suffer 2008 pain, Chase didn’t suffer either. So, here are 2 most prestigious “unregulated” institutions survived the storm, but 2 most prestigious “regulated” went under. - Fannie &amp; Freddie collapsed at exactly same time unregulated did. Which means that “regulated” is an empty word, and regulations were criminally wrong. Both assumptions are correct in my view.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347225294015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:14:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225493710-17</Id><Topic><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"from 2004 to 2006, the two [GSEs] purchased $434 billion in securities backed by subprime loans, creating a market for more such lending."[ “those who seek to deflect criticism of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac by pointing out that private lenders eventually issued most of the worst performing loans ignore the primary role that the GSE's played in expanding the use of subprime loans. In 1999, Franklin Raines first put Fannie Mae into subprimes, following up on earlier Fannie Mae efforts in the 1990's which reduced mortgage down payment requirements. At this time, subprimes represented a tiny fraction of the overall mortgage market. [54] In 2003, after the use of subprimes had been greatly expanded, and numerous private lenders had begun issuing subprime loans as a competitive response to Fannie and Freddie, the GSE's still controlled nearly 50% of all subprime lending. From 2003 forward, private lenders increased their share of subprime lending, and later issued many of the riskiest loans. However, attempts to defend Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac for their role in the crisis, by citing their declining market share in subprimes after 2003, ignore the fact that the GSE's had largely created this market, and even worked closely with some of the worst private lending offenders, such as Countrywide. In 2005, one out of every four loans purchased by Fannie Mae came from Countrywide. [55] Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac essentially paved the subprime highway, down which many others later followed.” “it was the Clinton administration, obsessed with multiculturalism, that dictated where mortgage lenders could lend, and originally helped create the market for the high-risk subprime loans now infecting like a retrovirus the balance sheets of many of Wall Street's most revered institutions.”</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347225493710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225631115-18</Id><Topic><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Banks have been placed in a Catch 22 situation by the CRA: If they comply, they know they will have to suffer from more loan defaults. If they don't comply, they face financial penalties and, worse yet, their business plans for mergers, branch expansions, etc. can be blocked by CRA protesters, which can cost a large corporation like Bank of America billions of dollars. Like most businesses, they have largely buckled under and have surrendered to their bureaucratic masters.” Forbes: “The CRA forces banks to make loans in poor communities, loans that banks may otherwise reject as financially unsound. Under the CRA, banks must convince a set of bureaucracies that they are not engaging in discrimination, a charge that the act encourages any CRA-recognized community group to bring forward. Otherwise, any merger or expansion the banks attempt will likely be denied. But what counts as discrimination? According to one enforcement agency, "discrimination exists when a lender's underwriting policies contain arbitrary or outdated criteria that effectively disqualify many urban or lower-income minority applicants." Note that these "arbitrary or outdated criteria" include most of the essentials of responsible lending: income level, income verification, credit history and savings history--the very factors lenders are now being criticized for ignoring.”</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347225631115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347225739413-19</Id><Topic><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And here goes the big candy: “The government has promoted bad loans not just through the stick of the CRA but through the carrot of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, which purchase, securitize and guarantee loans made by lenders and whose debt is itself implicitly guaranteed by the federal government. This setup created an easy, artificial profit opportunity for lenders to wrap up bundles of subprime loans and sell them to a government-backed buyer whose primary mandate was to "promote homeownership," not to apply sound lending standards.”</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347225739413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 17:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347236783389-20</Id><Title>Dipshidiots have a "secret plan", like Nixon</Title><Msg>Like Nixon's secret plan for peace, Romney and Ryan have a secret plan to bal budget &amp; won't reveal. Romney Refuses To Offer Details On His Tax Plan | Ryan Ditto On Loopholes They Would Cut</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347236783389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 20:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347240096592-21</Id><Title>Dipshidiot seriously confused</Title><Msg>Within Hours, Mitt Romney Takes Back Everything He Said About Preexisting Conditions Source: Mother Jones On national TV this morning, with millions of people watching, Mitt Romney told David Gregory that there were parts of Obamacare he actually liked. In fact, he said, one of the goals of his healthcare plan "is to make sure that those with preexisting conditions can get coverage." A few hours later, with approximately zero people listening, a spokesman quietly "clarified" what he meant: In reference to how Romney would deal with those with preexisting conditions and young adults who want to remain on their parents’ plans, a Romney aide responded that there had been no change in Romney’s position and that “in a competitive environment, the marketplace will make available plans that include coverage for what there is demand for. He was not proposing a federal mandate to require insurance plans to offer those particular features.” As it happens, we already have a competitive market for individual insurance. In addition, we already have demand for coverage of preexisting conditions. And yet, the marketplace doesn't make policies available to people with preexisting conditions. Why? Because policies that cover preexisting conditions are big money losers unless you charge premiums high enough that no one could afford them. Because of that, nobody bothers to offer them in the first place. That's how the free market works. It would be nice if Romney could explain how he intends to square this circle.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347240096592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:21:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347242036695-22</Id><Title>Red states on the dole</Title><Msg>Sun Sep 09, 2012 at 04:00 PM PDT In defense of red state socialism by Jon Perr For most liberals, the Constitution's aspirational goal for "We the people" to "form a more perfect Union" is a guiding statement of American national purpose. Nevertheless, these days many blue staters are growing exasperated with their red state brothers and sisters. After all, the "Southernization" of American politics has helped give conservative policies and politicians an outsized national influence for years. Almost 150 years after the Civil War resolved the issues once and for all, some Republicans still casually traffic in talk of nullification, secession and insurrection. And "states' rights," that pernicious ideological bludgeon first used to deny millions of Americans their freedom for the first century of the Republic and ignore their rights in the second, is now being redeployed to justify preventing a new generation from accessing health care and the ballot box. But almost as galling for many Democrats is the persistent phenomenon of red state socialism. That is, despite Republican paeans to "small government" and "rugged individualism," red states benefit from a one-way flow of dollars from Washington, a federal gravy train disproportionately provided by blue state taxpayers. But hypocrisy or no, that is as it should be. Because when it comes to health care, education, public safety, needed infrastructure and so much else, Americans' mutual commitment to life, liberty and the pursuit of happiness cannot end at the state line. To be sure, red state socialism is real. As a 2007 analysis by the Tax Foundation (above) of federal spending per tax dollar received by state shows, the reddest states generally reaped the most green. (As Politifact rightly noted, the rankings are based on 2005 data. The Tax Foundation is planning an updated study.) Eight of the top 10 beneficiaries of federal largesse voted for John McCain for president. Unsurprisingly, all 15 states at the bottom of the list—those whose outflow of tax revenue is funding programs elsewhere in the country—all voted for Barack Obama in 2008. Alaska's number three ranking was particularly ironic, given Gov. Sarah Palin's farewell message warning her state to "be wary of accepting government largesse; it doesn't come free." But the ironies don't end there. A 2010 map of personal government benefits received versus taxes paid showed secession birthplace South Carolina to be one of the big winners. And as the New York Times documented earlier this year, "even critics of safety net increasingly depend on it." Even, it turns out, Tea Party die-hards Dartmouth Professor Dean Lacy's research concluded that this development has been underway for some time now: Support for Republican candidates, who generally promise to cut government spending, has increased since 1980 in states where the federal government spends more than it collects. The greater the dependence, the greater the support for Republican candidates. Conversely, states that pay more in taxes than they receive in benefits tend to support Democratic candidates. And Professor Lacy found that the pattern could not be explained by demographics or social issues. Apparently, to those who complain loudest about government, much shall be given.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347242036695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347245418979-23</Id><Topic><Title>a republican women speaks up on women and democracy</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347219979200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 15:46:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Coulter wants to deny herself a vote. You should celebrate that. What are you whining about?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347245418979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 22:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347248037053-24</Id><Topic><Title>Red states on the dole</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347242036695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 21:53:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've always said Red States are the biggest socialist whoores</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1347248037053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-09 23:33:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>