<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350273751183-1</Id><Title>Log Cabin Members in Huge Hissy Fit !!!!!</Title><Msg>Slayer and his girlfriends/ multiple ID's are in a posting frenzy.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1350273751183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 00:02:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350277671328-2</Id><Topic><Title>CNN jumps off the sinking ship</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350257264346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 19:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Piers Morgan is not a liberal buffoon, he’s a much larger buffoon than that. At any rate, I wouldn’t take this as much of an endorsement. He would have had to draw direct, specific comparisons between Mitt and Barry, and explained why he preferred Mitt in most cases. That’s just the way the genre works. This piece is more of an attempt to present Piers as balanced because he’s writing about what he considers to be positive attributes. You’re forgetting about not getting too cocky. When Morgan comes out with a full-throttle appeal to the nation to give Bam a second chance, a lot of chins around here will be dropping into keyboards. 44.Machtyn Says: October 14th, 2012 at 9:13 pm</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350277671328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350278085557-3</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Members in Huge Hissy Fit !!!!!</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1350273751183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 00:02:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer is darling himself up for a weekend visit from Larry Craig - tap, tap, tap.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350278085557</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350278085575-4</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Members in Huge Hissy Fit !!!!!</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1350273751183</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 00:02:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer is darling himself up for a weekend visit from Larry Craig - tap, tap, tap.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350278085575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350279142207-5</Id><Topic><Title>dear repelicans please explian mitt's miracle cure for medicare</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350137703335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:15:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifica, You're a constand loser!!!!! Your math skills suck!!!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350279142207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350279142338-6</Id><Topic><Title>dear repelicans please explian mitt's miracle cure for medicare</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350137703335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:15:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifica, You're a constand loser!!!!! Your math skills suck!!!</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350279142338</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350280632709-7</Id><Title>The VP debate</Title><Msg>Eli J Los Angeles At this point it can only be classified as a correlation and not a conclusion but an overnight, post debate social media tracking poll by global information giant SDL, shows a severe drop off in sentiment for Congressman Paul Ryan in the latter 30 minutes of the debate in a key swing state. The poll which measures positive and negative postings on Facebook, Twitter and political blogs saw Mr. Ryan's sentiment score in New Hampshire go from a positive +2.6 in the first hour of the debate to a whopping negative -15.4 in the final 30 minutes of the debate and the thirty minute post debate period. Significantly it was during the end of the debate that the candidates we asked for their opinions on abortion ( see attached release) While other swings state showed a negative second hour trend for Mr, Ryan, none were as steep as New Hampshire's, a state renowned for being fiscally conservative and socially progressive, Overall Mr.Biden won seven of eight swings states, with only a slight loss in the State of Virginia.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1350280632709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 01:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350302966456-8</Id><Topic><Title>Biden's Drug Problem..</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350137957415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drug induced insanity in the White House!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350302966456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 08:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350303146578-9</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo, go Occupy your Copenhagen mansion and stop speaking mooo-sleem!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350303146578</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 08:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350307053562-10</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Benghazi is THE story..getting bigger, more info coming out!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350307053562</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350308002526-11</Id><Title>Mitt's death panel:</Title><Msg>Mitt says an arbitrary price cap is a market-based approach. "Romney/Ryan plan: it arbitrarily limits premium growth to GDP + 0.5% per year" "That's central control every bit as much as any panel of bureaucrats that Barack Obama has ever proposed" (whoops, the market just hiked your co pay, or your deductible or eliminated the procedure..... something has to give if there is a price cap........)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350308002526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350308190361-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Socio-path says you will pay for Healthcare for Illegals (FAIR!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349992786308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DEATH PANEL (15 person non-medical overlords)!! Thanks DUMBO!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350308190361</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350309298817-13</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's death panel:</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350308002526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and to top off mitt's death panel, employee health benefits will be taxed as income.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350309298817</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:54:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350309566826-14</Id><Title>it requires emergency healthcare treatment regardless of citizenship, legal status or ability to pay.</Title><Msg>reagan and the gop created Bushcare, aka. Mittcare: The Emergency Medical Treatment and Active Labor Act (EMTALA)[1] is a U.S. Act of Congress passed in 1986 as part of the Consolidated Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act (COBRA). It requires hospitals to provide care to anyone needing emergency healthcare treatment regardless of citizenship, legal status or ability to pay. There are no reimbursement provisions. Participating hospitals may only transfer or discharge patients needing emergency treatment under their own informed consent, after stabilization, or when their condition requires transfer to a hospital better equipped to administer the treatment.[1]</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350309566826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 09:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350310035612-15</Id><Topic><Title>North Carolina paper for BO</Title><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1350252829625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-14 18:13:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As they should... President Obama is the only clear choice..</Msg><Username>greekislandtaverna</Username><Timestamp>1350310035612</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350310110871-16</Id><Title>Market trader users ?</Title><Msg>Is your dividend % changing with trades today? mine is stuck at wherever the systemm opened.</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1350310110871</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350310467520-17</Id><Title>Giuliani On Romney: "I Have Never Seen A Guy Change His Positions So Many Times"</Title><Msg>Former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani slammed Mitt Romney on MSNBC's "Morning Joe." "I have never seen a guy -- and I've run a lot of elections, supported a lot of people -- I've never seen a guy change his positions on so many things, so fast, on a dime. Everything." Joe Scarborough argues that "Newt has switched pretty quickly on issues as well." "Nothing, absolutely nothing like what Mitt Romney did from governor of Massachusetts to candidate for president," Giuliani responds. "Pro-choice, pro-life. Pro-choice because somebody, a close friend died, and he became pro-choice because this woman died of an abortion. Then he figures out there are embryos, and he changes. He was pro-gun control. Fine. Then he becomes a lifetime member of the NRA. He was pro cap-and-trade. Now he's against cap-and-trade. He was pro-mandate for the whole country, then he becomes anti-mandate and he takes that page out of his book and republishes the book. I could go on and on."</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350310467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350312002630-18</Id><Title>Lyin' Ryan wastes water</Title><Msg>So this is pretty crazy: on Saturday, Paul Ryan planned to have a photo op washing dishes and serving food at a Youngstown, Ohio soup kitchen ... but by the time he arrived, the food had already been served and the dishes had apparently already been done. So he did what any politician in need of a photo op would do—he washed them again, for the benefit of the cameras: YOUNGSTOWN, Ohio — Paul Ryan visited a soup kitchen here Saturday on his way to the airport, but by the time the GOP vice presidential nominee and his family had arrived shortly before noon, the grits, sausage and doughnuts had been served, the hall was empty of patrons and the volunteers appeared to have already cleaned up. [...] Ryan stood at the sink and took some large metal pans that did not appear to be dirty, soaped them up and rinsed them, remarking as the cameras clicked and the TV cameras rolled that he had spent a summer washing dishes when he was younger. “We had a Hobart, though, which was — you get calluses on your fingers because it’s so hot,” he said, referring to the Hobart industrial dishwashing machine. That was The Washington Post's report. Here's what The New York Times reported: Afterward, Mr. Ryan stopped with his wife and children at a nearby soup kitchen. The family put on aprons and washed several large pans, though they did not appear to need washing, according to a pool reporter. There also was no one to serve at the soup kitchen, as breakfast had ended. In Paul Ryan's defense, he's running for office for Pete's sake. And nothing will stop him from trying to convince voters that Mitt Romney and he have the empathy Americans expect in a president and vice president—even if that means wasting everybody's time by washing dishes that don't need to be washed.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350312002630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:40:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350313277861-19</Id><Title>Vote GOP to empower the "thought police'!!</Title><Msg>Mon Mar 14, 2011 at 05:00 AM PDT Iowa Woman Jailed for Thinking about an Abortion by five Sounds far-fetched, right? Well it isn't. The anti-choice zealots aren't content to limiting a woman's access to safe and legal abortion, they're now thought police: Ms. Taylor became light-headed and fell down a flight of stairs in her home. Paramedics rushed to the scene and ultimately declared her healthy. However, since she was pregnant with her third child at the time, Taylor thought it would be best to be seen at the local ER to make sure her fetus was unharmed. That's when things got really bad and really crazy. Alone, distraught, and frightened, Taylor confided in the nurse treating her that she hadn't always been sure she'd wanted this baby, now that she was single and unemployed. She'd considered both adoption and abortion before ultimately deciding to keep the child. The nurse then summoned a doctor, who questioned her further about her thoughts on ending the pregnancy. Next thing Taylor knew, she was being arrested for attempted feticide. Apparently the nurse and doctor thought that Taylor threw herself down the stairs on purpose. Yes, as if Ms. Taylor's existing problems weren't enough, the anti-choice zealots got her jailed for 2 days for thinking of having an abortion, even though she voluntarily went to the ER to assure the health of her fetus. Funny how "pro-lifers" have never met a victim they don't want to punish. After three weeks, the District Attorney declined to prosecute, but not because of the obvious encroachment on a woman's right to choose (similar laws for which this woman was held exist in 37 states), but because she was only in her second trimester, and not third when she fell. No I'm not making this up, and unfortunately Ms. Taylor isn't alone: Last March, Florida resident Samantha Burton was in week 25 of her pregnancy when she paid a visit to her doctor. Burton was showing signs of potential miscarriage, so her physician ordered bed rest. Burton explained that, as a working mother of two toddlers, bed rest simply wasn't a viable option and then proceeded to ask for a second medical opinion. Seems reasonable, right? Her doctor, however, was having none of that. Rather than refer Burton for the desired second opinion, he instead felt it necessary to contact state authorities, who then proceeded to force Burton to be admitted to Tallahassee Memorial Hospital against her will and undergo any procedure the doctor felt like prescribing. When Burton had the audacity to request a change in the hospital in which she was being treated, the court denied her request. Three days into her forced hospitalization, Burton miscarried. Being forced to miscarry in a hospital bed for 3 days, to the anti-choice zealots it's wonderful, who cares about the traumatic effect on the woman and her toddlers left at home? In other news of anti-choice "victories", last March a Pennsylvanian teenager who sought an abortion without parental consent, was denied because the judge found her incapable of making an informed decision, because she had bad grammar: After questioning her for more than an hour, the judge decided that she couldn't have the abortion, ruling she was not mature and capable of making an informed decision about the procedure. The decision surprised her lawyer, Randall McKinney of the Allegheny County Office of Conflict Counsel, because bypass petitions are rarely denied. In his March 24 opinion, Judge Ignelzi wrote that he found the teenager wasn't mature because, among other reasons, she had used bad grammar and had not asked her parents for permission. He also was not persuaded that the teenager's trip overseas several years earlier with her mother demonstrated maturity. His next step was ruling that the abortion was not in the teenager's best interest. Not surprisingly the Judge was endorsed by People Concerned for the Unborn Child and LifePAC of Southwestern Pennsylvania. Somehow the Judge determined she was mature enough to be a mother to a child, but not enough to make her own decisions regarding her reproductive organs. Leave it to "pro-lifers" to make the best choices for the rest of us...even if it means confining a woman to a hospital-bed against her will, jailing them for having thought of an abortion, or denying the choice to a teenager because of her grammar.</Msg><Username>spenditol98_1</Username><Timestamp>1350313277861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350314390688-20</Id><Title>Bain explained by Reagan's budget chief</Title><Msg>Ronald Reagan’s budget director: Romney Is NO Job Creator-He Is A GAMBLER In A Rigged Market Last edited Mon Oct 15, 2012, 10:19 AM USA/ET - Edit history (2) Mitt Romney: The Great Deformer Oct 15, 2012 1:00 AM EDT Is Romney really a job creator? Ronald Reagan’s budget director, David Stockman, takes a scalpel to the claims. Bain Capital is a product of the Great Deformation. It has garnered fabulous winnings through leveraged speculation in financial markets that have been perverted and deformed by decades of money printing and Wall Street coddling by the Fed. So Bain’s billions of profits were not rewards for capitalist creation; they were mainly windfalls collected from gambling in markets that were rigged to rise. ................. ......... Mitt Romney was not a businessman; he was a master financial speculator who bought, sold, flipped, and stripped businesses. He did not build enterprises the old-fashioned way—out of inspiration, perspiration, and a long slog in the free market fostering a new product, service, or process of production. Instead, he spent his 15 years raising debt in prodigious amounts on Wall Street so that Bain could purchase the pots and pans and castoffs of corporate America, leverage them to the hilt, gussy them up as reborn “roll-ups,” and then deliver them back to Wall Street for resale—the faster the better. ....................... The Bain Capital investments here reviewed accounted for $1.4 billion or 60 percent of the fund’s profits over 15 years, by my calculations. Four of them ended in bankruptcy; one was an inside job and fast flip; one was essentially a massive M&amp;A brokerage fee; and the seventh and largest gain—the Italian Job—amounted to a veritable freak of financial nature. In short, this is a record about a dangerous form of leveraged gambling that has been enabled by the failed central banking and taxing policies of the state. That it should be offered as evidence that Mitt Romney is a deeply experienced capitalist entrepreneur and job creator is surely a testament to the financial deformations of our times.</Msg><Username>spenditol98_1</Username><Timestamp>1350314390688</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350316731243-21</Id><Title>SCHW Trading revenue daown 19%</Title><Msg>how much here</Msg><Username>pocheca5</Username><Timestamp>1350316731243</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350321368550-22</Id><Title>$7.50 is coming soon! EOM</Title><Msg>$7.50 is coming soon! EOM</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350321368550</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 13:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350323957913-23</Id><Title>What a pair</Title><Msg>The incompetent and corrupt community organizer and junior senator from Chicago, and the manic depressant life long bureaucrat hiena Joe(you'all)Biden running things,,,and is it any wonder why we are in the mess were in. Which reinforces the quote by P. T. Barnum...."You will never go broke under estimating the intelligence of the American people."</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350323957913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350325361781-24</Id><Topic><Title>What a pair</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350323957913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 13:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 'Commie' and the 'Crazy'!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350325361781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:22:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350327518619-25</Id><Topic><Title>Biden's Drug Problem..</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350137957415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next up, Candy's 'Food' problem..Angry lezz-boo. Another stacking against President Romney!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350327518619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 14:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350330444249-26</Id><Topic><Title>Essential ETFC News - Check it Out Right Now!</Title><Username>kirbymolina42</Username><Timestamp>1350303739427</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 08:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well spammer boy, your momma is on the CDC's HIGH ALERT list for that very unfortunate diseased "hoo haw". For more info, check out cdc.gov.</Msg><Username>irush59</Username><Timestamp>1350330444249</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 15:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350330752078-27</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can ETFC Last??</Title><Username>fitzgeraldstokes197</Username><Timestamp>1350136743014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spammer boy....your momma was quite explosive all night as well....released on more than one occasion. She dipped down on me as well. I was smart and had protection. Quit posting this crap and post on another board....douche. Speaking of that...pls tell your momma to do the same...quite a stench she carries.</Msg><Username>irush59</Username><Timestamp>1350330752078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 15:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350330866781-28</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heelory just left for PERU!! Total cover-up delay! Where the 'F' is she??</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350330866781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 15:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350332478456-29</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs, read this again.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350332478456</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350332478870-30</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs, read this again.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350332478870</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350332624632-31</Id><Topic><Title>Vote GOP to empower the "thought police'!!</Title><Username>spenditol98_1</Username><Timestamp>1350313277861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 11:01:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP still needs to admit the HUGE costs of eliminating the million per year U.S. abortions. By definition, it adds one million unwanted kids to the population per year, easily costing the country hundreds of $Billions.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350332624632</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:23:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350332735923-32</Id><Title>The Presidents priorities</Title><Msg>**Naturally, a feud of such magnitude was top of mind when the president called in to radio host Michael Yo's "The Yo Show,"** You have a dead ambassador, two dead Navy Seals, and a civilian dead in Benghazi, and this is where his focus is. He needs to come clean on what happened and the subsequent cover up... This man is an embarrassment, or is Obama just being Obama. President Obama thinks Nicki Minaj, Mariah Carey can sort out 'Idol' feud The President of the United States has weighed in on the greatest feud of our time. And by that we mean yes, Barack Obama has commented on the on-set tensions between "American Idol" hosts Nicki Minaj and Mariah Carey. If you recall, during a recent taping of the show Minaj unleashed a slew of not-safe-for-primetime words at Carey; Carey later countered with claims that Minaj threatened to "shoot" her (a claim Minaj has denied). Naturally, a feud of such magnitude was top of mind when the president called in to radio host Michael Yo's "The Yo Show," and in a display of diplomacy we've come to know well from Obama, the president does not take a clear side on the feud, but he's optimistic everything will be OK in the end.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350332735923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350332886548-33</Id><Topic><Title>The Presidents priorities</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350332735923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:25:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Dumbo 'Teachable Moment!"</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350332886548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350332949502-34</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary in PERU!!! Total criminal!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350332949502</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350332961796-35</Id><Title>In 1983 17 Americans were killed in Lebanon and at the time Reagan was our Prez.</Title><Msg>Sometimes, situation are beyond human control.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350332961796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350333094370-36</Id><Topic><Title>In 1983 17 Americans were killed in Lebanon and at the time Reagan was our Prez.</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350332961796</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for Dumbo-Cover up1</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350333094370</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:31:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350334778293-37</Id><Topic><Title>DUMBO! RESIGN NOW!! (cover up!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348936321730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary ran off to Peru! (Huma Lick-athon!) Criminal coverup!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350334778293</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 16:59:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350334939047-38</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs, read this again.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350334939047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350335436786-39</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals, please read this again!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350335436786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350336892215-40</Id><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Msg>It is too late for him to be capable or well-informed. Can't be a clear thinker. At this late date, can't learn to speak well without a teleprompter and a hall full of teachers/liberal arts majors/welfare recipients/union members/limousine liberals. But it is not too late to pout and shout. Let the anger fly, Obama. You are the man or something like it.</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350337801411-41</Id><Topic><Title>Was it just a matter of time?</Title><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1323386684000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-12-08 18:24:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't that the same guy the tapped a hose into a methane pipe and tried to convience Americans that the methane came out of his water well... EPA is set to kill American as that is Obama's goals. Oh yea, I think Reagan sent a squad of bombers all the way from American to kill the ugly dude but only killed one of his 50 kids.</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1350337801411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350340943918-42</Id><Title>Why In The World - Did They Blame The Embassy Attack On a Video?</Title><Msg>it is comical that the administration ran around for weeks apologizing for a video. it looks more foolish as each day goes by.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350340943918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 18:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350341825056-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why In The World - Did They Blame The Embassy Attack On a Video?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350340943918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 18:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Dumbo's SICK-O totalitrian world, The 'First Admendment' needs to GO! The 'Video' was a great way to push: 'Tolerence' and ultimately 'Hate Speech' censorship like they have in Europe and Canada. How dare anyone say ANYTHING bad about moo-sleems and they way they rape and beat women!! But they got caught and kept doubling down. Meanwhile we have 4 DEAD Americans. 'Watergate' never killed anyone!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350341825056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 18:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350342433166-44</Id><Topic><Title>Why In The World - Did They Blame The Embassy Attack On a Video?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350340943918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 18:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your reason is as good as any. other possibilities? 1) so out of touch and inept that they actually believed a video was the root cause 2) thought they could spin the blame to the video - to lessen damage to their re-election - beleiving the masses are too dumb to catch on</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350342433166</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350342752936-45</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I think slayer is q4bike" It means 'queer for bikers'</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1350342752936</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350342914156-46</Id><Topic><Title>Why In The World - Did They Blame The Embassy Attack On a Video?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350340943918</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 18:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not good to lie, spin, cover up...especially when they got soooo caught. Susan Rice, 5 days later spinning the video. State dept, under oath, had real time interaction with embassy during attack at 4:40pm our time...September 11th! When your in a hole...STOP DIGGING. The 4 DEAD Americans is what makes the story sooo horrible with respect to the ongoing cover up. This is why Hillary just left for PERU! Sick!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350342914156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350343120924-47</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary in Peru, grinding on the dance floor with 300 pound Leez-bo indians with Huma da' Licker!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1350343120924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350345386919-48</Id><Title>Oh my: Gallup shows Romney leading by five — in swing states</Title><Msg>posted at 5:22 pm on October 15, 2012 by Allahpundit Like Chuck Todd said this morning, “Structural shift.” A safe prediction for tomorrow night: You’re going to hear a lot about the “47 percent” and a lot lot lot about the “war on women.” As the presidential campaign heads into its final weeks, the survey of voters in 12 crucial swing states finds female voters much more engaged in the election and increasingly concerned about the deficit and debt issues that favor Romney. The Republican nominee now ties the president among women who are likely voters, 48%-48%, while he leads by 12 points among men… “In every poll, we’ve seen a major surge among women in favorability for Romney” since his strong performance in the first debate, veteran Democratic pollster Celinda Lake says. “Women went into the debate actively disliking Romney, and they came out thinking he might understand their lives and might be able to get something done for them.”… Now, the USA TODAY/Gallup Poll shows Romney leading Obama 51%-46% among likely voters in the swing states. Men who are likely voters back him 54%-42%. The states are Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Michigan, Nevada, New Hampshire, New Mexico, North Carolina, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Virginia and Wisconsin… When women were asked to identify the most important issue for women, though, the answers were strikingly different. The top concern by far was abortion, an issue that didn’t even register among men. Nearly four in 10 women cited it, and those who did supported Obama by more than 3-1. Fifteen percent cited equal rights, pay or opportunity. There’s an enthusiasm gap among women voters too, with 46 percent saying they’re “extremely enthusiastic” to vote for Mitt versus 38 percent who say so about O. (Married women, who trend Republican, are also more enthusiastic than singles.) You’ll be pleased to know that Team Hopenchange has already wet itself over these results and is circulating a memo written by their pollster dumping on Gallup’s likely voter screen. I’m intrigued that they’re so eager to bat this down with the next debate 28 hours away. Even if this is an outlier, they’ll benefit if the next poll is taken after the debate and shows the race tighter, which would lend itself to an “Obama comeback” narrative. They must be awfully nervous about perceptions taking hold in the electorate that O’s a loser beyond even the power of the next debate to change. And if you read Sean Trende’s piece last week, you know why: Constructing a sense of inevitability has always been their best defense against the forces of political “gravity.” Once that sense is shattered and Romney becomes plausible, they start to melt. The danger for Obama now, I think, is that he’s lost control of his own destiny. He’ll light into Romney tomorrow night but I don’t know how much harm it’ll do, especially since Mitt will be well prepared for the “47 percent” attack. Romney’s task was, and is, to show he’s a plausible president, and that depends much more on his own answers (and demeanor) than it does on Obama’s. If “President Romney” seems viable, gravity can do the rest. Update: A few swing-state odds and ends for you as gravy. A Romney aide told Byron York that their internal polls show Ohio dead even; ARG sees a dead heat in Iowa too. Meanwhile, PPP found Romney up two points in North Carolina — based on a D+10 sample. As Tony Lee says, lights out.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350345386919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350345412912-49</Id><Title>Just a few more weeks</Title><Msg>To put up with shitferbrains as president.... The etarded bored will be under severe duress.... They can morn with their queen leader pelosi</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350345412912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350346929199-50</Id><Topic><Title>Giuliani On Romney: "I Have Never Seen A Guy Change His Positions So Many Times"</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350310467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:14:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rudi can't seem to recall describing the Dipshidiot like that, curious.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350346929199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350347149953-51</Id><Topic><Title>Lyin' Ryan wastes water</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350312002630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 10:40:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Report: Charity President Objects To Paul Ryan’s Soup Kitchen Photo Op Last edited Mon Oct 15, 2012 Brian J. Antal, the president of an Ohio charity for the homeless, is objecting to a photo op staged by the Romney campaign on Saturday that featured vice presidential running mate Paul Ryan washing pots and pans that had already appeared to be clean, Felicia Sonmez of the Washington Post reports: “We’re a faith-based organization; we are apolitical because the majority of our funding is from private donations,” Antal said in a phone interview Monday afternoon. “It’s strictly in our bylaws not to do it. They showed up there and they did not have permission. They got one of the volunteers to open up the doors.” He added: “The photo-op they did wasn’t even accurate. He did nothing. He just came in here to get his picture taken at the dining hall.” ..... “Had they asked for permission, it wouldn’t have been granted. … But I certainly wouldn’t have let him wash clean pans and then take a picture,” Antal told the Post.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350347149953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350347807777-52</Id><Title>Aide to Dipshidiot's daddy trashes the unworthy spawn!!</Title><Msg>Longtime Aide to George Romney rips Mitt Romney October 15, 2012, 5:22 PM Romney Is Attacked by His Father’s Longtime Aide A longtime aide to George W. Romney issued a harshly worded critique of Mitt Romney, accusing him of shifting political positions in “erratic and startling ways” and failing to live up to the distinguished record of his father, the former governor of Michigan. Walter De Vries, who worked for the senior Mr. Romney throughout the 1960s, wrote that Mitt Romney’s bid for the White House was “a far cry from the kind of campaign and conduct, as a public servant, I saw during the seven years I worked in George Romney’s campaigns and served him as governor.” “While it seems that Mitt would say and do anything to close a deal – or an election,” he wrote, “George Romney’s strength as a politician and public officeholder was his ability and determination to develop and hold consistent policy positions over his life.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350347807777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350348478132-53</Id><Title>More classic GOP family values</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- The anti-abortion Tennessee congressman and doctor who admitted last week to an affair with a patient was hit with an ethics complaint Monday. The Huffington Post revealed the relationship between Republican Rep. Scott DesJarlais and the patient last week, printing details from a transcript of a phone call from 2000 in which he pressured the woman to get an abortion. Desjarlais admitted to the x-rated doctor-patient romps in an email to supporters, but denied the woman had gotten pregnant, in spite of a long conversation in which the two bicker over whether or not he should accompany her to an abortion clinic in Atlanta. The woman would have been about four months pregnant at the time, according to the email DesJarlais sent defending his actions in the affair. DesJarlais, who now casts himself as a family-values Republican, also said the relationship was entirely consensual and that he had an open relationship with his then-wife, Susan. The two had been trying to fix their faltering marriage at the time, according to court records, and the reconciliation collapsed shortly after the abortion discussion was recorded. A judge declared DesJarlais' indiscretions had started the marriage down the path to dissolution, beginning in 1998 when his wife alleged improper marital conduct by her spouse. DesJarlais admitted to four affairs in court papers. The complaint filed Monday by the group Citizens for Responsibility and Ethics in Washington argues that regardless of whether both parties wanted the relationship, it violates a state ethics law barring any sexual relations between doctors and patients. HuffPost noted the law in a story last week. “Tennessee law is crystal clear: Doctors are prohibited from engaging in sexual relationships with patients," said Melanie Sloan, the head of CREW. "The only question remaining is, now that Tennessee authorities are aware of Rep. DesJarlais’ blatantly unethical and scurrilous conduct, what are they going to do about it?” In a letter to the Tennessee Board of Medical Examiners, Sloan argues that the case merits an immediate investigation and sanctions, solely based on what DesJarlais has admitted. “It is hard to imagine behavior much more craven than a married doctor exploiting his position to conduct a sexual relationship with a patient," Sloan said in a statement accompanying the press release about the complaint. "It is mind-boggling that when confronted with the patient/mistress’s possible pregnancy, this ardent pro-lifer urged her to have an abortion. How much hypocrisy can we stand? Where is Speaker John Boehner’s much-touted zero tolerance for unethical conduct now?” Boehner tapped DesJarlais to lead a pro forma session of Congress last week, but has not commented on the tawdry affair.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350348478132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350348592852-54</Id><Topic><Title>More classic GOP family values</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350348478132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:47:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzz z z z z zzz yawn zzzzz z z z z z zz</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350348592852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350348906002-55</Id><Topic><Title>Aide to Dipshidiot's daddy trashes the unworthy spawn!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350347807777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:36:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzz z z z zzzz yawn zzz zzzz zzz zz</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350348906002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350349002758-56</Id><Title>Paging Jack Abramoff!!</Title><Msg>POLITICO By ANNA PALMER | 10/15/12 1:56 PM EDT President Barack Obama’s gone further than any president to keep lobbyists out of the White House — even signing executive orders to do it. But the mood on K Street is brightening. Industry insiders believe that Mitt Romney will unshackle the revolving door and give lobbyists a shot at the government jobs their Democratic counterparts have been denied for the past four years, a dozen Republican lobbyists said in conversations with POLITICO. "I've heard they are likely not to black ball anybody from any particular sector," said Republican lobbyist Sam Geduldig at Clark, Lytle &amp; Geduldig. "I assume, everyone is welcome to apply. I'm sure they are interested in getting the best people possible." Allowing lobbyists back into the White House could be a PR nightmare early on in a new administration, some Republicans fear. Romney would have to toss out Obama’s orders, which shook up how President George W. Bush did business and let Obama claim his agenda wouldn’t be hijacked by special interests. Sources close to Romney’s campaign say there has been no official word from the campaign on what the rules about lobbyists in the administration will be. And Romney himself has said nothing definitive on the trail about the issue. But there are clear signs that lobbyists could be back in the executive branch. (Also on POLITICO: Ryan's got plenty of friends on K St.) Some of the highest-level positions in a potential Romney administration are expected be filled by former lobbyists and Washington insiders. Health care consultant Mike Leavitt, who served as the head of the Environmental Protection Agency for Bush, is leading Romney’s transition effort. He’s considered a shoo-in for either White House chief of staff or Treasury Secretary. Campaign spokesman Kevin Madden, of JDAFrontline, is expected to get the job of White House spokesman. Other senior campaign advisers are former lobbyists, as well, including Ron Kaufman, a former lobbyist at Dutko Worldwide, and Drew Maloney, who left Ogilvy Government Relations to lead Romney's congressional outreach. Romney's campaign has also relied heavily on K Streeters to organize high-dollar fundraisers, including David Tamasi of Rasky Baerlein Strategic Communications, Jack Gerard of the American Petroleum Institute, Wayne Berman and Mark Isakowitz of Fierce, Isakowitz &amp; Blalock. A Romney spokeswoman did not respond to requests for comment. Romney’s transition team is beginning to draw up the qualifications for senior-level jobs in a potential Romney administration, putting an emphasis on corporate and industry experience — no surprise considering Romney’s own background as the former CEO of Bain Capital. "There's no question this will be a CEO president who will greatly valuate the contribution of people in business versus academia," said Ivan Adler, a headhunter with McCormick Group. "There will be a 180 degree switch with a Romney administration. The welcome mat will be put out."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350349002758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350349051802-57</Id><Topic><Title>Paging Jack Abramoff!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350349002758</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:56:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzz zzz z z z zz yawn zz z z zzzzzzz</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350349051802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 20:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350352024536-58</Id><Topic><Title>Oh my: Gallup shows Romney leading by five — in swing states</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350345386919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 19:56:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alla akbar ! GOD DAMN AMERIKKA !!! VIVA SUPREME LEADER BARAKA HUSSEINI OBOMBA !!!</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1350352024536</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 21:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350352147781-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have the best Marxist trained Muslim Prezidunce !!!!! GOD DAMN AMERIKKKA !!!!</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1350352147781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 21:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350355688158-60</Id><Title>Schwab also announced it's buying smaller asset manager ThomasPartners for $85 million upfront, and the possibility of milestone payments based on future growth in assets under management.</Title><Msg>Wellesley, Mass.-based ThomasPartners managed $2.3 billion in assets as of Sept. 30, in largely growth-oriented investment portfolios designed to generate dividend income streams. Using a similar metric - what would be the value of the $200+ billion in assets managed by Etrade?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350355688158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 22:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350356759270-61</Id><Title>ATTN GOP SENATORS: Walmart Is The Largest Food Stamp Recipient In The Country—Fine Them!</Title><Msg>Wed Jun 20, 2012 at 09:45 AM PDT by jillwklausen While our nation still reels from the economic crisis brought on by irresponsible Republican fiscal policies that saw millions of jobs being lost, the middle class being decimated, and a nearly unprecedented rise in poverty rates (only the Great Depression rivals it), our elected Representatives in the United States Senate are voting to reduce funding for the only source of sustenance for millions of impoverished Americans: Food Stamps. Trimming back on eligibility for the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program, or SNAP, as food stamps are called, would save $4 billion over the decade. Republicans are pushing to reduce that even more. ... "Is the benefit going to the right people? Is the money being expended wisely?" questioned Sen. Jeff Sessions (R-Ala.), who has led efforts to change the program, during a recent Senate speech. "Is it encouraging people to look for ways to be productive and be responsible for their families? Or does it create dependency on a series of government programs?" Senator Sessions, that question is offensive. It's especially offensive when you recognize that a significant number of Americans who rely on Food Stamps to feed their families, are working full-time but are not being paid enough by their employers to survive on. So of course the benefit isn't going to "the right people," or being "spent wisely," because it's going to line the pockets of billionaires and their billion-dollar corporations! So we have a question for you, Senator Sessions: » When will Republicans in Congress take up legislation that imposes severe fines on mulit-billion dollar corporations who line their pockets at the expense of taxpayers by refusing to pay their employees a 2012 wage and use government programs to supplement their payrolls? -------------------- Citizens from whom Walmart is stealing to pay their employees want our money back from WALMART, not starving children. Here's what Walmart's intentionally low wages are costing hard-working taxpayers like us: Walmart's intentionally low wages force hard-working employees to need approximately $420,000 per year, per store, totalling $2.66 BILLION annually in Food Stamps and other taxpayer assistance ... to survive. Walmart's intentionally low wages cost the country HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS of dollars in payroll tax deductions for Federal, State, and Local taxes. Walmart's intentionally low wages cost our communities the ability to hire and retain important public service workers like firefighters, police officers, maintenance workers, and teachers. Walmart's intentionally low wages cost our communities with their increased need for those same public services they are underfunding. Walmart's intentionally low wages and lack of covered benefits cost taxpayers over $1.02 BILLION a year in healthcare costs. Walmart's intentionally low wages cost taxpayers as much as $225 MILLION in free and reduced price lunches for school-age children. Walmart's intentionally low wages cost taxpayers over $780 MILLION in tax deductions for low-income families. And that's just some of the burden placed on taxpayers by Walmart's intentionally low wages. That's not Welfare for People, That's Welfare for Walmart at The People's expense!</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350356759270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350357378254-62</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are exactly what we expect from all republicans</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1350357378254</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350358473351-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is kindergarten out yet???</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350358473351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350358473387-64</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is kindergarten out yet???</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350358473387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350358473506-65</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to be Angry</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1350336892215</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 17:34:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is kindergarten out yet???</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350358473506</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-15 23:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>