<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343103214000-1</Id><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Msg>1) our potential inability to maintain profitability; 2) potential increases in our provision for loan losses if the residential real estate and credit markets deteriorate beyond our expectations; 3) our potential inability to manage the credit risk in our loan portfolio; 4) our potential inability to retain our current customer assets and accounts; 5) our potential inability to service our substantial indebtedness and, if necessary, to raise sufficient additional capital, and the potential negative regulatory consequences that may result therefrom; 6) our dependence on dividends from our subsidiaries, which are subject to advance regulatory approval in the case of our most significant subsidiaries; 7) liabilities and costs associated with investigations and lawsuits, including those relating to our losses from mortgage loans and asset-backed securities; 8) our potential inability to compete effectively; 9) adverse changes in general economic conditions, including fluctuations in interest rates; 10) our potential inability to manage the effects of changes in interest rates; 11) adverse changes in governmental regulations or enforcement practices, including those that may result from the implementation and enforcement of recently enacted regulatory reform legislation; 12) our potential inability to fully realize our deferred tax assets and the potential loss of a significant portion of our U.S. federal and state deferred tax assets as a result of a deemed “ownership change” in 2009; and 13) other factors described elsewhere in this prospectus or in our current and future filings with the SEC. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Actually Pilgrims, it's item 13 that Yinz should worry about, trust Da Bear on this. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343105711000-2</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ETFC is going $7.50+ tomorrow!! Market turns green and rally!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343105711000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343105969000-3</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$10.60 by Q3-CC!! Mark this!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343105969000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343106225000-4</Id><Title>ETFC is worth at least $4.5 billion!!</Title><Msg>$16 per share will be paid, if acquired!! I already figured out..!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343106225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343106614000-5</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, um, they're listing all the possible things that could go wrong. Basically: "If the economy tanks again, then it will adversely affect our company." Duh. If you think, for instance, that "residential real estate will deteriorate beyond expectations," then you should maintain your short position on ETFC. However, if you believe that the real estate market has bottomed out and has begun to slowly recover (which, btw, is what ALL available data indicate) then having a long position is the smarter choice. C YAZ - Da Bear's Dumb [RLYDUM] (This, pilgrims, iz where I's put one more dumb comment as a parenthetical, just in case you wuz wundering whether or not I'm really that dumb. I is.)</Msg><Username>aaron2874</Username><Timestamp>1343106614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343107344000-6</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gap to $8.20 will be filled very soon!!!!! Short-squeezing is coming!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343107344000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343107953000-7</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree. Even the lowest of lowball buyout offers ($2.5b) would bump the stock up to $8.75. But even without a buyout, the outlook is positive. It's a profitable company making steady progress chipping away at it's one negative, the loan exposure.</Msg><Username>aaron2874</Username><Timestamp>1343107953000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343108586000-8</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is worth at least $4.5 billion!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343106225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was worth at least $10 billion before the financial crisis!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343108586000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343126052000-9</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bear, check out the article headlined "Home Prices Reflect Strengthening" in the WSJ today and study the graphs. Not only are home prices begining to rebound, the number of past due loans is declining across the board, after peaking in Q4, 2009. Even in the hardest hit markets like Las Vegas, Phoenix, and Atlanta (where past due loans peaked at 26%, 19% and 18% respectively) the situation has dramatically improved (now 16%, 9%, and 14%, respectively). Yinz better cover your shorts before yinz get caught in da squeeze. C-Yaz.</Msg><Username>aaron2874</Username><Timestamp>1343126052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 06:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343132865000-10</Id><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Msg>one of the ways they wrecked the recovery is described here: In 2011, congressional Republicans came closer than ever before to breaching the debt ceiling and setting off a global financial crisis. .........they pulled back moments before we toppled into the abyss. But by then, they had already done serious damage to the recovery. Early in 2011, the economy seemed to be gathering momentum. In February, it added 220,000 jobs. In March, it added 246,000 jobs. In April, 251,000 jobs. But as markets began to take the Republican threats on the debt ceiling more seriously, the economy sputtered. Between May and August, the nation never added more than 100,000 jobs a month. And then, in September, the month after the debt ceiling was resolved, the economy sped back up and added more than 200,000 jobs.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343133884000-11</Id><Title>ETFC Attractive Here</Title><Msg>4 the FBI 4 Lawsuits 4 Satan AS I Gymmy Kramir veered in2 E-Trade and Fidelity yesterday with Daarck Knight we saw The women ALL happily mounted by Dobermans and German Shepards. The men all happily mounting each other and each wearing Satans pearl necklace.</Msg><Username>gymmykramir</Username><Timestamp>1343133884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:44:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343134068000-12</Id><Topic><Title>13 things E-Tub BTOs thinks Yinz should worry about ...more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343103214000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 00:13:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aaron{M], I don't usually reply to Mushrooms, however, I'll make a brief comment that's probably far more than yer little mind can comprehend, okay? It's not just da real estate market, it's da economy stupid! Revenue guidance, it's a crapper. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Y'all need a macroscope, not an electron microscope, get it? )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343134068000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:47:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343139052000-13</Id><Title>Willard's "global reach"</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney Mitt Romney has earned a lot of income overseas. WASHINGTON -- Mitt Romney accumulated more than $25 million in foreign income between 2005 and 2010, while he was governor of Massachusetts and a presidential candidate, according to an analysis of his 2010 tax return. The 2010 return lists foreign tax payments Romney made dating back to 2000. By Romney standards, the payments were modest through 2004, averaging $37,000 a year. In 2005, however, his foreign tax bill shot up to $333,149 and stayed high for the next three years, before dipping in 2009, as the financial crisis hit hard. In 2010, Romney's foreign tax bill was down to $67,173 on declared foreign income of $1,525,982. That's a 4.4 percent rate. After expenses and various other deductions, Romney declared a net foreign income of $392,000, making his net tax rate 17 percent. Because the presumptive GOP presidential nominee has so far declined to release his earlier tax returns, HuffPost made a rough calculation of his prior foreign earnings by assuming he paid similar tax rates in previous years. Using that analysis, paying $333,000 in taxes would translate into gross foreign income of $7.5 million in 2005, or net income of $1.9 million. Even using the much-reduced net income figure, Romney would have earned $7 million in foreign income from 2005 to 2010. Romney was elected governor of Massachusetts in 2002 and served a four-year term, during which time he took no paycheck from the state. He began running for president while still governor and continued until early 2008. On the campaign trail in 2011, he joked with a Florida voter that he was unemployed. But unemployment for Romney looks a lot more lucrative than it does for most Americans. "That may be one of the reasons they don't want to release the returns ... they don't want people to see that income," said Rebecca Wilkins, an attorney with Citizens for Tax Justice. Romney and Bain Capital, the private equity firm he founded, have profited by setting up offshore investment vehicles and shipping American jobs overseas. The money from those activities has continued to flow to Romney long after he claims to have retired in 1999 from Bain, as evidenced by his tax returns. One Bain investment that has been profitable for Romney, for example, is Sensata Technologies. The company is planning to shutter its Freeport, Ill., factory by November and move production to China. The soon-to-be-unemployed workers have pleaded with Romney to use his influence over Bain to stave off the closure. Romney has so far declined to do so. Instead, Romney has transferred $170,000 worth of Sensata stock he owns to a charity he controls, a move that gave him a sizable tax deduction. The Obama campaign has made Bain's offshoring efforts a top campaign issue, releasing a brutal ad overlaying Romney's outsourcing record atop a rendition of "America the Beautiful." During an interview with the National Review, Romney said that sub-companies in the Cayman Islands help foreign investors avoid paying taxes on investments in the United States. Bain Capital currently has 138 sub-companies headquartered in the Cayman Islands. "The so-called offshore account in the Cayman Islands, for instance, is an account established by a U.S. firm to allow foreign investors to invest in U.S. enterprises and not be subject to taxes outside of their own jurisdiction," Romney said. "So in many instances, the investments in something of that nature are brought back into the United States. The world of finance is not as simple as some would have you believe. Sometimes a foreign entity is formed to allow foreign investors to invest in the United States, which may well be the case with the entities that Democrats are describing as foreign accounts."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343139052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140161000-14</Id><Topic><Title>You should pull this up (ETFC)</Title><Username>masakocvu4358</Username><Timestamp>1343053948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 10:32:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just received your first email. It's very informational. Love it.</Msg><Username>garryabelmannn968</Username><Timestamp>1343140161000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140448000-15</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's quite a reach there. But understandably hatched out of desperation and necessity, since the blame Bush mantra has lost its effectiveness. Let history show that the only downgrade ever of US debt happened on the experiment's watch. Brak will be known bof for that and his ears.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343140448000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:34:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>30</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140741000-16</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is worth at least $4.5 billion!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343106225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back up the second truck already. PPS is trading below lower BB for the second day and certainly could continue. There has been very little demand since $11. Continued lower highs and lower lows. The market is still looking for fair value. Absent a buyout the least path of resistance is DOWN! imho</Msg><Username>dswanhmsk</Username><Timestamp>1343140741000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343140770000-17</Id><Title>Bought SKM @ 13.41</Title><Msg>But I could be wrong. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343140770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140890000-18</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the gop tantrum over the debt ceiling sabotaged the recovery and it's obvious to see. Also obvious that was their intention too, since they have already promised not to honor the deal they made to resolve the issue; and Mitt as has said that he will make no spending cuts in 2012 if elected, so there you go, his deficit will be larger than ever. 2011 feb........220,000 jobs added mar......246,000 jobs apr........251,000 gop begins its sabotage over the debt ceiling, threatening default. may..... less than 100K june...less than 100K july...less than 100K august... less than 100K jobs added debt ceiling resolved sep... over 200,000 added jeez........ nice work gop</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343140890000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343140942000-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's an interesting theory. All we have to do to help economy is to add few more trillions to the debt. Well of course. What the money is? - Just paper. So, lets do printing!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343140942000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>29</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141187000-20</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC is worth at least $4.5 billion!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343106225000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 01:03:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stevie has no friends with money. Those are very important. Nothing to support the stock as big funds just keep trimming positions and hedgie's shorting the stock every day and cashing in. The 50dma has moved down to around $8. Would not take much to push it above and reverse the trend. Not likely near term.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343141187000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141361000-21</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBIMBO FRAUD - shifting unemployment to disability! Highest level of disability collected in history under incompetent OBIMBO!!! The campaigner in THIEF! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343141361000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>24</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343141370000-22</Id><Title>Willard, unclear on the concept</Title><Msg>"The New Hampshire business featured in Romney's new commercial is the poster company for government aid. In the commercial, the business owner says: "My father’s hands didn’t build this company? My hands didn’t build this company? My son’s hands aren’t building this company?" A good line, but still no John Galt! The New Hampshire Union Leader’s John DiStato today reports that in 1999 the business in question, Gilchrist Metal, “received $800,000 in tax-exempt revenue bonds issued by the New Hampshire Business Finance Authority ‘to set up a second manufacturing plant and purchase equipment to produce high definition television broadcasting equipment’…” In addition, in 2011, Gilchrist Metal “received two U.S. Navy sub-contracts totaling about $83,000 and a smaller, $5,600 Coast Guard contract in 2008…” The businessman, Jack Gilchrist, also acknowledged that in the 1980s the company received a U.S. Small Business Administration loan totaling “somewhere south of” $500,000, and matching funds from the federally-funded New England Trade Adjustment Assistance Center. And just yesterday, Mitt held a rally about the virtues of self-sufficiency with... wait for it... defense contractors! Let's close our disturbing tour of "Mitt Romney's reality world" with his moving speech to Olympians before the 2002 games: "You Olympians, however, know you didn't get here solely on your own power,” said Romney, who on Friday will attend the Opening Ceremonies of this year’s Summer Olympics. “For most of you, loving parents, sisters or brothers, encouraged your hopes, coaches guided, communities built venues in order to organize competitions. All Olympians stand on the shoulders of those who lifted them. We’ve already cheered the Olympians, let’s also cheer the parents, coaches, and communities. All right! [pumps fist].” Once again, we have the same questions for Governor Romney. What, if anything, do you really believe? You seem to hold many contradictory positions. Are you lying now or were you lying then?"</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343141370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343141382000-23</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, stupid , it's called Keynsianism, which Romney explains, here so pay attention: "Time magazine asked him about cutting spending in 2013. “If you take a trillion dollars for instance, out of the first year of the federal budget, that would shrink GDP over 5 percent,” Romney said. “That is by definition throwing us into recession or depression. So I’m not going to do that, of course.” You couldn’t have gotten a clearer definition of Keynesian budgeting from Obama."</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1343141382000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343142291000-24</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Highest level of disability collected in history&gt;&gt; Two wars started by the GOP would do the trick. Pushing off the bill for those to the next administration and the next generation is the only game the self-absorbed and self-worshiping GOP knows how to play well...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343142291000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:04:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343143027000-25</Id><Title>High disability rates</Title><Msg>Not surprising. They go up every recession, the GREAT BUSH RECESSION is no different. Demographics place the Boomers in line for age and health issues to occur. And lack of healthcare aggravates treatable conditions into disabling injuries and diseases like diabetes and coronary disease.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343143027000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:17:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343144197000-26</Id><Topic><Title>-Smart</Title><Username>ellakkj800</Username><Timestamp>1343139009000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Thanks</Msg><Username>mearaexp966</Username><Timestamp>1343144197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 11:36:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343147332000-27</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me correct you, since you show here a little ignorance. Keynsian theory presumes throwing money into labor market in order to help economy. I didn't find that in this quote. He didn't say, he will propose another stimulus, which would be clear Keynsian move, he essentially said he won't do drastic cuts. But your side likes to put words in someone's mouth, i.e. does what it always does - paraphrase. $450B stimulus II proposed by Obama in 2011 was clear Keynsian aproach, so was $860B stimulus I. But you can take it to the bank, Republican House under Romney administration will do cuts.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343147332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343147891000-28</Id><Topic><Title>-Smart</Title><Username>ellakkj800</Username><Timestamp>1343139009000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:10:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice Post</Msg><Username>pheliazkp487</Username><Timestamp>1343147891000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343148380000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted GT @ 9.93</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343067779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-23 14:22:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>covered GT @ 9.95. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343148380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343148974000-30</Id><Title>Did I miss something? Did we report a .16 loss?</Title><Msg>Surely, at 52 week lows something terrible must have happened.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343148974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343149241000-31</Id><Title>Wow, E*TRADE Financial Corporation could soar!</Title><Msg>You think E*TRADE Financial Corporation could increase after this? http://BESTDIVIDENDSHARES.INFO</Msg><Username>katherynstribble</Username><Timestamp>1343149241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343149688000-32</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But you can take it to the bank, Republican House under Romney administration will do cuts. " Didn't Reagan and both the Bush criminals promise to cut spending too, only to run up the deficits wildly instead? Willard is waffling about the cuts way before he's even close to being elected.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343149688000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:08:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>24</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343150115000-33</Id><Title>Mrs. &amp; Mr. Crowley</Title><Msg>Monica Crowley: Reagan Was Right When President Obama won the presidency, he did so driven by an ideology that took precedent over the very people who voted him into office. Since entering office, his determination to fundamentally change America has been shown to include abusing and misusing our military, burdening our economy with near-endless government spending, and literally holding our energy supplies hostage. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1q97XUgGON4&amp;feature=related</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343150115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343150605000-34</Id><Title>Willard the Shredder</Title><Msg>After Romney pledged transparent Olympics, key documents were destroyed Source: Boston Globe (Boston.com) WASHINGTON — Mitt Romney promised “complete transparency” when he took charge of the scandal-plagued Salt Lake City Olympics, a pledge that included access to his own correspondence and plans for an extensive public archive of documents related to the Games. But some who worked with Romney describe a close-to-the-vest chief executive unwilling to share so much as a budget with a state board responsible for spending oversight. Archivists now say most key records about the Games’ internal workings were destroyed under the supervision of a staffer shortly after the flame was extinguished at Olympic Cauldron Park, after Romney had returned to Massachusetts. “Transparency? There was none with when he was there,” said Kenneth Bullock, a committee member who represented the Utah League of Cities and Towns. “Their transparency became a black hole. It was nonexistent.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343150605000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:23:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343150963000-35</Id><Title>Willard endorses BO's economic record</Title><Msg>"Mitt Romney interviewed by Larry Kudlow: But if they want to see this economy come roaring back with good—with good jobs, they ought to vote for me, in my view. And we ought to give, whichever president is going to be elected, at least six months or a year to get those policies in place. That's quite a shift from what Romney was saying eight months ago. Then he was essentially blaming Barack Obama for jobs lost in the year before he became president. Romney has since shifted a bit and allowed the president 11 days warm-up time. Obama only becomes responsible for the unemployment disaster that he inherited as of February 2009. Steve Benen at the Rachel Maddow blog has built the chart above illustrating the difference between using the old Romney claim that responsibility for the course of the economy begins immediately and that it doesn't began until six or 12 months into a president's term. [L]ook what happens when we start the clock, as Romney suggests, six months to a year after President Obama was sworn in. In fact, if we don't hold Obama's first year against him, the economy has added over 3.7 million jobs overall during his presidency, and over 4.2 million in the private sector. As we know all too well, the economy is not generating enough jobs to get us back to where we were in December 2007 when the Great Recession began. Stubborn obstructionism from the party for which Romney is now the standard-bearer has made certain of that. Determined to make Obama fail, as per Rush Limbaugh's prescription, it has worked diligently to ensure that the economic downturn exacts as much pain on the working classes as possible while laying out fat cushions for the top tiers. Exactly what Romney proposes to do a lot more of starting with Day One. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343150963000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343151540000-36</Id><Title>The "naked truth"</Title><Msg>http://s701.photobucket.com/albums/ww15/joost5/misc/?action=view&amp;current=romney-taxdodger-joost5.jpg</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343151540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343152094000-37</Id><Topic><Title>The "naked truth"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343151540000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:39:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They forgot to list the sponsors.... :)</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343152094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343152226000-38</Id><Title>The 359 Safest Banks in America</Title><Msg>E*TRADE United Bank Arlington VA Out of more than 7,300, there are just 359 banks in America with a perfect Texas ratio of 0.0..0.0 means zero risk The Texas ratio was developed by a financial wizard at RBC Capital Markets named Gerard Cassidy, who used it to correctly predict bank failures in Texas during the 1980s recession, and again in New England during the recession of the early 1990s. While the ratio has been excellent at predicting bank failures, it can also be used to find the banks that are the furthest from failure.</Msg><Username>Peak_N_Valley</Username><Timestamp>1343152226000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343152279000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Mrs. &amp; Mr. Crowley</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343150115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:15:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;America has been shown to include abusing and misusing our military....&gt;&gt; Under BUSH and the GOP - indeed - we agree...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343152279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 13:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343153533000-40</Id><Title>GOP assault on voters</Title><Msg>"Defendants in a case against one of the nation's strictest voter ID laws in Pennsylvania made a major concession to plaintiffs this week, just days ahead of the start of the trial over the measure. In a stipulation agreement signed earlier this month, state officials conceded that they had no evidence of prior in-person voter fraud, or even any reason to believe that such crimes would occur with more frequency if a voter ID law wasn't in effect. "There have been no investigations or prosecutions of in-person voter fraud in Pennsylvania; and the parties do not have direct personal knowledge of any such investigations or prosecutions in other states,” the statement reads. According to the agreement, the state “will not offer any evidence in this action that in-person voter fraud has in fact occurred in Pennsylvania and elsewhere,” nor will it "offer argument or evidence that in-person voter fraud is likely to occur in November 2012 in the absense of the Photo ID law.” The possibility of voter fraud has frequently served as the ideological underpinning for voter ID measures, whose supporters claim that the integrity of elections can't be preserved without requiring would-be voters to verify their identity at polling places. Reports on actual incidents appear to counter this contention, however, as figures suggest voter fraud is a highly infrequent occurrence. Opponents of voter ID laws argue that such legislation is an effort to establish obstacles for potential voters, particularly college students, minorities and the elderly, who tend to vote Democratic. A recent report from the Brennan Center for Justice found that a variety of factors could seriously hamper the ability of a half-million Americans in 10 states that have passed voter ID laws to obtain the required documents they would need to cast votes in November. Pennsylvania GOP House Majority Leader Mike Turzai fueled the concerns of anti-voter ID activists earlier this year when he claimed that the recently enacted measure would "allow Gov. [Mitt] Romney to win the state of Pennsylvania." Just weeks after those comments, Pennsylvania officials released a study finding that more than 758,000 registered voters in the state -- many of them in its urban center of Philadelphia -- lacked driver's licenses. While the law allows for a variety of other forms of identification to be used at polling places, the figure suggested that a large number of Pennsylvanians still didn't meet the criteria needed to cast ballots in the fall. A lawsuit filed against the state's voter ID law by the ACLU and NAACP on behalf of lead plantiff Viviette Applewhite, a 93-year-old woman who claims she will be disenfranchised by the legislation because she won't be able to get valid documentation before the election, is set to go to trial on Wednesday. On Monday, the U.S. Department of Justice also announced that it was investigating whether the law discriminates against minorities."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343153533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343153724000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Did I miss something? Did we report a .16 loss?</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343148974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 12:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market looks forward, not backward. Revenue was down, NIM in the toilet, where is the growth going to come from? However, now that the lower bollinger band has been pierced for the second day in a row, if pps can close inside lower bb, currently sitting near $7.14 there could be a short term trading pop on the other side. Otherwise this company needs to be sold for the sum of its parts. imho</Msg><Username>dswanhmsk</Username><Timestamp>1343153724000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343155135000-42</Id><Title>*** $7.01 *** $ 7.01 *** ...learn more...</Title><Msg>Yinz know, da tax on a grande double latte is more than da difference between $7.01 and where E-Tub is currently trading. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Bottoms uppity Pilgrims, and Mushrooms. Clever Dudes &amp; Geniuses already know. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343155135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343155604000-43</Id><Topic><Title>*** $7.01 *** $ 7.01 *** ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343155135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some would consider KG a clever dude. 27 mil shares at $10.30. $1.03 pre R/S. When does his cronies cover?</Msg><Username>dswanhmsk</Username><Timestamp>1343155604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:46:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343156125000-44</Id><Title>How long until ETFC gets baci</Title><Msg>to its pre reverse split price. I am guessing before the year end. Rookies, NEVER EVER BUY and R/S stock!!!!</Msg><Username>fingerme77</Username><Timestamp>1343156125000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343156470000-45</Id><Title>take the ceo from etfc ,aks</Title><Msg>and you have a start for a good clown circus!!IMHO why are they paid so much? replace and cut costs</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343156470000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:01:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343156814000-46</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is one name you, hypocrit, didn't mention. He actually promissed to cut the deficit in half. He trippled it instead. He is sitting President. He is The One, and thus cannot be blamed for anything. "waffling about the cuts" is better than fail on the promise. Another contrast with Obama.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343156814000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343158973000-47</Id><Title>interesting.</Title><Msg>http://www.cnn.com/2012/07/24/opinion/granderson-christians/index.html?eref=rss_mostpopular</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343158973000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:42:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343159592000-48</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure, romney promises to makes cuts in the FUTURE, but in 2013, if elected he isn't cutting any spending and has said so. and in fact all Romney promises is increased spending on the miliatary, more tax cuts for the rich...... all paid for in the FUTURE..... by cuts to middleclass programs like Social Security and medicare. the hypocrite gop wrecked the recovery in the present, their BS grandstanding and dishonesty over the debt ceiling cost hundreds of thousands of jobs NOW....... and the ruckus they threw was over the defict NOW........ but what will Romney do about the deficit NOW (2013 if elected) NOTHING at all, and that is what he said. so do tell what the destructive gop tantrum over the debt ceiling was about besides SABOTAGE of the economy?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343159592000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343159599000-49</Id><Topic><Title>*** $7.01 *** $ 7.01 *** ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343155135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, Kenny dumped his 12% springing lien notes and a goodly part of his stock when he had to make up big losses at Citadel. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Yinz won't believe it, BUT, Kenny Boy has managed to lose money on Da Hog, and man is he pisssssed. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343159599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 15:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343160767000-50</Id><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Msg>Didn't we hit these lows already...like three years ago. SOB... these Wall Street SOB'S like playing their greedy childish friggin games.</Msg><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343161749000-51</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am sure morale around the company is at an all time high right now. Every employee gets to read about etfc hitting another 52 week low.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343161749000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343162017000-52</Id><Topic><Title>*** $7.01 *** $ 7.01 *** ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343155135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not so sure that the tard will will get any closer to 7.01. Yesterday, I was convinsed that it would break easily through 7.00....and the freefall would begin. But today, after the fight the bulls put up during the lows of the day, I am not so sure anymore. 'sept for once, the bears couldn't touch 7.10. If the bulls could put up such a fight at 7.10, then the fight at 7.00 will be brutal. I'm a buyer again at 7.02.....I wanna get my shares before the bear...</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343162017000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343162259000-53</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tard hit 7.10 yesterday. Today they tied their 52 week low.....</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343162259000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343162522000-54</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then again, it's really like a 152 week low. Last time around this price....2009... Quite the turnaround story. 3 years later and back to BK rumor land.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343162522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343163318000-55</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are far from BK rumers. Your're right, we are at 152 week lows, but the R/S took alot of the shorts out of the picture. They artificially took us up, so that they could profit by bringing us back down again. They did this over and over. If anything, I think that we are closer to our true value then ever before. Look At the fight we put up today....Down only 2 points on a hard fought down day.</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343163318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:55:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343163768000-56</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The last 3 days you have about 37 mil shares of volume, heavy on the sell side. At some point, people are puked out.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343163768000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343163820000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Apple smackdown, LOL!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1343163512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep...Using Apples data, the talking heads are talking China slowdown now. We'll get the full picture at the CC call.</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343163820000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:03:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343163821000-58</Id><Title>healthcare reform repeal would increase deficit</Title><Msg>Health care repeal would widen deficit by $109 billion, says CBO http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/ticket/health-care-repeal-widen-deficit-109-billion-says-194408630.html Mitten's says don't believe it, trust the Mittster, and pay no attention to how he hides his tax returns, and does offshore banking in shady places, and has to explain that offshoring at Bain and such had nothing to do with him, he "retroactively" retired or something. One might also wonder if the Mittster was lying when he did romneycare and said it is the "responsible" thing to do, or if he is lying now about the ACA. he seems to lie or be confused about a lot of things, for instance: Romney: Removing the cap on earnings taxed for Social Security “doesn’t begin to solve the problem.” (Town Hall in Berlin, New Hampshire, August 16, 2011.) The Truth: Removing the cap on earnings taxed for Social Security would actually create a budget surplus for the program over the next 75 years, if the present maximum benefit limit were to remain in place.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343163821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343164142000-59</Id><Title>OMG! AAPL missed HUGE ...oh,oh...</Title><Msg>Yinz know, of course, this could mean a 10% dip in all stocks, unless, Helicopter Benny does his, you know, stimulus gig. GDP out later this weak, errrr week. Pundits think 1.5%, which will set Benny &amp; his Turesury Factor, Timmy, into action mode. Think Batman to da rescue! C Yaz = Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Hey, Benny's job is at stake, Timmy already was told he's gonners in Bro Obama's next Admin. It's up to Benny to bring home da bacon for Bro Obama, and he's running outta time. I'm guessing E-Tub will print $7.01 before Benny does his QE3 thing. GL tomorrow Pilgrims, it's gonna be brutal, maybe worser. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343164142000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343164242000-60</Id><Topic><Title>WHA! AGAIN</Title><Username>lifestyle76mc</Username><Timestamp>1343160767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:12:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People don't matter, the retail buyers and sellers are a drop in the bucket in this and most other stocks. Only the 'tutes deside if and when we go up or down. They won't get tired....they have a plan. Like Buffet says, buy when others are selling and sell when others are buying.</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343164242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:10:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165064000-61</Id><Topic><Title>*** $7.01 *** $ 7.01 *** ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343155135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:38:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I take it back, cancelled 9000 share buy at 7.02....This Apple miss is going to push the whole market down. Micro and Macro economics involved here.</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343165064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343165761000-62</Id><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Msg>Psychos that do these shootings just create More gun sales... http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/lookout/gun-sales-aurora-colorado-shooting-spike-tuscon-161409369--finance.html People are just Tired of being targets for pleasure!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343165878000-63</Id><Topic><Title>OMG! AAPL missed HUGE ...oh,oh...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343164142000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will be singing Smokey Robinson tunes at Romneys concession speech. LOL</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343165878000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343166217000-64</Id><Topic><Title>OMG! AAPL missed HUGE ...oh,oh...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343164142000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This from the nome who missed the entire run ! LOL !</Msg><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1343166217000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:43:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343166305000-65</Id><Topic><Title>OMG! AAPL missed HUGE ...oh,oh...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1343164142000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:09:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll lead with this http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E2E_RSJAhYU</Msg><Username>thesilverman109</Username><Timestamp>1343166305000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:45:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343166626000-66</Id><Title>GOP WILL raise taxes</Title><Msg>"Republicans Will Raise Taxes — Just Not on the Wealthy Republicans are holding middle class tax cuts hostage in order to give the wealthiest 2 percent of Americans yet another extra tax cut. If that wasn’t bad enough, the Republicans are now affirmatively proposing to raise taxes on tens of millions of poor and middle class Americans — even as they slash them on the wealthy. Here’s the rundown. If you want to know how Republicans really feel about the middle class, you need look no further than a doozy of a floor speech that Sen. Jon Kyl (AZ) — a member of the Senate Republican leadership — gave yesterday. Kyl attacked President Obama for “incessantly” talking about the middle class. And it’s not just their rhetoric that shows disdain for the middle class, it’s their actual proposals. TAX CUTS REPUBLICANS ARE HOLDING HOSTAGE: Tax cuts for 98 percent of Americans. (The wealthiest two percent would also still get a tax cut on their first $250,000 of income.) TAX CUTS REPUBLICANS ARE INSISTING ON: An extra tax cut for the wealthiest 2 percent of Americans, including millionaires and billionaires. TAX INCREASES REPUBLICANS WANT: Limiting eligibility for the child tax credit, which constitutes a tax increase on 12 MILLION families. This works out to an average tax increase of $800 per family. In the case of a family made up of one person earning minimum wage and two children, the tax increase would be much larger according to one estimate: $1545. Curtailing tax credits for higher education expenses from $2500 a year to $1800 and reducing the years of eligibility from four years to two. This translates into an average tax increase of $1100 for 11 MILLION families. Cutting back on the earned income tax credit for families with three or more children and worsening the so-called “marriage penalty” on working poor couples, which translates into an average tax increase of $500 for 6 MILLION families. All told, these Republican tax increases would hit more than 25 million poor, working, and middle class families. Worse yet, Republicans aren’t even being honest about their plans to raise taxes on millions of Americans. Here’s what Sen. Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY) claimed earlier today: “Republicans will head into tomorrow’s vote guided by a simple principle: do no harm. In our view, the best approach to taxes right now is to let every American and every American business know they won’t have a higher income tax bill at the end of the year. We think everybody in America should have that certainty.” Unfortunately, the only people Republicans are really interested in letting know that they won’t see a tax increase are the wealthiest 2 percent of Americans. Republicans claim to care about the middle class, but they are holding middle class tax cuts hostage. And even as they promise more tax giveaways to the wealthy, Republicans want to raise taxes on 25 MILLION families — including some of the poorest Americans. Tomorrow, Senate Democrats will try and move forward with their plan to preserve middle class tax cuts while asking the wealthiest Americans to give up the extra tax cuts that they simply do not need and that we cannot afford. IN ONE SENTENCE: Just like Mitt Romney, Republicans in Congress want to raise taxes on the middle class in order to give the wealthiest Americans yet another handout that they don’t need.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343166626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:50:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343167322000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went ahead and got in the spirit wif a new .45 springfield xdm over the weekend.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343167322000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343167869000-68</Id><Title>Willard refuted</Title><Msg>http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&amp;v=GSaJpEa_BCA#!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343167869000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168011000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Apple smackdown, LOL!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1343163512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news for the WS crooks...more likely QE3. I love these "free market" crony capitialist, privatize profits and socialize losses...scumbag money changers.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343168011000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168151000-70</Id><Topic><Title>healthcare reform repeal would increase deficit</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343163821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. cut and paste, have you ever had an orginal thought.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343168151000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:15:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>15</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168242000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Apple smackdown, LOL!</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1343163512000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 16:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rut row...looks like da bearski will get his 7.01 or worser...as he would put it...apple put the bear face on mean ole mr market...hehehe</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343168242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168508000-72</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't mention GOP's war on women? I thought this was a major obstacle for economic recovery, not to mention Arab spring and Iranian nukes. You go tell this gobbledygook in the room full of Obama drones, you'll sure get an enormous applaud. I somehow don't believe debt ceiling debacle stopped employers from hiring.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343168508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343168989000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;.45 springfield xdm over the weekend&gt;&gt; As the character Rooster Cogburn(John Wayne) said to Texas Ranger La Boeuf(Glen Cambell) in the movie True Grit..."too much gun".</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343168989000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343169625000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ya should got the 9mm less snap and your second shot is tighter. The springfield XD sub compact would be an excellent conceal carry tool. Very accurate gun. Glock 26 is also a good choice..... http://www.springfield-armory.com/xd.php?model=2</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343169625000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:40:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343169782000-75</Id><Topic><Title>GOP WILL raise taxes</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343166626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do a tax return on a minimum wage earner with two children...get back with us on that tax increase when your done.....you're so fos......</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343169782000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343169872000-76</Id><Title>Hey Freiberg. Did Ken call and read you the riot act?</Title><Msg>I figured he'd follow up on your promise to the shareholders. Its really too bad your sense of economics was so poor. Now that the outlook has diminished even further for OLBs and the discount rates have stacked, seems like a sale last year wasn't a have bad idea. What price did The Goldman Sachs tell you not to sell?</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343169872000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343170046000-77</Id><Title>OK, I am back. Freiberg's challenge</Title><Msg>Is to now get the pps to 20 bucks like in no time. We were at 15 when Freiberg and his dufus board decided not to sell. couls have sold for almost $20 bucks a year ago. Ya gonna put all the your bonus money and shares into a trust for the shareholders you doofed on?</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343170046000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:47:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343170311000-78</Id><Title>Freiberg: Gambled with shareholders money......</Title><Msg>............and lost big. he needs to answer to the shareholders. Mr market had ETFC at over 15 before Feiberg and his dufus board nixed the sale. Lesson 1: Never trust your money to a dude from a big bank.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343170311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343170483000-79</Id><Title>Audette' audacious Math......</Title><Msg>"ahem"... "may I have your attentions please".. My name is Audacious and my sense of economics is terrible. "Lets not sell the company at $15 plus, lets wait until it goes to 7 bucks. Then we can swing a deal with the buyer to keep our jobs"</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343170483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343171312000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Audette' audacious Math......</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343170483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:54:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you got clown # 2 pegged!</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343171312000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:08:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343171349000-81</Id><Topic><Title>Freiberg: Gambled with shareholders money......</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343170311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 18:51:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown # 1 pegged!</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343171349000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343172379000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Help</Title><Username>sidonnievkx758</Username><Timestamp>1343139597000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 10:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Expecting more news</Msg><Username>stevenrmz964</Username><Timestamp>1343172379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173166000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A new poll on gun control. http://www.topix.com/issue/gun-laws</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343173166000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173272000-84</Id><Topic><Title>healthcare reform repeal would increase deficit</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343163821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>still, it's true "Health care repeal would widen deficit by $109 billion, says CBO" Mitten's says don't believe it, trust the Mittster, and pay no attention to how he hides his tax returns, and does offshore banking in shady places, and has to explain that offshoring at Bain and such had nothing to do with him, he "retroactively" retired or something. and still, One might also wonder if the Mittster was lying when he did romneycare and said it is the "responsible" thing to do, or if he is lying now about the ACA. he seems to lie or be confused about a lot of things, for instance: Romney: Removing the cap on earnings taxed for Social Security “doesn’t begin to solve the problem.” (Town Hall in Berlin, New Hampshire, August 16, 2011.) The Truth: Removing the cap on earnings taxed for Social Security would actually create a budget surplus for the program over the next 75 years, if the present maximum benefit limit were to remain in place.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343173272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343173938000-85</Id><Topic><Title>How long until ETFC gets baci</Title><Username>fingerme77</Username><Timestamp>1343156125000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not sure it will go that low, but it will fall to the 5's for sure by the year end.</Msg><Username>blackstinkypuss</Username><Timestamp>1343173938000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343174193000-86</Id><Topic><Title>gop wrecked the economic recovery</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343132865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 08:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your typical lame and weasel reply. i knew you couldn't explain how the destructive gop tantrum over the debt ceiling was anything but SABOTAGE of the economy. Because that is what it was, and what a disgrace and what damage to the nation. all it accomplished was the loss of hundreds of thousands of jobs ................ the gop now says it won't honor what it agreed to anyway.... and Mittens has said if elected he will make no spending cuts in 2013...... and the gop says they won't honor their own agreement for automatic spending cuts...... so what happened to the urgency of the gop tantrums and brinksmanship over the debt ceiling? It was all obviously nothing but destructive grandstanding by the lunatic gop intent on wrecking the recovery.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343174193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343174232000-87</Id><Topic><Title>How long until ETFC gets baci</Title><Username>fingerme77</Username><Timestamp>1343156125000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 14:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock just can not get any momentum. I sold around 12 and have waited to get back in. Think I will stay on the sidelines!</Msg><Username>billsilva45</Username><Timestamp>1343174232000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343174363000-88</Id><Topic><Title>GOP WILL raise taxes</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343166626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:50:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Higher taxes lead to revenue maximizing, employing more people and taking on more expenses, aka GDP growth. Lower taxes lead to profit maximizing, reducing employment and lowering expenses, aka GDP contraction, all else being equal. Higher taxes encourage you to spend more to grow your business since you aren't benefitting as much from being more profitable.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1343174363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 19:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343180631000-89</Id><Title>A Most Serious Blunder. Ken Griffin Discovers the Reality</Title><Msg>Ken Griffin is reading Aesops fables tonite. Pride comes before a fall. Bells are going off in his head and his ears are ringing with anger. Ken is going to talk to F tomorrow about protecting shareholders value. He is also going to Fedex F a copy of the Fables.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343180631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 21:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343183555000-90</Id><Topic><Title>healthcare reform repeal would increase deficit</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343163821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:03:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>....and I heard it on the Evening News from Scott Pelly, anchor on CBS. This is no cut&amp;paste, but the naked truth! Bidder, you can't deny it!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1343183555000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 22:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343187228000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Gun Sales Spike in Colorado...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343165761000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 17:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even Better.... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_U6tORrODJE</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343187228000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-24 23:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>