<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348981102015-1</Id><Title>Let em come, I'm ready for em, all of em. ...learn why...</Title><Msg>I hope they come. I have 4 assult rifles, all of em loaded and set to automatic. Mrs Bear's afraid to fire her weapon, but, Kiki and her older sister Titi are both qualified experts. Kiki shot a burgler a couple of years ago. She shoulda killed em to death like I told her, but, she didn't listen and that crazy fool is suing us. Next time, Kiki will listen to me. I have a plan to take this AH out before our trial date. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Wish me luck. This fool is probably voting for Obama. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1348981102015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349000533701-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mooo-slims Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859063675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This WAR on these scummy mooo=sleems just got hotter!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1349000533701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 06:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349007117895-3</Id><Title>Amazon Loan Business</Title><Msg>Amazon getting into loan business - urls not allowed</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1349007117895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349009632799-4</Id><Topic><Title>Let em come, I'm ready for em, all of em. ...learn why...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1348981102015</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 00:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She should've droned hisass then bragged.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349009632799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349009828152-5</Id><Topic><Title>DUMBO! RESIGN NOW!! (cover up!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348936321730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No Wall around Bengahzi Consolate?? Another 'Hope and Changer' GENIUS idea!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349009828152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349009917546-6</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OHHH! The deabtes are going to be Awesome!!! Tick-Tock..'Hope and Change' is finally ENDING!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349009917546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 08:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349012955099-7</Id><Title>Gallup poll: Obama 50%, Romney 44%</Title><Msg>Gallup: Obama 50%, Romney 44% among registered voters Rasmussen Reports daily tracking poll : Obama 48% Romney 46% September 29, 2012 Rasmussen must be part of the conspiracy Tush whines about, since they also show Obama pulling ahead</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349012955099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 09:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349017654106-8</Id><Title>Simple fact-tell everyone over a "certain age"</Title><Msg>Every House Republican voted to kill Medicare - EVERY ONE! On April 15th 2011. That was a unanimous vote by the Repub Conference in the house to turn Medicare into COUPONS.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349017654106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:07:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349018247629-9</Id><Topic><Title>Simple fact-tell everyone over a "certain age"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349017654106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:07:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans are the true ' death panel '</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349018247629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349020198630-10</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's incomprehensible, imaginary tax plan</Title><Msg>"WASHINGTON -- Republican vice presidential nominee Paul Ryan promised again on Sunday that Mitt Romney’s tax plan would bring lower tax rates for all Americans while remaining revenue-neutral, although he didn’t fully explain how it would accomplish that. The Obama campaign has blasted the Romney-Ryan ticket for not providing details on how it would give Americans such large tax breaks without growing the deficit. Ryan reiterated in an interview on "Fox News Sunday" that the plan would drop taxpayers' bills by 20 percent without costing a dime, due to closed tax loopholes, but he was short on specifics when pressed by host Chris Wallace. “You haven’t given me the math,” Wallace said in one exchange. “I don’t have the ... It would take me too long to go through all of the math,” Ryan responded. “But let me say it this way,” he went on. “You can lower tax rates 20 percent across the board by closing loopholes and still have preferences for the middle class for things like charitable deductions, home purchases, for health care. What we’re saying is people are going to get lower tax rates and therefore they will not send as much money to Washington.” Wallace played a clip of President Barack Obama mocking the Romney campaign’s lack of details on the loopholes while on the campaign trail. “No matter how many times they tell you they’re gonna start talking specifics really soon, they don’t do it,” Obama said. “And the reason is because the math doesn’t work.” A report from the Tax Policy Center found that Romney’s tax plan would actually raise taxes on many middle-class Americans, although the Romney campaign has dismissed the report as partisan. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349020198630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 11:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349020932808-11</Id><Title>Undecideds revisited</Title><Msg>By David Lauter, Washington Bureau September 30, 2012, 5:00 a.m. WASHINGTON — For Mitt Romney, making a comeback in the race for president will require changing the minds of voters like Barry Hubscher, Cathleen Kimmel and Michael Gray. All three had considered voting for the Republican nominee as recently as August, but lately they have found themselves leaning toward President Obama. Listening to them and others like them helps explain the shift in polls toward Obama since the Democratic convention and illustrates the magnitude of the task that lies before Romney as he tries to catch up in an increasingly challenging race. In an effort to explore the sentiments behind the poll numbers as Romney approaches the first of three presidential debates, Los Angeles Times reporters over the last week interviewed four dozen voters who in mid-August had told pollsters for The Times and USC's Annenberg School for Communication and Journalism that they were undecided or only weakly committed to their candidates. Asked an open-ended question about what news regarding Romney or Obama had stuck in their minds over the last couple of weeks, 1 in 3 spontaneously mentioned Romney's videotaped remarks about the 47% of Americans who do not pay income tax — the only incident to be so widely recalled. In Wheat Ridge, Colo., a western suburb of Denver, R.J. Montoya, 31, who admires Ron Paul and deeply dislikes Obama, might have seemed a natural Romney voter. He hasn't closely followed the campaign, having just started a new job in healthcare, but he had heard about Romney's remarks. "They bother me," he said. "I'm not exactly sure which way I'll go," he said, raising the possibility of voting for a third-party candidate. Romney's remarks were "one thing I could see having an impact on how I see this election." Many voters, like Montoya, perceived Romney's remarks as an unguarded moment of truth, a peek behind the veil of the campaign. But the problem the GOP nominee faces goes deeper, the interviews made clear: His remarks have stuck with voters in part because many had already found his message wanting. Hubscher, who manages a dining club in one of Chicago's western suburbs, is one such voter. Over the last year, he has been listening for a compelling reason to back Romney. In the poll, he said he leaned toward the challenger. Indeed, Hubscher epitomizes the profile of a voter Romney should have been able to count on: a suburban, white, 50-year-old man who manages a business, thinks of himself as a Republican and has been disappointed with Obama after voting for him in 2008. And yet, a little more than five weeks before the election, he now leans toward giving the president another term. "I kind of feel like he hasn't fulfilled the promises he set out, so maybe we should look in a different direction," he said. "But I'm not really feeling the Republicans have put forth a candidate to replace him." "I just don't think Romney has made his case," he said, citing a lack of specifics in Romney's campaign pledges. Hubscher watched the Republican convention and was deeply impressed by Sen. Marco Rubio of Florida. "I felt a connection to the things he was talking about," he said. By contrast, Romney, who spoke later the same night, made little impression. His campaign, Hubscher said, boils down to, "'Look what a bad job Obama's done, and I'm not that guy.' That's not good enough." Even among Romney backers, that sense of disappointment came up frequently. When asked what they remembered of the two party conventions, only one of the four dozen interviewed brought up Romney's speech.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349020932808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349022838347-12</Id><Title>America''s young sent to die in Obama's quagmire</Title><Msg>Cowardly ivy-tower general Barry. His lilly a s s never served!</Msg><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1349022838347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349025493521-13</Id><Topic><Title>America''s young sent to die in Obama's quagmire</Title><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1349022838347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 12:33:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens and his five sons didn't serve! Rushbo didn't serve because he had a wart on his butt. In fact most Republican politicians never served in our military. The war in Afghanistan was started by the Dubja administration and President Obama will have all of the troops out by 2014.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1349025493521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349026676717-14</Id><Topic><Title>DUMBO! RESIGN NOW!! (cover up!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348936321730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're about as ignorant and stupid as they come. All sorts of theories are imagined by Repugnicans in regard to the attack in Bengahzi. A wall around the mission (not consulate)??? Give us all a break bigmouth, q4bike.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1349026676717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 13:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349028459870-15</Id><Topic><Title>DUMBO! RESIGN NOW!! (cover up!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348936321730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Want to know the worst theory about the Americans killed in Benghazi? Some people stay Obama did nothing. They say he played golf and went to fundraisers to yuk it up with millionaires. They say Obama does not give a s#it. And it is all true.</Msg><Username>mental_state_googoo</Username><Timestamp>1349028459870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349028538056-16</Id><Title>GOP assault on the poor</Title><Msg>Phoenix Mayor Attempts To Live On A Food Stamp Budget: ‘I’m Tired, And It’s Hard To Focus’ By Travis Waldron When local activist groups challenged Phoenix Mayor Greg Stanton to live on a food stamp budget for a week to mark Hunger Awareness Month, he took them up on the offer and found out just how hard it was. Stanton kept a diary on the challenge, which allotted him roughly $29 a week, the same amount 1.1 million Arizonans receive from the Supplemental Assistance Nutrition Program (SNAP) each week. By day four, Stanton noted that he was “tired” and “it’s hard to focus” after leaving the house for work without time to scramble eggs or eat a decent breakfast: OK- ran out the door today with no time to scramble eggs or even make a sandwich. So I’m surviving on an apple and handful of peanuts, and the coffee I took to the office until dinner. I’m tired, and it’s hard to focus. I can’t go buy a sandwich because that would be cheating- even the dollar menu at Taco Bell is cheating. You can’t use SNAP benefits at any restaurants, fast food or otherwise. I’m facing a long, hungry day and an even longer night getting dinner on the table, which requires making EVERYTHING from scratch on this budget. It’s only for a week, so I’ve got a decent attitude. If I were doing this with no end in sight, I probably wouldn’t be so pleasant. Watch a local news report about Stanton’s challenge, via Huffington Post’s Bonnie Kavoussi: According to Stanton’s Facebook page, the city he governs ranks 34th-worst among America’s 100 largest metro areas in terms of hunger, and one-in-four Arizona children are food insecure. Across the nation, there are more than 46 million people receiving SNAP benefits. Despite the challenges presented by poverty and hunger, Republicans have proposed cuts to the programs that help struggling families afford food. The House GOP budget could kick millions out of SNAP and hundreds of thousands of children out of school lunch programs, exacerbating the high rates of food insecurity America’s families are already facing.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349028538056</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349031459693-17</Id><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Msg>a Romney advisor has said that Mitt might "give on the tax cuts".... you know, if the tax cuts to the rich aren't made up by increased taxes on the poor and middle class.........Mitt calls increasing YOUR taxes and lowering his "broadening the base"</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035091601-18</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually I lie to pollsters if I talk to them at all. Or I tell them I'm voting for the least qualified candidate, so I'll be voting for the incumbent, for the first time since Reagan in 1984.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349035091601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 15:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349035858586-19</Id><Topic><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll pay for the increases in military spending since I've been paying taxes if YOU pay for the increases in social spending. Ohhh, did someone forget that when we went to war in 2001 we did so with a FRACTION of the military I served in during the early 80's? That the military budget was a significantly larger chunk of federal spending then. That the peon's hadn't yet discovered they could vote themselves largesse from the public coffers and so started to vote only for politicians smart enough to provide it? I wish I could say that, but unfortunately by that time 2nd generation recipients were already on the social roles, though since then we've added three more generations that have known nothing but government checks and hangin' out in the 'hood, while we've simultaneously cut the number of combat formations, and converted many of our heavy armor units (3rd ACR) into freaking lame #$%$ Stryker Combat Brigades which would be well challenged by an opposing formation using World War II era tanks. You of course see the math of it. You'll end up paying ME as WELL as the Federal budget because, since the days of the start of The Great Society and the end of the Cold War, military spending has ever decreased while social spending has ever INCREASED. Even under George Bush, the most hawkish President we've had SINCE Reagan.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349035858586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349038423753-20</Id><Topic><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you seem sadly misinformed. there is no problem with social security or medicare, Mitt leaves them alone and most boomers like me get them as is, not changed, and these boomers will be on them out into the 2040s. Plus we get a big new tax cut on top of the bush tax cut! and medicare fixed and cash back! and deficit reduction too! that was easy!! But Mitt wants to increase military spending. I wonder who will pay for that? and sure, "military spending has ever decreased .....Even under George Bush, the most hawkish President we've had SINCE Reagan." i guess by decrease you mean the 167% or so increase since 2000 from about $260 billion to about 700 billion.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349038423753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349038791145-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no problem with social security and medicare . . . I agree. Those are earned entitlement programs. There IS a problem with TANF Section 8 SSI SCHIP WIC and the LIST goes on . . . of UNearned entitlement programs.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349038791145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 16:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349039639212-22</Id><Topic><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you suppose poor people , disabled people, the elderly poor will just go away if you cut them off to pay for more tax cuts for the Romney types? I take it you think the poor in this country should be poorer. What's your plan ,starve poor people? And ntm, everyone knows that 1$ in food stamps trickles through the economy and helps keep a baker and a farmer and a truck driver and so on employed as well. We should be restoring progressive taxation not eliminating it. Adam smith said progressive taxation is essential to capitalism and most economists agree. It is as American as apple pie, and it's nuts that some want to allow the billionaires to become an aristocracy. "The property of this country is absolutely concentred in a very few hands, having revenues of from half a million of guineas a year downwards... I am conscious that an equal division of property is impracticable. But the consequences of this enormous inequality producing so much misery to the bulk of mankind, legislators cannot invent too many devices for subdividing property, only taking care to let their subdivisions go hand in hand with the natural affections of the human mind. Another means of silently lessening the inequality of property is to exempt all from taxation below a certain point, and to tax the higher portions of property in geometrical progression as they rise. " --Thomas Jefferson to James Madison, October 28,1785. ME 19:17, Papers 8:682</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349039639212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 17:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349045234724-23</Id><Title>They'll have "nun" of the Dipshidiot</Title><Msg>Nuns On A Bus: Romney’s 47 Percent Comments Show ‘He Has No Idea How Hard It Is’ To Be Poor By Travis Waldron The leader of the Nuns On A Bus tour that has criss-crossed the nation highlighting the effect the House Republican budget would have on low-income Americans said Monday that Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney’s recent comments about the “47 percent” “show that he is “out of touch” and “has no idea how hard it is at the margins of our society.” ThinkProgress spoke to Sister Simone Campbell, the executive director of NETWORK, a Catholic social justice lobby, in New York, where the Nuns got off the bus and onto the Staten Island ferry to highlight the GOP budget’s impacts on poverty programs in New York City. Aboard the ferry, Campbell said Romney’s comments “broke my heart” because they demonstrated his lack of knowledge about the living conditions of America’s poorest citizens: CAMPBELL: I mean, it was shocking to me that a person who says he wants to be the leader of our nation believes that 47 percent of our country is basically lazy or dependent or indolent. That was shocking to me. But then, it broke my heart that he would be so out of touch, that he would so not know the truth of folks at the margins of our society who work so hard. And he obviously doesn’t know that if you work a minimum wage job, if you’re a child care, if you’re providing janitorial services, or if you’re a day laborer, if you work for minimum wage, you’re still in poverty. He has no idea how hard it is at the margins of our society. The Nuns tour, which hit nine states earlier this year, was in New York to protest the House GOP budget authored by Republican vice presidential nominee Paul Ryan. Even before he chose Ryan as his running mate, Romney supported the Ryan budget, which makes a majority of its spending cuts from programs that benefit the poor, including food stamps, Medicaid, and other assistance programs. The Nuns On A Bus tour invited Romney and Ryan to join them during a stop in Ohio early in October but have yet to get an answer. But that visit, Campbell said, might be exactly what Romney needs. “That’s why we’ve invited them to come October 10 to Cincinnati, to have him listen to folks experience,” Campbell said. “Not speak, we want him to listen, to let his heart be broken by the truth of people in the U.S. That’s what he needs.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349045234724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349045794456-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney WANTS YOU to pay for the increases to military spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349031459693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 14:57:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is correct to say that the Bush precipitated the enormous deficits that we are now dealing with. Obama had to administer the bailout money that Bush authorized. The two wars that George Bush started where still paid for under the Obama administration. Obama wanted to end the wars, Republicans wanted the war to continue indefinitely, without thinking the effect that it would have on the deficit. In addition, the Bush tax cuts were still in place to benefit the job outsourcers. So, yes, it is correct to state that Bush is responsible for creating the deficits, after all, we had a budget surplus when Clinton left office. When Bush came in, the deficits started. All through these four years, Obama has been working hard to clean up Bush’s mess.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1349045794456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 18:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349048288115-25</Id><Title>Calif. woman fatally shot after allegedly driving into border patrol agent...</Title><Msg>Look at how upset the husband is...So goes the Nation! ...And this is from ABC News... Authorities are investigating the fatal shooting of a 32-year-old woman in the suburban San Diego area after she allegedly hit a Border Patrol agent with her car. Investigators said Valeria Alvarado ran down the agent with her car as border patrol agents were in a Chula Vista neighborhood to serve a felony warrant on Friday. The agent said he had no choice but to defend himself and fired at Alvarado get her to stop the car. Alvarado was hit by five bullets. According to eye witnesses, the shooting left the mother of five with bullet holes in her face, arms, and chest. "She literally ran our agent down, the agent actually was impacted, was hit by the vehicle and carried several hundred yards on the hood before fearing for his life did discharge his weapon to get the vehicle to stop," said Border Patrol Deputy Chief Rodney Scott. Alvarado's husband, Gilbert Alvarado said he wants the shooting investigated. "I want justice. Yes. Whoever shot my wife, that guy whoever that is, that guy needs to get shot," he said. Alvarado's family called the killing senseless. "Where's the evidence that my wife threatened a trained officer? You know? He's a trained officer to use lethal force, shoot my wife like that and just not even call an ambulance?" said Gilbert Alvarado. The FBI and Chula Vista Police are investigating the shooting. Officials have not released the name of the agent involved in the incident.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349048288115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:38:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349048550796-26</Id><Title>FLUCK YOU YAHOO!...</Title><Msg>Censor YOURSELVES!.... The Truth HURTS Doesn't It?.......................</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349048550796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349052109323-27</Id><Title>Wow...Yahoo Censors the word "CENSOR"....</Title><Msg>LMAO!.... What a Joke this counry has become! No Wonder Gordon Brown was on Fox saying that we are heading for a One World Government.... He is Right!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349052109323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 20:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349060538124-28</Id><Topic><Title>FLUCK YOU YAHOO!...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349048550796</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 19:42:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another right wing #$%$ demands his free, socialistic service And complains when it doesn't meet his expectations. Just another welfare whoore</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349060538124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-30 23:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>