<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349174873874-1</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry is a #$%$. That is why they were callin g him a: 'Flip-Flopper'</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1349174873874</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 06:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349180509422-2</Id><Topic><Title>This week: ETFC will fall to $8.20s~8.30s</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349065932257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stmoon has turned bearish. Can only mean one thing. ETFC is getting ready to Move up. He's about like cramer do the opposite of and make some $$</Msg><Username>davids4714</Username><Timestamp>1349180509422</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 08:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349183073349-3</Id><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Msg>I am sure this stock will hit 9.45 this week. My stop loss is 8.61 just in case of some trouble in the Middle East or Europe.</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349185398956-4</Id><Title>Cut deficit, but not on the backs of the needy</Title><Msg>"Let us never forget that when Bill Clinton left office in January 2001, this country enjoyed a healthy $236 billion surplus, and the projections were that this surplus would grow by a total of $5 trillion over a 10-year period. What happened? How did we go from a significant federal budget surplus to a massive deficit? Frankly, it is not that complicated. President George W. Bush and the so-called deficit hawks chose to go to war in Afghanistan and Iraq and put the funding for those wars on our nation’s credit card. By the time the last wounded veteran is cared for, those wars will end up adding more than $3 trillion to our national debt. During this same period, Bush and the “deficit hawks” provided huge tax breaks to the wealthiest 2 percent of Americans who were already doing phenomenally well. These tax breaks for the very rich will increase our national debt by about $1 trillion over a 10-year period. In addition, Bush and the “deficit hawks” established a Medicare prescription drug program written by the pharmaceutical and insurance industries. This program, which is far more expensive than it should be because it prohibits the federal government from using its purchasing power to negotiate cheaper drug prices, was not paid for. As a result, about $400 billion will be added to our national debt over a 10-year period. Further, as a result of the deregulation of Wall Street, and the greed, recklessness and illegal behavior of the major financial institutions, this country was driven into the worst recession since the 1930s, which resulted in a massive reduction in revenue coming into the federal government. .."</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349185398956</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:43:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349185990628-5</Id><Title>Mittens giveth and Mittens taketh</Title><Msg>he kills the home mortgage deduction............ but when touting his health insurance fix he promises a deduction to help with your increased health insurance costs. Mitt's "broadening the base" seems like a big shell game with one purpose: "Romney’s policies would mean a really big tax increase for people making between $100,000 and $250,000 in order to pay for a big tax cut on people making more than $250,000."</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349185990628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349188641763-6</Id><Title>GOP assault on democracy</Title><Msg>Judge halts Pa.'s tough new voter ID requirement HARRISBURG, Pa. (AP) — A judge is postponing Pennsylvania's tough new voter identification requirement, ordering that it not be enforced in the presidential election. Tuesday's ruling comes just five weeks before the election. An appeal is possible. The 6-month-old law requires each voter to show a valid photo ID. Democrats and groups including the AARP and NAACP mounted a furious opposition to a law Republicans say is necessary to prevent election fraud. Critics have accused Republicans of using old-fashioned Jim Crow tactics to steal the White House and have highlighted stories of registered voters struggling to get a state photo ID.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349188641763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349188920321-7</Id><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Msg>Bush-Appointed Judge Upholds Obama Administration’s Birth Control Coverage Rules Last edited Mon Oct 1, 2012, 06:44 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Source: ThinkProgress On Friday, Judge Carol Jackson, a George H.W. Bush appointee to a federal court in Missouri, rejected a Catholic business owner’s challenge to the Obama Administration’s rules requiring employer health plans to cover birth control. Like the many copycat lawsuits asserting similar legal claims, the plaintiffs in this suit argued that the birth control rules substantially burden their faith by requiring them to pay for employee health benefits which might then in turn be used to pay for birth control. As Judge Jackson’s opinions explains, however, this argument proves too much: The burden of which plaintiffs complain is that funds, which plaintiffs will contribute to a group health plan, might, after a series of independent decisions by health care providers and patients covered by plan, subsidize someone else’s participation in an activity that is condemned by plaintiffs’ religion. . . . is a shield, not a sword. It protects individuals from substantial burdens on religious exercise that occur when the government coerces action one’s religion forbids, or forbids action one’s religion requires; it is not a means to force one’s religious practices upon others. does not protect against the slight burden on religious exercise that arises when one’s money circuitously flows to support the conduct of other free-exercise-wielding individuals who hold religious beliefs that differ from one’s own. . . . The health care plan will offend plaintiffs’ religious beliefs only if an [] employee (or covered family member) makes an independent decision to use the plan to cover counseling related to or the purchase of contraceptives. Already, pay salaries to their employees—money the employees may use to purchase contraceptives or to contribute to a religious organization. By comparison, the contribution to a health care plan has no more than a de minimus impact on the plaintiff’s religious beliefs than paying salaries and other benefits to employees. A key insight in this opinion is that salaries and health insurance can be used to buy birth control, so if religious employers really object to enabling their employees to buy birth control, they would have to not pay them money in addition to denying them comprehensive health insurance. An employer cannot assert a religious objection to how their employees choose to use their own benefits or their own money, because religious freedom is not a license to “force one’s religious practices upon others.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349188920321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349189237974-8</Id><Topic><Title>47% of this Board has Disappeared</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349148992481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comment only proves you don't read the news. You just listen to Rush. But thanks for voting for Obama.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349189237974</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349189364382-9</Id><Topic><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10,000 message boards and you choose to follow ETFC. Why?</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1349189364382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349189367032-10</Id><Title>will the dressage horse tax write off continue?</Title><Msg>I know the gop wants to kill the home mortgage deduction. what about car elevators?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349189367032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349189468210-11</Id><Title>American Bull states "Buy Confirmed"</Title><Msg>They have a good track record but sometimes their buys last only a few days. However, that is more HFC, skimming the cream vs a problem with their methods.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1349189468210</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349189931976-12</Id><Title>BO spoke at his school</Title><Msg>"That high school Obama spoke at Sunday night? I wanted to tell y’all a few things about it, things that I know for a fact, because I taught there for many years. The school is 95% minority, largely free and reduced lunch, and about 15-20 percent of students are illegal. More accurately, their parents are illegal and took the students into this country. Some of the illegal nationalities I encountered over the year: Mexican (the stereotype). Guatemalan, Honduran, Salvadoran. Chilean, Peruvian, Colombian. Thai, Cambodian, Filipino, Laotian. Irish, English, Romanian, Greek, Russian, Turkish. Canadian. For various reasons, going “back home” is either impossible or just a very bad idea. I have had students with a 4.6 GPA, weighted with AP and honors classes, taken to the US at the ripe old age of one month, who do not speak any language other than English and cannot get a student loan – students that, had they been born here, would be a senator or president some day. I have had students that have won awards and scholarships that would make them the envy of anyone here, and students who have gone to colleges that are the envy of the world. Stanford, Harvard, Oxford – the kind of school that means parent can die happy. On virtually every day, the school lunch is cheese pizza, tater tots, and a fruit pie. That fulfills the FDA requirements. As the most underfunded district in the nation (for years we could say “At least we aren’t Mississippi!”), by law the only place we are allowed to profit from students is school lunch. We charge the federal government something like eighty cents for a lunch that costs us twenty-five. Walking in the door at lunchtime would kill poor Michelle. In a given year, about 15% of the girls will get pregnant and carry a baby to full term. Even so, abortions are very common. The school district in Las Vegas is made up of seven Mormon housewives, elected largely because people assume that women will somehow be better for schools, as if the presence of ovaries automatically blesses someone with simple common sense (and no, I’m not one of those MRA #$%$). As a result, the District’s sex education policies are set by a selected subcommittee made up of six other Mormons, even more conservative than those democratically elected. In the 90s, the board refused to allow Schindler’s List to be seen by high school seniors with parental permission, and still refuse to allow us to even show clips of a PG-13 movie shown to any student for any reason (I promise you, Shakespeare was meant to be seen, not read). As a result, I have allowed students to bring their own children into the classroom. I have personally bottle-fed and changed a diaper while I was teaching a classroom of 30-50 other students how to read; I don’t want any teenage mother to use their baby as an excuse to not graduate. One coworker went to a student’s house to get said student to take the high-stakes test. That employee ended up administering the proficiency exam while the student was in labor, then taking the student to the hospital to give birth. The mother of the student wasn’t a bad parent, but she had other kids, too, and if she’d left work she would have been fired. When one of my students gave birth, which was fairly often, I never missed an opportunity to go to their home and give them their make-up work. More than once I stayed and helped with a newborn while I also helped with homework. One of my favorite teaching-memories is hanging out with a girl while bottle-feeding that girl’s baby, discussing some of the intricacies of All Quiet on the Western Front, while my daughter and her youngest sister played Barbies on the kitchen floor. That number above was not a typo. I have spent an entrire school year with a fifty-minute period of fifty-five students, all of whom were below grade-level, and attempted to teach them how to read. I have separated Bloods from Crips. I have confiscated weed pipes, crack pipes, meth pipes, syringes, and god-only-knows how many pills. I have assisted the police in taking a gun away from a student. I have taken knives away from students. Once, I was told to take the student back to class because I had not followed the proper disciplinary procedures; I had not assigned detention and called his parents before he pulled a knife on another student. I have fed a dozen students a day. I have provided beds and other furniture for their homes. I have been to many of their homes, and turned down the crack and/or meth that was offered me (heroin people apparently don’t like to share). One of these kids lived with a meth addicted uncle because living with a cocaine addicted father was worse. He had his daughter at thirteen. He is literally the only students I tried hard to not join the military, because his life was so hard (I’m not including the details) that Afghanistan was literally a better option than life after graduation – and by god I made sure he took every extra class he needed to graduate. Years later, and actually in Afghanistan and getting shot at, he still Skypes with my wife once every week or two to let us know that he’s alive and he’s bored. He wants to be a teacher when he gets out. I love him like he was my son. I can show you the places in the school where the bullet holes have been painted up. At one time that school was known as “Drive-By High.” Once, one of my freshman once shot another freshman in the foot, on the last shot of a fourteen round clip. He was a good kid, except he was short and got picked on because of it. A former student stabbed another former student for no apparent reason, and the bleeding man managed to stagger back onto campus before he died. Most of the teachers I know have been to student funerals, but I seem to have been to far more of them. One of the big newspapers did an article last year on the worst zip codes in America: the residents of two of the top twenty worst zip codes send their children to the school Obama spoke at last night. I’m not going to talk about Arne Duncan here; it would get me, after eleven years, banned at DU. That having been said: in a few days I will be voting to re-elect President Obama. Though I don’t always agree with him 100%, he is the best choice for this nation. I hope you will get out the vote."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349189931976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:58:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349191759569-13</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349188920321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how does that compare to Kennedy killing his girl friend. Or Edwards getting other girls pregnate while his wife was dying.Hey how about Clinton playing cigar tag in the white house..Yea it appears that you have a know nothing attitude about women...</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1349191759569</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349192748601-14</Id><Title>Questions that need asking</Title><Msg>We're already seeings lots of people making suggestions about what questions Barack Obama and Mitt Romney should be debating Wednesday night. Everybody has a list. Among them is Mattea Kramer is senior research analyst at National Priorities Project. She writes Tough Talk for America: A Guide to the Presidential Debates You Won’t Hear: 1. Immediate deficit reduction will wipe out any hope of economic recovery: These days, it’s fashionable for any candidate to talk about how quickly he’ll reduce the federal budget deficit, which will total around $1.2 trillion in fiscal year 2012. And you’re going to hear talk about the Simpson-Bowles deficit reduction plan and more like it on Wednesday. But the hard truth of the matter is that deep deficit reduction anytime soon will be a genuine disaster. [...] Mattea Kramer 2. Taxes are at their lowest point in more than half a century, preventing investment in and the maintenance of America’s most basic resources: Hard to believe? It’s nonetheless a fact. By now, it’s a tradition for candidates to compete on just how much further they’d lower taxes and whether they’ll lower them for everyone or just everyone but the richest of the rich. That’s a super debate to listen to, if you’re into fairy tales. It’s not as thrilling if you consider that Americans now enjoy the lightest tax burden in more than five decades, and it happens to come with a hefty price tag on an item labeled “the future.” [...] 3. Neither the status quo nor a voucher system will protect Medicare (or any other kind of health care) in the long run: When it comes to Medicare, Mitt Romney has proposed a premium-support program that would allow seniors the option of buying private insurance. President Obama wants to keep Medicare more or less as it is for retirees. Meanwhile, the ceaseless rise in healthcare costs is eating up the wages of regular Americans and the federal budget. Health care now accounts for a staggering 24 percent of all federal spending, up from 7 percent less than forty years ago. Governor Romney’s plan would shift more of those costs onto retirees, according to David Cutler, a health economist at Harvard, while President Obama says the federal government will continue to pick up the tab. Neither of them addresses the underlying problem. [...] 4. The U.S. military is outrageously expensive and yet poorly tailored to the actual threats to U.S. national security: Candidates from both parties pledge to protect the Pentagon from cuts, or even, in the case of the Romney team, to increase the already staggering military budget. But in a country desperate for infrastructure, education, and other funding, funneling endless resources to the Pentagon actually weakens “national security.” Defense spending is already mind-numbingly large: if all U.S. military and security spending were its own country, it would have the nineteenth largest economy in the world, ahead of Saudi Arabia, Taiwan and Switzerland. [...] 5. The U.S. education system is what made this country prosperous in the twentieth century—but no longer: Perhaps no issue is more urgent than this, yet for all the talk of teachers unions and testing, real education programs, ideas that will matter, are nonexistent this election season. During the last century, the best education system in the world allowed this country to grow briskly and lift standards of living. Now, from kindergarten to college, public education is chronically underfunded. Scarcely 2 percent of the federal budget goes to education, and dwindling public investment means students pay higher tuitions and fall ever deeper into debt.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349192748601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349194153019-15</Id><Topic><Title>will the dressage horse tax write off continue?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349189367032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:49:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think the Dressage horse was written off as an educational expense. Lesson : Horses are obsolete, and a good truck'll go right through those pesky little barriers. and Only criminals posses horses trained to jump over barricades (the origin of the sport ya see, being the getaway horse).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349194153019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 12:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349195522200-16</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349188920321</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:42:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think you understood the decision. He's saying the employers can't choose what benefit plans to offer their employees umder 'BamaCare since choice of provider is a free choice economic activity. Obvious beating someone is not such an activity, although playing around on your wife could be one, a very very expensive one.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349195522200</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 12:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349195825155-17</Id><Topic><Title>47% of this Board has Disappeared</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349148992481</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 23:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see about ZERO chance the GOP takes the Senate. The House, maybe, try as they might to gerrymander Texas to eke out a few more Democratic seats. (you should see some of the districts these judges drew up, they make the Republican drawn redistricting map look absolutely boring, it's expressionism meets the cubist) Not gonna happen in the Senate though, not enough elections in vulnerable seats, though it would be amusing to see the OTHER MA senate seat go to a Republican as well. It would show signs that perhaps Boston is waking up.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349195825155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 12:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349197694145-18</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS debate &amp; ELECTION!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349122714181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMFAO-'Hope and Changers' are still 'clingin' to their Koran and 'Che' t-shirts!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349197694145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 13:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349198663805-19</Id><Topic><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone told me it'd go to 8.20 or so, so I cut my limit order to 8.40 just to "make sure" it fills . . . . and he asked why I didn't just buy at 8.8 anyway when I already have a pile at 9.14 or so, there's no point in that small a down average when I buy 500 shares at a time and I'm already at 2500 shares. Unless it gets THAT cheap its not worth the additional risk. Overall though, those without positions are idiots as this thing may take off at any time.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349198663805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 13:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349198847260-20</Id><Topic><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only reason to follow a stock board is if you have or intend to take in the near future a position in the eqity and are doing your due dilligence. If you've already done it and you decide its not a buy, you go away, if you decide its a short, then you short it and rag on the stock every day, now, answer your own question, WHY would he chose ETFC? Shorting is a serious business, limited upside, infinite downside, and if everyone is obeying the rules the shares you borrow could be called at any time, and if your broker can't borrow more to cover them, oh well . . .</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1349198847260</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 13:27:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349201689386-21</Id><Title>$8/70s today and $8.40s by tomorrow, then $8.20s coming....</Title><Msg>Keep falling and repeating the old cycle.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349201689386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349202033714-22</Id><Title>Q3-CC is scheduled on Oct. 16. Don't add until the AH. It will hit $7.50! Mark this!!</Title><Msg>I expect Q3 eps will be not so good....and ETFC will go under $8 easily with poor performance. DART is falling and margin interest is low. All brokers will go down with Q3 report.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349202033714</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349203585187-23</Id><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Msg>President Obama's Consumer Financial Protection Bureau Pick, Richard Cordray, Kicking Butt, AGAIN AmEx to refund $85 million to customers WASHINGTON (CNNMoney) -- American Express will refund $85 million for what government officials called deceptive practices involving about 250,000 customers. The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau said Monday that American Express (AXP, Fortune 500) subsidiaries illegally charged late fees, deceived customers by promising non-existent money rewards, and discriminated against new applicants over the age of 35. "Laws were violated at all stages of the game," said CFPB director Richard Cordray in a statement. In addition to refunding customers, American Express will pay a $27.5 million penalty that will be split among the CFPB, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp., the Federal Reserve and the Office of the Comptroller of the Currency. The American Express charges are the third to be announced this year from the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau that was launched last year. Last week, it struck a deal with Discover (DFS, Fortune 500) to refund $200 million, and in July with Capital One (COF, Fortune 500) to refund $140 million to customers for using deceptive marketing tactics and misleading cardholders.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349203585187</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349204109368-24</Id><Topic><Title>This week: ETFC will fall to $8.20s~8.30s</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349065932257</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 00:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really need to know 3 things to have a decent chance. The first and most important is the business and financials. The second is the overall market. Third is technical analysis. Moon has literally no idea about any of those. He looks at sites like Yahoo for key stats. That should tell you all you need to know. My kid can wake up in the morning and guess.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1349204109368</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349207648782-25</Id><Topic><Title>Questions that need asking</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349192748601</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 11:45:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadly.. All that you state, is true. American consumers are spoiled.. The piper will demand its dues.</Msg><Username>hellasmusic</Username><Timestamp>1349207648782</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 15:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349208200643-26</Id><Topic><Title>Blah Blah Blah Blah Blah ...</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1245102479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2009-06-15 17:47:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BBBBBLLLLLLLAAAAAAHHHHH!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1349208200643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349208398971-27</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like ETFC Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend</Title><Username>schultzbarker721</Username><Timestamp>1349179662692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 08:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good article working link</Msg><Username>sandywelch848</Username><Timestamp>1349208398971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349208423975-28</Id><Title>Insider Buing @ ETFC</Title><Msg>ETFC — last trade: $8.94 — Recent Insider Buys: Purchased Insider Title Shares Price/Share Value 08/13/2012 Rodger A. Lawson Director 7,528 $8.45 $63,610.85 08/13/2012 Frank J. Petrilli Board Member 119,250 $8.39 $999,994.7</Msg><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1349208423975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349208702153-29</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS debate &amp; ELECTION!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349122714181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean Romney - President and CEO of Bain Capital? The "outsourcing pioneers" ??</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1349208702153</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 16:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349212617267-30</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like ETFC Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend</Title><Username>schultzbarker721</Username><Timestamp>1349179662692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 08:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am waiting for. Thanks for giving out this article for free.</Msg><Username>chadwickchapman606</Username><Timestamp>1349212617267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349212731804-31</Id><Topic><Title>$8/70s today and $8.40s by tomorrow, then $8.20s coming....</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349201689386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 14:14:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr. Moon, what's your accuracy rate in pps predictions now? Is it still over 99.5%? Thank you.</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1349212731804</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:18:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349212745683-32</Id><Title>I bet $10,000 Mittens gets flustered and bets Obama $100K that his tax returns are clean</Title><Msg>Mittens might even go old school rich guy patrican and wave a cane or challenge Obama to a duel.....well , Mitt's 2nd, his dueling butler will be the one actually dueling.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349212745683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:19:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349213669171-33</Id><Title>Bernanke creating the third bubble</Title><Msg>** It’s the stock market that’s going to have to be carrying the load** The laugh is that Obama who is always touting redistrubution is now in fact distributing the wealth to the wealthy. If he had done a better job of focusing on the economy like a "lazerbeam" and let the private sector do what it does best create jobs, then the FED would not have to be playing god with the markets. The sad part is that Ben(subprime is contained)Bernanke is once again punishing the responsible savers and rewarding the speculators....didn't we see this movie before with Greenspan. reckless behavior. Take a look at a 25 year chart of the markets, three peaks, dotcom, housing bubble, and now the FED bubble. After the dotcom, and housing bubble there was a collaps. This rally from the bottom is not built on economic recovery, it is almost all FED QE and companies firing workers to raise productivity and profits. This bubble as be for will not end well when you have a market built on devaluing the dollar and money printing. So far the retail investor has not taken the bait, yet with the market rising on cheap money and the folks getting basically zero returns they will surcome and jump in...the market will have one more run up and then the party will be over. The small guy will again be the big loser as he gets in at the top, while the big money will be hedged or bailed out... sa la vi Little Guys Lose, Big Guys Win as Fed Takes Action Chairman Ben S. Bernanke is increasingly aiming for gains in stock prices as the Federal Reserve reaches for new tools to spur the three-year recovery and reduce unemployment stuck above 8 percent. In a speech yesterday in Indianapolis Chairman Ben S. Bernanke said higher stock and home prices would provide further impetus to spending by businesses and households. Photographer: Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg . Bernanke, setting the stage for a third round of quantitative easing in an Aug. 31 speech in Jackson Hole, Wyoming, said the strategy works in part by boosting the prices of assets such as equities. In a speech yesterday in Indianapolis he said higher stock and home prices would provide further impetus to spending by businesses and households. “It’s pretty clear that the stock market is the most important transmission mechanism of monetary policy right now,” said Peter Hooper, chief economist at Deutsche Bank AG in New York. “That’s where you’re getting most of the action in terms of lift to the economy. It’s the stock market that’s going to have to be carrying the load.” The Fed’s large-scale asset purchases will probably lift stocks by 3 percent over the two years following the Sept. 13 announcement of QE3 as low yields on government bonds push investors into risker assets, according to a Sept. 27 report by Deutsche Bank economists. They also estimate that QE will lift home prices by 2 percent over two years, assuming the Fed maintains purchases of Treasuries and mortgage debt through 2013.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349213669171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349214109567-34</Id><Topic><Title>I bet $10,000 Mittens gets flustered and bets Obama $100K that his tax returns are clean</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349212745683</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:19:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only gun the community organizer ever fired was one with a plastic stem and a rubber tip.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349214109567</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:41:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349214299562-35</Id><Title>O'reilly advice to Mittens on debate: Throw a mint julep in his face</Title><Msg>O'reilly added that Mitt should arrive in a sedan chair carried by a dozen trickle down butlers wearing tricorne hats as homage to the teaparty</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349214299562</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349214342664-36</Id><Title>Obama is Prepping For The Debate Like His Lady Parts Depends On It</Title><Msg>He served his term like his lady parts had a yeast infection.</Msg><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1349214342664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349214726416-37</Id><Title>Federal workers again partying on the taxpayers dime</Title><Msg>Perks of being a parasite government worker. **Events costs taxpayers more than $6 million while federal workers took free massages, limo rides, helicopter tours and Rockettes show tickets** VA employees turned Orlando conferences into taxpayer funded vacations Its budget and facilities already stretched thin, the Veterans Affairs Department wasted money on two summertime training conference to the vacation hot spot of Orlando, Fla., that cost taxpayers more than $6 million and let federal employees collect freebie gifts like meals, helicopter tours, limo rides, massages and show tickets from contractors, an internal investigation has found. The VA's inspector general concluded top agency officials failed to be good stewards of taxpayer money throwing conferences last year, including spending nearly $50,000 to create a parody video featuring the late Gen. George Patton. In all, federal investigators concluded about $762,000 of the money spent on the two events in July and August 2011 was wasteful, undercutting their legitimate human resources training mission for the conferences. "The issues described in this report and the lack of processes needed to control and track expenditures negatively affected the results of these HR conferences," Inspector General George Opfer wrote in the report released this week. "As VA moves forward, this report should serve as lessons learned that all VA management officials and staff share responsibility and accountability for meeting program objectives in an economical manner and reflect proper fiscal stewardship of taxpayer funds." Adding to the vacation-like atmosphere of the events, the watchdog found at least 11 VA employees accepted illegal gifts from hotels and other vendors seeking their business in connection with the conferences. VA officials toured three cities before choosing Orlando as the conference destination. The gifts they accepted during the selection process and subsequent conferences ranged from free lodging, room upgrades and limo rides to meals, gift baskets, gift cards, spa massages, Rockettes show tickets and a helicopter ride, the inspector general reported.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349214726416</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:52:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349214730848-38</Id><Title>Mittens will appoint an all male all mormon panel to repeal the 19th ammendment</Title><Msg>Mitt said it is obvious women belong only in 2 places , the bedroom and the kitchen, and never again will they be seen in the voting booth! "if god had meant women to vote he would have given them 2 brains like i have" said Mitt pointing to his crotch.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349214730848</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349215155869-39</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke creating the third bubble</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349213669171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow...3% and 2%!....Over TWO Years! Gosh...I can't Wait for Those Returns...Imagine the possibilities with All the Money! ...Have I mentioned just how Screwed we are Lately?...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349215155869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349215272700-40</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on democracy</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349188641763</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 10:37:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oct 2, 2012 | Victories Against GOP Voter Suppression Efforts Republicans have been on an all-out crusade against voting ever since they took control of numerous state legislatures in 2011. Here’s a map of where voting rights have come under attack: The good news is that there has also been a multi-pronged effort to push back against restrictive voting laws: And, in even better news, the pushback is working. Progressives achieved a tremendous victory today in Pennsylvania. A judge blocked most of Pennsylvania’s onerous voter ID law — for now. While the law remains on the books and voters will still be asked to present IDs, if they don’t have an ID they will still be allowed to vote on the voting machines like any other voter. (They may otherwise have been forced to cast provisional ballots which may never have been counted.) If the judge had not extended the transition period for voting without an ID, hundreds of thousands of eligible Pennsylvania voters could have been disenfranchised on Election Day. The Nation’s Ari Berman provides a round-up of our other victories in the GOP War on Voting: Voter ID Laws: Courts have nullified voter ID laws in Wisconsin and Texas (and, for now, in Pennsylvania), and a voter ID ballot initiative in Missouri. South Carolina’s law is blocked pending federal approval under Section 5 of the Voting Rights Act. Voter Registration: A federal court overturned Florida’s restrictions on voter registration drives for violating the First Amendment. Voters in Maine also repealed a ban on Election Day voter registration. Early Voting: After public outcry, the Ohio legislature repealed its own legislation cutting back on early voting days, but kept a ban on three days of early voting before the election, which a state court subsequently overturned (Ohio is appealing). A federal court blocked early voting limits in Florida in five counties covered by Section 5 of the Voting Rights Act for discriminating against African-American voters. Voter Purges: A district court in Iowa blocked an attempt by Iowa Secretary of State Matt Schultz to purge so-called “non-citizen” voters from the rolls. Student Voting: A New Hampshire court ruled that students do not have to register their car in the state in order to cast a ballot. Provisional Ballots: An Ohio judge ruled that provisional ballots mistakenly cast in the wrong precinct must be counted. Finally, in other voting news, the Republican National Committee and several state Republican parties in swing states are in hot water after their voter registration consultant — a GOP operative with a known history of questionable practices — was found to have turned in fraudulent voter registration forms in at least 10 Florida counties and perhaps elsewhere. The GOP has cut ties with the firm, leaving the GOP with no mass voter registration campaign in battleground during the key final weeks to register voters before pre-election deadlines. BOTTOM LINE: Despite their best efforts to restrict voting, it looks like voters will be spared the worst of new GOP voter suppression laws — this November anyway.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349215272700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349217091512-41</Id><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Msg>Video from drudge. Check out website.. To air on FOX NEWS tonight!! Yeah Yeah, I can hear you freaks saying it:(Use Smurf voice): Fox Lies!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349217159332-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Devestating rant!!! Oh, solid!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217159332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349217281163-43</Id><Title>Whats with all that pandering ?</Title><Msg>‘The Future Must Not Belong To Those Who Slander The Prophet Of Islam’ - Barak Hussein Obama</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1349217281163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349217365029-44</Id><Topic><Title>Whats with all that pandering ?</Title><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1349217281163</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:34:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mooo#$%$-id is a gay, rapin' pedophile!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217365029</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349217470348-45</Id><Topic><Title>a list of our friends and enemies</Title><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1113425267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2005-04-13 16:47:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry Dumbo!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217470348</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349217759213-46</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like ETFC Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend</Title><Username>schultzbarker721</Username><Timestamp>1349179662692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 08:07:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hoping it's good. Thanks for the link.</Msg><Username>richardsreid885</Username><Timestamp>1349217759213</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:42:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349218122595-47</Id><Topic><Title>a list of our friends and enemies</Title><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1113425267000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2005-04-13 16:47:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ET is huuuuuuuuuuuuuuugh !</Msg><Username>communist_rubbish</Username><Timestamp>1349218122595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:48:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349218319730-48</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh! The true meaning of 'Hope and Change'!!! Rev. Wright shout out!! Oh! Its political Super-Bowl time You Didn't Build That!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349218319730</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349218574357-49</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THE SHOUT OUT TO REV. WRIGHT, WHO IS IN AUDIENCE... 'My pastor, the guy who puts up with me, counsels me, listens to my wife complain about me. He's a friend and a great leader. Not just in Chicago, but all across the country'.. FOXNEWS 9 PM ET... 'We don't need to build more highways out in the suburbs. We should be investing in minority-owned businesses, in our neighborhoods'... Baraka Husseini Obomba</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1349218574357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349218753822-50</Id><Topic><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is $20 stock, but it trades below 10 because of Europe, US economy with the worst president in the US history, and a possible atack on Iran at any day now. Dow will go down 1300 - 1800 points in my opinion on the day Israel atack Iran. This is when I will buy 20,000 etfc shares at 5.92 Myop</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349218753822</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:59:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349218835635-51</Id><Topic><Title>Purchased 10000 etfc shares at 9.13 yesterday</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349183073349</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 09:04:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with you. It will explode at any day now.</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349218835635</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349219138672-52</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke creating the third bubble</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349213669171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 17:34:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Greenspan lowered the interest rate at the top of the housing bubble, and he knew what he was doing. It was like adding gasoline to the fire. What Greenspan and Bernanke have in common? They both are Iranians I think. No wonder.</Msg><Username>adsx_and_asgxf_investor</Username><Timestamp>1349219138672</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:05:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349219909314-53</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS debate &amp; ELECTION!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349122714181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did someone say KORAN ??? I'd like to bend over, grab my ankles and study KORAN together with my buddy Hussein ! love love love ! Pink ribbons and puppies and Jeremiah Wright !!!</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1349219909314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349222070385-54</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was gonna invest in a bidness but I invested my handouts at the liquor store.</Msg><Username>the_man_from_acorn</Username><Timestamp>1349222070385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 19:54:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349227586284-55</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS debate &amp; ELECTION!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349122714181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeeeuch ! Q4 just had a very public and messy wet dream.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1349227586284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 21:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349231870550-56</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry gals. Just ain't much there, is there.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1349231870550</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 22:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233460858-57</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233460858</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233460870-58</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233460870</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461044-59</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461083-60</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461083</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461094-61</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461156-62</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461156</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461318-63</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461318</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461509-64</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461509</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461535-65</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461535</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461697-66</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461841-67</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461841</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461928-68</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233461935-69</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233461935</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233462123-70</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233462123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233462224-71</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233462224</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233462229-72</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233462229</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233462339-73</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233462339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349233462379-74</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo October Surprise</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349217091512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 18:31:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You frigging coward, q4bike, No normal Repugnican would put up with you, because you lost it. It seems the kindergarten is in session again!!! Watch Faux??? Well, you're already insane!!!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1349233462379</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349234277278-75</Id><Title>pack your bags tories and Mitt sukubuses</Title><Msg>it's all over best head for the caymans or whereever your dressage horse will take you. but watch out, saddam can easily take over the caymans.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349234277278</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349234764660-76</Id><Title>Michelle bachman gay cure prayer clinics take over by bain</Title><Msg>Bain taking over Bachman gay prayercure clinics? Gonna convert to a pray for a cancer cure and more clinic</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349234764660</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349235517949-77</Id><Topic><Title>Another border patrol officer killed by Obama's illegal immigrants, with a "Fast and Furious" gun.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1349234582388</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:23:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You NRA maroons always say " guns don't kill people"</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1349235517949</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349235523176-78</Id><Title>GOP hate group- the FRC</Title><Msg>Dan Savage lashes out: “Tony Perkins Sits On A Pile Of Dead Gay Kids Every Day” Sex columnist Dan Savage lashed out at the Family Research Council saying: “Tony Perkins Sits On A Pile Of Dead Gay Kids Every Day”. Savage, who founded the It Gets Better Project for LGBT, spoke last week at Winona State University about “queer kids” killing themselves and said that “every dead kid is a victory for the Family Research Council.” He went on to explain why he thinks the Family Research Council is listed as a hate group by the Southern Poverty Law Center, saying: “Tony Perkins and the Family Research Council — First of all, they tell, Tony Perkins tells parents whose kids come out to reject them. Tony Perkins tells the parents of queer kids to do what Tony Perkins damn well knows drives those kids to suicide — doubles their already quadruple rate of suicide. Why would someone who calls themselves a Christian do that? Because every dead gay kid is a victory for the Family Research Council. They argue that the gay lifestyle is sick and sinful and dangerous and they point to the suicide rate, and then they turn around and do everything in their power to make sure that suicide rate does not come down and to drive it up. Tony Perkins sits on a pile of dead gay kids every day when he goes to work — and he calls himself a Christian. I don’t understand how real Christians let that little f-cker get away with that.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349235523176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:38:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349236718689-79</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS debate &amp; ELECTION!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349122714181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-01 16:18:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poll: Obama's lead with Latinos jumping to historic high Source: The Hill President Obama holds a 73-21 percent lead over Mitt Romney among Latino voters, a new high-water mark for the president. The new 52-point margin represents a high watermark for Obama in the weekly tracking poll from Latino Decisions, and is a significant jump from the 65-26 percent advantage he held six weeks ago. Romney has failed to make inroads despite a push at the GOP convention to highlight Hispanic Republicans, while Latino voters who have tuned in during the period shortly before and since the conventions have mostly gravitated towards Obama. Obama is polling a higher percentage in the poll than the 67 percent of the Latino vote he won four years ago, when GOP presidential nominee Sen. John McCain (R-Ariz.) won 31 percent, according to exit poll</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349236718689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-02 23:58:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>