<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346731882862-1</Id><Title>The Mitt-wit chronicles</Title><Msg>Mon Sep 03, 2012 at 05:00 PM PDT The Chronicles of Mitt: Sept 3, 2012 by Hunter pen on paper: 'Dear diary' Hello, human diary. It is I again, Mitt Romney, your better. Today is apparently "Labor Day," according to my advisers. I had never heard of it, but from what I understand it is a day in which all the people of America cease their activities and live only on the earnings in their stock portfolios. I have done that with frequency, but I was never aware there was a special day to honor the practice. I suppose I do recall it as being a bank holiday of some kind, now that they mention it, though that seems to make little sense. How would commoners know how much earnings their stock portfolios were generating that day if their bankers were absent? Setting all that aside, I am not sure why government should be in the business of dedicating special days for these things. Surely, if commoners want to take several days off and simply live on the earnings of their stock portfolios, they can do that whenever they like. Government should not specify a day of requirement for such things. Now that I look around, however, it seems very few of these people are adhering to the spirit of this day. Banking institutions are closed, but nearly all of these other businesses and eating establishments seem open. It seems the lower-income commoners simply do not know how to take time off and enjoy themselves. I find myself more committed than ever to ensuring the earnings from stock portfolios are taxed at a level as close to zero as possible, so that all these commoners will feel more comfortable leaving their places of work for the day and living on the earnings from their stock portfolios.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346731882862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 00:11:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346734152753-2</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're really incoherent. Janesville plant was scheduled for closure at the time Obama gave his speech in 2008. It was nothing new! Obama fired GM CEO Rick Wagoner in March 2009. Actual shut down took place in mid 2009 and Obama had plenty of time to interfere. So, no matter what GM management had in mind for the plant, Obama could change it at his own discretion. He did nothing! Now. Ryan's plan doesn't take a dime out of Medicare. No matter what cuts are scheduled, funds are staying in Medicare in order to save the program. Obama takes $716B OUT of Medicare to fund Obamacare. Stop your propaganda. you are not going to go away with lie.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346734152753</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 00:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346736537309-3</Id><Topic><Title>Bain investigated for TAX EVASION. Time for dipshidiot to turn over his returns.</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346560222021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-02 00:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why even bother, seriously, the pubs will state that is AMERICAN to evade taxes.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346736537309</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 01:28:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346766566661-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Mitt-wit chronicles</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346731882862</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 00:11:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It appears you read my hard drive, er, memory bank.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1346766566661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 09:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346768073528-5</Id><Title>3 more months...</Title><Msg>At most until we know whether they are calling the 12.5% notes.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1346768073528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:14:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346769124720-6</Id><Topic><Title>On Tuesday, ETFC will jump to $9+ Mark this!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346687137309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 11:45:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Marked. One of the 10 million posts which have turned out to be dead wrong.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346769124720</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346769388613-7</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the longtime GOP operative said Sunday. ”The man tells so many whoppers so often that I’m not sure he even knows when he’s lying.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346769388613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346769734101-8</Id><Topic><Title>3 more months...</Title><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1346768073528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm still trying to figure out how they are going to deal with that 112 million pre payment penalty. If they use the shelf, dilution to shareholders. If they re-fi then it's hard to make the numbers work at 6-7% which is about where etrade will be priced. I personally think they are simply better off waiting until the FED allows them to upstream a large amount of cash.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346769734101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346769749765-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me think you smoke Hydrocodine with your oxy... you hallucinate !! Not a well man.</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1346769749765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346770986565-10</Id><Topic><Title>Brak then Brak 4yrs 6T later</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346684127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's wif this bulshit? Caint link to articles, images or music anymore?. Fan-freakin tastic. What happen to avatars? Where be the default identity feature? Can only be described a bland, average and uninformative as it stomps on the creativity and free speech of its users.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346770986565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346772143709-11</Id><Title>The food stamp President</Title><Msg>Ask these folks if they are better off now then four years ago. This guy needs to go! Food-Stamp Use Climbs to Record, Reviving Campaign Issue Food-stamp use reached a record 46.7 million in June, the government said, as Democrats prepare to nominate President Barack Obama for a second term with the economy as a chief issue in the campaign. Participation was up 0.4 percent from May and 3.3 percent higher than a year earlier and has remained greater than 46 million all year as the unemployment rate stayed higher than 8 percent. New jobless numbers will be released Sept. 7.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346772143709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346772176042-12</Id><Title>R-Squared has the answers</Title><Msg>Bank on it -- vote in its favor ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Romney-Ryan ticket is pushing smart, pro-growth agenda By Brett M. Decker The Washington Times September 3, 2012 Hurricane Isaac might be pounding the GOP convention in Tampa this week, but on the political front, the skies are clear for Republicans looking toward this year’s election. During times of national crisis, the electorate acts rationally when presented with a clear alternative to the status quo that is responsible for the mess. In 2012, conservatives offer voters a comprehensive, united vision for cleaning up the Obama Great Recession and returning America to economic growth and prosperity. Taxation: The George W. Bush tax cuts are set to expire on Dec. 31. Letting the sun set on this package means an automatic tax hike of $3.2 trillion will wallop individuals and businesses as of New Year's Day 2013. In some states, the tax bill will jump by almost $6,000 per household. Overall, taxes would rise for 83 percent, including almost everybody making $60,000 or more, according to the Tax Policy Center. Stealing this fortune from the private sector and giving it to bureaucrats to waste on inefficient government programs mean it can’t be invested in job-creating enterprises. The right is united that extending these tax cuts is the least that must be done to attack the Obama unemployment surge. Energy: Polls show voters highly prioritize making the United States energy-independent. President Obama has pursued suicidal policies that have gutted our long-term energy-production capacity. These include deep-sixing the Keystone XL pipeline, persecuting the coal and oil industries, wasting billions on purportedly green technologies that don’t work, and prohibiting drilling in Alaska’s Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, the Gulf and all along our coasts. The movement challenging Mr. Obama for the Oval Office wants to, “Drill, baby, drill,” and undo other backwards liberal acts that threaten to starve U.S. industry and other consumers of needed power. Regulation: U.S. manufacturers are being suffocated by approximately 2,200 regulations imposed by the federal government over the past three decades. “In 2012, major regulations could reduce the total value of shipments from the manufacturing sector by up to $500 billion in constant 2010 dollars,” according to a new report released by NERA Economic Consulting and the Manufacturers Alliance for Productivity and Innovation. “Manufacturing exports in 2012 could be up to 17 percent lower than they would be without the estimated cost burden from major regulations.” The nanny-state regulatory agenda undermines U.S. competitiveness against foreign countries that pursue policies that don’t assume the corporate-government relationship has to be adversarial. The pro-business, conservative coalition wants to cut through the rat’s nest of red tape strangling America’s job creators. Debt: Republican National Committee Chairman Reince Priebus installed a debt clock at his party’s convention center in Florida. U.S. national debt is set to hit the heart-stopping $16 trillion mark about the time Mitt Romney makes his keynote address accepting the Republican nomination for president on Thursday. Since taking office, Mr. Obama has added nearly $5 trillion in debt, or more than was stacked up by the first 41 U.S. presidents combined, according to CNS News. The Obama administration’s trillion dollars in “shovel-ready” stimulus projects failed to jumpstart job growth and only dug the country deeper into a dark hole. The challengers promise to cut spending to lighten this millstone tied around the neck of the private-sector economy. A tropical storm may be hitting the Republican convention, but it’s Mr. Obama and the Democrats who need to worry about a November storm front moving in. Millions of Americans are jobless in the Obama economy. The president might literally feel their pain after this election is over.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346772176042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:22:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346772506325-13</Id><Topic><Title>Brak then Brak 4yrs 6T later</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346684127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Took you a week to figure it out, sigh!!! Yahoo was determined to kill the spammers and in the process took a lot of the fun out of the boreds.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346772506325</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346773435670-14</Id><Title>Eichenwald on taxation</Title><Msg>"a. The glory of tax cuts: Should taxes be cut? Of course. Should taxes be raised? Of course. Should interest rates be raised or lowered? Of course. And I am not contradicting myself. Each of these answers is correct depending on the economic circumstances at the time. Now, this topic is both so important and so involved that I need to break it down into pieces: 1. The Reagan tax cut mythology, part 1: Reagan’s tax cuts did not trigger an economic boom. In 1981, Reagan was correct that taxes needed to be cut; the American economy was facing an unprecedented beast called “stagflation” – inflation (normally associated with a runaway economy) and high unemployment (normally associated with low inflation.) The Federal Reserve, under chairman Paul Volker, needed to squelch inflation with a huge increase in interest rates, and did so (to see the horrors of this interest rate path, take a look at the historic rates for 20 year an 1 year Treasury bonds. One month before Reagan took office, the Prime Rate hit is all-time high of 21.5 percent. With the cost of money at the highest rates in history, economic activity had slowed to a near crawl. Outside of monetary policy, the other lever available to the government was fiscal; attempting to get more money in the hands of Americans — any Americans – was important to prevent the economy from falling off a cliff. Now, in the fantasy retelling of the Reagan years blathered out by modern Republicans with no knowledge or concern about economic history, the Reagan tax cuts passed in 1981, and the economy transformed into paradise. But that story is fiction. Instead, the tax cuts of 1981 went through – with carnival barkers like Arthur Laffer proclaiming that economic growth would rush in before the ink on the law was dry – and then precisely nothing happened. By 1982, the economy was in such bad shape that the GOP talking point was not “Reagan the magnificent,” it was the plea (a principled one) that Americans should “stay the course,’’ despite the fact that there had been no evidence of growth. In fact, the economy had grown significantly worse – beginning the first full quarter Reagan was in office through the 1982 election, the growth in Gross Domestic Product was negative 8.9 percent. (By way of comparison, for the comparable period in Obama’s term, GDP growth was positive 15 percent.) A few months after the 1982 election – in February 1983 – the Fed had finally cut the Prime Rate below 11 percent, less than half of what it was when Reagan took office. (PS – presidents don’t have any role in raising and lowering interest rates.) And, surprise! Economic growth returned. With the cost of money significantly cheaper, corporations and consumers unleashed a flurry of economic activity – by the end of the first half of 1983, GDP growth had reached positive 5.1 percent. By the 1984 elections. GDP had grown by just under 34 percent since January 1983. Now, did tax cuts help? Sure – they lessened the damaging impact of high interest rates and, when the economy turned around, they helped increase the amount of cash available for economic activity. But if interest rates hadn’t have fallen? Reagan would have been a one-term president and shuffled offstage by the GOP forever. 2. The Reagan tax cut mythology, part 2: One of the most revealing moments in the entire modern tax-cut debate occurred during Leslie Stahl’s interview of Eric Cantor, the House Majority Leader, on 60 Minutes. Actually, revealing isn’t the right word – terrifying is. Here was a man whose knowledge was critical in how this country would move forward, and he was woefully lacking. At one point, Stahl points out, despite Cantor’s protestations that Reagan never compromised, that Reagan in fact did raise taxes multiple times, with the biggest being in 1982 (before economic activity took off.) Cantor’s people were outraged by Stahl’s truthful recounting of history – outraged! ­– because it contradicted their Fairy Tales version of the Reagan years. “That just isn’t true,’’ one of Cantor’s aides yelled from off-camera, “And I don’t want to let that stand.” Cantor did nothing to correct his loudmouthed – and wrong – aide. In 1981, Reagan signed the Economic Recovery Tax Act – the tax cut law that GOPers slobber over to this day. The following year, in the bit of history excised from the Republican mind, Reagan signed the Tax Equity and Fiscal Responsibility Act (TEFRA). While Americans still received tax cuts when aggregated with the prior year’s law, TEFRA constituted the largest tax increase in American history at that time. Why did Reagan do it? Because he wasn’t, contrary to some GOP revisionists, a blind ideologue. After the adoption of the 1981 tax cuts, government analyses showed that the impact on four-year average impact on federal revenues would negative 2.89 percent of GDP. (Remember the whole supply side scam, that tax cuts pay for themselves? Well, they don’t.) After TEFRA, the four-year average was positive 0.98 percent. You see, it seems that when you increase tax, tax revenues go up. Funny, that. But, because the tax cuts were cumulative negative, deficits went up. The first time in American history when deficits exceeded $100 billion was in 1982. The deficits stayed above that number until 1998, during the Clinton Administration. The first surplus came in 1999. (For those who don’t remember economic history under Clinton, he raised taxes in 1993, and – surprise again – higher tax rates increased federal revenue and allowed the government to reduce the amount of publicly held debt outstanding. Funny, that.) 3. Reagan tax cut mythology part 3: At a meeting in the Oval Office, Obama commented on the fact that tax rates are lower now than they were under Reagan. After the meeting, Rep. Michelle Bachmann – one of the dangerous Republicans whose certainty to knowledge ratio might well be the first to exceed 100 percent – scoffed that Obama was fibbing. Of course, as the mantra goes, we have been pillories with higher taxes in the years after Reagan. But no – Obama was right. The total Average Federal Tax Rate for all income quintiles was between 21 and 22 percent in the Reagan years. When Obama took office, it was 17 percent. If the Democrats introduced the “Ronald Reagan Tax and Fairness Act” (I made the name up) calling for a return to the tax rates under Reagan, we would be talking about a 23 percent tax increase. Tax rates are at historic lows, which is why it is perfectly reasonable, in the face of massive federal debts, to raise them. 4. Laughing at the Laffer Curve: This has lasted for decades since Reagan, and I have touched on it above. But now let’s really delve into the most destructive mythology. In my opinion, Arthur Laffer has done far more damage to the future of America than Osama bin Laden. Here’s why: Laffer came up with his little device called “the Laffer Curve” which stated that tax revenues increased and then decreased once you moved up the rate scale from 0 percent to 100 percent. While there are some technical arguments about why the last number actually isn’t correct, theoretically, Laffer is correct. So, by his logic, there is a point where cutting taxes increases federal revenues. For now, I’ll accept that as true. But there is one huge problem with that argument: the Laffer Curve has no numbers! In other words, assuming Laffer is right, there is a point somewhere on the scale where tax rates bring in the highest amount of government revenues. And where is that number? Nowhere close to where it is now. The empirical analyses conducted by people who are less polemical than Laffer have come up with 68 percent, 70 percent and 35 percent. Whichever number you choose, they are all higher than the current rate of taxation. You see, what Republicans ignore is that it is the Laffer Curve, not the Laffer rising vector. There is some point – even if you want to assume that Laffer is right – where tax cuts decrease the amount of federal revenue. Since 1981, there has been a direct correlation between tax cuts and increases in the deficit. In other words, empirically, the tax rate was below the peal of the Laffer curve before cuts even started. Supply siders will #$%$ and moan at those numbers, but they are fact, not fantasy. Deficits went up under Reagan, down under Clinton and up (dramatically) under W. To argue that tax cuts pay for themselves is about as logical as saying Jesus rode dinosaurs – it is a statement made to justify a desired outcome, and not something based on any truth. 5. The Lucky Duckies who Pay No Taxes. The Wall Street Journal once wrote an editorial bemoaning the luck of the impoverished, since they don’t pay federal income taxes. At first, I thought it was a joke, and now it is a GOP talking point. They decry the lack of fairness to rich people, who are paying so, so much when others are getting a free ride. And this, as you might imagine, is utter bull. Here’s why: the Americans who are in the top 20 percent of income earners pay about 70 percent of federal taxes – but guess what? They also pull in about 60 percent of total pre-tax income, according to the Congressional Budget Office. In other words, they pay more in absolute dollars in income taxes because they have more income. The argument is akin to complaining that people living in mansions pay the majority of a town’s real estate taxes, while people renting apartments pay nothing. It’s both illogical and knowingly misleading. The statistics cited by the GOP speaks to income disparity not tax fairness. Now, there are 46 percent of Americans who pay no federal income taxes. The reason: they don’t make enough money. The income for twenty three percent of Americans is so low that, once they apply the personal deduction (which is taken by all taxpayers), their tax obligation goes to zero. This group includes the poor, the elderly, students, etc. The only way to bring in more cash from them, if it was possible, would be to cut the personal exemption (which the GOP would never do, because that would affect everyone) or dramatically increase taxes on low-income Americans. The other 23 percent who don’t pay taxes have enough income to pay after the personal exemption, but qualify for tax breaks that bring their bill to zero. This is seen at every income level – in fact, because of this, 1,470 millionaires paid no taxes in 2009. GOPers still moan that everyone should pay taxes by picking and choosing what they want to call a tax. Federal income taxes, in their lexicon, are the only ones that exist, ignoring payroll, state and local taxes. When actual tax burden – rather than bits and pieces of tax burden – are assessed, the bottom 20 percent of income earners pay 17 percent of the total tax bite, versus an effective rate of 30 percent for top earners. And guess what? Those numbers result in all the share of total taxes paid roughly matching the share of total income for each of the income groups. 6. The “Job Creators”: Let’s do the two-second version of this. A millionaire gets a $340,000 tax cut. And this translates into a job how? Maybe he’ll hire another housekeeper, maybe buy some more from Tiffany’s, but the vast majority of that money will not be spent on goods that drive the economy – it will be put into savings. Usually, that can be a good thing, but in a stagnant economy, the people whose financial activity creates jobs are the middle class. Give a middle class family $10 during a rough economy, they spend it. And that is how an economy gets moving. What we need is more tax cuts for the middle class, not tax cuts for the wealthy. (And, again, you have to look at actual numbers. The Bush tax cuts went into place in 2002: employment remained fairly stagnant until the financial crisis of 2008, when unemployment skyrocketed. They cuts have remained in place throughout the Obama Administration; so if the tax cuts fuel hiring, where the hell are the jobs? 7. The GOP is the party of tax cuts: I was horrified by something I saw in Obama’s first State of the Union in 2010 (not the GOP congressman who yelled out “you lie!” which should have led to his being sanctioned by Congress.) Instead, it was a point in Obama’s speech when he mentioned that the stimulus had given the middle class the greatest tax cut in history. It’s true – it did. This was not something I figured would be controversial. The Democrats jumped out of their seats and applauded. The Republicans did nothing – no applause, nothing. That was the moment that really put me on a path of contempt for a party I had once supported: they didn’t care about tax cuts, only about tax cuts for the rich. I had long considered that something of a canard, but from what I witnessed, I no longer had any doubt that Republican economic philosophy had nothing to do with economics (which was why so much of it was illogical) but instead was about one thing: their constituents wanted money. That’s it. The Laffer Curve, the fictionalization of the Reagan years, job creators, lucky duckies – all of that was no accident. It was a means of obfuscating the truth so that the middle class would sit by as the wealthy looted the federal treasury. And my realization was only reinforced in the years that followed: GOPers ranted and raved about the need for tax cuts for “job creators” but when the time came for a renewal of a payroll tax cut – which helped the middle class enormously but did almost nothing for the rich – the GOP fought it. When Obama proposed allowing the Bush tax cuts for the middle class to be renewed, the GOP refused, instead taking the proposal hostage in an attempt to force through tax cuts for the rich.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346773435670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:43:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346773880661-15</Id><Title>Eichenwald on the debt</Title><Msg>b. The debt. No matter how many times it’s said, the truth on this one struggles to become part of the American understanding. When George W. Bush assumed the presidency, the budget was in surplus and the projections showed that the government would be able to pay down much of its debt within the next six years. Then, came the Bush tax cuts. Beginning in 2002, the Federal government fell into deficit again – and hasn’t recovered since. The deficit is the annual contribution to the total debt owed by the federal government, and that number began climbing in 2002 in ways that are unprecedented in the history of the world. In 2002, the year that the first Bush budget was effective, the total outstanding debt of the United States was $6.2 trillion. It had barely budged in size from the previous year. By the end of the final Bush budget, the total outstanding debt had almost doubled, to $11.9 trillion. In the first two years of Obama budgets, the debt climbed to $13.6 trillion. But why? GOPers like to blame the stimulus – contrary to all available evidence. The stimulus did add an amount – extremely small as a percentage – in the short term. But Obama continued to have to work with the Bush tax cuts and the wars. The Bush tax cuts and the wars have been the single largest factor in the continued growth of the debt by far – both under Bush and under Obama. If the Bush tax cuts are allowed to expire at the end of this year, the Congressional Budget Office projects that future deficits will be cut in half. There is no way to accomplish that amount of cutback on the deficit by simply going after expenditures – particularly now that Romney and Ryan are pretending that they can kill Obamacare, leave Medicare untouched and increase military budgets. The numbers are simply impossible – there is no money there. Non-defense discretionary spending – areas like foreign aid, education and food safety that GOPers attack as being some huge driving force of deficits – account for only 15 percent of the budget. In other words everything the government does that isn’t military or Medicare only would provide $560 million if cut in its entirety. And the deficit would still be $800 billion – an unsustainable amount. Taxes must be increased if America is going to survive. c. The debt ceiling “debate”: There has never been a more irresponsible and reckless act on the part of any political party than the financial crisis engendered by the GOP in 2011 in its refusal to raise the debt ceiling limit without a fight; the real possibility was raised that America would, for the first time since its founding, default on its debt obligations to the world. The debt ceiling is nothing more than the legal limit on borrowing allowed for the federal government. Both houses of Congress have to approve the limit and have done so repeatedly since 1917. Usually, raising the debt ceiling was a perfunctory matter – it had been done 74 times since 1962. Reagan raised the debt ceiling 18 times and Bush II raised them 7 times – tax cuts have to be paid for with borrowings, after all. Put another way, Reagan raised the debt limit every five months, Bush every 13 months, and Obama every 15 months. (Clinton was every 24 months.) So, without the possibility of contradiction, the presidents who needed the debt ceiling raised the most often were Reagan and Bush, and the Republicans burbled happily as they did it. Suddenly though, in the middle of a global financial trauma, those same GOPers decided that now raising the debt ceiling mattered. And, somehow, they portrayed this as being representative of out-of-control spending by the Democrats. (I showed why that was bogus up above.) There were a few other things that the Republican talking points hid from America – raising the debt ceiling wasn’t about allowing future spending, it was about paying past bills. In other words, the money had already been spent – demanding cuts in future budgets did nothing to affect the structural debt. Now, American debt has been considered the safest investment globally for decades. Whenever international financial markets are rocked, investors take a flight to safety by buying American debt. Treasury bonds are part of untold thousands of investment strategies, used as a means of diminishing the risk profile of a portfolio. All of this works solely because of international faith that America would never default on its debt. But once the economic illiterates known as the Tea Partiers came into office, their hopes, wishes and assertions became the other side of an economic debate about facts, figures and reality. Oh, investors wouldn’t care about America not paying its obligated interest on the debt, they intoned, as the actual investors who owned the debt squealed about the impact of such a delay being disastrous. The Tea Partiers seemed to believe that the holders of American debt were little old ladies in Idaho, picking out breadcrumbs from their tea cozies while waiting for the next check from the government. And that ain’t reality. The vast majority of American debt is held by sophisticated international investors who, as I said, use Treasuries as part of a complex portfolio of investments. If the cash doesn’t arrive as planned, the investment strategy dies. If people trading Treasury bills know that there is a default, the value of those Treasuries would crash through the floor. The debate – which in truth was over nothing real – put at risk the global financial recovery, simply so the GOPers could score a few points and work to appease the economic idiots they had helped usher into government. That’s why, in the middle of this pointless debate, S&amp;P downgraded American debt from the first time in history – something that Romney and Ryan blame on Obama, which is, of course, a lie. The real reason? That the debt ceiling had been turned into a political football. S&amp;P wrote: The political brinksmanship of recent months highlights what we see as America’s governance and policymaking becoming less stable, less effective, and less predictable than what we previously believed. The statutory debt ceiling and the threat of default have become political bargaining chips in the debate over fiscal policy. Moreover, the country’s rating had been damaged because of the GOP’s apparent insistence to keep the Bush tax cuts in place. S&amp;P wrote: Our revised base case scenario now assumes that the 2001 and 2003 tax cuts, due to expire by the end of 2012, remain in place. We have changed our assumption on this because the majority of Republicans in Congress continue to resist any measure that would raise revenues, a position we believe Congress reinforced by passing the act. If Americans understood what had really happened in the debt ceiling debacle, and the possible horrific damage it could have inflicted on the country, they would – hopefully – run these people out of Washington and instead replace them with either Republicans more interested in governing than in rage or, if they can’t be found anymore, with Democrats.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346773880661</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346774161549-16</Id><Title>Bartlett on over regulation</Title><Msg>Misrepresentations, Regulations and Jobs By BRUCE BARTLETT Bruce Bartlett held senior policy roles in the Reagan and George H.W. Bush administrations and served on the staffs of Representatives Jack Kemp and Ron Paul. Republicans have a problem. People are increasingly concerned about unemployment, but Republicans have nothing to offer them. The G.O.P. opposes additional government spending for jobs programs and, in fact, favors big cuts in spending that would be likely to lead to further layoffs at all levels of government. Today’s Economist Perspectives from expert contributors. Republicans favor tax cuts for the wealthy and corporations, but these had no stimulative effect during the George W. Bush administration and there is no reason to believe that more of them will have any today. And the Republicans’ oft-stated concern for the deficit makes tax cuts a hard sell. These constraints have led Republicans to embrace the idea that government regulation is the principal factor holding back employment. They assert that Barack Obama has unleashed a tidal wave of new regulations, which has created uncertainty among businesses and prevents them from investing and hiring. No hard evidence is offered for this claim; it is simply asserted as self-evident and repeated endlessly throughout the conservative echo chamber. On Aug. 29, the House majority leader, Eric Cantor of Virginia, sent a memorandum to members of the House Republican Conference, telling them to make the repeal of job-destroying regulations the key point in the Republican jobs agenda. “By pursuing a steady repeal of job-destroying regulations, we can help lift the cloud of uncertainty hanging over small and large employers alike, empowering them to hire more workers,” Mr. Cantor said. Evidence supporting Mr. Cantor’s contention that deregulation would increase unemployment is very weak. For some years, the Bureau of Labor Statistics has had a program that tracks mass layoffs. In 2007, the program was expanded, and businesses were asked their reasons for laying off workers. Among the reasons offered was “government regulations/intervention.” There is only partial data for 2007, but we have data since then through the second quarter of this year. The table below presents the bureau’s data. As one can see, the number of layoffs nationwide caused by government regulation is minuscule and shows no evidence of getting worse during the Obama administration. Lack of demand for business products and services is vastly more important. Bureau of Labor Statistics These results are supported by surveys. During June and July, Small Business Majority asked 1,257 small-business owners to name the two biggest problems they face. Only 13 percent listed government regulation as one of them. Almost half said their biggest problem was uncertainty about the future course of the economy — another way of saying a lack of customers and sales. The Wall Street Journal’s July survey of business economists found, “The main reason U.S. companies are reluctant to step up hiring is scant demand, rather than uncertainty over government policies, according to a majority of economists.” In August, McClatchy Newspapers canvassed small businesses, asking them if regulation was a big problem. It could find no evidence that this was the case.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346774161549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 11:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346776226328-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Paul Ryan said Tuesday that he wasn’t suggesting that President Barack Obama was responsible for the closure of an auto plant in Janesville, Wis., during his convention speech last week. “What they are trying to suggest is that I said Barack Obama was responsible for the plant shutdown in Janesville. That is not what I was saying; read the speech. What I was saying is the president ought to be held to account for his broken promises. After the plant was shut down, he said he would lead efforts to restore the plant. It’s still idle,” said Ryan on NBC’s “Today"... ...Ryan, who is from Janesville, said the president had promised to “retool the plant.” ... Asked on ABC to respond to Vice President Joe Biden’s line that Osama bin Laden is dead and GM is alive, Ryan responded, “General Motors isn’t alive in my hometown.” ------------- So the liar says he was misunderstood. He's implying he wanted BO to override GM mgt. decision to force them to retool Janesville, in other words, clean up the GOP mess. Can you imagine the GOP screams had BO interfered with GM to force Janesville retooling? The reality is BO commented in Feb. 2008. By late 2008, the GOP economy had tanked to the point that GM decided to close Janesville. It wasn't BO's call or responsibility by then. Ryan needs to get a new lie, this dog won't hunt.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346776226328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346776666339-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ly'in Ryan</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346730780441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Paul Ryan became Mitt Romney's running mate with a reputation, in the Beltway press at least, as the Republican who engaged seriously and truthfully with policy, an earnest wonk who'd lay out his case with statistics, not talking points. But in the wake of the convention speech that gave every fact-checker in the nation a serious workout and his marathon lie that suggested that Ryan lies not just for political gain but for the hell of it, that reputation has taken a beating. The press is waking up to the fact that Ryan is not just a politician but a 21st century Republican politician, with all that implies about his truthfulness. But Jonathan Chait points out that Paul Ryan has always been a liar; what's new is that the media is noticing it: Ryan seems to have fallen victim to circumstances he didn’t quite foresee. The Romney campaign has spent the last several weeks practically daring the national press corps to call out its lies. Well beyond the usual exaggerations of a national campaign, Romney has built its entire message around two accusations — “you didn’t build that” and “just send them a check” — that are obviously false. A day before Ryan’s speech, a Romney adviser told reporters, “We're not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers.” The media that had spent the last two and a half years nuzzling gently in Ryan’s lap had been prodded with sharp sticks and reacted in the predictable fashion, though probably not predictable to Ryan himself. The thing about Ryan is that he has always resided in a counter-factual universe. He is a product of the hermetically sealed right-wing subculture. Many of the facts taken for granted by mainstream economists have never penetrated his brain. Ryan burst onto the national scene with a dense, fact-laden attack on the financing of Obama’s health-care bill that was essentially a series of hallucinations, pseudo-facts cooked up and recirculated by conservative apparatchiks who didn’t know what they were talking about or didn’t care. His big-think speeches reflect the influence of fact-free conservatives and collapse under scrutiny. We're talking about the traditional media, here. Of course the full scope of Ryan's falsehoods and fraudulence as a policy expert and deficit hawk will never be fully reflected in the Associated Press, the Washington Post, or the New York Times. Definitely not in PolitiFact. But at least they're getting past the view that if Paul Ryan says something, it should be taken seriously and at face value. For that, we owe Runner's World a debt of gratitude."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346776666339</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346777459829-19</Id><Title>Dipshidiot admits we're better off!!!</Title><Msg>Romney On Whether We’re Better Off: ‘Of Course It’s Getting Better’ By Pat Garofalo on Sep 4, 2012 at 9:30 am The Romney campaign this week is reprising former President Reagan’s “are you better off?” question, in an attempt to paint President Obama as a failure when it comes to the economy. “He can’t tell you that you’re better off,” said Vice Presidential candidate Paul Ryan. “Simply put, the Jimmy Carter years look like the good old days compared to where we are now.” Romney introduced the theme during his speech before the Republican National Convention, saying, “every president since the Great Depression who came before the American people asking for a second term could look back at the last four years and say with satisfaction: ‘you are better off today than you were four years ago.’ Except Jimmy Carter. And except this president.” “Saying that things are better off is an insult,” added Romney campaign adviser Eric Fehrnstrom. But if it’s an insult to say that the economy is better off, then Mitt Romney has been slinging some insults of his own, considering how he answered a question from conservative talk radio host Laura Ingraham back in January: INGRAHAM: You’ve also noted that there are signs of improvement on the horizon in the economy. How do you answer the president’s argument that the economy is getting better in a general election campaign if you yourself are saying it’s getting better? ROMNEY: Well, of course it’s getting better. The economy always gets better after a recession, there is always a recovery. […] INGRAHAM: Isn’t it a hard argument to make if you’re saying, like, OK, he inherited this recession, he took a bunch of steps to try to turn the economy around, and now, we’re seeing more jobs, but vote against him anyway? Isn’t that a hard argument to make? Is that a stark enough contrast? ROMNEY: Have you got a better one, Laura? It just happens to be the truth. When President Obama took office, the economy was shedding 800,000 jobs per month and contracting at a rate of 8.9 percent. As Time’s Michael Grunwald noted, at that pace, “we would have shed the entire Canadian economy in 2009.” Literally four years ago, in September 2008, the U.S. was gripped by financial panic. Investment banks were failing, mortgage giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac were placed into conservatorship, and the groundwork was being laid for the Bush administration’s $700 billion bailout of the financial system. Now, a slow recovery has taken hold, which is undoubtedly an improvement. And not that long ago, Romney himself was willing to concede as much.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346777459829</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 12:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346782149031-20</Id><Title>Obama moving to smaller venue</Title><Msg>The magic is gone. Mr. hope and change can't round up enough dopes to fill the place up even with bringing in folks from out of state...you gota love it! Democrats set to move Obama's big speech from 74,000-seater outdoor stadium to 20,000-seater indoor arena Democrats are poised to avoid the danger of President Barack Obama accepting his party’s nomination before a partially-empty stadium by shifting his speech to an indoor arena and citing ‘severe weather’. The Obama campaign have been working desperately to ensure that the 74,000-seater Bank of America stadium in Charlotte would be filled. Buses for students from across North Carolina and even members of black churches in neighboring South Carolina have been arranged.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346782149031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:09:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346782946531-21</Id><Topic><Title>Obama moving to smaller venue</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346782149031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe they should choose a broom closet. One big enough to hold the messiah's 'Empty Chair'!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346782946531</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346783364597-22</Id><Title>Some tax history</Title><Msg>It was Republican Abraham Lincoln who created the first federal income tax to finance the Civil War. And it was Republican William Howard Taft who helped enact the 16th Amendment to the Constitution to overcome constitutional objections to a permanent income tax. And it was Republican Herbert Hoover who raised the top income tax rate from 24 percent to 63 percent in 1932 when the Great Depression decimated federal revenues. …In the 1950s, Republican Dwight Eisenhower fought his own party to keep the top tax rate over 90 percent, saying it was needed to help balance the budget. Republican Richard Nixon signed into law the Tax Reform Act of 1969, which raised the capital gains tax rate from 25 percent to 35 percent and created a minimum tax to ensure that the rich could not escape taxation through the use of tax loopholes. Republican Gerald Ford supported the Tax Reform Act of 1976, which raised the minimum tax and further restricted tax loopholes for the wealthy. On signing it into law, he said, “We are moving toward a tax system under which each taxpayer bears his or her fair share of the overall tax burden.” Republican Ronald Reagan supported taxing capital gains as ordinary income – they are now taxed much less – and supported higher taxes on corporations. -------- “What we’re trying to move against is institutionalized unfairness. We want to see that everyone pays their fair share, and no one gets a free ride. Our reasons? It’s good for society when we all know that no one is manipulating the system to their advantage because they’re rich and powerful.” Ronald Reagan, June 6, 1985</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346783364597</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346786495689-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama moving to smaller venue</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346782149031</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 14:09:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I went ahead and did my version of Eastwooding this morning on FB. It was an empty chair wif an empty suit hanging next to it out in the garage.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346786495689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 15:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346789093263-24</Id><Title>$8.80s tomorrow and $9+ by Friday!!</Title><Msg>It's about time again....</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346789093263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346789907111-25</Id><Title>16T</Title><Msg>That should give those homercraps a little something extra to mull over this evening.</Msg><Username>marthamccallums_bathwater</Username><Timestamp>1346789907111</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346791012314-26</Id><Topic><Title>Ly'in Ryan</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346730780441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you ever hope to be taken seriously here jb, you got to start getting your apostrophe situation under control.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346791012314</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346792757451-27</Id><Title>Dumbo Lies, Lies Lies!!!</Title><Msg>Composite Girlfriends??? Is any part of his 2 Autobiographies true??? Is pathological lying the only thing Dumbo has achieved...Ever??</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346792757451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346792989488-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ly'in Ryan</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346730780441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 23:53:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody, and I mean nobody can lie like good old Billy Clinton......"It depends on what the meaning of the word 'is' is".</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346792989488</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346793433982-29</Id><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Msg>I don't think he would be as close in the polls with his dismial record. The "big" question is are the folks that are saying they are going to vote for the junior senator and community organizer saying it to the caller as not to sound racist?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346794334715-30</Id><Title>Welfare lie vanishes</Title><Msg>Tue Sep 04, 2012 at 11:40 AM PDT The end of the Romney welfare lie? by Joan McCarter Republican U.S. presidential candidate Mitt Romney and U.S. Congressman Paul Ryan (R-WI) wave after Romney introduced Ryan as his vice-presidential running mate during a campaign event at the battleship USS Wisconsin in Norfolk, Virginia &amp;nbsp;August 11, 2012. attribution: REUTERS Liars. Steve Benen notes that something big was missing from the remarks Paul Ryan and Mitt Romney gave at the convention, along with every other major RNC speaker's speeches: the big lie that President Obama is gutting the work requirement in welfare. That lie had dominated the airwaves with five separate ads and was in all of Romney's stump speeches. And last week, it was gone. Benen: Romney has given three speeches since his convention address, delivering remarks in Lakeland, Jacksonville, and Cincinnati. The combined total of references to welfare in those speeches? Zero. Also, I spoke this morning with a Democratic source who confirmed that the Romney campaign's television ad featuring the welfare lie is not currently on the air. So, over the course of about a week, this one transparent falsehood went from being the most potent attack in the Republican arsenal to a lie Romney and his team suddenly didn't want to repeat. Why Romney has given up the welfare attack, and for how long, is the big question. Was the campaign finally overcome by a sense of decency? Seems highly unlikely. Did all the fact-checking organizations and traditional journalists who reported on the attacks and called them out as lies finally convince the campaign that the media wasn't going to let them get away with it? Again, hard to believe since, as of last Tuesday, the campaign said it was going to stick with the lie because it worked, and that "we’re not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact checkers." The most likely answer was noted by our own Greg Dworkin last Thursday: National Journal's Ron Fournier, a highly respected inside-the-beltway reporter and narrative setter laid it out: Romney is cynically playing the race card. When a charge like that comes from someone like Fournier, the rest of the establishment starts paying attention. That could have been damaging enough to Romney to have finally scared the campaign off. Whatever the reason, the welfare attack has disappeared, for now. But don't be surprised if it comes back. Romney and Ryan have already proven that there's nothing they won't say, no level to which they will not sink, to win.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346794334715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346795495736-31</Id><Title>September 2008</Title><Msg>Are We Better Off? 10 Headlines From September 2008 By Zack Beauchamp and Judd Legum on Sep 4, 2012 at 11:40 am Recently, the Romney campaign has taken to telling voters that Obama “can’t tell you that you’re better off” now than four years ago. While the economic numbers suggest otherwise, there’s a simpler way to understand the reality of four years ago: take a look at what people were saying at the time. September 2008 was the month where the financial crisis — caused in significant part by Republican-supported deregulation of the financial industry — really took off, a point reflected clearly in the newspaper headlines from the time: STOCK SHOCK FELT ROUND THE WORLD. Gets ‘nasty’ as Lehman tanks, Merrill vanishes, AIG wobbles [New York Daily News, September 16, 2008] Depression Coming? Boil Some Beans; Ladies Who Quilt Give Tips On Surviving Tough Times [Albuquerque Journal, September 21, 2008] One day on the brink On Wednesday, it seemed U.S. economy might collapse [St. Louis Post-Dispatch, September 21, 2008] ‘Great Depression’ closer than U.S. admits, report finds [Pittsburgh Tribune-Review, September 27, 2008] Will Bush become the new Hoover? [Politico, September 19, 2008] Developers bend under housing meltdown [Colorado Springs Gazette, September 27, 2008] Depression seen possible [Florida News-Press, September 27, 2008] Wall Street Meltdown Continues [CNN, September 17, 2008] Is It Really the Next ‘Great Depression’? [NPR, September 19, 2008] Behind Closed Doors, Warnings of Calamity [The New York Times, September 20, 2008]</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346795495736</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346801563230-32</Id><Topic><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he were not black, he'd lead by ten percentage points, and the tea party would not exist.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1346801563230</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 19:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346802175271-33</Id><Topic><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How 'The Shy Republican' Could Be Masking a Landslide By Adam Shaw At time of writing, polls show the race for the presidency to be tight. General consensus seems to be that whoever wins, the 2012 election will be won by a bat squeak. Yet to many, especially those of us on the right, it seems peculiar that Obama is still remotely in the race. With high unemployment, minimal GDP growth, a 100% increase in food stamp costs, and out-of-control spending, many conservatives are asking how just under half of the American population can possibly want more of the same. While it is not possible now to get into the many reasons certain people will vote Democrat in November, I propose that all polls, not just left-leaning polls, may be being strongly misled by their data, and Romney/Ryan may actually have a huge lead not seen in polls. It is my contention that this is due to a mix of the infamous Bradley effect and what is known in Britain as "the Shy Tory Factor," with both coming together to exaggerate just how popular Obama is in America. The Bradley effect is a much-debated polling distortion that is easy to demonstrate but difficult to prove. The idea that when a black or minority candidate is on the ticket against a white candidate, certain voters may lie under pressure from a pollster, worried about being seen as a racist for choosing the white candidate over the minority, sounds highly plausible. The consequence, should the Bradley effect be in play, would be a skewed poll indicating that the minority candidate is in better political shape than his or her opponent. Some argued that while it may have been a factor in the past, it was not a factor in the 2008 election, when Barack Obama was elected convincingly, just as polls predicted. Yet this dismissal may be premature. A closer look at the statistics shows that predictions for how much of the white vote Obama would win were strongly exaggerated by polling companies. For instance, a CBS poll near election day predicted that McCain would win the white vote by a mere 3%, and on election day the Republican actually brought in 12% more of the vote than the Democrat. Had it not been for an unusually high turnout among blacks and minorities, Obama's landslide would have been a lot closer. Therefore, there is no reason why we cannot expect at least a similar Bradley effect this year. In fact, it could possibly be even stronger -- after all, the liberal smear that those who oppose Obama are racist is one that really took off since Obama took office, specifically with the rise of the Tea Party. This could serve only to magnify the Bradley effect, as some white voters may feel ashamed of being seen as sympathetic to a "racist" organization. Yet there is another factor that, mixed with Bradley, could radically distort the numbers -- and it is a concept not known in America, but known very well in the United Kingdom. Called "The Shy Tory Effect," it could be the little-known variable that could be hiding a landslide for Mitt Romney. The concept was coined after the British general election of 1992, the result of which stunned the pollsters, the politicians, and the media. After 13 years in office, the ruling Conservative Party was Thatcher-less and divided. Led by their extreme Welsh socialist leader Neil Kinnock (the same Neil Kinnock whose speeches Joe Biden had already ripped off), the left-wing Labour Party were firmly ahead in the polls. Britain was drifting toward a socialist authoritarianism that they hadn't experienced since the 1970s. As election day approached, Labour held a chunky lead, causing Kinnock to yell giddily into the microphone in his final speech to the Party before election day, "We're all right, we're all right" repeatedly, to rapturous applause. It seemed Labour had it in the bag. The only exception was the cool and collected Tory prime minister, John Major, whose internal polling suggested that things were not as they seemed. As the results came in on election night, Labour started off celebrating. However, by 10 o'clock, the BBC's exit poll predicted that Labour might not win, but there would be a hung parliament, which would still probably cause Kinnock to be prime minister of a coalition. Yet the final result was a total shock -- a comfortable win for the Tories, losing a few seats, but picking up the highest total number of votes for any political party since 1951. Left-wing pundits couldn't explain what had happened.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346802175271</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 19:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346802953374-34</Id><Topic><Title>3 more months...</Title><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1346768073528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 10:14:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the FED doesn't let them upstream capital the most I could see them doing is a partial call of about 200 mil total, about half their corporate cash. I don't really think dilution makes sense at this PPS since it wouldn't be that accretive to earnings.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1346802953374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 19:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346803896337-35</Id><Topic><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*If he were not black, he'd lead by ten percentage points, and the tea party would not exist* You coudn't be more wrong, if he were white McCain would have been President today. White guilt played a huge roll in the 2008 election, and the "big" question still is will folks vote their pocketbooks this time around, or not want to kick out the first black(although Clinton had that intial label) President.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346803896337</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346804066878-36</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The plant was shut down in mid 2009, not in December 2008. Obama was in charge of GM after he fired GM CEO in March 2009. Obama is completely responsible for everything happened with GM therafter. He failed on his promise. Try again.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346804066878</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346806794547-37</Id><Topic><Title>$8.80s tomorrow and $9+ by Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346789093263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346806794547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 20:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346811121053-38</Id><Topic><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most any Dem. could have won in 2008 given the unmentionable GOP President of the previous eight years. If Obama had been white, there would have been far less right wing energy devoted to defeating him and everything he tried to accomplish at every possible turn from day one of his term.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1346811121053</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346812076990-39</Id><Topic><Title>If Barrack was white</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346793433982</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:17:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joeleo, If "he were" not black.........you must be a webe? We be taking the chicken, we be taking the silver ware, we be taking the napkins, we be taking the key to the toilet, but we be leaving no tip! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346812076990</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346812430866-40</Id><Topic><Title>16T</Title><Username>marthamccallums_bathwater</Username><Timestamp>1346789907111</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 16:18:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No use of putting up a debt clock at the DNC, they can't count that far! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346812430866</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:33:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346812626727-41</Id><Topic><Title>Dirty Harry erased</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346695795845</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 14:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"General Motors ad during the superbowl" It was Chrysler...please pay attention. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346812626727</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:37:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346813763093-42</Id><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Msg>I will open tihs up to anyone who can give an honest opinion as Pacifican will NOT answer and wilol only try and change the subject. How can an argument be made that it was the C.R.A. LAW that caused the financial meltdown when only regulated banks had to follow the law, given this info? "Federal Reserve Board data show that: **More than 84 percent of the subprime mortgages in 2006 were issued by private lending institutions. **Private firms made nearly 83 percent of the subprime loans to low- and moderate-income borrowers that year. **Only one of the top 25 subprime lenders in 2006 was directly subject to the housing law that's being lambasted by conservative critics.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346814734329-43</Id><Title>What did Michelle Obama really say?</Title><Msg>Get comfortable with sacrifing more...and more.... Wants you to believe they're just like you. Make no mistake... they're not. Populist garbage. Other than that... I thought she was charming.</Msg><Username>krisspcritter_da_1</Username><Timestamp>1346814734329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346816416381-44</Id><Topic><Title>Pacifican says : "Liar" loans were originated by Fannie and Freddie too. Your "unregulated" institution argument has no merit</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346813763093</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 22:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posted on Sun, Oct. 12, 2008 Private sector loans, not Fannie or Freddie, triggered crisis David Goldstein and Kevin G. Hall | McClatchy Newspapers last updated: November 24, 2010 01:49:33 PM WASHINGTON — As the economy worsens and Election Day approaches, a conservative campaign that blames the global financial crisis on a government push to make housing more affordable to lower-class Americans has taken off on talk radio and e-mail. Commentators say that's what triggered the stock market meltdown and the freeze on credit. They've specifically targeted the mortgage finance giants Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac, which the federal government seized on Sept. 6, contending that lending to poor and minority Americans caused Fannie's and Freddie's financial problems. Federal housing data reveal that the charges aren't true, and that the private sector, not the government or government-backed companies, was behind the soaring subprime lending at the core of the crisis. Subprime lending offered high-cost loans to the weakest borrowers during the housing boom that lasted from 2001 to 2007. Subprime lending was at its height from 2004 to 2006. Federal Reserve Board data show that: More than 84 percent of the subprime mortgages in 2006 were issued by private lending institutions. Private firms made nearly 83 percent of the subprime loans to low- and moderate-income borrowers that year. Only one of the top 25 subprime lenders in 2006 was directly subject to the housing law that's being lambasted by conservative critics. The "turmoil in financial markets clearly was triggered by a dramatic weakening of underwriting standards for U.S. subprime mortgages, beginning in late 2004 and extending into 2007," the President's Working Group on Financial Markets reported Friday. Conservative critics claim that the Clinton administration pushed Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac to make home ownership more available to riskier borrowers with little concern for their ability to pay the mortgages. "I don't remember a clarion call that said Fannie and Freddie are a disaster. Loaning to minorities and risky folks is a disaster," said Neil Cavuto of Fox News. Fannie, the Federal National Mortgage Association, and Freddie, the Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corp., don't lend money, to minorities or anyone else, however. They purchase loans from the private lenders who actually underwrite the loans. It's a process called securitization, and by passing on the loans, banks have more capital on hand so they can lend even more. Conservative critics also blame the subprime lending mess on the Community Reinvestment Act, a 31-year-old law aimed at freeing credit for underserved neighborhoods. Congress created the CRA in 1977 to reverse years of redlining and other restrictive banking practices that locked the poor, and especially minorities, out of homeownership and the tax breaks and wealth creation it affords. The CRA requires federally regulated and insured financial institutions to show that they're lending and investing in their communities. Conservative columnist Charles Krauthammer wrote recently that while the goal of the CRA was admirable, "it led to tremendous pressure on Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac — who in turn pressured banks and other lenders — to extend mortgages to people who were borrowing over their heads. That's called subprime lending. It lies at the root of our current calamity." Fannie and Freddie, however, didn't pressure lenders to sell them more loans; they struggled to keep pace with their private sector competitors. In fact, their regulator, the Office of Federal Housing Enterprise Oversight, imposed new restrictions in 2006 that led to Fannie and Freddie losing even more market share in the booming subprime market. What's more, only commercial banks and thrifts must follow CRA rules. The investment banks don't, nor did the now-bankrupt non-bank lenders such as New Century Financial Corp. and Ameriquest that underwrote most of the subprime loans. These private non-bank lenders enjoyed a regulatory gap, allowing them to be regulated by 50 different state banking supervisors instead of the federal government. And mortgage brokers, who also weren't subject to federal regulation or the CRA, originated most of the subprime loans. In a speech last March, Janet Yellen, the president of the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, debunked the notion that the push for affordable housing created today's problems. "Most of the loans made by depository institutions examined under the CRA have not been higher-priced loans," she said. "The CRA has increased the volume of responsible lending to low- and moderate-income households." In a book on the sub-prime lending collapse published in June 2007, the late Federal Reserve Governor Ed Gramlich wrote that only one-third of all CRA loans had interest rates high enough to be considered sub-prime and that to the pleasant surprise of commercial banks there were low default rates. Banks that participated in CRA lending had found, he wrote, "that this new lending is good business." McClatchy Newspapers 2008</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346816416381</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346817166705-45</Id><Topic><Title>What did Michelle Obama really say?</Title><Username>krisspcritter_da_1</Username><Timestamp>1346814734329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:12:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What did Ann Romney say? She said, I need a fifth level to park my caddillacs.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1346817166705</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:52:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346817462385-46</Id><Title>Michelle Kicked Romney's Huge White Bottom !!!</Title><Msg>Michelle has better arms than slayer and all his butt buddies put together. She's lean and mean. And she speaks from reality. Not fantasy liked the Romneys. Mitt's toughest job was to ask for loans from his wealthy Daddy, when his trust funds were emptied. And Mitten's military experience was to run to France. MITTENS BECAME FRENCH WHEN AMERICA CALLED ! And he tells students today to just ask their parents for $$$$$$ . As if everyone had wealthy parents. 1%. Totally out of touch. Michelle brings it all back to reality.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1346817462385</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346817538541-47</Id><Title>Where's the GOP outrage?</Title><Msg>Former SEAL’s Book Reveals Classified Information: Pentagon Source: Bloomberg News The Pentagon’s chief spokesman said for the first time that a book written by a former Navy SEAL who participated in the raid that killed Osama bin Laden contained classified information. “Sensitive and classified information is contained in the book,” spokesman George Little said today at a Pentagon news conference. The comment escalates a conflict between the Pentagon and the author who wrote “No Easy Day: The Firsthand Account of the Mission That Killed Osama Bin Laden.” Little has previously said the author, who wrote under the pen-name “Mark Owen,” violated a non-disclosure agreement he signed as a Navy SEAL by not submitting the book for pre-publication review. The author’s attorney, Robert Luskin, has said a 2007 agreement “invites but by no means requires” pre-publication review. Luskin didn’t immediately respond to phone and e-mailed requests for comment today. The book was scheduled for publication today by Dutton, a unit of Penguin Group USA.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346817538541</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 23:58:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>