<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346472157512-1</Id><Title>still short 300 FB @ $27.50 ...yea baby...</Title><Msg>I would have been short 600 shares, but, know it all Mrs Bear thought FB would be over $100. Oh well, no big loss, she would have spent da money on something stupid any way. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Oh, I don't own E-Tub so I don't have a doggie in da fight-so to speak-but, Walley heard Yinz is in serious talks with AMTD along with some hedge fund. Don't get too excited, Da OTS, your regulator, will never permit a hedge fund-aka Kenny Boy &amp; friends-to own an FDIC bank. If any news breaks, it's a good time to dump. happy LD. So, who gets da day off, huh? Anybuddy? Ans: Da suits! )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1346472157512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346473137000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Longs?</Title><Username>mica_winona18</Username><Timestamp>1346471221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 23:47:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Promised Profit</Msg><Username>kary_malissa145</Username><Timestamp>1346473137000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346475983000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Longs?</Title><Username>mica_winona18</Username><Timestamp>1346471221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 23:47:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am Impressed!!!</Msg><Username>marlo_ivy48</Username><Timestamp>1346475983000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 01:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346478545000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Longs?</Title><Username>mica_winona18</Username><Timestamp>1346471221000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 23:47:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic. I will check it out.</Msg><Username>tomi_theodora15</Username><Timestamp>1346478545000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 01:49:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346484429851-5</Id><Topic><Title>clint denounced W's invasion of bushghanistan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346424917264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Darn, yes. Than what "bushghanistan" means? We had no business in Afghanistan? So, we are 3.5 more years in this war after Obama took it over. Taliban is right where it was with no signs of surrender. The number of Americans killed is going up. Troop moral is going dow because of abscence of clear strategy and clear goal. And the press pretends this war doesn't even exists. Much like covergae of Iraq, right? Are we ready to get out now? What a hell are we trying to accomplish? Nation building? That what the left was mocking Bush for. So, now it is OK under Obama? If the answer is no, to troop withdrawal now than what magic 2014 will change? That was the question Eastwood asked.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346484429851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 03:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346503201266-6</Id><Topic><Title>clint denounced W's invasion of bushghanistan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346424917264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 10:55:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clint says your odaddy doesnt have a clue on how to run a country...he's got to go.....</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346503201266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:40:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346507297661-7</Id><Topic><Title>My neighborhood odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344457137000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-08 16:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yesterday.... there were 5 tv's piled on the curb in front of my odumbomite neighbor's house....i said you're gettin serious on this carbon foot print reduction thing, most are just hypocrites....he said it's not that..they are broken..Broken??..i replied...he said...yeah,...Clint Eastwood was talkin to "president obama" the other night at the RNC and i couldn't see or hear him, checked all of them...the same... I said you don't mind if I dispose of them for you? ...i took them down to a"good will" store a secured a charitable tax deduction.</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346507297661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346509866000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Loans paying down at record pace. By $2B a year</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346365648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But kind sir: the statement is correct. The funny thing about the helocs, while most are in the interest only mode, the helocs are actually paying down. So its not like one of those situations where helocs are on interest only and when amort starts, the default rAtes start popping up. I am not that certain that the credit marks taken in a sale transaction would be outrageous anymore. They flushed all the junk - largely.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346509866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346511848000-9</Id><Title>Ken and his Pen</Title><Msg>Where could they be? Ken and his pen went wild last june. Now silence? Perhaps the company is being sold this weekend? Else, we would be hearing from Ken and his Pen!</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346511848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346512230000-10</Id><Title>Clint Eastwood Tells It Likes It Is</Title><Msg>Hilarious! We own this country. When the guy is not up to the job, you have to let him go.</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1346512230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:10:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346518663000-11</Id><Topic><Title>This is interesting</Title><Username>sherita_isabelle09</Username><Timestamp>1346514053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I singed up too...</Msg><Username>jenni_leola54</Username><Timestamp>1346518663000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346524634844-12</Id><Title>The laughingstock and the liar</Title><Msg>"Jon Stewart opened The Daily Show‘s final night in Tampa by basking in the “awesome” and “hilarious” speech Clint Eastwood gave at the Republican National Convention, which consisted of the Oscar-winning actor yelling at a chair for ten minutes. But while Stewart was awe-struck over Eastwood’s speech, he was not so kind to Mitt Romney‘s acceptance speech, bashing it as being a whitewash of American history. Stewart admitted he was “dispirited” by being in Tampa all week, but at the last second, Eastwood saved him with “a fist full of awesome.” He gleefully expressed his amazement that Eastwood “spent twelve minutes on the most important night of Mitt Romney’s life yelling at a chair,” describing the speech as the most amazing old-man moment he’s seen since “Dick Cheney non-fatally shot one in the face.” Stewart told the Tampa crowd that in New York City, it’s not uncommon to see old men yelling at inanimate objects, but generally it does not happen on stage at political conventions. Of course, the highlight of last night was supposed to be Romney’s acceptance speech, but Stewart noted that no matter what Romney had said, there was no way he could have outshined Eastwood. However, Stewart did slam Romney’s speech as being too idealistic about America’s recent history, and noticed it was part of a recurring trend at the convention that America could be great once again if it were not for President Obama and his policies. But what set off Stewart the most was Romney’s comment last night that he wanted Obama to succeed from the very beginning. Stewart rebutted Romney by running clips of conservatives saying, less than six months after Obama was inaugurated, that he was already a failure. And most damning of all, Stewart ran a clip of Romney himself, eight days after Obama was inaugurated, saying that he “partially agree[s]” with Rush Limbaugh saying that he hopes Obama fails. Stewart brought the segment home, going back to Eastwood’s speech and why he did a “huge favor” for the GOP. By criticizing an invisible Obama for doing things that the real Obama hasn’t even done, Stewart could reach only one logical conclusion: “there is a President Obama that only Republicans can see,” and this Invisible Obama is the one they have been running against all along. Watch the epic segment below, courtesy of Comedy Central:</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346524634844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:37:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346525306747-13</Id><Topic><Title>The laughingstock and the liar</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346524634844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:37:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>eastwoods mission is accomplished...he got you odumbomites all tore up......his point was an inanimate object would had done as good as your odaddy.........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346525306747</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346526056265-14</Id><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Msg>how's it feel getting duped by an 80 year old degenerative.....you #$%$ are so naive....you wonder why you constantly cry all the time.............wah wah wah..my vagina hurts........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346526767055-15</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow! Weakest spin ever attempted.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346526767055</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346526782299-16</Id><Title>Ryan will lie about anything</Title><Msg>" By Alana Horowitz Posted: 09/01/2012 9:38 am Updated: 09/01/2012 10:08 am Paul Ryan's campaign walked back comments the VP nominee made about running a marathon. " I had a two hour and fifty-something marathon, Ryan said last week an interview. I hurt a disc in my back, so I don’t run marathons anymore " But the Ryan campaign confirmed to Runner's World that he has only run one marathon, the 1990 Grandma’s Marathon in Duluth, Minnesota, which he finished in just over 4 hours. "</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526782299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346526879189-17</Id><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Msg>"Ret. USAF Col. Klass: Romney Failing the Commander in Chief Test Now some of this is perfectly rational. Why mention the war in Iraq when the president who started it is also unmentionable. And, if mentioned, it would have to be acknowledged that President Barack Obama ended that war. And worse, in a torrent of claims of Obama's broken promises, it would not do to highlight that he kept his promise to end that war. But you would think that Mr. Romney might acknowledge that we still have a war going on in Afghanistan and that young Americans are still dying there. But then he might have to mention President Obama's decisions to increase troop strength and his strategy to wind down that too long conflict, while he has criticism but no alternative. The promise thing also nixes mentioning alQaeda or, quiet now, Bin Laden. People might remember that Mr. Romney said that it did not make sense to spend millions to get "one man" or, worse, that the President kept his promise and did it. Failure to acknowledge this nation's debt to veterans also raises awkward questions about promises kept. President Obama pledged to fulfill the "sacred trust" between the nation and our veterans. It would not be helpful to mention that promise was kept by the largest increases in the Department of Veterans' Affairs budgets in years, appropriations Congressman Ryan voted against. And someone might notice that Mr. Ryan also voted against the New GI Bill of Rights that is honoring today's veterans with educational opportunities akin to those that sent their grandfathers to college after WWII. It would also not do for someone to mention that the word "veteran" does not appear in Mr. Ryan's budget that is supposed to outline a future for America. I suppose it is possible for Mr. Ryan to imagine an American future without veterans. I cannot. And, though a mumbling Clint Eastwood could be tolerated, mentioning ending "don't ask, don't tell" would get you booed off the stage. So Mr. Romney and Mr. Ryan, when you are asking whether we are better off today than four years ago, I have some suggestions of some people to ask. Ask military members and their families if they are better off without multiple tours to Iraq and painful family separations. Ask veterans if they are better off with the educational opportunities offered by the New GI bill of Rights. Ask the vets who were excluded from earned veterans' care by the policies of the unmentionable previous president. Ask the spouses who have found it easier to transfer professional credentials to new duty station states due to the work of Michelle Obama and Dr. Jill Biden. Ask the formerly homeless vets who have been the beneficiaries of another Obama promise kept. And, stealthily of course, no sense stirring up the bigots, ask the thousands of gay and lesbian servicemen if they are better off not having to live a lie."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346527482642-18</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know it's true...thinking outside the box is not an odumbomite attribute....too bad an 80 year old put the whammy to ya....so ya could make a big ta do out of it...haven't heard any success stories about your odaddy...be tough for you to spin one...hehehehe</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346527482642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:24:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346527862580-19</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty much universal agreement that "Dirty Harry" soiled himself and the GOP but keep trying to whistle past it.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346527862580</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528012609-20</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in your mind..maybe....your an odumbomite..#$%$ do you know...........other than... if it's free its for me</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346528012609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528757949-21</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aug 31, 8:39 AM EDT Trouble with the chair: Clint mocked for RNC bit By DERRIK J. LANG AP Entertainment Writer AP Photo AP Photo/Charles Dharapak Entertainment Video Buy AP Photo Reprints Multimedia Oscars 2010: Nominations Oscars 2009: Red Carpet Oscars 2009: Red Carpet Panorama Roman Polanski timeilne Latest Movie News Venice premiers first-ever Saudi film Anderson: 'The Master' inspired by L. Ron Hubbard Release date for third 'Hobbit' film announced Documentary pays tribute to Jackson's genius 'Hugo' editor Thelma Schoonmaker wins Gucci award Document Paris Hilton in Federal Court: Deposition Paris Hilton in Federal Court: Exhibit 56 LOS ANGELES (AP) -- Clint Eastwood earned plenty of bad reviews for his latest performance: a bizarre, rambling endorsement of Mitt Romney. "Clint, my hero, is coming across as sad and pathetic," tweeted film critic Roger Ebert as Eastwood ad-libbed Thursday night to an audience of millions - and one empty chair - on stage at the Republican National Convention in Tampa, Fla. "He didn't need to do this to himself. It's unworthy of him." Eastwood carried on a kooky, long-winded conversation with an imaginary President Barack Obama, telling him that he failed to deliver on his promises, and it's time for Romney and his running mate, Paul Ryan, to take over. "Mr. President, how do you handle promises that you have made when you were running for election, and how do you handle them? I mean, what do you say to people?" he said at one point to the empty chair. Twitter was instantly ablaze with comments mocking the Oscar-winning director of "Unforgiven" and "Million Dollar Baby." "Clint has now eclipsed the total word count of his last three films," tweeted film critic Richard Roeper during the speech, which was intended to last five minutes but went on for nearly 12. Howard Kurtz, host of CNN's "Reliable Sources," said "Clint's empty chair act" was the "weirdest convention moment I have ever seen." Joe Scarborough, the conservative host of MSNBC's "Morning Joe," declared that "a great night for Mitt Romney just got sidetracked by Clint Eastwood." Minutes after Eastwood began his speech, someone created an (at)InvisibleObama account on Twitter. It has already amassed 30,000 followers and counting. "I heard that Clint Eastwood was channeling me at the RNC," tweeted comic actor Bob Newhart, known for his one-sided conversation bits. "My lawyers and I are drafting our lawsuit." The 82-year-old actor and director also talked about Oprah Winfrey, Obama's unfulfilled promise to close the U.S. prison at Guantanamo, the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan and lawyers. At one point, he referenced dismissing Obama and making a change. "When somebody doesn't do the job, you gotta let `em go," Eastwood said. The tough-guy actor of "Dirty Harry" fame then drew a finger across his throat. The Obama campaign shot back afterward by tweeting a photo of the back of the president's chair, with Obama's head peeking over it, along with the line: "This seat's taken." Romney's wife, Ann, said she appreciates Eastwood's support, even if the actor's monologue isn't earning rave reviews. Ann Romney said she did not know what to expect when Eastwood came on as a warm up act for the evening's speakers. "He's a unique guy and he did a unique thing last night," she told "CBS This Morning." Eastwood, a fiscal conservative who takes left-leaning stands on social issues such as gay marriage and environmental protections, made waves with conservatives earlier this year when he starred in a Super Bowl spot for Chrysler, a company that benefited from government support. Eastwood, who endorsed Romney earlier this month at a campaign event in Sun Valley, Idaho, and once served as mayor of Carmel, Calif., defended his appearance in the commercial, noting it had nothing to do with his politics. Inside the convention, the crowd cheered Eastwood's entrance and shouted his famed catchphrase, "Go ahead, make my day." But backstage, stern-faced Romney aides winced at times as Eastwood's remarks stretched on. After his speech, Romney's camp defended Eastwood. "He's an American icon," Romney spokeswoman Gail Gitcho told CNN's Piers Morgan. "You can't look at him at through the same political lens that you would other politicians. He's Clint Eastwood." There was seemingly more discussion Thursday night on Twitter about Eastwood's awkward performance than Romney's actual acceptance speech. "Is this a segment for `Mrs. Eastwood and Company'?" asked "Star Trek" actor Zachary Quinto on Twitter, referencing the "Keeping Up with the Kardashians"-like E! reality series starring Eastwood's wife, Dina. Several celebrities and comedians lightheartedly hypothesized on the micro-blogging site how Democrats could top the over-the-top routine at their own convention in Charlotte, N.C., next week. "To restore balance to the universe, Obama must have Tommy Chong onstage at the DNC talking to a steak," joked Patton Oswalt. Original "Star Trek" actor George Takei said he was "drafting a DNC speech to (an) imaginary Romney in an empty factory." "Saturday Night Live" cast member Seth Myers had an entirely different idea: "(Vice President Joe) Biden has to go shirtless for DNC to top it."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346528757949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346529103836-22</Id><Topic><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is an opinion like no other and so true - thank you very much!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346529103836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346529761257-23</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like you are easily skewed...a weakness the odumbomite clan has.....just because they think that way is why you think that way...you are weak...very characteristic of a follower.....must be why you are an odumbomite..........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346529761257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346530353208-24</Id><Topic><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you believe all opinions to be true...??..i bet...only when they're convenient for ya....a fair weather kok suckin odumbomite who can't form an opinion on your own....you must be sufferin............</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530353208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346530980594-25</Id><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Msg>what has he accomplished?...please list...no bush whiners or blamers......now's your chance...tell all</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346533691000-26</Id><Title>Really now...... Who are they kidding?</Title><Msg>This yahoo change sucks by the way. But seriously, does this management really believe that they can compete in this environment of shrinking darts? Who are they kidding? They plan on cutting costs to hit profitability? How much can they expect to cut in order to hit acceptable earnings levels? I suspect they had to fire off that Freiberg because he was just in the way. But i would not be surprised to wake up tuesday to a deal announcement. AMTD needs darts and sorely needs a new system. They must also be painfully aware that wealth management units at other institutions are suffering from stagnant earnings. I think that given etfc's circumstances, they are in a position to finally sell this</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346533691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346534244963-27</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't all of ya throw input at the same time now....why the big silent sound...i would had thought the anointed one would have many accomplishments to brag about since his time as a senator and president........#$%$s the deal</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346534244963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346535124304-28</Id><Title>you wanna know what's laughfable jbeast</Title><Msg>yahoo has censors on acronyms.....that is pure odumbonism</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346535124304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346535670790-29</Id><Title>The GOP model</Title><Msg>1-23-09 Here is a summary of George W. Bush’s ratings, compared with the 41 presidents who preceded him: Rated worst ever: 67 (61%) Rated in worst quartile (worst 11), but not worst ever: 38 (35%) Rated a failure, but not among the worst 11: 2 (2%) Rated a success: 2 (2%) Here is a graphic representation of Bush’s ratings of failure vs. success: And here is a graphic representation of his comparison with other presidents: Reasons for poor ratings Here is a sampling of reasons provided by the historians for their poor ratings of the Bush presidency: The economy “Mr. Bush inherited a sizable budget surplus and a thriving economy…. Bush transformed the surplus into a massive deficit. The tax cuts and other policies accelerated the concentration of wealth and income among the very richest Americans. These policies combined with unwavering opposition to necessary government regulations have produced the worst economic crisis since the Great Depression.”… “His domestic policies have had the cumulative effect of shoring up a semi-permanent aristocracy of capital that dwarfs the aristocracy of land against which the founding fathers rebelled.”… “Bush does only two things well,” said one of the most distinguished historians. “He knows how to make the very rich very much richer, and he has an amazing talent for #$%$ up everything else he even approaches. Bush’s “War on Terror” and effect on our international standing “In the wake of the terrorist attacks on September 11, 2001, the United States enjoyed enormous support around the world. President Bush squandered that goodwill by taking the country into an unnecessary war of choice and misleading the American people to gain support for that war. And he failed utterly to have a plan to deal with Iraq after the invasion. He further undermined the international reputation of the United States by justifying torture.” “When future historians look back to identify the moment at which the United States began to lose its position of world leadership, they will point – rightly – to the Bush presidency.” Other major issues  “Trampled on our Bill of Rights”; “Has broken the Constitution more often than even Nixon”  “Appointed foxes in every henhouse”  “Compounded the terrorist threat”  “Turned a blind eye to… a looming ecological disaster”  “Encouraging a mindless retreat from science and rationalism” General summations of the Bush presidency “Glib, contemptuous, ignorant, incurious, a dupe of anyone who humors his deluded belief in his heroic self”… “Bush has set this country on a course that will take decades to correct”… “God willing, this will go down as the nadir of American politics.”… “He is not a conservative, nor a Christian, just an immoral man” . . . “Bush’s denial of any personal responsibility can only be described as silly.”… “His administration has been the most reckless, dangerous, irresponsible, mendacious, arrogant, self-righteous, incompetent, and deeply corrupt one in all of American history.” How did we do it? Americans should think long and hard about how this happened. I can think of four reasons: Money in politics George W. Bush received tons of cash for his campaign for the presidency from the rich and powerful… the corporatocracy. These people and corporations contributed huge amounts of money to the Bush campaign because they knew that they would be rewarded many times over. And indeed they were – through massive tax breaks; deregulation of our laws against environmental pollution, worker safety, consumer protection, and much more; and no-bid contracts with almost total lack of oversight. The corporate news media Of all the corporations that have the power to influence our elections, those of the corporate news media head the list. Through progressive consolidation of the telecommunications industry, largely enabled by the Telecommunications Act of 1996, the news we receive has been controlled by fewer and fewer wealthy corporations. In the run-up to the 2000 elections, they repeated lie after lie against Al Gore, making an honest, decent, highly experienced, and competent statesmen to appear as a corrupt buffoon. In the run-up to the 2004 election, they repeated lies (See section on “The swiftboating of John Kerry”) about John Kerry’s war record, making a true war hero appear as a phony, while covering up for George Bush’s shirking of his National Guard duty as a young man and his lying us into a disastrous war against Iraq as President in 2003. Election fraud In 2000, Al Gore received more than half a million more votes than George Bush. But Bush “won” an electoral victory due to a fraudulent election in Florida. Prominent among the reasons for the Bush “victory” were the purging of tens of thousands of mostly Democratic “felons” who weren’t really felons from Florida’s voter roles. Even with that, Al Gore came within 538 votes of winning Florida, before the right wing U.S. Supreme court stopped the vote recount in a 5-4 decision several days prior to the mandatory deadline, in perhaps the most corrupt U.S. Supreme Court verdict in American history. A later non-binding recount of the Florida vote showed conclusively that Al Gore would have been the clear winner if all the votes had been fairly and accurately counted. In 2004, once again Bush needed massive voter purging – this time in Ohio – to achieve his re-election. In addition, exit polls indicated a clear victory for John Kerry, and there was a great deal of evidence of vote switching on electronic voting machines which counted our votes in secret and could not be recounted. The gullibility of a segment of the American people Even with all of the above-noted huge advantages of Republican, corporate friendly politicians, the American people cannot escape some of the blame. Voter turnout in the United States is routinely notoriously low compared to other industrialized countries. And even among those who do vote, too many Americans just don’t pay enough attention and are fooled too easily into believing the crap they’re fed from their corporate news media. What now? The problems noted above need to be corrected if our country is to thrive as a democracy. There is a tendency of many liberal/progressive Americans to believe that now that we have elected a new and much better president, our problems will go away. There is no question that Barack Obama will be a much better President than George W. Bush. He may even be a great President. But, as explained in an editorial by the editors of The Nation: As we have learned from earlier periods of our history, progressive reform is not born from one election but out of a sustained struggle involving a mobilized public seeking change. With the defeat of John McCain, one part of that struggle is over. But another has begun… The point made by that article and in other articles from the same issue of The Nation is that our country has many systemic problems that will require a prolonged struggle to correct. Chief among those problems is the example set by our outgoing President. Though George W. Bush leaves office with historically low public approval ratings, as well as historically dismal ratings by professional historians, the many terrible crimes committed by his administration have as yet been unaccounted for and unpunished. Crimes against our Constitution have gone unpunished. Crimes against humanity and war crimes have gone unpunished. If those numerous crimes continue to go unaccounted for and unpunished, that leaves the door open for future corrupt Presidents to commit similar crimes. The American people need a full accounting of those crimes, and we need to set an example that dissuades future Presidents from believing that they can commit similar crimes with impunity. Neither our country nor the world can afford another four years of what we’ve just been through.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346535670790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346536260993-30</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's team cleared the Eastwood fiasco. That's the kind of disastrous bad judgement to expect from them.</Title><Msg>August 31, 2012 Before Eastwood’s Talk With a Chair, Clearance From the Top By MICHAEL BARBARO and MICHAEL D. SHEAR TAMPA, Fla. — For all the finger-pointing about Clint Eastwood’s rambling conversation with an empty chair on Thursday night, the most bizarre, head-scratching 12 minutes in recent political convention history were set in motion by Mitt Romney himself and made possible by his aides, who had shrouded the actor’s appearance in secrecy. Mr. Romney privately invited Mr. Eastwood, of “Dirty Harry” fame, to speak after the actor had given him a gravelly, full-throated endorsement at a star-studded fund-raiser at the Sun Valley Resort Lodge in Idaho this summer. “He just made my day. What a guy,” Mr. Romney joked with his donors that night, flanked by the fake log columns of the lodge. Thus began an effort by Mr. Romney’s campaign over several weeks to inject a Hollywood-style surprise into the highly scripted, tightly controlled convention where Mr. Romney would formally accept the nomination of the Republican Party to be president. Behind the scenes, Mr. Eastwood’s convention cameo was cleared by Mr. Romney’s top message mavens, Russ Schriefer and Stuart Stevens, who drew up talking points that Mr. Eastwood included, in his own way. They gave him a time limit and flashed a blinking red light that told him his time was up. He ignored both. The actor’s decision to use a chair as a prop was last-minute, and his own. “The prop person probably thought he was going to sit in it,” a baffled senior aide said on Thursday night. Mr. Eastwood’s rambling and off-color appearance just moments before the biggest speech of Mr. Romney’s life instantly became a Twitter and cable-news sensation, which drowned out much of the usual postconvention analysis that his campaign had hoped to bask in. It also startled and unsettled Mr. Romney’s top advisers and prompted a blame game among them. “Not me,” an exasperated-looking senior adviser said when asked who was responsible for Mr. Eastwood’s speech. In interviews, aides called the speech “strange” and “weird.” One described it as “theater of the absurd.” Ann Romney, who made the rounds of the three network morning shows, hardly pretended that she was happy as she was repeatedly asked about the speech. “I was thrilled for his support,” she said on NBC, trying to be positive. Gov. Scott Walker of Wisconsin said on MSNBC that he “cringed” as he sat in the hall during Mr. Eastwood’s performance. The speech was a reminder of how fleeting a successful political moment can be, and how carefully staged events can be upset by an unpredictable turn. And it suggested a slip-up inside the button-down, corporate-style headquarters of the Romney campaign in Boston. Romney advisers so trusted Mr. Eastwood, 82, that unlike with other speakers, they said they did not conduct rehearsals or insist on a script or communicate guidelines for the style or format of his remarks. For Mr. Eastwood, the convention speech was a bit part in a career that has had its political moments. Angered by zoning laws he did not like, he served one two-year term as mayor of Carmel-by-the-Sea in California. In 1988, George Bush briefly considered choosing him as his running mate; he picked Dan Quayle instead. During the weeks after Mr. Romney extended the invitation in Idaho, the actor’s role in the convention lineup was kept secret. On the public schedule, his slot was listed as “to be announced.” As the last night of the convention approached, planners tried to keep a lid on the story even as Mr. Eastwood’s name leaked out on the Internet, hoping his appearance would be the good kind of a surprise, not the bad kind. “If we announced it, it wouldn’t be a mystery anymore,” Mr. Schriefer told reporters, playfully. Another adviser said that several top aides had reviewed the talking points given to Mr. Eastwood just a few hours before his appearance. They included a request to mention the millions of people who remain unemployed — something Mr. Eastwood did, though he misstated the number. As actors sometimes do, he improvised. Instead of reading off a teleprompter — something Mr. Eastwood is said to despise — he pretended to have a sarcasm-filled conversation with President Obama, seated by his side. “What do you mean, shut up?” Mr. Eastwood said, mumbling to a befuddled audience. A moment later, he stopped again, saying, “What do you want me to tell Mr. Romney?” “I can’t tell him that. He can’t do that to himself,” Mr. Eastwood said. “You’re getting as bad as Biden.” Initially, there were no plans for Mr. Eastwood to take a chair onstage. But at the last minute, the actor asked the production staff backstage if he could use one but did not explain why. Had Mr. Eastwood appeared earlier, many fewer people might have noticed. The networks began their hour of convention coverage at 10 p.m. Eastern time, which meant that Mr. Eastwood was the first act of the night for their millions of viewers. He was scheduled to speak for about five minutes but stayed onstage for more than twice as long, throwing off the schedule for Mr. Romney. Mr. Stevens, in an interview, said he would not discuss internal decision making, but he said that Mr. Romney was backstage during Mr. Eastwood’s remarks. “He spoke from the heart with a classic improv sketch which everyone at the convention loved,” Mr. Stevens said, calling it “an honor that a great American icon would come and talk about the failure of the current president.” Rush Limbaugh called Mr. Eastwood’s performance “bold.” But other members of the party faithful were not so sure. As they flew home from Tampa on Friday, some delegates grumbled that Mr. Eastwood was a waste of a prime-time slot that might have been better used to feature other speakers or the biographical video of Mr. Romney’s life. Mr. Eastwood is generally liked and respected in Hollywood, where his colleagues often do not agree with his politics. Leonard Hirshan, Mr. Eastwood’s manager, said the actor was traveling and would not be available for interviews.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346536260993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346537768102-31</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot's team cleared the Eastwood fiasco. That's the kind of disastrous bad judgement to expect from them.</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346536260993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep..a raving success.......wasn't it......the media is tearing it up...bwahahahaha</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346537768102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:16:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539871667-32</Id><Topic><Title>you wanna know what's laughfable jbeast</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346535124304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:32:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey...here's a tip for ya...bush isn't running against romney...ya communist bass turd</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346539871667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346541484398-33</Id><Topic><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>returnusignoramus, you're sick poppy!!!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1346541484398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542382137-34</Id><Topic><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i get those lameass replies all the time from the dumbfounded.....you just gonna stand there....or continue to be mesmerized by the headlights..idiot</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346542382137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:33:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346542797072-35</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i see you witty #$%$ fkwads were quick to jump on this topic.....w#$%$a matter...communisn got your tongue</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346542797072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:39:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543253500-36</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i guess all you odumbomites are split tails.....................</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346543253500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543860880-37</Id><Topic><Title>An opinion from the military</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346526879189</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:14:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey col, ERIC SHINSEKI, retired US ARMY, 4 star GENERAL, 34TH CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE US ARMY, lost part of his foot in VIETNAM, publicaly clashed with RUMSFELD, regarding how many troops would be needed in post war IRAQ, Eric S. stated several hundred thousand troops, rumsfeld, didn't want the truth, why would Romney , remind the american people about the no WMD-or that cheney said we'd be treated as liberators in DOWN town BAGDAD? obama appointed shinseki, the head of the VA hospital system so the vets would be taken care of, the REPS, just use our service people, as soon as there through, they don't feel responsible, as it costs too much $. as far as killing BIN LADEN, GUTTSY move, awesome, he gave the generals 1 more year to wrap it up, then the draw down, the reps never had a plan , i mean really, what idiots start 2 major wars, don't fund them , then cut taxes? the reps, unreal, that guy cheney/bush, handed obama a mess, vote for the reps if you want to bomb IRAN/SYRIA/put troops in lybia, hassle the chinese/russians/koreans, and remember the reps don't raise taxes, they just borrow money from the chinese. unreal. any way, ETFC, IS AT OR ABOVE ITS 10-20-50-100 dma'S. imho. ps, CHENEY SAID THE ORIGINAL COST OF THE iraq WAR WOULD BE 50 BILLION$'S! THEY SAID IT WOULD BE A 1 WEEK CAKE WALK? WOLFOWITZ SAID IN 6 MONTHS THE IRAQ OIL WOULD TAKE CARE OF RECONSTRUCTION. that 1 trillion$ war, basically destabalized the middle east, set all the crap we see now into motion. plus, IRAQ was a good counter weight to the IRANIANS, and besides how many people ever heard of operation "AJAX" ? and you wonder why the Iranians don't trust us! really, how many americans ever heard of "operation AJAX" ?jmo</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1346543860880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346546426086-38</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anything???????</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346546426086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:40:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346546768383-39</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok... Ill start with an example....He successfully blew a super majority in the house of representatives and got pelosi kicked square in the #$%$.... That's one good thing</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346546768383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346547947755-40</Id><Topic><Title>hey odumbomites...</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346526056265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:00:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO!!!!!!!! Twitter was instantly ablaze with comments mocking the Oscar-winning director of "Unforgiven" and "Million Dollar Baby." "Clint has now eclipsed the total word count of his last three films," tweeted film critic Richard Roeper during the speech, which was intended to last five minutes but went on for nearly 12. Howard Kurtz, host of CNN's "Reliable Sources," said "Clint's empty chair act" was the "weirdest convention moment I have ever seen." Joe Scarborough, the conservative host of MSNBC's "Morning Joe," declared that "a great night for Mitt Romney just got sidetracked by Clint Eastwood." Minutes after Eastwood began his speech, someone created an (at)InvisibleObama account on Twitter. It has already amassed 30,000 followers and counting. "I heard that Clint Eastwood was channeling me at the RNC," tweeted comic actor Bob Newhart, known for his one-sided conversation bits. "My lawyers and I are drafting our lawsuit." The 82-year-old actor and director also talked about Oprah Winfrey, Obama's unfulfilled promise to close the U.S. prison at Guantanamo, the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan and lawyers. At one point, he referenced dismissing Obama and making a change. "When somebody doesn't do the job, you gotta let `em go," Eastwood said. The tough-guy actor of "Dirty Harry" fame then drew a finger across his throat. The Obama campaign shot back afterward by tweeting a photo of the back of the president's chair, with Obama's head peeking over it, along with the line: "This seat's taken."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346547947755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346549008397-41</Id><Title>Dipshidiot is a liar</Title><Msg>Chronicling Mitt's Mendacity, Vol. XXX By Steve Benen - Fri Aug 17, 2012 2:50 PM EDT 963 Getty Images Mitt Romney gave a speech Beallsville, Ohio, this week, and presented an unfortunate attack against President Obama. "How can you go out there and tell people things that just aren't true?" he asked rhetorically. He added, "This is a time for truths." In context, Romney was referring to Obama's claim that "we're adding jobs in the coal industry." In reality, the nation really is adding jobs in the coal industry -- Romney was looking for an example of the president saying something that "just isn't true," and he pointed to an Obama quote that happened to be accurate, though he told his audience the opposite. It's hard not to appreciate the ironic circle -- the president said something true, Romney lied when he said the accurate claim is false, and then he complained about falsehoods in the campaign. I don't know the Republican candidate personally, but from a distance, it appears there's a part of his brain that allows him to create some kind of deliberate blind-spot. It's actually a little scary to think of a leader -- a man who'd be given enormous power and influence, literally making life and death decisions on a regular basis -- who can convince himself that his falsehoods are true, and that others' truths are falsehoods. But here we are. If this is, as Romney claims, a "time for truths," I can only hope the Republican candidate will take a few moments to consider the 30th installment of my weekly series, chronicling Mitt's mendacity. (This is the biggest list I've ever done.) 1. At an impromptu event in South Carolina yesterday, Romney said on Medicare policy, "Our plan [has] no change for current seniors and those 55 and older." That's plainly false. Romney's plan eliminates all new benefits for seniors under the Affordable Care Act, which necessarily means higher prescription drug costs for seniors, and more expensive preventive care. 2. At the same event, Romney argued, "Under the president's plan, [Medicare] goes bankrupt... Under the plan I propose, it is solvent." That's the exact opposite of reality. Obama's policy strengthens Medicare's finances, and under Romney's plan, the system would be closer to insolvency faster. 3. In Chillicothe, Ohio, Romney said that under Obama, "We've got lower economic growth." Actually, we got higher economic growth. 4. In the same speech, Romney said that under Obama, "We've got higher unemployment." Actually, we got lower unemployment. 5. He went on to say the annual budget deficit has hit the $1 trillion mark under Obama for the "first time the history of our country." Not true. The first time in the history of our country that the deficit hit $1 trillion was George W. Bush's last year in office, when the annual shortfall was $1.3 trillion. 6. Romney added that Obama promised "he'd get the unemployment down to under 5.6 percent today if we pass that $1 trillion stimulus package." That's actually two falsehoods wrapped as one. For one thing, the stimulus wasn't $1 trillion (Romney's off by over $200 billion, and that's real money). For another, that's not what Obama promised. 7. Romney added, "You see unlike President Obama, I won't raise taxes on small business." Obama has repeatedly cut taxes on small businesses -- by some counts, 18 times -- and if given a second term, his tax plan would have no effect on 97% of small businesses. 8. In an interview with Fortune magazine, Romney said the president's stimulus measures "have not put Americans back to work." Yes they have. 9. In the same interview, Romney said he would create jobs by "taking advantage of America's energy resources, particularly natural gas, as well as coal, oil, nuclear, solar, and wind." Much of this is contradicted by Romney's own agenda. He opposes the wind production tax credit, no matter how many jobs it costs the nation, and has vowed to cut off investments in renewable energy programs (Romney has said wind and solar do not constitute "real energy.") 10. Romney went on to say, "A nation which is a highly productive nation as we are benefits by trade with others... The Obama administration has negotiated no new [trade] agreements." Did Romney not hear about the trade agreements with Panama, Colombia, and South Korea? 11. Romney added, "We have to cut the deficit and get America on track to a balanced budget in order to convince investors that America is a good place to invest long term.... The president has done virtually nothing other than to propose a series of tax increases." Actually, Obama proposed a massive, $4 trillion "grand bargain," most of which was made up of spending cuts. Congressional Republicans turned it down anyway. 12. Romney also said, "We're at a 30-year low in new business startups." Still not true. 13. Romney went on to say, "I indicated as I announced my tax plan that the key principles included the following. First, that high-income people would continue to pay the same share of the tax burden that they do today." At a minimum, this is ridiculously misleading. Under Romney's plan, high-income people would get an enormous tax break. 14. Romney added, "Obamacare is a tax. It's been so determined by the Supreme Court, and it falls predominantly on the middle class." He's referring to an individual mandate that would apply to 1% of the population. And if President Obama's health care policy "raised taxes on the middle class," then Mitt Romney raised taxes on the middle class. 15. Romney also said, "President Obama raises taxes on the middle class. I will under no circumstances raise taxes on the middle class." There's overwhelming evidence to the contrary. 16. Romney went on to say, "I will follow a model similar to Simpson-Bowles." No he won't. 17. Romney also said, "I believe infrastructure is going to see very substantial investments over the coming decade." He may believe that, but he's also endorsed a budget plan that drastically curtails infrastructure investments. 18. Romney argued, "I believe that you're going to see us having created 12 million new jobs." If we do nothing, we're on track to create 12 million new American jobs over the next four years anyway. 19. In a televised ad, Romney said Obama "cut $716 billion dollars from Medicare ... to pay for Obamacare." Oh, please. 20. The ad goes on to say, in reference to seniors, "So now the money you paid for your guaranteed healthcare is going to a massive new government program that's not for you." That's plainly false. Under the Affordable Care Act, seniors pay less for prescription medication and preventive care -- meaning the policy is "for" them, too. 21. At a campaign stop in Ohio, Romney said under Obama we're not "adding jobs in the coal industry" and not "producing more coal." Romney's lying. In reality, we're adding jobs in the coal industry and producing more coal. 22. Romney said this week that Paul Ryan reached out to Sen. Ron Wyden (D-Ore.) to "co-lead a piece of legislation that makes sure we can save Medicare." According to Ron Wyden, that's ridiculously untrue. 23. In another attack ad this week, Romney once again accused Obama of "quietly ending work requirements" in the welfare law." He's still blatantly lying. 24. In Beallsville, Ohio, Romney argued, "President said he'd cut the deficit in half. He's doubled it." Maybe Romney doesn't know what "double" means. The deficit on Obama's first day was $1.3 trillion. Last year, it was also $1.3 trillion. This year, it's projected to be $1.1 trillion. When he says the president "more than doubled" the deficit, as he has many times, Romney's lying. 25. In the same speech, Romney added that Obama has "raided that [Medicare] trust fund." Obama has strengthened the Medicare trust fund. 26. Romney went on to call the Affordable Care Act an "unproven federal government takeover to health care." There is no universe in which this makes sense -- "Obamacare" relies on private insurers, not a government takeover. (Also, it's not "unproven" -- the policy works quite well in, ahem, Massachusetts.) 27. Romney also said, "My number four [goal] is to stop spending massively more than we take in to get America on track to have a balanced budget. And I'll do it." No you won't. Romney says his plan "can't be scored," but independent budget analysts have found his agenda would make the deficit bigger, not smaller, and add trillions to the national debt. 28. Romney went on to say, "Seventy-five percent of small businesses in this country surveyed by the Chamber of Commerce said that Obamacare makes it less likely for them to hire people." The "survey" is a joke. The Chamber, a pro-Republican lobbying institution heavily invested in helping Romney, put up an unscientific online survey. Treating this as a legitimate poll of businesses is fundamentally dishonest. 29. Romney also said, "I'm going to put work back into welfare." Work hasn't been taken out of welfare. 30. Romney went on to say, "[Obama] said if you have a business, you didn't build that. Someone else did that." That's not even close to what the president said. 31. At an event in St. Augustine, Florida, Romney said the president "won't want to remind people of Greece because that's where he's taking our country if we don't get off the road we're on." That's painfully untrue. 32. In the same speech Romney said of the president, "He said he'd measure progress also by whether people were able to have a good job that kept them in their home and paid their mortgage. Well, 8.5 million homes foreclosed, a record level, is not success, Mr. President." Putting aside how dishonest it is for Romney to blame the housing crash on the president, let's also not forget that Romney intends to deliberately avoid any efforts to curtail foreclosures. 33. Romney added, "I'm going to take every government program and apply this test: Is this program so critical it's worth borrowing money from China to pay for it? And if it's not, we'll get rid of it." This continues to be misleading. The implication here is that U.S. debt is financed by the Chinese, but this isn't true -- China only holds about 8% of the nation's debt. Previous editions of Chronicling Mitt's Mendacity: Vol. I, II, III, IV, V, VI, VII, VIII, IX, X, XI, XII,XIII, XIV, XV, XVI, XVII, XVIII, XIX, XX, XXI, XXII, XXIII, XXIV, XXV, XXVI, XXVII, XXVIII, XXIX</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346549008397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:23:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549173132-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot is a liar</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346549008397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't take much to incite a whinefest with you guys</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346549173132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346550555343-43</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama got osama bin laden, wound down the war in IRAQ, helped liberate lybia, w/o putting american troops on the ground, even though that POS, war mongerer McCain, wanted american troops on the ground. is using diplomacy in syria,iran santions, unlike the lousy stinkin reps, who want to bomb IRAN, WANT TO BOMB SYRIA, WANTED TROOPS ON THE GROUND IN LYBIA, instead ofur allies getting involved. he saved the auto industry, which represants 40% of the manufacturing base of the USA, its a national security issue as far as i'm concerned, -he spear headed national health care, modeled after romneys MASS. plan, even though mr flip flop romney, doesn't want to admit! has told israel we don't want to bomb IRAN. by the way, the federal USA government did a 250&amp; million, war study of a war between Iran and the USA, they concluded we'd lose about 13 ships including a aircraft carrier! thats a 5000 sailor aircraft carrier, which has betwwen 80-140 planes on board! some thing the #$%$ in the media, won't discuss! in 1992 the reps blocked clintons health care bill, with scare tactics, back then we had 35 million w/o health coverage, today, 55 million,. it's funny the reps always want to go to war, they've made the world dependant on american military, but who's paying for the USA, to protect the sea lanes? the stupid american tax payers. the reps will give the world a FREE $, pass on protection, but when trying to help the american people ? they give them the shaft! in 2001 the bush adminstation came in with a balanced budget, left obama with a mess. they started 2 major wars, did they fund them?NO, so howethey pay for the war? easy they borrowed the money from the chinese! not only that, the idiots cut taxes. really what kind of idiots start 2 wars don't fund them, then cut taxes? who would do that? easy, the neo con, conservative reps! thats who. they did bank reform, hey ever hear of KNIGHT CAPITAL? AND THE GUY WHO RUNS IT TOM JOYCE, THEY LOST 440 MILLION$'S IN 45 MINUTES! 2 W/E'S AGO TOMMY BOY CALLS SHAPIRO AT THE SEC, ASKS FOR A REDO, BLAMED THE LOSS ON THE COMPUTERS, AND WANTED TO CANCEL ALL THE TRADES AND GET THE MONEY BACK, AND F, THE LITTLE GUY! mary shapiro told tommy boy to pound salt! yeah i love how the 1% cry like babies when they lose money, and cry to the regulators when they (knight capital f'd up), but hey, the little guy? run hiom over, yeah, gotta love the corporate welfare. now if romney was in charge, would he had told tommy at knight capital to pound salt? not to sure. so here's how i look at the 2 guys running, vote for obama and get a windmill and a solar panel on your front lawn, or vote for romney, and get ready for bombing IRAN, bombing SYRIA, put boots on the ground who knows where, or say hassle the chinese/russians/koreans, yep a heck of a pick. if there was a MODERATE REPUBLICAN, i'd vote for em, but look at those guys, rush limbaugh? a pill popping what ever? sara palin, i mean a nise attractive lady, with air between her ears? newt? a broken down POS, who resigned from congress,hasn't been in the game in 17 years, and no way can get 51% of the vote? oh yeah don't forget my favorite rep, MR Perry, from TEXXXXXAS, wow, give me a f'in break, the guy can't remember what he had for breakfast, let alone remember ????? oh yeah, MR cain, the only reason he ran, was to promote a book, yeah, and don't forget the loss of memory about how many women he slept with while still married! oh yeah michelle backman, oh man, another air head, i mean really can you imagine her at the swithch? what a f'in motley crew! finally, really, if you had brains, why would you run for president to take this abuse? one more thing, how come we never get to see where romneys live? how come? i mean really where does he live? what bolck? who are his neighbors? the reason they don't show you is obvious, they don't want to remind the public, that the dude is out of touch with the masses? i still don't know who the guy is. he's been running non stop for 6 straight years, if he wasn't worth 250 million $'s, does any one really believe he'd be in contention? no f'in way. to sum up the reps, norquest, rush L., fox news chanell. really unreal. but IMO, this will be tight, but if jeb bush was running, i really believe he would win this year, obama, is beatable, but romney? what ever. IMHO g/l.</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1346550555343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:49:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552431612-44</Id><Topic><Title>anybody got any success stories to share for obama/?</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346530980594</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 16:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calm down there partner....got yer bomb belt cinched a little tight.....now what ta fks that got to do with 1 in four people out of work and half the country on food stamps</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346552431612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552594000-45</Id><Topic><Title>This is interesting</Title><Username>sherita_isabelle09</Username><Timestamp>1346514053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>hong_glenna54</Username><Timestamp>1346552594000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346553917402-46</Id><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Msg>ryan is such a lunatic liar: at the convention he lied about the GM plant.... it closed in 2008.... and he lied about Obama's "medicare cuts".... recently he said he "forgot" to disclose a multi million dollar trust fund he owns ........ he even lies about his running : The conservative radio host then asked him what his personal best time is. For a marathoner this is a badge of honor, but Ryan couldn't recall exactly. "Under three, high twos. I had a two hour and fifty-something," Ryan said. Hewitt was surprised, saying, "Holy smokes." Ryan replied: "I was fast when I was younger, yeah." But it turns out, he's only run one and it wasn't under three hours or even under four hours" . 0users liked this posts0users disliked this posts Reply</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346556970159-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan a pathological liar ? (like Palin,Limpbalz,brietbart,fox &amp; the gop)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346553917402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:45:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>February 2008 campaign speech then-Sen. Obama gave at the Janesville plant: "And I believe that if our government is there to support you, and give you the assistance you need to re-tool and make this transition, that this plant will be here for another hundred years. The question is not whether a clean energy economy is in our future, it’s where it will thrive. I want it to thrive right here in the United States of America; right here in Wisconsin; and that’s the future I’ll fight for as your president." Wagoner announced GM plans to over time cease production at four plants: Oshawa, Canada 2009 Moraine, Ohio 2010 or sooner if demand dictates. Janesville, Wisconsin 2010 or sooner if demand dictates So here is the fact: “General Motors will end medium-duty truck production in Janesville on April 23 [2009], four months to the day after the plant stopped building full-size sport utility vehicles. About 100 employees associated with the line learned of the layoffs Wednesday. April will mark the end of vehicle production at the Janesville plant that traces its roots to 1919 and the Samson Model M tractor. Chevrolet production started in Janesville in 1923. The Isuzu line and its employees build about 25 trucks four days a week. The cab-forward truck is commonly used as a delivery vehicle. GM and Isuzu strengthened their partnership in 1994 with the launch of the NPR gas-powered trucks in Janesville. Two years later, GM and Isuzu started a separate project that put Isuzu-designed cabs on GM’s medium-duty chassis. That line eventually moved from Janesville to Flint, Mich.” It is April 23, 2009. George W Bush was in Crawford, Texas. Elected President was Barack Hussein Obama. As Senator in 2008 promissed to keep the plant operational. When will you start looking for facts? Never?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346556970159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:36:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>