<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348806932069-1</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And here goes another blatant lie. “After House GOP Leader John Boehner forced the Smithsonian to remove an excerpt of artist David Wojnarowicz's video "A Fire in My Belly", other museums around the country are stepping forward to post the video. The New Museum in New York is now showing the film in its lobby, as is the CB1 Gallery in Los Angeles. Representative Boehner and fellow Congressman Eric Cantor attacked the piece as "an outrageous use of taxpayer money and an obvious attempt to offend Christians during the Christmas season." Understand what misuse of taxpayer’s money is? Or it is too hard for partisan knucklehead to grasp? You, lefties, don’t want pledge of allegiance anywhere near public schools, but when it comes to some anti Christian piece of crap being criticized you suddenly start worrying about 1st amendment. You can show your dirty movies at your own expense anywhere using private channels. And that’s exactly what happened in the case you mentioned. Where is your outrage about arrest of the author of anti Muslim movie? He didn’t use a dime from taxpayers.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348806932069</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 00:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348835996084-2</Id><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Msg>Mark this post!! Remember 4pm on Election day 2004?? Jon Stewart and Jon Bon Jovi doing the most rediculous over-the-top Victory dance?? The Polls said John Kerry (BILLIONAIRE) was the new president! Upcoming: 1- Debates (Oh! This is going to be good!!) 2- Bengazy-GATE (Coverup-palooza) 3- Conservatives NEVER talk to pollsters 4- 2010 Election results (PLEEZE.. the day before Democrats were calling for NO CHANGE in House!! 5- Democrats are screaming that Romney has lost (The Debate Is Over..Gore-style!!) Finally, All of you 'Hope and Changers' out there...Really? Does your Gut tell you that Dumbo is going to WIN??? Dumbo will lose BIG!!! This next month will be what counts and it begins this weekend!! MARK THIS POST!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348840084509-3</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They say Rumney is going to expose and call Brak out on his lies during the first debate. An hour and a half is not enough time to show all the instances where the emperor has no clothes.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348840084509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 09:48:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348841446733-4</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kerry had much more going for him than just being a billionaire. And we all know he only lost because Bush scooped to new levels of weaselly with the swift boat attacks, and Kerry did not know how to respond. He tried to be ABOVE the lies, bad choice..... But public is smarter now that it lived through the experience. Similar tactics were used against Obama with no results in 2008... The public already KNOWS a republican will do and say anything to get elected. Romney is definitely following that path..... saying whatever he is told to say by his puppeteers. as for your point of hope: 1. Debates : Romney will be swatted around like a fly. Did you notice how shaken and desperate he starts to look the moment he is pressed to clarify his stance or provide details??? His eyes get all small and twitchy..... Good luck looking like a weasel with millions watching. 2. are you trying to invent an imaginary problem? keep trying... 3. Of course they don't - They don't need reality (or facts) to get in the way... instead they just create their own polls within their own offices which clearly show overwhelming support for their own. 4. OK - I think now it's GOP guys that are on the hook- and yes - this can be just as bad for GOP as it was for DEMS in 2010. 5. I believe before DEMS were yelling that Romney lost, the GOP was yelling Obama is a toast... One side always yells that at one time or another. Let's face it - Romney was a non-starter to begin with - his only appeal could be that he is white - that would be enough a century ago - but not now. He won your precious primaries through ATTRITION - he was simply the last man standing after your candidates proved either crooks or crazies, one after another.... and if I recall - he was THE LAST CHOICE... Even now - all GOP SuperPacs are switching from spending money supporting him to local senate and House races. The online betting sites apparently all show Obama win being 4:1 favorite. Follow the money... Romney is done... or - if you are a betting man and so sure of your prediction - put a large bet on Romney.... if he wins - you'll be rich! I will mark your post as a voice of desperation.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348841446733</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348843539502-5</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ the exibit was privately financed and my post was meant to ridicule and show the gop hypocrisy of a post from your brother: US Muslims, limit free speech by biddermon_caSep 27, 2012 5:12 P</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348843539502</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 10:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348845964821-6</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smithonian is: ' A Trust intrument of Congress funtionally Legal Biody of the U.S. Goverment. Do you want to tlak about seperation of Church and State??</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348845964821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:26:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348846174249-7</Id><Topic><Title>Democracy wins one in WI</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348802883360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 23:28:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Rowdy_Rodent is probably having a hearth attack by now. First - the state is still heavily leaning towards Obama regardless of Ryan's presence on the ticket - and now it looks like there will be no voter suppression allowed either. How is a republican to win if they allow decent folks to vote????</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348846174249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348846267682-8</Id><Title>Bought WU 18.26</Title><Msg>but you never know...</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1348846267682</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:31:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348847467301-9</Id><Title>Targeting Gramps</Title><Msg>Obama camp urges young voters to warn their grandparents about Romney-Ryan Source: Politico The Obama campaign on Friday launched a new campaign asking young people to send e-cards to their parents and grandparents warning them that Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan will increase taxes on their Social Security benefits. "Romney wants to raise taxes on benefits that seniors have already paid for so that millionaires can pay less," one card asserts. Another says: "These are the people who taught us to whistle and tie our shoes, so no, you can't raise taxes on their social security benefits by $460 a year." The campaign is designed to coincide with a trip by Vice President Joe Biden to Florida, where he will push the same points. "Romney’s $5 trillion tax cut plan will either drive up the deficit or raise middle-class taxes and – if these tax increases are made across the board – an average middle-class senior could pay $460 more in taxes on his or her benefits," the campaign said in a statement.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348847467301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348847708516-10</Id><Title>GOP found a way to lose MO?</Title><Msg>Cornyn: Missouri 'not a winnable race' Source: Politico (via the Lexington Courier-Journal) Texas Sen. John Cornyn, the chairman of the National Republican Senatorial Committee, said on Thursday that he does not intend to put money into the race of controversial Missouri Senate candidate Todd Akin. “We have no plans to do so,” Cornyn told The Courier-Journal in an interview just a short time ago. “I just think that this is not a winnable race,” he said. “We have to make tough calculations based on limited resources and where to allocate it, where it will have the best likelihood of electing a Republican senator.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348847708516</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 11:55:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348848839575-11</Id><Topic><Title>US Muslims, limit free speech</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348780330508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:12:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who will these Savage Animal moooo-slimms brtally torture and KILL next???</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348848839575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348849128838-12</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney to LOWER taxes!!</Title><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1348781494017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, Hmmm, lower taxes. Great but Obama will give you a free phone. So, lets do the math 47% * (0 * 1-.20%) = 0 but $40 * 12 = $480. Which would you chose. LOL Romneys talks too much to the "have mores" and does little for the "have some" and "have nots". ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348849128838</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:18:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348851445978-13</Id><Title>LORCH these TURDS!!!!</Title><Msg>WEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>unclefestersdonkey</Username><Timestamp>1348851445978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 12:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348851875521-14</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Fans Sure are Quiet !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348714730835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**and how come you blame me for changing subject? YOU brought John Kerry into this conversation** Think about what you just said....I was responding to yours and your cohorts point about the election, and was using the Bush/Kerry election to make a point you dopes started. BTW, You seem to have a dislike for folks that live in trailers...aren't you being a little judgemental. A lot of your fellow Democrats live in trailers parks.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348851875521</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348852107541-15</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney to LOWER taxes!!</Title><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1348781494017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So why is he already saying - "well yeah - don't expect much from those tax cuts I promised, because once I shut down all the exemptions you suckers got so used to, you'll be begging for Obama to return.... but hey -my buddies at my club will LOOOOOVEEEE me.!!! "</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348852107541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348852166201-16</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Hope and Change' IS quite a big, PHAT Lie!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348852166201</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348852441655-17</Id><Topic><Title>NEW DIPSHIDIOT TAPE UNEARTHED</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348759875391</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 11:31:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wouldn't it be "unearfed" in today's vernacular?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348852441655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348852654710-18</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that exhibit was privately financed, as are many if not most of the annual exhibits from the "$65 million that the Smithsonian gets from foundations for its annual exhibits and programs." and that particular exhibit was paid for by the Andy Warhol Foundation. the rightwing religious bigots had no right to limit free speech .....</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348852654710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:17:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348853329623-19</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I look forward to the moo-lim exibite at the Smithonian of moos-lim Women being raped and beaten..</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348853329623</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:28:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348853504099-20</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Cantor and gop and religious bigots demand film be banned</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348780913782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Play the 'Innocense of MOOO-slims' Video at the Smithosonian.. Its only (as dumb spews out) "FAIR"!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1348853504099</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348853988989-21</Id><Topic><Title>US Muslims, limit free speech</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348780330508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 17:12:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hand out DVD copies of the 'Innocence of Moooo-slims" to that rabid savage animal mooo-slim anti-Free Speech crwod and watch them kill each other...</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348853988989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348855133748-22</Id><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Msg>mooslim this and mooslim that. fact is they have a long way to go to match the the messes of christian europes 2 world wars or the centuries of slavery and the the USA civil war when Americans slaughtered themselves by the hundreds of thousands........ and ntm that right off the bat in colony USA the Puritans were hanging the Quakers for heresy.... and today religious bigots in the USA burn the books of religions they hate, and every denomination claims to be the one true faith , all the others are 'cults'...... we all know Catholicism is the one and only true chruch......... and sure there are lots of muslims that are horrible people same as with jews and christians and a lot of them are just fine people: one thing they have in common is a dogma that hates the other religions..... oh , and another thing , they all seem to hate women too....... just read your bible to see that women are blamed for the cause of all evil, should never be in a position of authority and so forth..........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348856886036-23</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It really doesn't matter what gibberish you spew about mooo-slims if they KIll You! So bad mouth people like me who want to live all you want! Don't be like Chamberlain with Hitler. Yeah that worked out great!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348856886036</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:28:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348857421497-24</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how did you get to be so stupid? maybe you should listen to one of your own, Ron Paul who says if we stop murdering and meddling in their countries the blow back will stop. If your mooslim on the brain is so bad. just charge on over there yourself...... Built it yourself, On your OWN, form a brigade of "democracy spreaders" volunteers and get your whiny lazy cowardly rear ends over there and fight for your favorite dictator, monarch or maybe join up with the IDF, in which case maybe YOU can murder Americans citizens like Rachel Corrie or the 3 dozen crew of the USS liberty murdered with napalm and machine gun fire in a deliberate attack.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348857421497</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:37:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348857797064-25</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please get back on your MEDS. Your blathering stew of nonsense is not a good look for you...</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348857797064</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 14:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348859063675-26</Id><Title>Mooo-slims Chemical Weapons</Title><Msg>Secretary of Defense for the Untied States of America just announced that Syrian Chemical Weapons have been moved and we don't know where they went.... Moo-slims....Religion of Peace...</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859063675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348859167738-27</Id><Topic><Title>Mooo-slims Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859063675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leon Panetta is the Secretary of Defense.... Obama crony...</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859167738</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348860626904-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mooo-slims Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859063675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you - like Romney - want to start another war?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348860626904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348861095105-29</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well - WE were hoping the economy would not collapse completely after Bush's machinations and shenanigans , and we were praying for change - from negative GDP and LOOSING 800 thousand jobs a MONTH and GOP destroying the very fabric of the country for their personal profits.. To quote from Bush ...... "Mission Accomplished" !!!! Of course - if your HOPE was that you would get miraculously smarter and that people would CHANGE their negative opinion of you - I can understand your resentment.... May I suggest establishing achievable goals???</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348861095105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348861934203-30</Id><Title>A Poem</Title><Msg>WHEREFORE ART THOU, MITT ROMNEY? By Ralph Maxwell O, Romney-O, Romney-O, Wherefore art thou, Mitt Romney? You flip-flop here, you flip-flop there, You flip-flop almost ev'rywhere. You ballyhoo what you're gonna do And then you pull a switcheroo; You now malign what you found fine; Seems like you've got a jellyfish spine. Obamacare, by you begun, Now you'd trash it on day one. Gun control you did extol, But now you're preaching decontrol. O, Romney-O, Romney-O, Wherefore art thou, Mitt Romney? We've got no clue what you will do Or what new view you'll pander to. Time was you championed women's choice, But you no longer heed their voice; On gay rights, too, guess you withdrew Support they once enjoyed from you. Global warming, EPA, Immigration, minimum pay, Roe V. Wade, also fair trade, All joined your flip-flop cavalcade. O, Romney-O, Romney-O Wherefore art thou, Mitt Romney? So many things that you were for You've turned against and slammed the door. Stimulus and cap and trade, Education, foreign aid, Campaign reform, tarp rescues, too, All victims of your switcheroo. You take your stand on shifting sand, We never know where you will land; You vacillate, and you fabricate, A wishy-washy candidate. O, Romney-O, Romney-O, Wherefore art thou Mitt Romney? As gov'nor you let taxes rise, Now ev'ry tax you demonize. You say regardless of the facts You'd take an axe to the millionaire's tax; You'd feed the greed of the richest few The poor and middle class you'd screw. Your tax returns you hide from view What evil lurks there we've no clue; If they're not bad why hesitate? Is it that they incriminate? O, Romney-O, Romney-O, Wherefore art thou Mitt Romney? At Bain you plundered with a flair And walked away a zillionaire. You shipped off-shore, good jobs galore To China, India, Singapore; A job creator you are not. And to boast you are is tommyrot. As a total fraud, Mitt's got no peer; What we must do is crystal clear: Let's give Obama four more years! Yes, it's Obama – four more years! FOUR MORE YEARS! FOUR MORE YEARS! FOUR MORE YEARS!</Msg><Username>burnsjoy43</Username><Timestamp>1348861934203</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862309970-31</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much time will it take to expose Mitten's complete flip flops on every issue ?</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1348862309970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862512468-32</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hydroponicoctopus, you have said a lot dumb things over time, but I didn't think you were suicidal.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348862512468</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348862704174-33</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The country hired the wrong man for the job at hand, I hope they have the wisdom to fire him.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348862704174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:05:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348863635560-34</Id><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Msg>Looks like Hussien Obama has choosen his side... (It's the movie stupid) So much for the first amendment. Next time they will come for you if they don't like what you say. Not a good day for free speech no matter what side of the isle your are on. Feds Arrest Producer Of Controversial Anti-Islam Film On Probation Violation Charge The producer of the controversial anti-Islam film “Innocence of Muslims” has been arrested for violating terms of his probation and is set for an appearance today in U.S. District Court in Los Angeles. Nakoula Basseley Nakoula, 55, is scheduled for an initial appearance in the courthouse where Judge Christina Snyder sentenced him in June 2010 following a bank fraud conviction. [UPDATE: Citing Nakoula’s “lengthy pattern of deception,” a federal magistrate this afternoon ordered him held without bond for alleged probation violations, including making false statements to his probation officer and using aliases. The judge rejected a plea from Nakoula’s lawyer, who argued that the convicted felon’s life would be in danger at an L.A. lockup due to the facility's large population of Muslim inmates. Nakoula will remain in custody in advance of a probation revocation hearing, the date for which has yet to be scheduled.] Investigators have not yet provided details about how Nakoula allegedly violated probation, but it seems clear that his involvement in the “Innocence of Muslim” production is central to the government's new charge.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864249344-35</Id><Topic><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The guy was out on probation from serving his previous crimes and got re-arrested for probation violations. Are you trying to say that those bashing non-christian religions should be exempt from the law? Which one of your heroes gone fishing again? Rush? Palin? or was it some of the Faux News fruitcakes?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348864249344</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864480116-36</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get on with the program biddermon - Bush was let go 3 years ago.... your side dares not to even mention his name anymore</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348864480116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348864647283-37</Id><Title>the #$%$ anti muslim film is not the reason for his arrest. neo loons and rightwing bigots just have their usual pantie wad fest to make political hay</Title><Msg>the fact is that if the #$%$ had not violated his parole he would not be in jail right now. and FYI you lunatic righties ,Obama has cited our free speech as the reason for not banning the video "We understand why people take offense to this video because millions of our citizens are among them. I know there are some who ask, `Why don't we just ban such a video?'" he said. "The answer is enshrined in our laws. Our Constitution protects the right to practice free speech." Against that backdrop, federal officials are looking into whether Nakoula, 55, violated probation for a 2010 check fraud conviction by uploading the trailer to YouTube. Nakoula was sentenced to 21 months in prison and ordered not to use computers or the Internet for five years without approval from his probation officer"</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348864647283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348864872635-38</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crown, pointing to other poor behavior doesn't change the fact that Obama no better.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348864872635</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348865377093-39</Id><Topic><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even for you I am surprised you would defend this action, it's not a partisan issue. It is a free speech issue. BTW, if you are right then why was he not arrested before the attacks...wise up while you still can.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348865377093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348866483105-40</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The situatiuon then was that they had two wrong men to chose from* and they picked the one they liked best. The situation is much the same now but one of the men has told 47% of the country citizens that they are worthless freeloaders. I wonder who the 47% will vote for. Romney is toast. ~S *Shame Hillary didn't make the cut.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348866483105</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348866704436-41</Id><Topic><Title>Mooo-slims Chemical Weapons</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348859063675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This time when before we start the war, can we raise some taxes to pay for it?</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348866704436</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348866737261-42</Id><Topic><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>/ if you are right then why was he not arrested before the attacks / quite simple - if you mind your own business and don't attract public attention to yourself - you get less visibility and less scrutiny. for example: if Romney did not run for the president - not many people would get to learn what a weasel he really is, nobody would be asking him to show his tax returns and nobody other than IRS would be interested in his offshore tax evading schemes.... If Bachmann didn't run for president - nobody would find our she was a practicing witch. If Obama was not the president - nobody would accuse him of not being US born. If Palin wasn't selected to be McCains VP - ........... we would all be sooo much better off.... and so on - and so forth .... Bottom line - if you become a public figure - more scrutiny will come your way..... as you said " it's not a partisan issue ....... so wise up while you still can"</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348866737261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:12:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348867151131-43</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>neo loons and their jumping up and down while farting and yapping "mooslims are after me", "mooselimbs are after me"... 'mooselims are coming" are quite the idiot spectacle.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348867151131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348868603965-44</Id><Topic><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crown loves big government - he rests in its bosom.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1348868603965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:43:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348868851182-45</Id><Title>On topic - sorry....NOT !!!! What you guys and gals think of ETFC bouncing off the 50 Day average</Title><Msg>It bounced off hard and held most of the gains at the EOD. IMO, I think it will hold unless we have a market melt down to sart off next qtr on Monday. Also reading articles that mortgages are becoming profit centers at Banks. Since we are not lending anymore, not sure if that applies to us. Some people had mentioned that we may have some write-ups on some of the properties. That would be a nice change. I suspect that the new BOD is looking to sell off the Bank portfolio. Now that properties have stabilized there is a greater chance that could happen. I think things between now and the end of the year could be interesting. The new BOD claim they are acting with shareholder value in mind. We shall soon see, as they have not done much so far that warranted the firing of the Bank Pres and CEO.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1348868851182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 17:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348873179388-46</Id><Topic><Title>crazy rightie neo loons have islam on the brain. maybe they should move over there?</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348855133748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 13:58:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/11 was inside job! And of course, "mooslim this and mooslim that" didn't kill ambassador Stevens. IT WAS THE VIDEO!!!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348873179388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 18:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348873206051-47</Id><Topic><Title>What will you do when they come for you</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348863635560</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 16:20:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geeze bidder, no wonder you live in Riverside! You're too stupid to get out of that slum. Now you're supporting felons who break parole ? Why don't you impress everyone and stop posting?</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1348873206051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348886638283-48</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer, debate or no debate - Willard is toast!!! The big money is now on Bami!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348886638283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 22:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348886639375-49</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer, debate or no debate - Willard is toast!!! The big money is now on Bami!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348886639375</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 22:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348887625646-50</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about we make a bet !!!! If Romney wins, I never post again. If Obama wins, YOU never post again ! Do you have the balls ?</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1348887625646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348888093066-51</Id><Title>Ann Romney has Doubts About Mitt's Brain</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON, Sept 28 (Reuters) - Ann Romney told a Nevada television station her biggest concern if her husband, Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney, becomes president was his "mental well-being." In an interview Thursday with television station KTVN, Mrs. Romney was asked what her biggest worry was should Mitt Romney be elected to serve in the White House. "I think my biggest concern obviously would just be for his mental well-being," she said. " ................................. I think we are all worried about Mitt's mental capacity !</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1348888093066</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:08:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348888384491-52</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rowdy took a powder when I challenged him. I make the same offer to you, q4bike, or any other Pub in this board for that matter. Shall we say a bet of $500 is in order. I put my money on Bami! Anyone in this board who accepts my offer will receive one of my email addresses for further instructions. q4bike, Show us what you're made of!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348888384491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348888387835-53</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rowdy took a powder when I challenged him. I make the same offer to you, q4bike, or any other Pub in this board for that matter. Shall we say a bet of $500 is in order. I put my money on Bami! Anyone in this board who accepts my offer will receive one of my email addresses for further instructions. q4bike, Show us what you're made of!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348888387835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348888960900-54</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's not a good challenge, because money speaks louder and I like to win money.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348888960900</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 23:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>