<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343621081000-1</Id><Topic><Title>What's with all the billy monikers</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343499095000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 14:11:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here' billieeee!!!</Msg><Username>billtimmeehom</Username><Timestamp>1343621081000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 00:04:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343624408000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much did the Romneys pay for Ann's horse? How much did it cost to fly the horse to the Olympics? They took a tax write off on the horse. Do you Log Cabin darlings have nothing better to do but rehash the clothing of the First Lady? Nancy Reagan and Laura Bush sported som pretty expensive outfits. Give me a break you la la boys.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1343624408000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 01:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343624784000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Log Cabin girls are discussing fashion tonight. Could it be any gayer ?</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1343624784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 01:06:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>25</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343654067000-4</Id><Title>E*TRADE Financial Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial Corporation looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in E*TRADE Financial Corporation http://SMALLCAPSHARES.INFO</Msg><Username>devinbosa</Username><Timestamp>1343654067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343655604000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder what Obama was doing here in 2008: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tl-GHERR9hM That’s not pandering, that’s speaking his heart! But wait a minute, was telling a lie? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eSBh6C5eZgc Didn't make a single visit to Israel after 2008. Once proposed to Israel returning to 1967 borders. Romney? So far he did now what Obama did 4 years ago. With no equivocation. And I sure hope Israel won’t have his hands tied in defending its interests under his presidency as much as it currently has under Obama.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343655604000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:40:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343656360000-6</Id><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Msg>After short stop to insult the British by turning on the "GOP charm" - Romney continues to tour, and insult, the world. http://news.yahoo.com/romney-comments-fundraiser-outrage-palestinians-115109978.html</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>37</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343658220000-7</Id><Title>Bought CDNS @ 12.20</Title><Msg>But I could be wrong. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343658220000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343659038000-8</Id><Title>Dear Shareholders.....</Title><Msg>Thanks for taking the losses on our sub par reports as of late. I really screwed up by boasting about doubling our sales group in the past, as our revenues continue to drop like a rock. Now, I am switching to cutting costs and deleverging the balance sheet at a time when rates are low and it will hurt revenues even more. My plan will result in losing more money for shareholders going forward but my pay will increase next year. Your buddy, Stevie....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343659038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343659766000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumney, on his overseas trip, is proving himself a statesman. Which finally and definitively puts the last piece of the puzzle in place. Therefore, wif much regret, I'm left no choice but to pull the last bastion of support I harbored for the current administration and tender it to the Rumney campaign.</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343659766000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343660163000-10</Id><Title>Bought SWHC @ 10.04</Title><Msg>but I could be wrong. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343660163000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343661017000-11</Id><Title>ETRADE is a piece of dog sheit</Title><Msg>I am getting option quotes from Friday on numerous stocks from this freaking scumbag company.</Msg><Username>king_john_holmes</Username><Timestamp>1343661017000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343662039000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Shareholders.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343659038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Stevie: Last summer, after I fired off my activist missive to you and the board, I was given certain assurances that things were changing at etrade. I appreciate your efforts in some areas, such as board organization. But most of the sigificant change that has taken place would have happened under any average management team, as certainly as an apple would fall from a tree. Based on your encouraging conversation in the summer of '11, i agreed to forbear in my activist pursuit. However, since the summer of 11, the stock price has fallen precipitously, and the company now faces deteriorating nim, and a continued challenging dart environment. It is now time to forgo your hopes snd dreams plan and fulfill your responsibilities and fiduciary duty. This cannot be a experiment to maintain salaries and positions. The majority of investors are now in loss positions despite your assurances last summer that a greater value could be derived independently. The management of etfc cannot ignore the financual position of the company and the macfo economic headwinds. At this time, the demand is simple. There is no longer time for expert analysis and backroom discussions regarding ultimate potential. The proof is in the pps, now 50% from last years levels. We expect that the company embark on a sale process immediately. Yours truly, Ken</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343662039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343662304000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney insults the British, and to compensate, he becomes jewish. The flip flopper nominee probly got circumcised in his desperation to make up for his stupidity. At least now, he's where he belongs. Sitting on a Polish toilet.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343662304000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343662583000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Didn't make a single visit to Israel after 2008. Once proposed to Israel returning to 1967 borders. Romney?" Obama didn't have to visit, they came here, Doofus. As for Romney, he will say and do anything, because he ain't da Leader of the World, Doofus. What he says means nothing. Romney is not a leader. He's a spineless jellyfish who flows with the current.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343662583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343662887000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Shareholders.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343659038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Kenny, What you need to understand is that I don't care about the share price. I only hold a few shares in comparision to my annual take in salary and bonus. Even with this stock hitting a 152 week low, I have no interest in buying additional shares as that is not where I make my money. My new pitch is a long term turnaround. Over the next 10 years, I will bring in more than 60 million (without raises) and that dwarfs any buyout premium since I have so little stock and with a buyout I would have to take losses on all of those positions. I have managed to scare away any potiential buyers by my complete and total mis-management of this company Therefore, I will continue on my road of hunkering down, being quiet except for those prickly earnings calls I have to attend and collect my check every Friday. BTW, did you notice the President of the Bank left? I am currently trying to convince the BOD that the compensation that comes with me taking on that additional role should be given to me. Check back next quarter as I will report falling revenues with darts and nim lower, and I start to hint about a secondary offering of common stock to bolster our capital position on the backs of shareholders. Your truly, Stevie</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343662887000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:41:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343663599000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Shareholders.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343659038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if they wanted this company to soar all they would have to do is announce resignation or retirement of the ceo!!!street waiting for meaningful sign that there is hope to be bought out!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343663599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 11:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343664516000-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did you get statistics showing that it takes less than 50 colonoscopies to detect 1 real case of cancer polips? Where did you get $2000 rate for colonoscopy? My regular blood test costs almost twice as much. Where did you get that statistics showing people really willing to go for colonoscopy anyway? You have to literally go through hell to prepare for it. And finally, tell me again that mandate to buy coverage is not a tax. Why are you whining about unconfirmed, unproven, unreal tax increase when we have a real tax in form of mandate to buy a very expensive thing people are unwilling to buy otherwise? It is tax. And huge one.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343664516000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 12:08:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343665948000-18</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, every Repub in Congress voted to extend their own free health care benefits. Democrats voted against it. Pubs are greedy hypocrites.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343665948000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 12:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343666453000-19</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have a link? It seems like exact opposite is true.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343666453000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 12:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343666499000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bought SWHC @ 10.04</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343660163000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but I could be wrong. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ (3 year) life of contract highs, http://stockcharts.com/h-sc/ui?s=SWHC&amp;p=D&amp;yr=3&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;id=p88003351970 you could be right, Got Gun? beats buying 3 year life of contract lows. http://stockcharts.com/h-sc/ui?s=ETFC&amp;p=D&amp;yr=3&amp;mn=0&amp;dy=0&amp;id=p25845476137 like tbt, been trying tbt for two months , tlt will break some day. http://stockcharts.com/h-sc/ui?s=TLT&amp;p=D&amp;yr=0&amp;mn=5&amp;dy=0&amp;id=p15185143694</Msg><Username>hard_on_eraser</Username><Timestamp>1343666499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 12:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343667185000-21</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you miss it that the gop healthcare tax add $1500 a year to a family health insurance premium to pay for bushcare at the ER? can you comprehend that much of that ER care could have been prevented or dealt with FOR MUCH less cost if the person had insurance and could just go to the doc instead of the ER? and the FACT IS that a colonoscopy costs in the $2K range and that it MOST CERTAINLY can nip a cancer in the bud, since part of that is cut out precancerous polyps........ So, why do you think it is wiser for millions of poor people to never have insurance and never be able to afford a colonoscopy, and instead arrive at the ER at age 50 or whatever, with lots of bleeding, an emergency that would require surgery and intensive care and then chemo........ get the picture? and the examples would be the same for heart surgery that could have been prevented with doc visits and statins, and on and on. you people are just disgrace, really. and furthermore, the ACA reduces the deficit, which is one reason the man who enacted the blue print for it , Romneycare, said of his mandate in Ma. that is the "responsible" thing to do. Is Mittens a liar?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343667185000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 12:53:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343668849000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Calling Obama the "Leader of the Free World" though assumes a great many facts NOT in evidence. For instance. The word "Leader" . . .</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1343668849000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 13:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343669496000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I fully agree and here it is: http://thecaucus.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/07/30/romney-comments-on-palestinians-draw-criticism/ How can Mitt ever broker a deal between Palestine and Israel?</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1343669496000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 13:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343669673000-24</Id><Title>SVU surging higher.....</Title><Msg>on firing the CEO. Up 11% after horrid earnings but getting rid of the CEO is a major positive. Sound familiar?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343669673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 13:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343671357000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Dear Shareholders.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343659038000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:37:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No kidding. Citadel has to be smoking mad at this point. All those 28 million shares got cut in half. The only people making any dough here are the note holders. Stevie has no clue on that subject except to say they submitted a capital plan to regulators. Why he couldn't share some thoughts on the proposal is beyond me. With Amtd, schwab, and Scottrade all suffering for darts and asset accum, there has to be a deal out there somewhere. There will come a time in the near future when consolidation will be a necessity.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343671357000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343671967000-26</Id><Topic><Title>SVU surging higher.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343669673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 13:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Etfc will never attract a top end talent. The handwriting is on the wall here and no one will take the job just to get layed off in a short period of time. Stevie is a short termer brought in to fumble around while the loan book declines via collections and charge-offs. The situation is just to right not to sell this piggy. Timing may not be better as the sale could close just after the call on the 12 1/2% notes. Stevie and his board need to get real, real fast</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343671967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343672273000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bought SWHC @ 10.04</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343660163000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be better when the general market goes green. Where is the Euro talking head that guarantees the currency today? tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343672273000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:17:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343672697000-28</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't answer a single question I asked. Please, confirm the source where you are getting your numbers from if you don't want me to call them fake. GOP Tax increase? Understand the difference between voluntary action of buying insurance coverage (by paying asking price) and involuntary action of taxation or mandatory purchase of such coverage?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343672697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343673211000-29</Id><Title>Just remember this my friend</Title><Msg>Kenneth sold off his converts at $16 per share. He didn't sell to dolts. They wanted a 20% return.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343673211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343673504000-30</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Where did you get statistics showing that it takes less than 50 colonoscopies to detect 1 real case of cancer polips?&gt;&gt; Here is a case of a moron talking!!! 50 colonoscopies? You do ONE colonoscopy every 5 years if everything is OK and that's starting at the age of 40. One every 2 years otherwise.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343673504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343673988000-31</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am talking about 50 patients undergoing single procedure, not a single patient taking 50. You have to live hundreds of years to be recommended 50 colonoscopies. Who is an idiot here?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343673988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343674184000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Nancy Reagan and Laura Bush sported som pretty expensive outfits&gt;&gt; The difference is that they didn't pretend to be one of you, and have a photographer conveniently snap photos of them shopping at Target...wise up!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343674184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343674192000-33</Id><Topic><Title>Just remember this my friend</Title><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343673211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://247wallst.com/2011/02/24/etrades-secondary-drop-is-actually-good-for-holders-etfc-schw-amtd-ms-gs</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343674192000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343674409000-34</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you promoting "emergency-room-only" medical care system?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343674409000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343674503000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Just remember this my friend</Title><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343673211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead they got a big fat tax loss sale to cover the gains on all that aapl stock they held. Whoever Kenny sold those shares too are not going to be coming back to the well again on anything he wants to dump. Not a good thing for KG in the big picture. You can make excuses for OLB's with the rate situation. You can't make excuses for the dramatic underperformance of this stock tho. There can't be one person who thinks Freiberg has done a good job. All he has really done is roll off the loan portfolio. He even farms out the servicing which costs them 100mil per year, which leaves me to think... What exactly does Stevie really do?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343674503000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343675557000-36</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I confront fake argument.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343675557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343676691000-37</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fake argument? What is fake about our health care approach being at least 3 times more expensive than anywhere else while ranking 37th in quality (just above Cuba) ??? http://www.photius.com/rankings/healthranks.html http://www.businessinsider.com/us-most-inefficient-healthcare-system-in-the-world-2011-3 Our health care system delivers life-expectancy equivalent of CHILE while costing 7 times more. Prevention is always cheaper and better for the patient, businesses and the country. What you advertise is equivalent with never changing oil, just hoping and praying the car will not break.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343676691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:31:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343676701000-38</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are the idiot, obviously. you miss it that the gop's hidden healthcare tax adds $1500 a year to a family health insurance premium to pay for bushcare at the ER. can you comprehend that much of that ER care could have been prevented or dealt with FOR MUCH less cost if the person had insurance and could just go to the doc instead of the ER? "families will pay an additional $1,502 in premiums .. to cover the unreimbursed costs of the uninsured in 2010. " http://www.marketwatch.com/story/covering-costs-of-uninsured-boosts-health-premiums "It is estimated that $1,502 is added to the cost of Texas family premiums for costs for the uninsured" http://www.hhsc.state.tx.us/reports/UncompCareReport.pdf</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343676701000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343677178000-39</Id><Title>Billboard in Aurora Colorado...</Title><Msg>Remember the peace prize?... http://news.yahoo.com/obama-aurora-billboard-everyones-talking-203448772.html?_esi=1</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343677178000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:39:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343677779000-40</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican - the IDIOT here is CROWN the CLOWN!!! Hudson Medical Center, WI or HCMC - MN and HUMANA INS: One colonoscopy every 10 years staring at age 40 till 60. (unless there is a family history problem) Then every 5 years unless otherwise ordered! For me it's every 3 years, because of benign polyps and every 5 years for her! This guy knows everything better and is nothing but a argumentative clown on EVERY subject, save yourself the time to reply! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343677779000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343677889000-41</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, Jealousy will get you nowhere. You Log Cabin ladies have nice day/night.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1343677889000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343678296000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Just remember this my friend</Title><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343673211000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 14:33:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ken let go of his shares to stay under 10%. Who ever picked them up must feel a little sheepish right now. Aaaaaaa</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343678296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 15:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343678525000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Bought SWHC @ 10.04</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343660163000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sold SWHC market on close. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343678525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343678606000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Bought CDNS @ 12.20</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343658220000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sold CDNS market on close. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343678606000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343678703000-45</Id><Title>ETFC will close above $8.40 by this Friday!!</Title><Msg>ETFC will rally tomorrow and Wednesday!! Expecting $8+ by Wednesday!! Mark this!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343678703000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343678920000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;You Log Cabin ladies have nice day/night&gt;&gt; You seem obsessed with queers.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343678920000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:08:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343679176000-47</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so rather than pay for the colonoscopy (about $2k),which can PREVENT colon cancer, you would rather the uninsured show up at the ER with a medical emergency requiring, surgery, intensive care and then chem....cost maybe $100K .....</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343679176000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343680197000-48</Id><Title>NIM continues to erode YOY earnings comparisons</Title><Msg>Get used to the financials constantly being downgraded in the next few quarters as NIM continues to erode YOY earnings comparisons. But turdholders knew that already. However, they failed to look at the distribution on the chart and failed to sell the pops to reduce loss's. Oh well...something's never change, like E management and badholders of the worst run company on the street. imho</Msg><Username>dswanhmsk</Username><Timestamp>1343680197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343681274000-49</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hydro - don't put words into my mouth, that's NOT what I said! I just gave a corrected schedule as to what insurance companies and MEDICARE do! All our hospitals will NOT take you unless there is an EMERGENCY, colonoscopy is prevention, just like mammograms If everybody is required to buy insurance, then there will be no way that they can afford it, especial on minimum income or being laid off! After she got laid off, we went with HUMANA till medicare kicked in, which was 435/mo and a deductible of $7500, now you tell me how those "POOR" people, un/underemployed can afford that??? They will have NO insurance and won't be able to pay the FINE either! MN and WI already don't take MEDICAIDE patients! If this OBIMBOCARE takes place, watch for there only being 2 or 3 insurance companies left and they will SET THE PRICE of the policies! ROWDY (I do appreciate your civil conservation)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343681274000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343681621000-50</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC will close above $8.40 by this Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343678703000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish you would write some enthusiastic propoganda which leads Freiberg to sell this woofer.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343681621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343681777000-51</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ah - yes - Mr Rodent, a life long government program beneficiary (ex-air-force-pilot) - still on government payroll (retired - getting pension and SS benefits - all provided by the taxpayer) - but against anyone else getting "perks" (like union negotiated pension plans) speaks up...!! We are so glad you could enlighten us with your self-absorbed, self-worshiping wisdom. Yeah Rowdy - we know you like yourself.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343681777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343681991000-52</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC will close above $8.40 by this Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343678703000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stevie is an extremely savy guy. Watch out for his anticipation of the future. Everyone is in good hands here at ETFC..... Money Quote: “Where you think there would be a fire — in our subprime portfolio — it actually looks pretty good,’’ Freiberg said at an investor conference in September 2007. Citigroup’s subprime mortgages ultimately led to billions of dollars of write-downs at the bank that required Citigroup to receive a $45 billion taxpayer bailout.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343681991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343682026000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you throw snit fit at cindy mccain's $300K 2008 gop convention outfit? 2008 was when W was mumbling about how "unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down" from Vanity Fair Cindy McCain's wardrobe for the gop convention: Oscar de la Renta dress: $3,000 Chanel J12 White Ceramic Watch: $4,500 Three-carat diamond earrings: $280,000 Four-strand pearl necklace: $11,00 to $25,000 Shoes, designer unknown: $600 Total: Between $299,100 and $313,100. and don't forget Romney wrote off $70k for "dressage" ....or as one wit described it, for taking his horse to the prom, that's more than most people make in a year.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343682026000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343682077000-54</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have tried to post that link several times today - something in it that Yahoo blocks, but the vole was middle of July. All of GOP and few democrats voted to keep their current ultra-pampering health insurance, that covers them free of charge FOREVER, rather then get the same insurance their constituents are getting through exchanges.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343682077000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:01:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343682096000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He made a fool of himself in England. He shamelessly pandered to the Israelis, What next? Will he suggest that Poland attack Russia, and guarantee that the US military will lead from the front?</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343682096000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:01:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343682479000-56</Id><Title>Kenneth Griffin and Stevie Freiberg: the untold story</Title><Msg>Freiberg: Ken, we are going to turn this thing and get the pps up to $27 within a couple years no problem. Stock price is $18 now. Griffun: steve, i am going to go ape-schitz on your face you are one reckless dude. You think the company is going to hold up this mcap through 2012? You are nutz. Too much headwind. Freiberg: trust me. We got some new baby commercials and a new ipod app, plus the superbowl adds Griffun: you are nutz. Spending like $60,000,000 a year to pick up a few accounts on a net basis. You'd be better off buying up a few small brokers or some niche businesses. Freiberg: we like commercials. Its our identity. Griffun: i think i am going to jump off the building. You get one year to do something with this. Then me and Leon are going to railroad your sorry skeleton into a sale. Freiberg: this call is over</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343682479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343683447000-57</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I though you guys had no issue with rich people being rich. Hell - your GOP party runs on "trickle down economics", so you should be happy about this. At least she looks good in it.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343683447000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:24:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343684453000-58</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here she is in her 2nd grade yearbook pic. http://www.funiacs.com/poze/mare/5179_4_1280949356_1289904782.jpg</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343684453000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 17:40:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343689139000-59</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC will close above $8.40 by this Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343678703000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:05:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm long but that if that is true that is a great find</Msg><Username>rolltide6</Username><Timestamp>1343689139000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 18:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343689268000-60</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, It's the other way around! You Pukes are the Log Cabin queers!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1343689268000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:01:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343690165000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we know who you are and the picture you posted of the First Lady is just what we expect of a sicko Puke!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1343690165000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343690379000-62</Id><Topic><Title>Continued Bullish Phase?</Title><Username>claribeldfv728</Username><Timestamp>1343652377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>billiesrm635</Username><Timestamp>1343690379000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343690463000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney has to have some of the most inept advisers, speech writers and spokespeople that have ever undertaken a presidential campaign.</Msg><Username>tuerpe2</Username><Timestamp>1343690463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343690954000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>. . . . . . . . .. A US president must have both sense and sensibility. Mr. Romney has a business sense but may be in short supply for other senses and definitely lacks sensibility. It is only in the US that people believe that if you make it big in business, you are bestowed with other capabilities. Mr. Romney has proved time and again that although he may have shown immense success in a narrow business field (selling and buying businesses) he has shown utter ignorance in many fields essential to grasp the US domestic and foreign policy issues What surprises me most is that Mr. Romney was the Governor of Massachusetts and that executive experience is more valuable than that of running a business. Since he has disavowed many good decisions he took as the Governor, he is left nothing to bank on but his business experience that required a sharp, one dimensional approach to the goal of making money at the expense of other sensibilities. Mr. Romney’s insensitive comments in England and Israel are evidence of that.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1343690954000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343691844000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's not forget that whatever the political tactics of their leaders, the Palestinians as a people are individuals and families who mainly just want a chance to flourish. What Mr. Romney says about the Palestinians, he says about all of us who, despite hard work in difficult circumstances, may not have enjoyed the luck and opportunities and connections to fulfill our potential. I see in President Obama a confident, successful man with the virtue of gratitude. He knows he isn't where he is because he's a superman, but because he was able to find avenues for his excellence that are not always available to everyone who deserves a chance to achieve. He understands this both as an American and as a citizen of the world. Wars are caused by the greedy and arrogant, not by people who, like ordinary Palestinians, only want a reasonably happy life. Mr. Romney has repeatedly told us that he wants to lead only those who are motivated by a relentless need to acquire more and more, not those of us who aspire to peace and prosperity on a human scale for all.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1343691844000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 19:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343698169000-66</Id><Title>A Mr., A Mrs. "You No Build That"</Title><Msg>The entire country is tired of all the business bashing. Also sick of the enabling and coddling of an ever-growing segment of the population who will not work. Periot! http://hotair.com/archives/2012/07/29/a-you-didnt-build-that-convention/</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343698169000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 21:29:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343698921000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer, honey, Poland's former leader Lech Walessa "endured" Mitt Romney and Polish labor unions kept their distance. Mittens trip abroad was a complete and miserable failure.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1343698921000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 21:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343701621000-68</Id><Title>Now Obama Proclaims Economic Prowess...</Title><Msg>And he Adds Little Timmy to the Call!... http://news.yahoo.com/obama-warns-headwinds-europe-sees-euro-surviving-002106478--business.html</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343701621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 22:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343702239000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Now Obama Proclaims Economic Prowess...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343701621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 22:27:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't 'Headwinds' code for bj in homercrat circles?</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343702239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 22:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343702541000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Now Obama Proclaims Economic Prowess...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343701621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 22:27:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah... But more like this... http://news.yahoo.com/earnings-perform-2009-boos-then-boos-now-231602882--finance.html</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343702541000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 22:42:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343705774000-71</Id><Title>At Least We are Not This Guy...</Title><Msg>He Claims Bad Luck... http://sports.yahoo.com/blogs/soccer-dirty-tackle/ever-banega-ferrari-burnt-crisp-184633745--sow.html</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343705774000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 23:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>