<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352266206297-1</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney starts TODAY !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1352205542008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 07:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The trouble with socialism is that eventually you run out of other people's money." - Margaret Thatcher. When we run out of people like Romney, we become 3rd world country. But that's all socialists goal anyway. We are Greece very soon. Equal misery for all.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1352266206297</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 00:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352273561908-2</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney starts TODAY !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1352205542008</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 07:39:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good grief! Obama can't fix it? So, it makes sense to give him another 4! We accumulated only $6T. Point of no return is almost there.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1352273561908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 02:32:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352292458629-3</Id><Topic><Title>505Mil at 6% and 800Mil at 6.375% pricing.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1352241422104</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 17:37:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should save the company between 60-70 million per year.</Msg><Username>deepwater531</Username><Timestamp>1352292458629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 07:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352296611784-4</Id><Title>ETFC Baggies Just Dump! By BBY Best Buy Buyut Happenning For Real Soon! Not ETFC $25 BBY Buyout! News!</Title><Msg>Yup!!</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1352296611784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 08:56:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352301515258-5</Id><Topic><Title>505Mil at 6% and 800Mil at 6.375% pricing.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1352241422104</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 17:37:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stock Buyback? Are you high? Regulators are not going to let this company use cash to buy back stock or issue a dividend. Last quarter, they identified 90mil worth of loans that were performing but....had filed bk. Etrade took a 50mil charge. That means the loans on the books or loan amounts are significantly higher than actual value. They still have 5 billion in HELOC's and those have close to ZERO actual value if default, a total writeoff. It will be 2 more years of healing and hopefully just treading water for this company. Rates will stay low and the trading situation does not look to improve.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1352301515258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:18:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352302010239-6</Id><Title>Your Local Best Buy Store Will Exist The Stock Is Private Now Soon $25 Buyout!!! By Now $15 For $10 points!!</Title><Msg>Yup!!!</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1352302010239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:26:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352304310335-7</Id><Title>BBY not ETFC Buyoout! Schulze Lined Up Money Private Equity! F Off Kenney G! ETFC Never byout!!!</Title><Msg>HAHAHAGHAHA</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1352304310335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 11:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352304683172-8</Id><Title>I would like to congratulate president Obama</Title><Msg>He bought enough votes for the win. He was successful in selling the argument that it's easier to take from others than to do for yourself. I feel he garnered a large share of the yute and female vote because kids don't want to go to war and their moms don't want to send them. The black vote he won because he promised them free stuff. He bought the Mexicans off giving back-door amnesty. He will however, have some big issues to deal wif IE; fiscal cliff, tax-mageddon, deficit, debt ceiling, national debt, high UE. Along with answering tough questions on Benghazi and fast and furious. Also, how long can he kick the can on the Israel - Iran nuclear issue? Let's hope his second term turns out better than his first. The country made its choice. Now we gotta deal with its aftermaf.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1352304683172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 11:11:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352328043470-9</Id><Title>In the end</Title><Msg>crown1111 comments on Obama's victory is telling. ** That's right. Get used to it. The more conservatively extreme you will get - the more of a social outcast you will be** This attitude is exactly why the country will stay devided....talk about my way or the highway. In the end it did not come down to the economy, it came down to entitlements. To many folks afraid of losing their benifits in a bad economy...in the short term in a way I can't blame them, in the long term a bad idea. There is no substitute for a job and the self esteem that acconpanies it....a lot of folks who cast their vote for Obama couldn't relate to a self reliant rich guy, and therefore were much more comfortable associating with weakness...si la vie</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1352328043470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 17:40:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352340850014-10</Id><Title>$7.25 is coming very soon within a month!!</Title><Msg>Wait until I give you a signal... Or Sell now and add more later.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1352340850014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 21:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>