<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344571363000-1</Id><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Msg>Editor's note: Peter C. Canellos, a lawyer, is former chair of the New York State Bar Association Tax Section. Edward D. Kleinbard is a professor at Gould School of Law at the University of Southern California. He is the former chief of staff of Congress's Joint Committee on Taxation. (CNN) -- Mitt Romney's refusal to release tax returns in the critical years of his income accumulation has done little to dispel the legitimate concern that arises from hints buried in his scant disclosure to date: Did he augment his wealth through highly aggressive tax stratagems of questionable validity? Opinion: Why won't Romney release more tax returns? One relevant line of inquiry, largely ignored so far, is to examine what exists in the public record regarding his attitude toward tax compliance and tax avoidance. While this examination is hampered because his dealings through his private equity company, Bain Capital, are kept shrouded, there are other indicators. A key troubling public manifestation of Romney's apparent insensitivity to tax obligations is his role in Marriott International's abusive tax shelter activity, as previously reported by Jesse Drucker in Bloomberg. Edward D. Kleinbard Edward D. Kleinbard Romney has had a close, long-standing, personal and business connection with Marriott International and its founders. He served as a member of the Marriott board of directors for many years. From 1993 to 1998, Romney was the head of the audit committee of the Marriott board. During that period, Marriott engaged in a series of complex and high-profile maneuvers, including "Son of Boss," a notoriously abusive prepackaged tax shelter that investment banks and accounting firms marketed to corporations such as Marriott. In this respect, Marriott was in the vanguard of a then-emerging corporate tax shelter bubble that substantially undermined the entire corporate tax system. Son of Boss and its related shelters represented perhaps the largest tax avoidance scheme in history, costing the U.S. many billions in lost corporate tax revenues. In response, the government initiated legal challenges that resulted in complete disallowance of the losses claimed by Marriott and other corporations. In addition, the Son of Boss transaction was listed by the Internal Revenue Service as an abusive transaction, requiring specific disclosure and subject to heavy penalties. Statutory penalties were also made more stringent to deter future tax shelter activity. Finally, the government brought successful criminal prosecutions against a number of individuals involved in Son of Boss and related transactions not associated with Marriott, including principals at major law and accounting firms. In his key role as chairman of the Marriott board's audit committee, Romney approved the firm's reporting of fictional tax losses exceeding $70 million generated by its Son of Boss transaction. His endorsement of this stratagem provides insight into Romney's professional ethics and attitude toward tax compliance obligations. Like other prepackaged corporate tax shelters of that era, Marriott's Son of Boss transaction was an entirely artificial transaction, bearing no relationship to its business. Its sole purpose was to create a gigantic tax loss out of thin air without any economic risk, cost or loss -- other than the fee Marriott paid the promoter. The Son of Boss transaction was vulnerable to attack on at least two grounds. First, the transaction's promoters and consumers relied on a strained technical statutory analysis. Second, the Son of Boss deal violated the fundamental tax principle that the tax law ignores transactions unless they have a motivating business purpose and a substantial nontax economic effect. In the Marriott case, the IRS raised both arguments and won on the first interpretive issue.</Msg><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344571399000-2</Id><Topic><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Court of Claims (affirmed by the Court of Appeals) rejected Marriott's technical analysis, finding no reliable argument or authority to support it. The court therefore did not need to reach the issue of business purpose and economic substance. In subsequent decisions, involving similar transactions but other parties, the courts have sustained the second line of attack as well, finding the claimed losses to be fictitious. The complete judicial rejection of the Son of Boss tax scheme was entirely predictable. In mid-1994, for example, roughly contemporaneously with Marriott's execution of its Son of Boss trade and well before Marriott filed its return claiming the artificial loss, the highly respected Tax Section of the New York Bar Association filed a public comment with the U.S. Treasury and IRS urging rejection of the technical claims made by promoters of such schemes. In his key position as head of the board's audit committee, Romney was required under the securities laws and his fiduciary duties to review the transaction. In fact, it has been publicly reported that Romney was the Marriott Board member most acquainted with the transaction and to whom the other board members turned for advice. This makes sense because aggressive tax-driven financial engineering was a large part of what Romney (and Bain) did for a living. For these reasons, it is fair to hold him accountable for Marriott's spurious tax reporting. Romney's campaign staff has attempted to deflect responsibility, arguing that he relied on Marriott's tax department and advisers. This claim is disingenuous. In a transaction of this magnitude, sensitivity and questionableness, the prudent step would be to secure advice to the audit committee and the board from experienced and independent tax counsel, who would certainly have cautioned that the Marriott position was risky and not supported by precedent or proper statutory interpretation. Moreover, on the key issue of the business purpose and economic substance, Romney was, or should have been, aware of the facts that the transaction had its genesis solely in tax avoidance and was a "marketed" tax shelter. He had an insider's perspective on the motivation and lack of substance in the transaction, as well as the financial sophistication to understand the tax avoidance involved. Romney failed in his duties to Marriott and its shareholders and acted to undermine the fairness of the tax system. No one could accuse Romney of lacking the intelligence and analytical skills to have dealt with this transaction appropriately. Indeed, his strengths in this regard were the reason the other board members relied on him. What emerges from this window into corporate tax compliance behavior is the picture of an executive who was willing to go to the edge, if not beyond, to bend the rules to seek an unfair advantage, and then hide behind the advice of so-called experts to deflect criticism when a scheme backfires.</Msg><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571399000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344571649000-3</Id><Title>Futures = RED. ...learn why...</Title><Msg>China GDP taking Da Dirt Nap. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Thems of Yinz who were smart enough to implement "Da First Byte Rule" may put [CD] after yer moniker for da next 5 days. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344571649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344572058000-4</Id><Title>Romney's Greatest Achievement</Title><Msg>His own staff says it's his health care bill.</Msg><Username>hobojimattentionwhore</Username><Timestamp>1344572058000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:14:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344572112000-5</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal intolerance of religion, esp Mormonism.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1344564209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 22:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crown[P], I'm gonna tell Jesus you said that. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( I'd be very careful in thunder storms if I were y'all. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344572112000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344572689000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Futures = RED. ...learn why...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344571649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:07:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hahaha... bear, you are the funniest home video guy. Now, you're talking my future talk!!! ETFC will be going up again tomorrow regardless of future or negative market!! Go back to sleep until I wake you up!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344572689000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:24:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344573279000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal intolerance of religion, esp Mormonism.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1344564209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 22:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You continue to exercise ignorance. Christians criticizing Mormons is NOT racism. It may be religious bigotry, but not racism. Racists like you don't even know the definition. But we know you attack Mooselims and juice, and you ARE a racist !</Msg><Username>reefbeveler</Username><Timestamp>1344573279000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344575690000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Citadel buyout</Title><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1344569429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree that Citadel is setting up Etrade so they can bought out. Citadel is behind it and they lead the search for a new CEO. He must be ready to sell ETrade to get the job I think. I missed this run up and I have to wait for a pullback below $8.20</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1344575690000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 01:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344580730000-9</Id><Title>Get in at $8.40 tomorrow morning!!</Title><Msg>After pull back to $8.40, it will jump to $8.80+, possibly $9!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344580730000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 02:38:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344583303000-10</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Directors owe Shareholders $3,500,000,000</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344546074000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 17:01:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Directors dont owe squat! The "small print" says very clearly that investments are NOT guarenteed to go up or be profitable period! Thats why Goldman and company will never be charged in any court of law.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1344583303000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 03:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344599148000-11</Id><Topic><Title>History of E-Tub's BTO ...laern more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344570733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:52:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok. Yinz can go back to what you do. Freeberg is cleaning out his desk.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344599148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344599807000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Citadel buyout</Title><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1344569429000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have three thumbs and something else. All four of them are up.</Msg><Username>million_shares</Username><Timestamp>1344599807000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 07:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344601639000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Freiberg drove Etrade into a Ditch</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1344567799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 23:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey lawyers, stop chasing the financial ambulance. Nothing to see here. No dead bodies , just slow trading and lower NIM.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344601639000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344604901000-14</Id><Title>Mitt &amp; "son of boss" tax avoidance scam</Title><Msg>"..... Romney personally approved over $70 million in fictional losses to the IRS as part of the notorious 'Son of Boss' tax scandal," "One of the largest tax avoidance schemes in history. Isn't it time for Romney to come clean?" [this]..refers to Romney's role as chairman of the audit committee for hotel giant Marriott International for six years in the 1990s. During that time, the company took advantage of complicated tax avoidance measures, including the so-called "Son of Boss" tax shelter which was later challenged successfully by the Justice Department and IRS. Romney, as an auditor, presumably knew about the practice." fits in with the Mittens banking where enron did, the Cayman islands and other tax scamming places, and it fits in with his shady hiding of his income tax records too.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344604901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:21:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344605113000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "son of boss" tax avoidance scam</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344604901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, you're LOST. This s the Etrade stock board. Go change your DEM, gumbed down bong water, buy lots of dope- cause your Kenyan born boy king, Stalin jr. is losing in a landslide this Nov. Now get lost. Thanks you mental midget.</Msg><Username>teninchwangbar</Username><Timestamp>1344605113000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344605413000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt &amp; "son of boss" tax avoidance scam</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344604901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:21:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stupid, spare me your little miss manners has her panties in a wad routine, you phony hypocrite and weasel.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344605413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344605641000-17</Id><Topic><Title>New report out: (ETFC)</Title><Username>starrxfl966</Username><Timestamp>1344521991000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>mariannaltm1657</Username><Timestamp>1344605641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:34:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606007000-18</Id><Topic><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>worth repeating: "In his key role as chairman of the Marriott board's audit committee, Romney approved the firm's reporting of fictional tax losses exceeding $70 million generated by its Son of Boss transaction. His endorsement of this stratagem provides insight into Romney's professional ethics and attitude toward tax compliance obligations. Like other prepackaged corporate tax shelters of that era, Marriott's Son of Boss transaction was an entirely artificial transaction, bearing no relationship to its business. Its sole purpose was to create a gigantic tax loss out of thin air without any economic risk, cost or loss -- other than the fee Marriott paid the promoter." romney and key lay have a lot in common, huh, besides their cayman island bank accounts and incorporations?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344606007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606184000-19</Id><Topic><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We told you to LEAVE little boy. Now you're going to get your i.d. yanked - go find the DEM nut ball forum. You're on DOPE and lost. SHUTTING you down.</Msg><Username>teninchwangbar</Username><Timestamp>1344606184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344606377000-20</Id><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Msg>By David Benoit While several analysts were looking at E*Trade’s CEO change as a potential white flag for buyers to come in, Raymond James says that doesn’t make sense. Bloomberg News “We believe this was a decision based on finding a different skill set at the CEO position, and contrary to the market scuttlebutt we think this could actually be a sign that E*Trade is not anywhere close to selling the firm,” analyst Patrick O’Shaughnessy wrote in a report. The brokerage firm on Thursday fired Steven Freiberg and put in his place Chairman Frank Petrilli, a long-time brokerage executive. O’Shaughnessy believes the move was made because Freiberg, a long-time Citigroup executive, didn’t have the right experience to turn around a brokerage. But anytime something moves at E*Trade, the market leaps to talk about selling, a possibility the company explored last year but decided against. O’Shaughnessy has some cold water for these theories. “First, E*Trade’s Board did not need Steven Freiberg’s permission to sell the company. If a company were to approach E*Trade with an offer (TD Ameritrade is the most often-suggested potential suitor) that offer would be evaluated by the board, not by the CEO,” he said.”Second, one could argue that hiring a more online brokerage-oriented leader actually indicates a longer-term commitment to the business. If it were just a matter of babysitting the company for another quarter or two Freiberg could have done the job quite adequately, in our opinion.”</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606561000-21</Id><Topic><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>miss manners, please keep your pantie wad blatherings to yourself. I guess you think Romney's approval of phony transactions for tax scams should remain hidden like his own income tax returns?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344606561000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606669000-22</Id><Topic><Title>"Son of Boss"</Title><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344571363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:02:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone with a record of championing and enabling corporate tax schemes, possibly felonious, has no business being POTUS. Public has right to know and to see the tax returns of such a candidate.</Msg><Username>topgun_0476</Username><Timestamp>1344606669000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:51:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344606894000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consider the known facts: Harry is a Mormon with connections. Huntsman is a Mormon who absolutely HATES Willard and whose kin are big wheels at Bain. That's called access. Also with access is McCain- he's seen the returns, hates Willard (pretty much all Pubs do) and might think a convention disaster would lead the party to him as a fallback candidate.</Msg><Username>topgun_0476</Username><Timestamp>1344606894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344607144000-24</Id><Title>manipulation at its best</Title><Msg>takes 10 million shares to go up 50 cents and 300 k to drop 16 cents. etfc at its best IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344607144000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344607295000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone else see this? (ETFC)</Title><Username>karoleqxh381</Username><Timestamp>1344520930000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>martyxhi0071</Username><Timestamp>1344607295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344607695000-26</Id><Title>The Willard experience</Title><Msg>"The only thing we've seen him stand up for, so far, is hiding his taxes. On every other issue, from abortion to health care to guns, he's flip flopped and wimped out. Electing this guy probably means Grover Nordquist will be the most powerful man in the world. That's scary."</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344607695000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 10:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344611014000-27</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Girls don't wanna discuss this bowl of ice water in the face.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344611014000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344611181000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think anyone except trusted tax preparer or IRS can have "strong cards" about Romney's tax returns. In both cases the source is vioating the law. I would press Harry hard to release the name of the person who provided him information. In case he refuses, I would file the case to House ethics committee against Harry for smearing private citizen. Just like in case of Joe the Plumber. My take, Harry either has very little respect for the law or no ethics whatsoever. Neither discovery would surprise me much.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344611181000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344611492000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://articles.latimes.com/2012/aug/07/news/la-pn-gop-screams-foul-but-harry-reid-still-winning-20120806 "Salon.com talked to tax attorneys and found the claim that Romney paid zero over a decade “nothing short of ludicrous.” Harry, Harry, pants on fire!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344611492000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344612413000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love the republican hypocrisy in all this. Obama MUST release documents that NO candidate has ever released in the past(bith records, college records) But Romney should not have to release tax documents that ever candidate has released since his father created the standard. Pubs pushed and pushed and pushed till Obama finally released his full form birth cirtificate, now it is fair for dems to push and push and push for Romney to release his tax records. Oh and Romney is now a very public figure running for the highest office in the land, he can clear his name in 2 seconds adn smear harrys reputation all over the wall by simply doing what all other presidential candidates have done since his father, release his tax records. Wonder why he is not doing this very simple and damaging to the democratic party act??? What do you think?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344612413000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:26:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344612522000-31</Id><Title>I added more at $8.45 today!!</Title><Msg>Momentum set!! A new CEO will reshape the company!! ETFC is going up to $20+ next year!! Get in now!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344612522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:28:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344612543000-32</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crotch: Rj rationale is sound and i agree wif it. They do leave out one reality which is in fact part of the company strategy. The best offer that comes in will be a unsolicited offer , then any followon competing offers. The industry is sufferin from declining darts and soon will experience contraction in their lending businesses (margin). So while doing nothing is not a plan, it is a strategy. The loans are not toxic as they were several years ago and a final mtm adjustment would not be a deal killer. There are too many synergy effects here that will juice a sale price. I am thinking $300,000,000 easily then upwards to $450,000,000 and thats in g&amp;a alone. Just think the company is spending over $120,000,000 in advertising alone.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344612543000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:29:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344612857000-33</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No deal, no one wants this POS.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344612857000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:34:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344613107000-34</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I've long suspected as much but kept it to myself out of respect for a fellow pedophile"</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1344613107000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344613340000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I would press Harry hard to release the name of the person who provided him information. In case he refuses, I would file the case to House ethics committee against Harry for smearing private citizen." Uh, Harry is in the SENATE! Harry's too smart to blatantly lie. Someone reputable did tell him this story but Harry, like the American people, can only wait for disclosure to find out the truth. Until then, the Dems will taunt the Wimp with his furtive behavior.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344613340000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344614336000-36</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry must disclose the source of allegations, doofus. Mitt Romney is not an official fugure, Harry is. Harry is obligated to follow ethics rules. Romney, on other hand, is obligated only to file his tax returns to IRS. Disclosing them to the public is only to show good will. Nice gesture. Nothing more. Allegation that Romney didn't pay taxes for 10 years is flat out lie.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344614336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344614363000-37</Id><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+</Title><Msg>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+ Expecting $10+ very soon!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344614363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344614792000-38</Id><Topic><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344614363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wish you were right for once.I see this as coming quarter will be horrible so they get price up dump and short back to low 7's nothing but sucker rally going on!!remember etfc never fails to disappoint!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344614792000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344615055000-39</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your speaking in terms of absolutes is enough for me to know you are wrong.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344615055000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344615355000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Name just one GOP leader demanding Obama to disclose his college records. What is this required "standard" Romney's father established? You create standards on the fly when it fits your purpose. There is no standard, there is good will. Obama's birth certificate? A person must present US form of birth certificate to become US President. It is in Constitution. Did you know that? Tax forms? Where this is written?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344615355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344615655000-41</Id><Title>ceo sa a good start</Title><Msg>now they need to get rid of the sleeping board members that let frieburg last so long as ceo!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344615655000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:20:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344615758000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Continued Bullish Phase?</Title><Username>elvynuew441</Username><Timestamp>1344600562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 08:09:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am glad I am in the right site.</Msg><Username>charletonrlh798</Username><Timestamp>1344615758000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344616194000-43</Id><Title>Bank Pres gone, CEO gone</Title><Msg>Both Citi buddies. Board is cleaning house and placing people they want to run the company. I suspect the Brokerage and bank are going to somehow split. The CEO and Board may have disagreed on this direction.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616194000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344616249000-44</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dynamics of the company have changed. I would assume with the CEO out all of the opportunities will be explored more deeply. That guy with 27.5 million shares on the BOD will be driving this car more than in the past. Hard to say that is not a good thing for the stock.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344616249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:30:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344616485000-45</Id><Title>Told ya Kenny would not let this stock sit at 52 week lows</Title><Msg>The man has been getting his way since he went active. Slowly replacing the board to do his bidding. You know what he wants most? How can anyone say a sale is out of order when the man running the show desires just that. My biggest fear is he trys to steal ETFC with a low ball offer and takes it private. If he controls the hedge fund votes, he may try to do it. However, he doesn't want to be regulated like a bank, so first must get rid of it.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344616631000-46</Id><Topic><Title>RJ scorns buyout chatter</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344606377000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 09:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RJ's logic is sound until you add this piece of logic. Who is in control at ETFC and what do they want? Then their logic fails.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344616807000-47</Id><Title>buying more</Title><Msg>JUST PUT IN A GTC AT 7.30. SOONER THEN 9 imho</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344616807000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344616903000-48</Id><Title>Sale may not be pending but a short risk is not worth it</Title><Msg>Kenny may get us an offer even if it is his own. What if he offers $14 to buy. We jump up in a day. Even if the board rejects it, it sets a floor. Is the 1.40 back to our lows worth the $ 5.50 loss on a short?</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:41:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344617135000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Sale may not be pending but a short risk is not worth it</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:41:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember etfc never fails to disappoint. always make money on the short!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344617135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344617467000-50</Id><Title>could ceo firing</Title><Msg>be an act of desperation? knowing next quater numbers will be horrific and they want to unload their shares.Bump the price up and sell and short back to the 7'S.IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344617467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344617696000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Sale may not be pending but a short risk is not worth it</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344616903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:41:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obvious power play going on. Change isn't coming, it is here. Short away my friend, but if you hold overnight you are a fool, unless you have calls to protect you.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344617696000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:54:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344617823000-52</Id><Topic><Title>could ceo firing</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344617467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UR really reaching there buddy. More like the CEO wanted to dilute shareholders to refi, and Kenny would have nothing to do with it!!!!!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344617823000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344617902000-53</Id><Title>Why does ETFC need two Bankers if there is no Bank?</Title><Msg>Just saying, stay tuned</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344617902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344618069000-54</Id><Topic><Title>could ceo firing</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344617467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may be wrong about firing but the stock is still selling off with no real buyers!!!looking for 7'sIMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344618069000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344618216000-55</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK I can fly with that. Romneys father set a bar for 'good will' for a presidential candidate to relase many years of tax returns. Romney must not care about that goodwill, and I am free then to wonder what he has to hide. As to Obamas birth cirtificate, he did release his birth cirtificate, but birthers like yourself, demanded a long form (even though the short form is what all other Hawaii citizens use to prove citizenship)</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344618216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344618573000-56</Id><Title>A Big Announcement on Monday!!!</Title><Msg>A Big Announcement on Monday!!! Just a hunch!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344618573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:09:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344618681000-57</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Announcement on Monday!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344618573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the shorts don't believe that and will continue to make money as etfc flounders !IMHO they need to show a plan for improvement or sale .way too times have we heard buyout!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344618681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:11:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344618956000-58</Id><Title>victims of just another</Title><Msg>pump and dump!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344618956000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344619440000-59</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Announcement on Monday!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344618573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trust me Kenny has plans. He just had to get rid of the obstacles to "His" plan. Now, is his plan good or bad long term? We will see.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344619440000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:24:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344619471000-60</Id><Topic><Title>could ceo firing</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344617467000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:51:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...but the stock is still selling off with no real buyers!!! Don't forget Moon is buying All the shares being sold!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344619471000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344619763000-61</Id><Title>No plan for ETFC?</Title><Msg>Are you deaf , blind, and stupid?????? Uhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh, thewre is a plan and it is being implemented with the Firing of the Bank President and CEO. I say, that is a mighty big plan, and the implementation continues!!!!!!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344619763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344619770000-62</Id><Topic><Title>*** ... Does ETrade Pro SUCK or What? ... ***</Title><Username>equities.trader</Username><Timestamp>1311089699000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-07-19 11:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What trading platform do you use? Ive been having serious issues with etrade pro myself..</Msg><Username>jsdou</Username><Timestamp>1344619770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:29:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344620039000-63</Id><Title>Embattled Stiffanie, Stephanie Cutter</Title><Msg>Embattled? Why not call her what she is? A lying sack, caught in a web of her own making. Brak aint no better than her if he don't denounce her actions and send her packing. http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Journalism/2012/08/09/Embattled-Stephanie-Cutter-Drops-ABC-This-Week-Appearance</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344620039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344620438000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, "Romney must not care about that goodwill". Why would he? Every single line of his tax returns would be subject of frivolous interpretation and distraction from what this election discussion should be about: economy, debt, deficit. Obama is desperate to switch the subject from obvious failures. Yes, Obama showed his long form of birth certificate. 2.5 years after it was requested by public. And request was 100% legitimate. Maybe, it is OK for Romney to release his tax forms couple of years from now too? And where is your mistrust for beloved IRS coming from? Aren't they supposed to scrutinize every single line of tax return of filthy rich? You are "free then to wonder what he has to hide". Who cares? Normal Americans, unemployed and looking for job, I hope understand, Romney's tax returns are fiction movie comparing to troubles we are in.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344620438000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344620736000-65</Id><Title>Added More at $8.35!! EOM</Title><Msg>Added More at $8.35!! EOM</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344620736000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344621116000-66</Id><Topic><Title>No plan for ETFC?</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344619763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The burning question is what to they do? Make people trade more? No Make interest rates go up? No Make people pay mortages and HELOCS? No There is no magic bullet here. Firing a CEO and a resigning bank president is not exactly a positive catalyst for the stock past yesterday. If it were, heads would be rolling all over wall street. I do think firing Freiturd was a good move tho.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344621116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344621403000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, here is something for you: Nice story - good to hear that Romney did something nice for one couple. For those of us who lived in Massachusetts when he was governor, it does not undo the harm that he has done. Of course, we don't know what Romney would do as president. In Massachusetts he ran as a liberal - pro-gun control, pro-abortion rights. He even gave an impassioned speech about his mother's friend who died during an illegal abortion and how necessary it was to keep abortion legal. So, on the basis of his past actions and statements, are you sure you want to vote for him? A new Mitt can be just around the corner.</Msg><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1344621403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344621634000-68</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to ignore over and over that Obama did release his birth certificate, the same one all other Hawaiians use to prove citizenship, he simply did not provide the long form racist required of a black man. and no, the IRS does not have the manpower to scrutinize the tax forms of all Americans. So your theory that all is well, because he has not been indicted is simply false. Also, the point of this is not that he did anything illegal, it is simply that we are having a discussion on tax fairness, and that the wealthy cannot afford a tax increase from 36 to 39% because it would kill the job creation. But if Romney has been paying way less than 10% the American public will wonder, "He cannot afford to pay 10-13% even"? Why would he, because there is a precedence for presidential candidates to release their forms, all other candidates have born the burden, when not Romney. So he can create goodwill or not, but do not cry when he loses the election because he did not want to follow precedence, expectations of the american voter.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344621634000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344622025000-69</Id><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Msg>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622206000-70</Id><Topic><Title>No plan for ETFC?</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344619763000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you see they let him go because of anemic trading by investors. that means really poor quarter coming.Pump up the stock sell and short to the 6-7 dollar range because they have no plan to get customers back!!!!they killed the golden goose</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344622206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622336000-71</Id><Topic><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sorry to hear that</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344622336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622358000-72</Id><Topic><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344614363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ETFC is heading to $20..... Watch and learn!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622385000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, I’m skeptical this will work, but I am glad to see candidates start to notice Romney’s anti-jobs record. Remember, during Romney’s only service in public office, his state’s record on job creation was “one of the worst in the country.” Massachusetts really did rank 47th out of 50 states in jobs growth on Romney’s watch (and unlike President Obama, Romney didn’t inherit an economic crisis). There was a reason Romney served one term and then quit — he was not at all popular with his constituents and probably would have lost a re-election bid if he’d tried.</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1344622385000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:13:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622514000-74</Id><Topic><Title>A Big Announcement on Monday!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344618573000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 13:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still have time to get in at $8.37~8.38 now before it will skyrocket to $16 in a very near future!!!!!!! LOL!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622514000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622609000-75</Id><Topic><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will be regretting when it hits $16+ very soon!!!!!! Besides, it will close above $8.45 today!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344622705000-76</Id><Topic><Title>Why does ETFC need two Bankers if there is no Bank?</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344617902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ETFC will sell the bank to big banks to keep the brokerage only?</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622705000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344623180000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican54 Slick Willard was only elected because he faced a Coakley-esque candidate in Shannon O'Brien and because he was able to hoodwink enough Bay State voters into believing he was a moderate.</Msg><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1344623180000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344623782000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why does ETFC need two Bankers if there is no Bank?</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344617902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bankers need jobs and paychecks thats why.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1344623782000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:36:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344624184000-79</Id><Topic><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what makes etfc worth 16 bucks? they don't make much money for investors just the hedge fund!! This is nothing but a poker chip for citadel to short and sucker longs into!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344624184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:43:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344624240000-80</Id><Topic><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344614363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tomczyk named CEO. Story developing</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344624240000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344624388000-81</Id><Title>Tomczyk Named CEO</Title><Msg>Psych!!</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344624388000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344624695000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Harry must disclose the source of allegations, doofus. Mitt Romney is not an official fugure, Harry is. Harry is obligated to follow ethics rules." What ethics rules govern Harry Reid's statement of hearsay evidence? None that I know of, you can cite some? Hearsay may not be allowed in a court of law but like claims about Obama's citizenship it plays in the court of public opinion. Harry revealed his source to Washington reporter Dana Bash and she confirmed it was credible (putting her credibility on the line). So, unless Harry lied (you need to prove it), he's in the clear and quite credible himself.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344624695000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344625206000-83</Id><Title>with citadel involved</Title><Msg>ever since they became involved investors have lost money in etfc. what makes you think for one second things are going to change? constant pumping and then shorting has been the game taking investors money!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1344625206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344626898000-84</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama "simply did not provide the long form racist required of a black man."? Hawaiians can use anything to "prove" citizenship their local authorities accept. US Presidential candidate must have standard form as 100% legitimate proof to meet Constitutional requirement. Black, white, dark or pale. Now. One of the highest authority on your side claims Romney didn't pay taxes for 10 years. Why aren't you demanding him to release the source of his information? Harry makes deliberately unsubstantiated claim. Where is the standard for public official to back up allegations? Romney is being accused of murder too. Where is the proof? For you, creeps, anything goes.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344626898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344627371000-85</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitt should show his tax records. He is hardly above suspicion.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344627371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344627452000-86</Id><Topic><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344614363000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 11:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah!! It may end up like that!! Give me $16+ or 1 to 1 stock swap!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344627452000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344628128000-87</Id><Topic><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like what I said!!!!!! 99% accuracy!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344628128000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344628259000-88</Id><Title>Obama smear backers</Title><Msg>Obama smear backers Pander-in-chief kissing the Jewish communities ring for shekels...the man has no shame! Ten Donors Financing Obama’s Super PAC Smears Meet the Hollywood moguls and actors, outsourcing pioneers, heiress gardener, and others responsible for outrageous Obama Super PAC ad linking Mitt Romney to woman’s death from cancer A group of ten wealthy mega donors have donated a combined $12.55 million to Priorities USA: 1. Jeffrey Katzenberg, CEO Dreamworks 2. Irwin Mark Jacobs, founder Qualcomm 3. Fred Eychaner, political activist 4. Barbara Stiefel, philanthropist 5. Amy Goldman, gardener 6. Steve Mostyn, trial lawyer 7. Kareem Ahmed, CEO of Landmark Medical Management 8. Bill Maher, TV host and comedian 9. Franklin Haney, real estate developer</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344628259000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:50:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344628704000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Now. One of the highest authority on your side claims Romney didn't pay taxes for 10 years. Why aren't you demanding him to release the source of his information? Harry makes deliberately unsubstantiated claim. Where is the standard for public official to back up allegations? Romney is being accused of murder too. Where is the proof? For you, creeps, anything goes. " ------- So many incorrect statements!! Harry claims he was TOLD and that is why he BELIEVES Wimp didn't pay INCOME taxes. These terms sometimes get conflated as when the GOP bloviates about the "48% of Americans who pay no taxes", just not accurate. As for "proof", your team is still claiming the birth certificate is forged, silly rabbits! The only 'proof' resides with the Wimp. As for accusing Wimp of murder, not true. Wimp is being accused of being the "proximate cause" , a legal distinction. Also, the accuser is a PAC, by LAW and by virtue of Citizens United and the right wing SCOTUS - not affiliated with BO.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344628704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 15:58:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344629085000-90</Id><Topic><Title>$9 by tomorrow!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344523406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 10:43:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, didn't happen. $15 Monday, I think that'll be one hit and two strikes, assuming you were right about the CEO getting the boot this week in advance. Got another prediction, you're still in the game . . . Note so far it seems you have no balls :-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1344629085000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:04:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344629296000-91</Id><Topic><Title>My Last Order at $8.33 Filled!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344622025000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 14:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops, never mind, strike 3, you're out, but it was SO close. OK, we'll count that one as a foul ball on the third strike . . . still one strike to go.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1344629296000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:08:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344629860000-92</Id><Title>Just out!!!</Title><Msg>Posted at 02:04 PM ET, 08/10/2012 Jon Huntsman Sr., longtime Romney backer, calls on him to release tax returns By Greg Sargent The internet is alive with speculation that the secret source Harry Reid claims to have on Mitt Romney’s tax returns is Utah industrialist Jon Huntsman Sr. He is the founder of Hunstman Corporation and the father of the former GOP presidential candidate — and the speculation is based on the fact that his profile fits with much of what we publicly know about Reid’s presumed confidante. But I just got off the phone with Huntsman, and he confirmed to me that he is not Reid’s source. However, in a move that could be significant, Huntsman forcefully called on Romney to release his tax returns. This matters, because Huntsman is a longtime backer of Romney — he has long been close to Romney; he supported his early campaigns; he was the national finance chairman of Romney’s 2008 presidential campaign; and he has raised a lot of money for him over the years. (He backed his own son in the latest GOP primary.) “I feel very badly that Mitt won’t release his taxes and won’t be fair with the American people,” Huntsman told me. In a reference to Romney’s father, who pioneered the release of returns as a presidential candidate, Huntsman said: “I loved George. He always said, pay your taxes for at least 10 or 12 years.” (See update below.) “Mr. Romney ought to square with the American people and release his taxes like any other candidate,” Huntsman said. “I’ve supported Mitt all along. I wish him well. But I do think he should release his income taxes.” Reid has claimed that he has it from someone who knows that Romney paid no taxes for a long time. Some have speculated Huntsman is Reid’s source because Huntsman is partners with Robert Gay, a lontime managing director of Bain; they are both officers at Huntsman Gay Global Capital. Huntsman is also close to Reid. But Huntsman adamantly denied discussing Romney’s returns with Reid, and said he knew nothing about them. “That’s absolutely false,” Huntsman said of the speculation. “I have absolutely no knowledge of Bain or Mitt Romney’s tax returns.” Asked directly if he had ever had a conversation of any kind with Reid about Romney’s returns, Huntsman reiterated he hadn’t. Huntsman said his main connection to Reid is through their shared interest in cancer research. In any case, the more important thing here might be Huntsman’s call for Romney to release his returns. He may be the highest profile Republican — and he’s certainly the one closest to Romney — to do so thus far. *************************************** UPDATE: Huntsman’s phrasing above — in which he quoted George Romney saying we should “pay” our taxes for 10 or 12 years — was inadvertently awkward phrasing on his part. Huntsman’s assistant confirms that he meant George said candidates should release their returns for 10 to 12 years. Obviously this doesn’t change the story at all.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344629860000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344630166000-93</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To use the word wimp on Romney is a gas, if there was ever a wimp in the Whitehouse it is the present occupant. This metroman has never even fired a BB gun, held a private sector job, or earned a penny that someone else did put up...I would bet that Zimmerman could whop this skinny wuss. BTW, could someone tell this sissy to quit bowing down to every head of state he meets...it's disgusting to watch.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344630166000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344630648000-94</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>compared to draft dodger wimp Mitt who toured the French wine country with his maids during the nam years? Mitt who never did anything but throw daddy's money around and cheat on his taxes.....</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344630648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344631304000-95</Id><Title>Obama is for the rich</Title><Msg>So far since this community organizer has been in office the wealthy are doing just fine thank you. The stock market is only 100 points away from a 4 1/2 year high, and who has the capital to invest in the markets...that's right, the rich. The top 20% in this country are partying at the middle classes expence. Look at Nordstroms stock, close to a 52 week high...you can bet that are lefty friends on this MB aren't shopping their, more like Target with Michelle Obama. While the community organizer and his wife are eating at 5 star restaurants our liberal friends are lucky to grace the likes of the Olive Garden on special occasions...so much for spreading the wealth around! Thank you Barry for the frozen vodka and Caviar Blinis with a touch of crème fraîche.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344631304000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344631422000-96</Id><Title>Mitten's grecian formula 44 tax plan</Title><Msg>Mitten's grecian formula 44 tax plan: everyone do as mittens and hide your money, bank in the caymans, use phony transactions to hide gains and just do as the greeks do and stop paying taxes............ then let's see the gop blather about increasing military spending every year. Let's all pretend we are big shots like Mitt and like Lenona Helmsley who said " we don't pay taxes, the little people pay taxes"......... I think i will write off all my income next year to dressage for my unicorn.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344631422000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344631463000-97</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;compared to draft dodger wimp Mitt who toured the French wine country with his maids during the nam years? Mitt who never did anything but throw daddy's money around and cheat on his taxes&gt;&gt; To thin hydroponico, to thin.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344631463000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344631891000-98</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That summed up mittens well: the rich kid who supported the war in Nam, but spent his time touring france.... the businessman who started off rich and connected, the shady tax scammer and etc, what else is there? On the plus side he wrote the blueprint for the Affordable care Act and said the mandate was the "responsible" thing to do.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344631891000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344631893000-99</Id><Topic><Title>Futures = RED. ...learn why...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344571649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 00:07:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"...ETFC will be going up again tomorrow regardless of future or negative market!!..." Bro Moon[P], it's hard to out smart Da Bear who's 3 standard deviations smarter than da averagest Bear. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( I say again: remember Da 1st Byte Rule. It works every tyme. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1344631893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344632392000-100</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact of the matter is, this issue has gotten so big that unless Mitt releases his returns, he has no chance of winning the presidency. If he wants to win he has to put them out there. This isn't going away.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1344632392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 16:59:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344632977000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you really this dense? He provided a document good enough to get a passport with...is that clear enough for you? but that is right, the document he provided is only good enough for a white candidate, not a black candidate. Right Pacifican? Why, he said it was a 'claim from a reliable source', he provided the source name to a reputable newsman. The public can now decide if Rieds information is credible enough to be concerned about or not. in the end, the source name is not going to end the speculation, Romney can simply claim that he is lying, only one thing can clear this up at this point... release his tax documents. no you simply again want to ignore, the dems are simply asking for him to release what many, many other presidential candidates have released. What makes him special?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344632977000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344633525000-102</Id><Title>Big Jump on Monday!!! Relax!!</Title><Msg>Big Jump on Monday!!! Relax!! ETFC is heading $16+!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344633525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:18:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344634224000-103</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fri Aug 10, 2012, 03:18 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Source: The Washington Post A bumpy overseas trip and a month of pummeling by Democratic ads depicting Mitt Romney as an out-of-touch plutocrat and possible tax evader appear to have taken a toll. Three polls released in the last 24 hours show Present Obama widening his lead over the former Massachusetts governor to as much as nine points. The surveys of registered voters, all conducted sometime between Aug. 2 and 8, also have Romney’s unfavorable ratings headed north. Two of the polls show his support among independents slipping. A Fox News poll found the largest deficit, with Romney trailing by nine points (49 percent to 40 percent) That’s the widest gap Fox has reported all year. Its July survey had Obama up by four points (45 percent to 41 percent).Fox found that Obama’s increasing advantage comes mainly on the strength of a big bump from independents, who now support the president by 11 points, up from four points in July.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344634224000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344634360000-104</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is my expectation Fists, I do not think Romney is a fool. If he was vetted by McCain and there were any problems, he would clear them up over the next 4 years. I suspect there were issues and he does not want to release more than 4. So, what to do? Answer: stonewall long enough so that when you do release your returns, the dems will have to be satisfied with 3-4 (calling for more will just seem petty at that point). If this is not how it plays out then I was wrong, he is a fool.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344634360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344634809000-105</Id><Title>My Boss Gave Me the Weekend Off</Title><Msg>Because apparently I did a good job.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344634809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344635738000-106</Id><Title>how mittens was on Marriot's audit committee</Title><Msg>business experience?......tax scam experience...? well maybe but the daddy thing is most likely: Romney as Audit Chair Saw Marriott Son of BOSS Shelter Defy IRS Mitt Romney has long had close ties to hotel operator Marriott International Inc. (MAR) The candidate for the Republican presidential nomination, whose full name is Willard Mitt Romney, was named after the chain’s founder, J. Willard Marriott, a friend of his father. He joined the company’s board in 1993, and has served on it for 11 of the past 19 years, including six as chairman of the audit committee.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344635738000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344635882000-107</Id><Title>Citadel cronnies boost, then bust the price.</Title><Msg>citadel capital owns the board and the stockholders hostage as they can hire and fire as Griffin sees fit. the pump and dump is an old story here. the limit orders for years can exceed by a penny any side of the trade i have the confirmed orders and print outs to prove what i say ! waiting for the class action group to form as a penny on a hundred or a thousand or even ten thousand is not enough to call the attorney.....i just need the list of daily dart errors to make it worthwhile</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1344635882000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 17:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344636898000-108</Id><Title>New CEO to be paid A Niggardly Amount</Title><Msg>But get bonus paid on performance</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344636898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:14:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344637733000-109</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal intolerance of religion, esp Mormonism.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1344564209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 22:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;crown[P], I'm gonna tell Jesus you said that. &gt;&gt; If you ever get a chance - sure - tell him. He may actually agree with me. I don't think he cared much for religion himself. Didn't he himself say not to build "houses of worship" in his name? If he truly was the man/power the story makes him to be, he would cry at the pettiness of all the religions that pretend to worship him, but are to shallow and self-righteous to follow his example.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344637733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344638494000-110</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long form applications are required for passport applications, not short one. There is no requirement to provide tax returns. Romney released tax returns for 2 years. Why is this not satisfactory? Why 10? Is that a new "standard" now?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344638494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344638601000-111</Id><Title>Mitens Runs on His Record, but Won't Discuss it</Title><Msg>Mittens is asking the Dems to stop criticizing his business record But he refuses to reveal any details. And he wants Americans to elect him because of his business record But he won't discuss it. He's sounding more like a hormonal woman every day.</Msg><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344638601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344639374000-112</Id><Title>The "Cancer Murders" Ad BackFiring</Title><Msg>Dirty rotten liar campaign takes hit in new poll. &lt;--justified http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/08/10/cancergate-ad-flap-hurting-obama</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344639374000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344639477000-113</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FALSE, the document Obama provided IS the official document the state provides, good for passport applications. Educate yourself.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344639477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:57:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344639708000-114</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's typical for presidential candidates to release 10 or 11 years of returns... http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2012/aug/01/bill-clinton/its-typical-presidential-candidates-release-10-or-/ Please educate yourself.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344639708000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344640171000-115</Id><Topic><Title>new ceo 500k a month? WTF</Title><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1344543623000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 16:20:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow, the ceo made 16k today... and will make 16k on saturday... and 16k on sunday... what is that, 2000$ a freakin hour?</Msg><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1344640171000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:09:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344641132000-116</Id><Title>My guess: bank is sold; SF gone...</Title><Msg>Bank buyer wanted nothing to do with freiberg, Freiberg had nothing to offer the brokerage. I bet the bank is gone</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344641132000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344641255000-117</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as Mr. Romney withholds his returns, continued speculation, and even outlandish conjecture, will probably flourish. “It’s reinforced my view that he’d be better off just releasing the returns rather than having people blindly speculating,” Leonard E. Burman, a tax specialist and professor of public affairs at the Maxwell School of Syracuse University, told me this week. “It seems like one of those slow-drip water torture things, and eventually he’s going to have to do it.”</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1344641255000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344641470000-118</Id><Topic><Title>Mitens Runs on His Record, but Won't Discuss it</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344638601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Mitt Romney appears to be seeking an agreement with the Obama campaign to remove his business record from the conversation, a sign that the repeated attacks on his tenure at private equity firm Bain Capital may be getting under the presumptive Republican presidential candidate's skin. NBC's First Read has the following excerpt from Romney's interview with Chuck Todd, conducted Thursday as part of a forthcoming documentary on MSNBC, in which he said he would like a pledge with Obama barring "personal" attack ads: “[O]ur campaign would be-- helped immensely if we had an agreement between both campaigns that we were only going to talk about issues and that attacks based upon-- business or family or taxes or things of that nature." [...] “[W]e only talk about issues. And we can talk about the differences between our positions and our opponent's position.” Romney said of his own campaign: “[O]ur ads haven't gone after the president personally. … [W]e haven't dredged up the old stuff that people talked about last time around. We haven't gone after the personal things.” In response, First Read asked, "Is Romney really saying that scrutinizing his business record -- which he has held up as one of his chief qualifications to be president -- is personal?" The comments come in the wake of a controversial ad by pro-Obama super PAC Priorities USA Action, linking a woman's cancer-related death to the decision by Bain Capital, once led by Romney, to close down a steel plant. The ad posits that the woman's husband, who is featured in the ad, lost his job and health insurance and was therefore unable to provide health care for his wife when she needed it the most. While that ad did not come from the Obama campaign itself, the president's reelection team has also hammered away at Romney's business record, branding him an "Outsourcer-in-Chief," and releasing numerous attack ads focused on Romney's time at Bain Capital. To date, Romney has insisted that the attacks are personal, but the interview with MSNBC would be the first time the former Massachusetts governor has requested the Obama campaign to stop talking about his business record -- as he appears to imply in the quote. But Romney himself has touted that same record throughout his candidacy, frequently making the case that his private enterprise background would enable him to serve as a better commander-in-chief than President Barack Obama. Romney's remarks also ignore the fact that the super PACs and outside groups backing his presidential bid and other Republicans have been no less negative than those aligned with Obama and Democrats. The issue of negative campaigning notwithstanding, recent polling has indicated that voters have an increasingly unfavorable opinion of Romney -- a sign that the scrutiny around his tax returns, and attacks on his background at Bain Capital, are leaving their mark on voters in key swing states across the country. When The Huffington Post reached out to the Romney campaign for comment, campaign spokeswoman Andrea Saul did not clarify if Romney was, in fact, asking Team Obama to drop the business talk. "The governor was expressing his view that he hopes we can have a campaign focused on the issues rather than one of desperation and lies as we’ve seen from the Obama campaign," Saul responded in an email."</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344641470000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:31:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344642061000-119</Id><Topic><Title>Mitens Runs on His Record, but Won't Discuss it</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344638601000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 18:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is why they call him WIMP!!! "“[O]ur campaign would be-- helped immensely if we had an agreement between both campaigns that we were only going to talk about issues and that attacks based upon-- business or family or taxes or things of that nature." After 5 years of taking every cheap shot imaginable at BO, suddenly they want Marquis De Queensbury rules.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344642061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344642698000-120</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. "For the record, in 1980, Ronald Reagan offered up just one return." "McCain only released two." "But individual candidates released anywhere from 30 to one." It is typical now? Not a standard?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344642698000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344643013000-121</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple research, dummy! http://www.taxhistory.org/www/website.nsf/web/presidentialtaxreturns</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344643013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 19:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344643523000-122</Id><Title>Irony of GW</Title><Msg>by Scott Stenholm "There is a widely held theory that former Vice President Al Gore lost his bid for the presidency in 2000 because of his insatiable, career-long desire to curb the effects of global warming by first and foremost informing the public on the world's climate crisis. At the time, there was overwhelming scientific evidence to support his claim that our planet was dramatically warming as a direct result of the release of manmade greenhouse gases into our atmosphere. However, like a cancer patient in denial who has been diagnosed but has yet to feel the symptoms of their illness, too many Americans failed to give him credence because they were not physically and financially reeling from the side effects of climate change. Twelve years later, our planet is still sick and this summer Americans are seeing and feeling the symptoms like no other time in recorded history. Posthumously for the Gore campaign, a recent report said the ten hottest years since 1895 have occurred since they lost the election in 2000. The average national temperature has been rising in every state since 1970. This year has seen the warmest first seven months of any year on record for the United States. The national temperature of 56.4 degrees was 4.3 degrees above the long-term average. A NASA scientist recently told a Senate panel that he was "99% certain" recent warming trends that resulted in the Oklahoma and Texas droughts were caused by a buildup of carbon dioxide and other gases in the atmosphere from burning fossil fuels, not by Mother Nature herself. Half of all U.S. counties are now considered disaster zones, mostly due to drought. And on August 8th, federal scientists announced that July was the hottest month in U.S. history. National interest in warming statistics has been overshadowed by more immediate concerns such as terrorism, war, and a poor economy. However this summer has marked the dawn of a new era where a poor economic climate will not only pale in comparison to, but will be exacerbated by, actual climate. Global warming is literally cooking our lakes, rivers and oceans as evident when it was recently reported that hundreds of thousands, possibly millions, of fish have died as a result of water temperatures reaching as high as 100 degrees in Iowa and Illinois at an enormous cost to the fishing industry there. "Those fish have been in these rivers for thousands of thousands of years, and they're accustomed to all sorts of weather conditions," said Mark Flammang, a fisheries biologist with the Iowa Department of Natural Resources. "But sometimes, you have conditions occur that are outside their realm of tolerance." Texas Republican Governor Rick Perry has been a champion for deniers by claiming that man-made climate change is a hoax by scientists, all the while his state saw record losses to their agriculture, livestock and timber industries, and its decimation of cattle herds and cash crops which often causes a significant rise in costs for food, clothing and other items. Bottom line: the effects of climate change will only become more devastating to our local, national and global economies.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344643523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344643557000-123</Id><Topic><Title>Irony of GW</Title><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344643523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:05:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To little befuddlement, Mitt Romney has flipped-flopped on climate change numerous times. While Governor of Massachusetts he enacted restrictions on carbon dioxide emissions on power plants in his state. But while running for President, he has said the "idea of spending trillions and trillions of dollars to try to reduce CO2 emissions is not the right course for us." He recently acknowledged that the globe is warming, but added, "we don't know what's causing climate change on this planet." This stance is equal to a man who has been diagnosed with cancer by 98% of the world's doctors but can't bring himself to accept such a diagnosis nor to take steps to heal his illness. And this is where the true irony enters, much of the states bearing the brunt of the global warming-induced droughts are deep red states such as Texas and Oklahoma. More rural, conservative areas of the country are expected to see the most immediate effects of climate change in the near future in the form of continued drought and other forms of extreme weather like heightened flooding and tornado outbreaks with increased viciousness. While Democrats in Washington haven't been immune to dragging their feet in taking the necessary steps to address global warming, the partisanship line here is akin to that of tax cuts for the top 1% or gay marriage: it is the right side of the aisle that is consistently on the wrong side of this issue. Though to be fair, President Obama has yet to put the full force of the White House behind his past acknowledgements of the crisis, a campaign promise both in 2008 and as this year's incumbent, saying in April, "I will be very clear in voicing my belief that we're going to have to take further steps to deal with climate change in a serious way." Hopefully, we will see this come to fruition as the campaign heats up with the DNC Convention and the debates as platforms. It should be noted that the President recently pushed congress to pass a farm bill that would provide sweeping disaster relief to farmers effected by this summer's drought - something that deals with the effect, not the cause. Regardless, the Obama Administration has overseen policies that have helped create hundreds of thousands of jobs in the clean energy industry. And the President enacted the largest expansion of land and water conservation and protected wilderness in a generation while nearly doubling America's generation of electricity from solar power since he took office. It is safe to say that a second term for President Obama would be a much more Earth-friendly, and in turn long-term economic-friendly, environment in comparison to that of a Romney administration. Climate change is an issue of far greater concern than that of terrorism, war, the economy, gay marriage, abortion, education and gun control combined if for no other reason than it is the only issue that truly effects every single living thing on the planet. One can only hope that this will be at the forefront of the electorate's mindset when voting for all levels of government this November."</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344643557000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344644097000-124</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW a truly LMFAO moment. You have now dropped even lower in my opinion. Not a math wizard I see. LMFAO. Maybe you need to look up MEDIAN and OUTLIERS. "Mathematically speaking, our tally shows the median number of tax returns released to be seven and a half." I feel confident that mean, median or mode, would all be significantly higher than 2 (well he has only released ONE so far) Please educate yourself. p.s. maybe you noticed that it is the pubs that have the lower outliers. Wonder why.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1344644097000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344644623000-125</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you. Are we interested in pre-election year returns only? Barack Hussein Obama released only 8 tax returns? Substandard!!! It seems George W Bush didn't release a single one. Neither did Cheney. Ronald Reagan - none.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344644623000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:23:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344645670000-126</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dummy, Are you sure those tax returns do not include presidency years? Mitt is not President. Yet. So, median is standard? According to whom?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344645670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646143000-127</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://factcheck.org/2012/07/romney-and-the-tax-return-precedent/</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344646143000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344646227000-128</Id><Title>GOP leaders want to see tax returns</Title><Msg>COLUMBUS, Ohio -- One of Ohio's top Republican leaders says GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney should release more tax returns because it's become a distraction in the campaign. Romney has faced repeated criticism for refusing to release several years' worth of tax returns. Several Republicans have joined in the call for more transparency, including several U.S. senators and Texas Gov. Rick Perry. Ohio House Speaker William Batchelder said in a taped television interview that the issue has become a problem for the candidate, and that Romney should release the forms so he can move on to other topics. Batchelder has been a state lawmaker in the presidential battleground off and on since the 1960s.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646277000-129</Id><Topic><Title>GOP leaders want to see tax returns</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George Will. On ABC’s “This Week,” Will, a long-time conservative commentator and Washington Post columnist, said, “The costs of not releasing the returns are clear, therefore he must have calculated that there are higher costs in releasing them.” At one point, he even played devil’s advocate to Republican consultant Mary Matalin, who was defending Romney.</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646277000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646318000-130</Id><Topic><Title>GOP leaders want to see tax returns</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Kristol. “Here’s what he should do,” said Kristol, another conservative commentator, on Fox News. “He should release the tax returns tomorrow. This is crazy… you’ve got to release 6, 8, 10 years of back tax returns. Take the hit for a day or two. Then give a serious speech on Thursday.”</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646318000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:51:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646435000-131</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican54 Fri Aug 10, 2012, 03:18 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Source: The Washington Post A bumpy overseas trip and a month of pummeling by Democratic ads depicting Mitt Romney as an out-of-touch plutocrat and possible tax evader appear to have taken a toll. Three polls released in the last 24 hours show Present Obama widening his lead over the former Massachusetts governor to as much as nine points. The surveys of registered voters, all conducted sometime between Aug. 2 and 8, also have Romney’s unfavorable ratings headed north. Two of the polls show his support among independents slipping.</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1344646435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:53:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646757000-132</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal intolerance of religion, esp Mormonism.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1344564209000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 22:03:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"global warming" and "climate change" are the latest religions designed for sheep management. pretty simple formula really. just scare the sheep with fire and brimstone and you can get the beleivers to do anything for you....</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1344646757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344646769000-133</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump Pacifican had no words for this.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1344646769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344647024000-134</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Mitt Romney is not an official fugure, Harry is" ?????????????????????????????? WTF ????????????? What do you call an X Gov and Presidential candidate ? God you are stupid !</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1344647024000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344647253000-135</Id><Topic><Title>Harry continues to tease the Wimp</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344562697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-09 21:38:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"To use the word wimp on Romney is a gas, if there was ever a wimp in the Whitehouse it is the present occupant" Mitt, like Bush, was a college cheerleader, not a player. Mitt competed with the girls. And the best he could do was gang up on little gays. Mitt is a girlie man wimp.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1344647253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344647578000-136</Id><Topic><Title>GOP leaders want to see tax returns</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ron Paul. Unitl just days ago, Paul was the other Republican presidential candidate. He is also one of those calling for Romney to release the returns. Paul told Politico today, “Politically, I think that would help him. …In the scheme of things politically, you know, it looks like releasing tax returns is what the people want.”</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344647578000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:12:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344647611000-137</Id><Topic><Title>GOP leaders want to see tax returns</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344646227000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 20:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alabama Gov. Robert Bentley. The Alabama Governor actually went further than others in suggesting that perhaps Romney is hiding something by not releasing his tax returns. “If you have things to hide, then maybe you’re doing things wrong,” he told the AP. “I think you ought to be willing to release everything to the American people.“</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1344647611000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 21:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344656149000-138</Id><Topic><Title>Getting Killed</Title><Username>svetlana_merry44</Username><Timestamp>1344615284000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 12:14:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>stephanie_tyler98</Username><Timestamp>1344656149000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-10 23:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>