<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352786767971-1</Id><Title>Insightful article on Japan,,,,</Title><Msg>Here,,, check out this article on Japan,,, http://www.marketwatch.com/story/yen-edges-toward-brink-andy-xie-2012-11-12?pagenumber=1 See any similarities,,,,,??????? Ugh,,,,, p ,</Msg><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1352786767971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352788734493-2</Id><Topic><Title>Piggy Ponderings,,,,</Title><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1334440787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-04-14 17:59:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dang,,, I was reading my old posts tonite, and I really liked this one,,, Ok, ok,,, I got nuttin',,,,, ,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,, : -) ,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,, p ,</Msg><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1352788734493</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 01:38:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352835230323-3</Id><Title>Cool, young, hip out of work on food stamps</Title><Msg>Romney never had a chance. How does it feel that you lefties are cutting out coupons while these hipsters are eating like they live on NY's upper eastside....suckers! **About half of his friends in Baltimore have been getting food stamps since the economy toppled, so he decided to give it a try; to his delight, he qualified for $200 a month** Hipsters on food stamps They're young, they're broke, and they pay for organic salmon with government subsidies. In the John Waters-esque sector of northwest Baltimore — equal parts kitschy, sketchy, artsy and weird — Gerry Mak and Sarah Magida sauntered through a small ethnic market stocked with Japanese eggplant, mint chutney and fresh turmeric. After gathering ingredients for that evening’s dinner, they walked to the cash register and awaited their moments of truth. “I have $80 bucks left!” Magida said. “I’m so happy!” “I have $12,” Mak said with a frown. The two friends weren’t tabulating the cash in their wallets but what remained of the monthly allotment on their Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program debit cards, the official new term for what are still known colloquially as food stamps. Magida, a 30-year-old art school graduate, had been installing museum exhibits for a living until the recession caused arts funding — and her usual gigs — to dry up. She applied for food stamps last summer, and since then she’s used her $150 in monthly benefits for things like fresh produce, raw honey and fresh-squeezed juices from markets near her house in the neighborhood of Hampden, and soy meat alternatives and gourmet ice cream from a Whole Foods a few miles away. “I’m eating better than I ever have before,” she told me. “Even with food stamps, it’s not like I’m living large, but it helps.” Mak, 31, grew up in Westchester, graduated from the University of Chicago and toiled in publishing in New York during his 20s before moving to Baltimore last year with a meager part-time blogging job and prospects for little else. About half of his friends in Baltimore have been getting food stamps since the economy toppled, so he decided to give it a try; to his delight, he qualified for $200 a month.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1352835230323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:33:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352836346712-4</Id><Title>By the year-end, ETFC may drip to $6s!</Title><Msg>By the year-end, ETFC mayl drip to $6s! Mark this!! And if ETFC delivers bad Q4 eps on January, it will drop to $5!! Avoid this stock until Feb. 2013. GLTA!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1352836346712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 14:52:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352837696126-5</Id><Title>Four star bizzar</Title><Msg>The administration need to send Susan Rice back on the Sunday talk shows and explain to the American people that this whole mess is because of the"video"...I am down with that, the whole thing is a non story, lets move on. David Petraeus sex scandal: FBI agent who began probing disgraced spy chief allegedly sent shirtless photos of himself to whistleblower Jill Kelley The unnamed agent was a friend of Kelley, the raven-haired knockout whom Petraeus biographer Paula Broadwell jealously suspected of having the hots for the former CIA director, The Wall Street Journal reported.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1352837696126</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 15:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>