<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-26"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348642107605-1</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I sold all out at $9.60s~9.80s, which wasn't bad at all. Most of them were purchase at low $7s. No regret! I will start adding again at $7s. The cycle repeats again and again and again............. This is the best stock you can accumulate your retirement fund. I've never lost a penny by trading ETFC for the last 10 years... Follow me!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348642107605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 02:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348662419981-2</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say bull - go away</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1348662419981</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348662425475-3</Id><Topic><Title>There is no evidence that Obama stimulates economic growth</Title><Username>redistribute_this</Username><Timestamp>1348627574869</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 22:46:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI EVERYONE knows UE would be 12% now and gdp growth would be 3 or 4 % less were it not for obama. When bush left town he babbled "unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down"..... and he presided over a far greater rise in UE than happened since Obama improved the mess bush and the gop left behind. Now go and take your gop true believer idiot pill and get back to repeating the gop mantra: "tax cuts for the rich fix all problems, find the wmd, tax cuts fix all problems, find the wmd, the trickle down is coming, find the wmd , the tricklel down is coming, tax cuts for the rich fix all problems"</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348662425475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348663031513-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot the Iraqis who needlessly died.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348663031513</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 08:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348667592008-5</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep it up, I'm listening. From want I observed over the last month, your predictions seem spot on.</Msg><Username>doubledown</Username><Timestamp>1348667592008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 09:53:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348669899618-6</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is possible that Moon is the most uninformed person ever when it comes to this stock. He was pumping this company in the $15 range and has been or several years. The stock has fallen from $17 to $7 and he was pumping the whole way down. If anyone actually reads his posts and acts on any thing he writes, you deserve to lose money.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1348669899618</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670019309-7</Id><Title>Carter = Obama</Title><Msg>American humiliation</Msg><Username>contempt_4_conservative_idtios</Username><Timestamp>1348670019309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348670042054-8</Id><Topic><Title>Romney = Palin</Title><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1348602243114</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 15:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't Romney become French when he was drafted ? There's a real American ........ NOT</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1348670042054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348670193097-9</Id><Title>Neverending GOP voter fraud</Title><Msg>FL GOP FIRES ROMNEY CONSULTANT'S VOTER REGISTRATION FIRM AFTER FRAUDULENT FORMS REPORTED IN PALM BEACH COUNTY Firm owned by notorious GOP operative Nathan Sproul, accused of destroying Democratic registration forms in years past, hired 'at request of RNC', still operating in several key swing states... By Brad The Republican Party of Florida's top recipient of 2012 expenditures, a firm by the name of Strategic Allied Consulting, was just fired on Tuesday night, after more than 100 apparently fraudulent voter registration forms were discovered to have been turned in by the group to the Palm Beach County, FL Supervisor of Elections. The firm appears to be another shell company of Nathan Sproul, a longtime, notorious Republican operative, hired year after year by GOP Presidential campaigns, despite being accused of shredding Democratic voter registration forms in a number of states over several past elections. According to the Center for Responsive Politics, Strategic Allied Consulting has been paid some $667,000 this year by the FL GOP, presumably to run its voter registration campaigns in the state. That number, however, does not account for another identical payment made in August. The Palm Beach Post is reporting tonight that the firm received "more than $1.3 million" from the Republican Party of Florida "to register new voters." The firm is not only tied to the FL GOP, but also to the Mitt Romney Campaign, which hired Sproul as a political consultant late last year, despite years of fraud allegations against his organizations in multiple states. Moreover, the firm is also reportedly operating similar voter registration operations on behalf of the Republican Party, to the tune of hundreds of thousands of dollars, in a number of key battleground states this year, including North Carolina, Virginia and Colorado. Strategic Allied has recently taken steps to hide their ownership by Sproul's notorious firm, Sproul &amp; Associates. Palm Beach County Supervisor of Election Susan Bucher confirmed to The BRAD BLOG late this evening that she turned over 106 suspicious voter registration applications to the Florida State Attorney during a meeting yesterday afternoon in Palm Beach, after the "questionable" applications were submitted to her office by a worker for Strategic Allied. The forms were said to all have similar signatures, changed addresses and party affiliations, and other defects which appear to have all been done by the same hand. The case emerging in Florida tonight mirrors a similar incident reported earlier this year when more than a thousand fraudulent voter registration forms were discovered to have been turned in to the Sacramento County, CA Registrar of Voters by a group hired by that state's Republican Party. But that's not the only similar case, as a massive GOP voter registration scheme, which appears to involve the upper-echelons of the national party, begins to emerge... 'Questionable' registrations in Palm Beach The Palm Beach Post reports tonight that Bucher turned the "questionable" applications over to FL State Attorney Peter Antonacci and Chief Assistant State Attorney Paul Zacks during a meeting on Monday in "an abundance of caution" after her staff "had questions about similar-looking signatures, missing information and wrong addresses on the forms." The paper reports that "some of the applications she questioned were for new voter registrations while others were for address or party affiliation changes or requests for new voter cards." According to the FL Election Code, the alteration of a "voter registration application...without the other person's knowledge and consent" is a third degree felony, punishable by a $5,000 fine and up to five years in jail. Similarly, the willful submission of "any false voter registration information" is also a third degree felony. (Though don't tell fading GOP superstar Ann Coulter that, since she submitted fraudulent information on her own voter registration form --- in Palm Beach County, FL, coincidentally --- back in 2005, before knowingly voting at the wrong precinct illegally, as we have covered in great detail here over the years. The Post reports that "The 106 applications flagged by Bucher were part of a batch of 304 turned in Sept. 5 by the contractor, using the Republican Party of Florida’s identification number." As of tonight, the Republican Party of Florida (RPOF) says they have fired the firm, which they claim they had hired at the request of the Republican National Party. "When we learned today about the instances of potential voter registration fraud that occurred in Palm Beach County," RPOF Director Mike Grissom said, "we immediately informed the Republican National Committee that we were terminating the contract with the voter registration vendor we hired at their request because there is no place for voter registration fraud in Florida." Palm Beach Post reports that Strategic Allied Consulting was given "identical payments of $667,598 in July and August" by the RPOF. Strategic Allied Consulting Strategic Allied Consulting, which has only a single-page, generic website (including typos, as seen above) has been advertising for paid registration workers on "Craigslist, Monster Jobs, Jobs Indeed, Conservative Jobs, etc.," according to a source who has been researching them over the past several days. Late last month, Greg Flynn at the North Carolina blog BlueNC reported on some of their job listings seeking workers in that swing-state, which Obama narrowly won in 2008, offering to pay anywhere from $11 to $13 per hour. "WANT TO HELP REPUBLICANS WIN IN NC?," reads one ad, "We are currently hiring self-motivated people to contact voters for the election. No experience needed! We are paying $13/per hour for this program." "Are you interested in helping Mitt Romney win North Carolina?," reads another, "I am with the North Carolina Republican Party working with Voter Registration Projects and am looking for team members to help expand Republican voter registration." "Republican Voter Registration Captains Needed," begins another, requesting applicants submit resumes to John Bria of Strategic Allied Consulting. "Help GOP candidates win in November and become an integral part a [sic] presidential campaign." "Employees will go to high traffic areas, identify conservative voters, ensure that their voter registration is up to date, and then report back at night with their data and the voter registration forms that they collected." Curiously, that's exactly what is seen in a rather breathtaking viral video we reported on this morning revealing a young voter registration worker in Colorado Springs, CO (El Paso County), asking a potential registrant, "Would you vote for Romney or Obama?" before she would offer a voter registration form. While the worker, when pressed, reluctantly admitted, "we're out here in support of Romney," she then claimed to be working for the El Paso County Clerk's office. In fact, as we reported, the El Paso County Republican Party Chairman has since admitted the young lady was working for the party. Following publication of our story, we were informed by a tipster that the young lady was actually hired by a third-party contractor, though we have not yet been able to either confirm that point, or identify the name of the contractor. BlueNC reports, however, that, in addition to FEC campaign filings showing the NC Republican Party paid some $333,000 to Strategic Allied Consulting for services in that state in July, "There is evidence that similar operations are being conducted in Colorado, Florida and Virginia on behalf of the Republican Party." Was the young worker in Colorado Springs hired by Strategic Allied Consulting for her work with the local GOP? The techniques described in the NC help wanted ads sound very familiar to what was seen on video tape in CO. At BlueNC, Flynn reports "The company was set up in Virginia in June 2012 and filings with the Virginia Secretary of State reveal no identifying information other than that of a corporate filing service." He adds: "There is no evidence of business registration in either North Carolina, Colorado, or Florida (or Arizona)," where Sproul's Sproul &amp; Associates is based. At the time of BlueNC's report, the domain StrategicAlliedConsulting dotcom was registered to Sproul &amp; Associates in Tempe, Arizona. The day after they published their report, the domain name registration was quickly changed to "private", but not before Flynn was able to grab a screen shot confirming the ownership of the domain: The notorious Nathan Sproul We've reported on Sproul many times over the years, as the GOP operative, and former chair of the Arizona GOP and the state's Christian Coalition, pops up again and again in each Presidential Election year. He is hired over and over by the Republican Party, despite years of fraud allegations in multiple states against his organizations, which are said to have routinely changed or entirely destroyed Democratic voter registrations. He operates as Sproul &amp; Associates as well as Lincoln Strategy Group, among other names, including now, apparently, Strategic Allied Consulting. And this year, after being hired by the Bush/Cheney campaign in '04 and the McCain/Palin campaign in '08, Sproul was "quietly" hired by the Romney campaign as a political consultant late last year, according to a June report from Lee Fang at the non-partisan Republic Report: Late last year, Mitt Romney’s presidential campaign began paying Nathan Sproul, a political consultant with a long history of destroying Democratic voter registration forms and manipulating ballot initiatives. Sproul, who changed his firm’s name from Sproul and Associates to Lincoln Strategies, has received over $70,000 from Romney’s campaign ... Republic Report reviewed disclosures from the Federal Elections Commission. Sproul’s Lincoln Strategy Group has received about $71,391 in payments for “field consulting” and “rent &amp; utilities” by the Romney for President Inc. committee from November 30th through March 2nd of this year. Fang then goes on to highlight what he describes as some of Sproul's "greatest hits" as detailed by ThinkProgress while reporting on Sproul's Lincoln Strategies astroturf work for a so-called "Clean Coal" industry campaign in 2009 [emphasis in original]: - In Oregon and Nevada, Lincoln Strategies - then known as Sproul and Associates - was investigated for destroying Democratic voter registration forms. The Bush-Cheney 2004 presidential campaign paid Sproul $7.4 million for campaign work. [CNN, 10/14/04; KGW News, 10/13/04; East Valley Tribune, 09/07/06] - In Nevada, people who registered as Democrats with Lincoln Strategies - then known as Sproul and Associates - found their names absent from the voter registration rolls. [Reno Gazette-Journal, 10/29/04] - During the 2006 midterm elections, Wal-Mart banned Lincoln Strategies for partisan voter registration efforts in Tennessee. The Republican National Committee had hired the firm. [Associated Press, 08/24/06] - In Arizona, Lincoln Strategies employed a variety of deceptive tactics - including systematically lying about the bill - to push a ballot initiative to eviscerate the state's clean elections law. [Salon, 10/21/04] - Lincoln Strategies, then employed by the Republican Party, was behind efforts to place Ralph Nader on the ballot in states such as Arizona. [American Prospect, 06/25/04] Despite all of those years of allegations, the McCain campaign went on to hire Sproul in 2008, according to Sam Stein at Huffington Post, who reported at the time: John McCain's campaign has directed $175,000 to the firm of a Republican operative accused of massive voter registration fraud in several states. According to campaign finance records, a joint committee of the McCain-Palin campaign, the RNC and the California Republican Party, made a $175,000 payment to the group Lincoln Strategy in June for purposes of "registering voters." The managing partner of that firm is Nathan Sproul, a renowned GOP operative who has been investigated on multiple occasions for suppressing Democratic voter turnout, throwing away registration forms and even spearheading efforts to get Ralph Nader on ballots to hinder the Democratic ticket. ... That Sproul would come under the employment umbrella of the McCain campaign --- the Republican National Committee has also separately paid Lincoln Strategy at least $37,000 for voter registration efforts this cycle --- is not terribly surprising. Sproul, who has donated nearly $30,000 to McCain's campaign, has been in the good graces of GOP officials for the past decade despite charges of ethical and potentially legal wrongdoing. In Fang's report, he goes on to note that "Even former Rep. Chris Cannon (R-UT), during a hearing on voter fraud, admitted that 'the difference between ACORN and Sproul is that ACORN doesn't throw away or change registration documents after they have been filled out.'" GOP voter registration fraud epidemic continues As we described earlier today, in our story on the disturbing Colorado GOP voter registration worker video, while Republicans had long been critical of fraudulent voter registration efforts they inaccurately attributed to ACORN, the non-partisan, four-decade old community organizing group (which has since been forced into bankruptcy as a result of the years-long GOP effort to mischaracterize them and their work) there is no evidence, to our knowledge, that any of its tens of thousands of registration workers ever screened out potential registrants from one party or another before allowing them to register, as seen in CO. Neither is there evidence that any of their workers ever changed party affiliations on registration forms, as is being alleged tonight in Palm Beach County, or destroyed Democratic forms, as has been alleged over the years, as noted by Republican Rep. Cannon. Moreover, it should be noted that of the handful of ACORN registration workers who submitted fraudulent applications over the years, almost all of those workers were turned into officials by ACORN themselves. The group checked all applications for validity before turning them in, flagged those which appeared to be fraudulent, and then turned them in to officials, along with the names of the workers who had defrauded them. Contrast that with the disturbing activities of Sproul &amp; Associates, Lincoln Strategies and now Sproul's Strategic Allied Consulting, along with what was admitted to by the Republican Party today in Colorado, and revealed by a number of recent cases of massive registration fraud by the Republican Party in California. (For the record, ACORN was never hired to do registration work by the Democratic Party, despite inaccurate Republican claims to the contrary.) In 2006, GOP voter registration firms in California were reported by the LA Times to have turned in thousands of invalid registration forms, as well as fraudulent signatures on petitions in San Bernardino County. In once instance, "About 4,800 of more than 5,600 signatures submitted [by John Burkett Petition Management] were found to be invalid and were tossed out by election officials," the paper reported. In 2008, at the height of that year's GOP/Fox "News" ACORN "voter fraud" scam, a group calling itself Young Political Majors (YPM) was hired by the CA Republican Party to do voter registration. The firm was reportedly paid $7 to $12 for every Californian it registered as a member of the GOP. YPM was subsequently found to have been changing thousands of voter registration forms from Democratic to Republican. The group's CEO, Mark Anthony Jacoby, was eventually arrested (see video of my appearance announcing the news on Fox in a live "Fox News Alert" that year) before he later pleaded guilty to voter registration fraud. And, earlier this year, in 2012, the Sacramento Republican Party was found to have hired Momentum Political Services, a firm headed up by a woman described as a "professional con-artist". The group allegedly turned in thousands of fraudulent voter registrations as part of a $50,000 bounty scheme seeking Republican registrations, as paid for by the GOP in the district of Republican Congressman Dan Lungren. All the while, Republicans were loudly accusing Democrats of committing "voter fraud" requiring polling place Photo ID restrictions to stop it, even though there are just 10 known cases of in-person impersonation --- the only type of voter fraud that can possibly be deterred by Photo ID --- out of hundreds of millions of votes cast in all 50 states since 2000, according to a recent exhaustive report by the non-partisan investigative news consortium, News21. Perhaps it's a case of projection. Perhaps the GOP knows about the fraud that they are carrying out, so they presume that Democrats must be doing something similar. Nonetheless, when it comes to voter registration fraud, Republicans are the champs, hands down. And it remains to be seen how wide and how high this story will go. This one may have legs. As to actual voter fraud, it's Republicans --- and very high profile ones at that, including Mitt Romney himself --- who are winning that contest as well. See our recent report detailing 10+ recent cases of voter fraud and other related election fraud crimes by very high profile Republicans right here.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348670193097</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 10:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348675968871-10</Id><Title>Low float stocks with great earning- FFN &amp; IMH! Easy 300% gain!</Title><Msg>The stocks are taking off now! Loading up for a 300% return! The fair value for FFN is $5! The fair value for IMH is $25! The train is leaving station now! Great entry point now!</Msg><Username>savvy_investor123</Username><Timestamp>1348675968871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348677533576-11</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only when the e-trade baby poops on my tickets</Msg><Username>qaddaffis_toupee</Username><Timestamp>1348677533576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348678709109-12</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, does it fast and often gets me a price lower than my limit. Now on small thinly traded issues some limit orders might take awhile, but that's because of the market for the stock, not because of any particular broker.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348678709109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 12:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348679055622-13</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Er, most of us didn't sell all our holdings, so we don't need to buy. And if, as you say, its the best stock to accumulate for your retirement, our positions are quite safe. You only spend every day watching the ticker if you're either actively trading, or sitting on short term or potential long term positions that you're not sure about yet, otherwise the likely gain from swing trading isn't worth the time spent burning your eyes out with back-lit screen that it doesn't seem you can make dim enough not to give you a headache after a day of glaring at it. Sometimes I invert the colors on my screen image just to give myself some novelty, save that it makes images turn out a tad funky. I can also tell it to go to greyscale for some amusement, but that all just makes the ticker harder to read.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348679055622</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:04:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348679826843-14</Id><Title>Romney = Bush + OJ Simpson and Ken Lay</Title><Msg>Romney is a bush rerun who banks in the caymans like OJ simpson and like Ken lay did before he croaked before he could go to jail for his fraud and lies about how putting enron traders between you and your previously regulated utility would save you money!...... jeez..... talk about moochers, all enron did was bully into the process and rip everyone off with fraudlent trading , shill bidding...... they used to really laugh at how they would shut down a power plant for "maintenance" and then shill bid the price of power up, free market at work.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348679826843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348680126021-15</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So whether you agree with the posts or not, at least this thread is actually related to the stock and not about politics or spam. It would be nice if this becomes a trend.</Msg><Username>df4612</Username><Timestamp>1348680126021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348681459523-16</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone here having problems with etrade executing trades?</Title><Username>dsc20601</Username><Timestamp>1348605614502</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 16:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is very very slow. It is impossible to trade almost. #$%$?</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1348681459523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 13:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348686747473-17</Id><Topic><Title>Jimmy Carter II says keep pretending to talk to Iran. There is still time.</Title><Username>noshowl23</Username><Timestamp>1348610356477</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 17:59:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yea, Hussein Obama will let Iran obtain a nucular weapon and then what..."no more war". You don't get do you, then again if you did you wouldn't male naive comments twice as you do.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348686747473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348687231730-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I do know is that name calling is a sign of lack of thought and wanting to end debate, which is followed by more name calling...you need to have a talk with yourself about growing up, it's long over due.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348687231730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348687642045-19</Id><Title>get rid of the dead weight that hired freiberg in the first place!!!</Title><Msg>why do they keep these dead weight on the board after they have made so many poor if not stupid decisions? they need to replace all the wood that let the company get into this position ! major changes are needed at the top!!!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1348687642045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:27:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348688439320-20</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC may fall under $8 again within a month! Expecting not-so-good Q3-eps...</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348263854463</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well. I only see the price action in the first 30 min. of opening and last 30 min. of closing. It seems like, with 10 years of trading experience in ETFC, it is the best to add or sell at the last 5~10 min. of closing, otherwise, you'll be burnt a lot. Now, I am trying not to check every day basis, like you said, it's just wasting of my time and eye-health. GLTA!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348688439320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348688463839-21</Id><Title>next thing hedge fund will do</Title><Msg>is get them to sell the secondary shares and dilute the shareholders to pay for springers all the while shorting it to the 5's. only one to make money on this is the hedge fund!!IMHO that's why they keep the dummies as hdic's IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1348688463839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348688650321-22</Id><Topic><Title>get rid of the dead weight that hired freiberg in the first place!!!</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1348687642045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:27:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Toad. The guy who hired Freiberg was Robert Druskin a Citi flunky. Druskin is no longer with etrade and neither is Freiberg. You are running short on excuses. How about the company's financials look like crap?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1348688650321</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:44:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348688818871-23</Id><Title>ETFC has to hit $7 again before turning to rise again. Hold until it hits $7, then start adding!</Title><Msg>ETFC has to hit $7 again before turning to rise again. Hold until it hits $7, then start adding! ETFC will continually slide down until the good news is delivered. Right now, there is no catalyst to turn it around as so many investors expecting a worse-than-expected Q3 eps. ETFC may eventually rise but not any time soon... I am looking into Q2-2013 to have it rise above $10.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348688818871</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 15:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348710088973-24</Id><Title>Another GOP scam exposed</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- The same group that exposed the previously little-known American Legislative Exchange Council (ALEC) as a dominant force advancing corporate interests at the state level has now turned its sights on exposing the National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB). NFIB is hardly operating in near-secrecy, like ALEC was. The organization, which describes itself as "the voice of small business," was the lead plaintiff in the ultimately unsuccessful lawsuit against the Affordable Care Act, taking it to the Supreme Court. The left-leaning Center for Media and Democracy has posted on NFIBexposed dotorg, its new website, a study that reveals how consistently the NFIB lobbies on issues that favor large corporate interests rather than small-business interests; its thoroughly partisan agenda; and the millions it receives in secret contributions from groups associated with Karl Rove and the Koch Brothers. "I think that this new site helps expose the fact that the National Federation of Independent Business is not so independent, and it certainly is not acting as the voice of small business," said Lisa Graves, the center's director. But Jean Card, NFIB's vice president for communications, lashed out at the new website Wednesday. In an emailed statement to The Huffington Post, she wrote: "It is an insult to small-business owners across the country for another organization, with no connection to small business whatsoever, to imply that job creators don't know what's best for themselves." "NFIB is a member-driven, issue-driven organization. All of our advocacy and legal efforts are based purely on the positions of our membership, whose views and priorities we monitor constantly … and its membership are not concerned with party affiliation; we focus on policies, not party." The NFIBexposed dotorg website, however, chronicles how 98 percent of NFIB's campaign contributions so far in the 2012 election cycle have gone to Republicans, and how 100 percent of its advertising budget supported either Republicans or opposed Democrats. Looking at all donations since 1989, the NFIB is ranked third highest on Opensecrets.org's list of political "heavy hitters," based on the percentage of its contributions going to Republican candidates. NFIB's 93 percent is higher than Koch Industries with 90 percent; Exxon Mobil with 86 percent; and the National Rifle Association with 82 percent. By contrast, small-business owners are not as partisan. In fact, a recent poll showed that 47 percent of small-business owners plan to vote for President Barack Obama, compared to 39 percent who plan to vote for Mitt Romney. The website also links to documents that detail NFIB's top executive Dan Danner's compensation package, totaling $743,676 in 2010. "That tells me that there's some big-money interests willing to pay a real big-business corporate salary for the head of this organization," Graves said. "That is not on par with a typical small-business owner's salary. It's a big-business salary." Although NFIB doesn't disclose where it gets its money, some of its funders have to list their donations in public documents. The new website and other research shows that a big chunk of its budget came from the Donors Trust, a secretive conservative group that also funnels money to groups like the Koch Brothers' Americans for Prosperity Foundation, and from Karl Rove-founded Crossroads GPS. Ironically, Rove's Crossroads GPS gave NFIB $3.7 million as part of Rove's efforts to persuade the IRS that his group spends less than half of its money on overtly partisan activities. According to Crossroad's tax return, the donation was in the interest of "social welfare." Wendell Potter, author of "Deadly Spin, An Insurance Company Insider Speaks Out on How Corporate PR Is Killing Health Care and Deceiving Americans," said he recalled from his days as an insurance company executive that NFIB was available for message-laundering. "The industry has known that it can typically rely on the NFIB to carry its water," he said. More than a dozen years ago, when the insurance industry was working to kill legislation that would have established a "Patients' Bill of Rights," Potter recalled, "they knew that messaging from them wouldn't work," so the industry partnered with NFIB. "It was an organization that had the perception of representing small business and it really was representing the interests of the insurance industry," Potter said. NFIB's opposition to the Affordable Care Act is the perfect example, he said. Obama's signature law "will enable more small business to offer coverage to their workers and get some tax exemptions for doing that," Potter noted. "In the past, small businesses have not enjoyed the same benefits from the tax point of view that the larger companies have." So, in fact, NFIB was "working against the interests of small business," Potter said. Mother Jones recently noted that the NFIB lobbied heavily against Obama's plan to increase taxes on the wealthy, even though "[o]nly 3 percent of small businesses net more than $250,000 a year, the lowest income that would be affected by Obama's tax plan." "They're actually throwing the voice of big businesses," said Graves. "That has an impact on media coverage. The media will highlight the perspective of the NFIB as if it were representative of small business."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348710088973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 21:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348714730835-25</Id><Title>Romney Fans Sure are Quiet !</Title><Msg>The base is not happy. The race is over and they know it.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348714730835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:58:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348714919011-26</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Fans Sure are Quiet !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348714730835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slayer can't leave the house without a disguise. Sad</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348714919011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348714979738-27</Id><Title>Dipshidiot forgot he hates Romneycare</Title><Msg>'This may be where the real implosion starts to take manifest itself. When the Right Wing begins to eat Romney alive: “Don’t forget — I got everybody in my state insured,” Romney told NBC. “One hundred percent of the kids in our state had health insurance. I don’t think there’s anything that shows more empathy and care about the people of this country than that kind of record.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348714979738</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348715781822-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Fans Sure are Quiet !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348714730835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 22:58:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, but he has about 15 disguises. And we know he can't leave this chat board.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348715781822</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-26 23:16:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>