<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345003355000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Want to Know Who they're Voting for ..........</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345002254000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:44:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody ??? I guess I'm right.</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345003355000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345003441000-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Homos on this Board Say "Leave Bristol Alone "</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345002829000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The same homos are here every day and night. And dey got no ansers</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345003441000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:04:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345005483000-3</Id><Title>Results are coming in!</Title><Msg>Another landslide for REPUBLICANS in MN $ WI!!! Bachman of MN wins with 81%! District #8, a MN Left wing stronghold for 56 years is republican!!! ;o) Al Quist, R. is back and in for MN senator! Tommy Thompson (as I predicted) wins big to challenge and face Tammy Baldwin (nobody ever heard of her) to replace the OBIMBOCRAT senator Herbert Kohl, a liberal misguided German, in Nov.! That makes WI REPUBLICAN ALL THE WAY and MN is following!!! So will OH, IA and many other states, WI the strong hold of democRATS and unions rules! ND &amp; SD are already in the bag and we need to see what MI does with their now republican leadership? ROWDY GO WI, GO USA and follow the NORTHERN EX democRAT states! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345005483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345005898000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Results are coming in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345005483000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction: should read - ........the EX stronghold of democRATS! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345005898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345006006000-5</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pacifican As usual you argue until you're blue in the face. Do you think the allies worried about the German population when they tropped firebombs on German cities? Do you think President Truman worried about the Japanese population when he authorized the A-Bomb to be dropped on Japanese cities? When General Eisenhower became President he said, "beware of the military complex." You Pubs want to push this country into a war with Iran. Pacifican, you want us to learn about all of this crap you mentioned. Have you served in the military??? Didn't think so!!!</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345006006000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345006325000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/We'll Discuss Tax Policy After the Election</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1344992138000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, drill baby......I am too, learned a lot from OBIMPOLOSI! She showed me the way as to how to do insider trading, hiding accounts in foreign countries, etc! GREAT TEACHER! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345006325000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345006631000-7</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, The California Republican party has lost alot of members. The party has a hard time paying its bills. The Pubs party in California fell behind with the rent, electric and phone bills and may have to declare bankruptsy. Pubs in California are in bad shape. How about that, pacifican???</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345006631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 00:57:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345007369000-8</Id><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Msg>The NY Times just wrote about the demise of the CA GOP. It claimed its dramatic loss in voter registration, now just 30% of the state's voters, is due to the fact that the party has run out of ideas popular with the electorate and that it has grown increasingly conservative, out of step with independents who decide elections. Yes, the GOP has declined to insignificant status. It's minority status is now so small it can no longer block any legislation or budget that Gov. Brown and the Dems want. We live in a one party state. The state GOP simply sits in the legislature, relegated merely as silent observers watching in agony.</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345007875000-9</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rampant..doesn't matter what party CA is BK, San Bernardino, Stamford, etc is only the start! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345007875000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345028525000-10</Id><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Msg>Steals more money from Medicare than I'll probably make in my entire lifetime. http://townhall.com/tipsheet/guybenson/2012/08/14/boom_romney_campaign_releases_aggressive_medicare_ad</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345030564000-11</Id><Title>New Music video</Title><Msg>Far cry from the Obama girl vids from the past, yet poignant. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0rdry_gY_E&amp;feature=player_embedded</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345030564000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345038418000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The next thing I expect is for to come along and ask me if I'm really naive enough to think that I'm the only one to think of this.</Msg><Username>stokesfitzgerald</Username><Timestamp>1345038418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 09:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345040638000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Romney’s latest TV ad says: “You worked hard, paid in to Medicare. Now when you need it, Obama has cut $716 billion dollars from Medicare.” THIS ROMNEY AD IS COMPLETELY FALSE! Obamacare and Medicare do not cut a single guaranteed benefit!!! The $716 billion is only a projection of how Obamacare reduces the rate of growth in Medicare spending, and eliminates current waste and inefficiencies over 10 years. EVERY SINGLE GUARANTEED BENEFIT REMAINS IN PLACE!!! BUT ROMNEY-RYAN CAN’T WIN UNLESS YOU BELIEVE THIS BIG FALSEHOOD! " There's only one party trying to turn MEDICARE into a voucher system, the GOP.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345040638000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:23:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345040988000-14</Id><Title>Isn't that convenient?</Title><Msg>Ryan: GOP ticket to wait to disclose tax specifics Source: Associated Press WASHINGTON (AP) — Republican vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan says he and Mitt Romney will wait until after they're elected to disclose what tax loopholes they plan to get rid of. Ryan tells Fox News that — quote — "that is something that we think we should do in the light of day, through Congress." Ryan says the GOP ticket wants to get feedback from Americans about what tax cuts should be kept and what loopholes to close. In the interview, Ryan accused President Barack Obama of cutting Medicare to pay for his federal health care overhaul. It was the Romney campaign's line of the day, and it drew a blistering response from Obama's campaign, which labeled the latest Romney ad dishonest and hypocritical.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345040988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345041292000-15</Id><Title>Ryan, he didn't build that</Title><Msg>"Ryan Family Fortune Built on Public Works Projects That Romney Campaign Mocks Paul Ryan is a living, breathing GOP example of how public infrastructure and private entrepreneurship work hand-in-hand. When Paul Ryan took to the stage in Mooresville, North Carolina, as Mitt Romney’s running mate, he attacked President Obama’s “you didn’t build that” remark about the role of government in supporting private innovation. But while Republicans have been clamoring to make this election a false dichotomy between the private sector and the public sector, Paul Ryan — heir to a private fortune made by building public highways — is a gaping pothole in that plan. Paul Ryan is a living, breathing GOP example of how public infrastructure and private entrepreneurship work hand-in-hand. Paul Ryan’s great-grandfather started a construction company to build railroads and, eventually, highways. According to the Web site of Ryan Incorporated Central, the company was “ founded in 1884 with a single team of mules building railroad embankments in Southern Wisconsin.” And in the 1800s, railroad construction was subsidized by the federal government. Mid-century, President Lincoln signed the Pacific Railway Act into law, providing taxpayer dollars to fund the construction of a transcontinental railway. All railroads thereafter connected to, and benefited from, that public investment. ------------- What’s funny is that Mr. Anti-Spending secured millions in earmarks for his home state of Wisconsin, including, among other things, $3.3 million for highway projects . And Ryan voted to preserve $40 billion in special subsidies for big oil , an industry in which, it so happens, Ryan and his wife hold ownership stakes. Yet Ryan wants to gut financial aid for college students, food stamps for hungry families , Medicaid,Medicare and Social Security — the very things that have, historically, helped poor families climb the ladder of opportunity in America. And this is precisely the problem with the Romney-Ryan vision for America: It takes the ladder of opportunity and public infrastructure that helped the previous generation and yanks it up for the next generation. Your grandfather went to college on the GI Bill? We’re not even going to give you measly Pell Grants! Your grandmother lived independently thanks to Social Security? We’re giving yours to Wall Street to crash with the rest of our economy! Your great-grandfather got rich building public railways and roads? We’re going to cut taxes for the rich to historic lows and raise taxes on the struggling middle class to barely cover the cost of plugging potholes! It’s “I Got Mine, Now Screw You!” economics. This kind of hard-heartedness may appeal to the extreme fringe base of Republican voters, but it is as repulsive to mainstream voters as it is corrosive to the American dream. The Romney-Ryan budget focuses 62 percent of its cuts on programs that help the poor — in order to pay for more tax breaks for the already-rich and, incidentally, raise the deficit . "</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345041292000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:34:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345041328000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what are you talking about??</Msg><Username>t.gibbs91</Username><Timestamp>1345041328000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345042529000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/We'll Discuss Tax Policy After the Election</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1344992138000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:55:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Drill baby drill. How is that working out for natural gas shareholders!!!!!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1345042529000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345042532000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&amp;v=UH5dEPbB5yQ</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345042532000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:55:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345042754000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt; townhall.com &gt;&gt; Still reading that garbage? Why are you so addicted to it? Do they have a section on sex with sheep or something? &lt;&lt;Steals more money from Medicare than I'll probably make in my entire lifetime.&gt;&gt; Dude - like that is a challenge of some sort? I probably pay more taxes in a year than you will make in your entire lifetime....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345042754000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:59:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345042814000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget junglebob you are supposed to be for the weak, disenfranchised and sorry-sorts of the country. How you can continually and vehemently defend a president who only champions himself, unions and thegays is beyond me. Americans are getting pretty tired of his failed policies and lies. Take my parents for instance who are on ss/ medicare and who live and vote in battleground state of FL. They said they are mad ashell and it didn't just come around recently. Remember when there was that budget debate a few years ago and he threatened to stop checks to seniors? &lt;-- just because he could. Well my parents, along wif most in their retirement community lost a lot of respect for that man who would use them as pawns or leverage to gain an advantage in a political battle. So the folks aint happy and I remind them not to forget whenever I call.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345042814000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345043261000-21</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;CA is BK, San Bernardino, Stamford, etc is only the start!&gt;&gt; Still rooting for the country to fail Rowdy? So typically GOP!!! At least in your case you have an exit option of moving back to Germany. I wonder why the rest of the GOP is so eager for (and actively working towards) the US to fail, yet still call themselves PATRIOTS.... unbelievable.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345043261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345043380000-22</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For FY 2013, the Federal government has budgeted $851 billion for security spending Not one dime can ge cut in this budget and keep us secure? Doubtfull.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1345043380000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345043491000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't that convenient?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345040988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So the GOP team will keep their tax policy secret AND their returns secret. Great way to run a campaign!!</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345043491000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345044414000-24</Id><Title>Potential Buy Out Price</Title><Msg>I found this interesting and encouraging. Certainly this is a good time to buy or accumulate. The down side is limited. ----In a takeover, E*Trade could still fetch $12 to $18 a share, according to Credit Agricole’s Fischer. The likely buyer is TD Ameritrade because it would be able to cut the most costs and potentially partner with Toronto-Dominion Bank to manage the loans that would be inherited in a takeover, he said. ---- The rest of the story is at: http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-15/citadel-s-e-trade-exit-still-seen-blocked-by-mortgages-real-m-a.html?cmpid=yhoo</Msg><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345044414000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:26:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345044755000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is going to be big. Pay back time to the hedge naked shorts.</Msg><Username>deandrehale30</Username><Timestamp>1345044755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345045105000-26</Id><Title>Capital gains v. labor debate</Title><Msg>Capital gains should be taxed HIGHER than labor. All this repuke talk about the how the poor don't know that value of work is nothing but projection. It is the repukes who don't value work. They want to tax work income at 30%, while taxing capital gains (where you get money without lifting a finger) at ZERO. The unfairness is mind boggling. If anything, labor should be taxed at a lower rate, because it is a diminishing asset, so to speak. We can only provide so many years of labor, then we can't work anymore. Then we die. Life is short and most people, if they could, would spend their limited time here on earth hanging out with their loved ones or seeing the world, engaging in hobbies, etc. Work, in general (particularly low wage work), sucks. So why further discourage work by taxing it many times more than other forms of income? And most people who have to work for a living need every dime they make for the basics. Therefore, they spend everything they make, which is way more stimulative to the economy (70% of the economy is based on consumer spending). Capital gains, on the other hand, are generated by money --and money does not die. It lives forever and can continue generating capital gains forever. Plus, the rich people who get these gains just stash it away. Relatively little of it is spent on consumer goods to drive the economy. The rich already have all they need. Their spending is discretionary. Why would you tax capital gains at a lower rate if it does not boost the economy like labor income? (Rhetorical question--I know it is because the rich rule congress and are money hoarders).</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345045105000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345045599000-27</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McCain was talking about that yesterday. Discretionary. Yes. Military has a lot of bureaucracy and ineffectiveness too. That's not what original poster had in mind alluding that military spending is immoral.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345045599000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345045739000-28</Id><Topic><Title>Potential Buy Out Price</Title><Username>strietwise</Username><Timestamp>1345044414000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:26:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An excellent article!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345045739000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:48:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345046190000-29</Id><Title>Bloomberg on E*Trade - Aug 15, 2012</Title><Msg>"After plunging 50 percent in 2011, E*Trade shares had risen less than 1 percent this year before Freiberg’s departure was announced last week. Even after the subsequent 8.1 percent rally to $8.67 yesterday, the shares were still valued at a 51 percent discount to the company’s $5.08 billion in book value, or assets minus liabilities, data compiled by Bloomberg show. In a takeover, E*Trade could still fetch $12 to $18 a share, according to Credit Agricole’s Fischer. The likely buyer is TD Ameritrade because it would be able to cut the most costs and potentially partner with Toronto-Dominion Bank to manage the loans that would be inherited in a takeover, he said. After the broker rejected putting the company up for sale in November, the New York-based company is looking for a new leader as its stock trades at 0.49 times the value of E*Trade’s net assets, trailing rivals TD Ameritrade Holding Corp. (AMTD) and Charles Schwab Corp. (SCHW) that fetch double their book value, according to data compiled by Bloomberg." http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-15/citadel-s-e-trade-exit-still-seen-blocked-by-mortgages-real-m-a.html?cmpid=yhoo</Msg><Username>Quizotical_al</Username><Timestamp>1345046190000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:56:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345046224000-30</Id><Topic><Title>OMG, futures = sunburn RED ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1345001798000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow..... you lost your credibility totally! Why are you still hovering around in this board? Better find other message board soon!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345046224000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345046230000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Has No Job Experience</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344971364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your statements are nothing but idiotic. President Obama was a law professor and that was a real job.</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345046230000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 11:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345046602000-32</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It definitely exceeded my expectations.</Msg><Username>carson.bowers70</Username><Timestamp>1345046602000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:03:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345047208000-33</Id><Title>Next resistance at $8.76, then $8.88</Title><Msg>Once we passed a small bump at $8.76, it will go smoothly to $8.87 to meet another bump at $8.88! After passing $8.88, we will see $9!! This may happen on Friday!! Hold or add more here!!! I added earlier at $8.60!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345047208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345048264000-34</Id><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Msg>Knowing PUBS on this board, they will probably cry when they read this .... http://www.boston.com/business/technology/2012/08/09/may-have-electric-car-breakthrough/eUbA0pxSsW8E892i0pTdBL/story.html</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345049531000-35</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go back and see the original post to see what is immoral about it, you are confused and dishonest as usual. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_E/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=24619&amp;tid=2036101&amp;mid=2036101&amp;tof=8&amp;rt=1&amp;frt=1&amp;off=1</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1345049531000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345050114000-36</Id><Title>Huffington Post!</Title><Msg>Quote: "The road for the presidency runs through WISCONSIN and so does the SENATE!" Tommy Thompson, R. is going to defeat Tammy Baldwin in Nov. and replace Herbert Kohl, D. (I predicted that Tommy would win) and the "new senate" will be Republican. (His republican rivals in yesterdays election however accused him of being too MODERATE) Thompson predicts today that the OBIMBO/BIDEN days are over with the Nov. election. ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345050114000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:01:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345050140000-37</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bTbLslkIR2k</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345050140000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345050538000-38</Id><Title>"Do Nothing" GOP congress</Title><Msg>"Source: USA Today Congress is on pace to make history with the least productive legislative year in the post World War II era. Just 61 bills have become law to date in 2012 out of 3,914 bills that have been introduced by lawmakers, or less than 2 percent of all proposed laws, according to a USA TODAY analysis of records since 1947 kept by the U.S. House Clerk's office. In 2011, after Republicans took control of the U.S. House, Congress passed just 90 bills into law. The only other year in which Congress failed to pass at least 125 laws was 1995. These statistics make the 112th Congress, covering 2011-12, the least productive two-year gathering on Capitol Hill since the end of World War II. Not even the 80th Congress, which President Truman called the "do-nothing Congress" in 1948, passed as few laws as the current one, records show." I guess this is what happens when the Ryan led Congress passes the same bill to repeal healthcare reform over thirty times.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345050538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345051451000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't that convenient?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345040988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Outsourcer In Chief asks that you just trust him? "One of the things I have found in previous elections is that announcing my plans makes people want to vote against me!" -- Mitt Romney We may never see a more honest remark from a politician. Romney may have said this lightly, but I have no doubt that he discovered the truth of these words during his last campaign. So this time around, he's attempting to keep quiet while he tunes his message to what he thinks we all want to hear. But the truth is, as he himself admitted, that if he told us what he plans to do once he takes office, we would never vote for him. Giving him the presidency is like handing your car keys to a person who says to you, "Yeah, if you knew what I was going to do with your car, you wouldn't be handing me these keys."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345051451000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345051501000-40</Id><Topic><Title>Isn't that convenient?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1345040988000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Nobody should be able to seek the highest office in this land who has no core principles or values and who is unwilling to be clear and level with the American public about who and what he is and how he plans to govern. Mitt Romney is one of the most fundamentally dishonest, fraudulent and hollow men to ever seek the Presidency. The Mormon Madoff has been a political chameleon his whole life shedding skins more frequently than a snake. Mr. ‘Etch-A-Sketch’ is attempting to do a fly by the democratic process in America refusing to be held accountable not just to the base of his party, investigative journalists and the remaining citizens who he hopes will consider voting for him. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345051501000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345052339000-41</Id><Topic><Title>immoral &amp; lunatic gop want to increase this spending</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344962477000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:41:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_E/threadview?m=tm&amp;bn=24619&amp;tid=2036101&amp;mid=2036121&amp;tof=8&amp;rt=1&amp;frt=1&amp;off=1</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345052339000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345053785000-42</Id><Title>When eTrade is in flux</Title><Msg>All anyone here can do it seems is comment on an election when, boiled down to its basics, is simply a choice between the lessor of two evils. So lets ignore that for now and try to figure out if the recent movement presages a greater upward movement in the medium term future or indicates our rally from earnings has petered and the stock price is about to tank again? The reality has to be somewhere in the middle yet I see no attempt by the board to come to an honest consensus. A "room" full of amateur (and some slumming pro) traders should be able to do just as well or better than the pro's. We sure beat the heck out of their estimates on the Apple board when I was a regular there, although eventually we had to move it to another site because of all the spam anything having to do with Apple was getting. So, until I hear some convincing arguments either way, particularly at these price levels, I'm not buying, I'm not selling, I've increased my permanent position to 2500 shares and still have an extra 500 shares picked up on the cheap during the latest dip. This could easily be a $30 company again in 3 years, if they aren't snuffed out by over-regulation or some trick to cut direct retail investors out of the equity markets in the name of "protecting the little guy", when in fact the equity markets are the little guy's chance to at least become a medium guy, and a medium guy's chance to make it big, absent some novel business idea popping into your head AND executing it properly.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345053785000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345054640000-43</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Has No Job Experience</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344971364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary Clinton spokesman Phil Singer: "Sen. Obama has often referred to himself as “a constitutional law professor” out on the campaign trail. He never held any such title. And I think anyone, if you ask anyone in academia the distinction between a professor who has tenure and an instructor that does not, you’ll find that there is." A job? Community organizer was his full time job.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345054640000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345054694000-44</Id><Topic><Title>When eTrade is in flux</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345053785000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:03:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will be sold at $16~17 per share within a year before it hits $30 per share in 3 years!! Just get in for 100% potential profits!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345054694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345055623000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine our potential !!!!!</Msg><Username>christian.finch10</Username><Timestamp>1345055623000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:33:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345055694000-46</Id><Topic><Title>"Do Nothing" GOP congress</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345050538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 13:08:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>q4dike.........we don't need any more new laws, we already choking in the current ones set forth by the OBIMBORAMA! What we need is to throw OBIMBO and his bunch out and recall OBIMBOCARE and eliminate MEDICAIDE! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345055694000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:34:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345056206000-47</Id><Topic><Title>$3.00/$4.00 at most lil'sis of Lehman Bros</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1344868810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 10:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is like Wal-mart.....cozy crooked deals with front runned municpal mexican building officials and now money laundering inquiries......hummm? Citadel and Griffin with their front running propritary trading or charging a cent or two on every trade every day for years. And now with the detireation of the municipal bond market, etade don't make as much money and soon shall staret loseing a lot each month.....down it goes darts and same store sales, down down and you know how it goes who wants a dying bank who wants a decreaseing trade account who wants to spend m&amp;a monies just to have then walk out the door next month, because of old antique trading platform.....down it goes today or after options friday</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345056206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345056617000-48</Id><Topic><Title>$3.00/$4.00 at most lil'sis of Lehman Bros</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1344868810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 10:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh yeah fugbar, if more people with less money can manage their money for less at etrade and walmart ,,, as the cost association keeps going down so does the value of newbies in the market as etrade can not retain them. and if the costs gets to zero....where is the value add on for that myth,,,, manufactureing tries selling that too we can build it cheaper, cell phone bill plans are so cheap now that the masses are pey go's..............30 days and they can be done out of business and they have to shut the phones lines down themselves...........greedy griffin's generation has ruined the suspicious next gen.</Msg><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1345056617000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345056753000-49</Id><Title>8.34 thursdayclose/8.02fridayclose</Title><Msg>eom from my point of view</Msg><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345056753000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345056825000-50</Id><Title>Place a buy order at $8.60! Let's see!!</Title><Msg>It can go down to $8.60 and jump to $8.70s before closing!! Just my hunch!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345056825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345057002000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Place a buy order at $8.60! Let's see!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345056825000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:53:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey sweetie: If you get one more call right, i'm gonna send you a cake with me in it! Eat me.</Msg><Username>princesslabium</Username><Timestamp>1345057002000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 14:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345057896000-52</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;due to the fact that the party has run out of ideas popular with the electorate and that it has grown increasingly conservative, out of step with independents who decide elections&gt;&gt; There are no independents in California, only three classes of people. One, illegals and people on the doll. two, bureaucrats, and three, up state liberals who are insulated (for now)from the rest of the state because of Silcon Valley. This once beautiful state has turned into a cesspool of takers and third world vermin...an example of liberalism at its finest.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345057896000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:11:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345057904000-53</Id><Topic><Title>$3.00/$4.00 at most lil'sis of Lehman Bros</Title><Username>nurse26yrs</Username><Timestamp>1344868810000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 10:40:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi there Precious. Its meee, the big princesslabium. You can check my pic out on this board. Just wanted to say hi! And also mention that Citadel will never lay hands on Etrade. Its a conflicted transaction especially at the price you discuss. To the end, etrade is worth $20 samolians at sale. Really now with all the declining darts its time for AMTD to make etfc its bee-0tch. Consolidation be the word. Stop by for cake and coffee. I will have the cake and you can have the coffee. My doctor says that my heart will explode if i drink coffee. I love cake so Eat me</Msg><Username>princesslabium</Username><Timestamp>1345057904000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345058290000-54</Id><Title>GTC5kbuytocvr@$8.55soldshrt@$8.75</Title><Msg>i shall take the k for the day ....thank you batter up for da buyers "K"'s for the short pitcher, gotta luv does ball players</Msg><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345058290000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:18:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345058308000-55</Id><Title>Put away the barbie</Title><Msg>Another first for the community organizer...beef prices don't effect the rich only the folks in the middle not on food stamps. Oh, one other acommlishment gas back over $4 a gallon...he's the man! Price of Ground Beef Hits Record High The average price of ground beef hit a record high in the United States in July, according to data released Wednesday by the Bureau of Labor Statistics. The BLS has been tracking the average price of a pound of 100% ground beef since 1984. In July, it cost $3.085, up from $3.007 in June. Prior to June, the average cost of 100% ground beef in the United States had never topped $3.00.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345058308000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345058538000-56</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;only three classes of people.&gt;&gt; which one are you biddermon? Assuming you are not in the "illegals" or "up state liberals" groups, that would qualify you for the following: a) "people on the doll" b) "bureaucrats" c) both a and b (tough to do - but wouldn't surprise me from a dumb GOP'er like yourself)</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345058538000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345058583000-57</Id><Topic><Title>GTC5kbuytocvr@$8.55soldshrt@$8.75</Title><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345058290000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:18:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c'mon down to my "price is right" i will wait til the 'morrow but it's gonna be great when it slip sliding away yeah</Msg><Username>Buck_o_shot</Username><Timestamp>1345058583000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:23:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345058776000-58</Id><Title>Take a byte outta Da Hog, y'all ...learn when...</Title><Msg>before that hungry Hog take a byte outta y'all. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( That buyout/consolidation gig don't last more than a couple or three days anymore. Everytime they pull that rabbit out, E-Tub make a new multi-year low. $*** 7.01 *** )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1345058776000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345059260000-59</Id><Title>Latest poll.......</Title><Msg>..........90 million people which voted for OBIMBORAMA will stay home and NOT vote for him - synopsis - disappiontment of the outcome of his "Hope and Change"! Love it! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345059260000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345059266000-60</Id><Title>Now is time to get in!! $8.56 is bottom!!</Title><Msg>Now is time to get in!! $8.56 is bottom!! Get in at $8.57!!! It will close flat or higher!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345059266000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345059614000-61</Id><Title>More insiders will add at this low price!!!</Title><Msg>Get in now at $8.57 before it hits $9 this Friday!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345059614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345059743000-62</Id><Title>Here Comes the Shorties......</Title><Msg>to pound this thing back down to the 7's. Good luck buying all the way down moonie. Lows of the day. Defines Etfc.....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345059743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345059957000-63</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing but bad news for PUBS. Now, despise their coordinated efforts to the contrary, there are "more signs of economic growth" http://news.yahoo.com/stocks-rise-more-signs-economic-growth-142716828--finance.html The PUBS mourn...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345059957000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345060094000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GM "MAY" have.....MAY - within a couple of years - MAY?????????? They need more money for their union funds - that's all! Lithium batteries are the most efficient batteries but also most expensive, so the "poor people" wont be able to afford such a car, and when the replacement time for the battery package comes its PARKING TIME for the POS!!! Lithium is the most energy retaining battery type but here in the Northland needs to be on a "Trickle charge" in the winter - so where do you plug all those cars in for instance in down town Minneapolis???? I can carry spare gas in case I get stranded in an ice/snow storm but I won't/can't carry a spare battery pack - cant lift it and I am no whimp! So, to make it economical - it's another job for China with years to come in development and approval!! I just renewed my car's insurances (listed in a IOWA company - lowest premium with max. coverage) and my insurance agent (broker) said, that the premium on a Volt is $2417.50 with progressive 715-386-7112, call them and talk with Melanie!!!! My new Traverse is together with the Cadi, BMW and Fiat $658.00 and I wouldn't even get a quote in CA, NY, NJ etc. - now I want all the "POOR OBIMBOCRATS buy a Volt! So again THINK do your research, you OBIMBOCRAT CHEERLEADER before you post your CRAP! ROWDY (EE)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345060094000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345060336000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See the difference between us is that I am talking FACTS, you are talking OBIMBO BS! ROWDY (Start doing your home work before you post some stupid articles!)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345060336000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:52:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345060895000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Here Comes the Shorties......</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345059743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck with your shorting, bring plenty of friends, it'll help on the pop later on, pretty much no matter what happens. Short of stumbling over a pile of naked PUTS they wrote and forgot about I think eTrade has pretty much purged itself of toxic debt, or provisioned for it. Any surprises in that area are likely to be to the upside.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1345060895000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345060974000-67</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;but wouldn't surprise me from a dumb GOP'er like yourself&gt;&gt; Does your mother know you are still name calling. I am in the waiting to exit category...maybe I'll move to your all white community and bring a couple of illegals alone to live in the basement. They could to do the house and yard work during the day, and let them rob my neigbors houses, sell the ill gotten goods on Craigslist and Ebay...sounds like you could use a little diversity.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345060974000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345061126000-68</Id><Title>Gap to $8.53 filled!! New Support at $8.50!!</Title><Msg>ETFC will go up tomorrow to $8.78+!!! Mark this!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345061126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345061332000-69</Id><Topic><Title>Gap to $8.53 filled!! New Support at $8.50!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345061126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:05:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AH up 13 cents!!! Last trading at $8.66!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345061332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:08:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345061462000-70</Id><Title>Group of Democrats:...........</Title><Msg>........bar debt commission questions from debates! All the sudden the planless OBIMBOCRATS are in trouble on every front - OBIMBO is toast! - LOVE IT! ;o) Trump will have a BIG surprise for the GOP CONVENTION opener!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345061462000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345061626000-71</Id><Topic><Title>Here Comes the Shorties......</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345059743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all that is irrelevant. Whats relevant is that the stock is going to $5. Thats all thats relevant.</Msg><Username>skiselev81</Username><Timestamp>1345061626000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345061808000-72</Id><Title>13 miion charge in Q3 for firing..</Title><Msg>Freiberg according to Sandler. Drops estimates to 7 cents. Somebody please tell this company to stop shooting itself in the foot. It's really just awful.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345061808000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345063621000-73</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>San Bernardino, Sockton, Vallejo. GOP is weak here. I quit years back. Tea Party is gaining strength. And it is the only tool to keep GOP worry about the country rather than power.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1345063621000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:47:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345064059000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Latest poll.......</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345059260000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:34:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;90 million people which voted for OBIMBORAMA will stay home and NOT vote for him&gt;&gt; Really ROWDY??? Are you truly THIS STUPID??? 90 million people? I knew your case of dementia was advanced - but at this point - you should probably have your legal competency reviewed. There is only 72 million registered Democrats, 55 million registered republicans and 42 million registered as independent. Additionally - there were only 69,456,897 votes cast for Obama and 59,934,814 against in last election.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345064059000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345064087000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Im Rubbing it in with ETFC... I Sold Today...</Title><Username>romeo.hughes</Username><Timestamp>1345034777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 08:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My opinion about the share market is the better the economy gets,the more the market should sell off.When is good news really bad and bad news really good- Keep reading this jornal to know more about stock market. Lets hope for the best</Msg><Username>danielbarber706</Username><Timestamp>1345064087000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345064428000-76</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidder is most certainly on the 'doll'. A blowup doll.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1345064428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:00:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345065270000-77</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;I am in the waiting to exit category&gt;&gt; Most people in the Tea Party would fit this description... Definitely you and Rowdy.... too old to be of any use... just "waiting to exit"...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345065270000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345065439000-78</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, clown............another 4000 laid off from Google, 800 more to come from Best Buy, Target down sizing on employees and ALL small business down sizing to 49 employees - estimates of 10000's losing their jobs till November and MAYBE rehired when OBIMBOCARE gets thrown out! - OBIMBORAMA at it's best!!! Retail sales forecast look dim for the upcoming quarter based on uncertainty! Less sales taxes, less employees - all going the wrong way till Romney/Ryan gets elected! ROWDY (Clown, my research/knowledge talks - you BS, copy articles walks!)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345065439000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345065558000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Group of Democrats:...........</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345061462000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:11:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Trump will have a BIG surprise for the GOP CONVENTION opener&gt;&gt; oh boy.... Trump will be opening GOP convention?... what a joke... What will he be doing? 'Romney's Roast' ???</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345065558000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345065914000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as I said - the PUBS on this board will cry.... thanks Rowdy.... I was surprised at the silence....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345065914000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345066132000-81</Id><Title>Which Direction: $8.78 or $8.28?</Title><Msg>We are at the intersection of $8.53 today!! It can go higher or lower from here... My bet is it will go higher tomorrow as more and more insiders and institutions are adding as they realize that the current pps is too low compare to the true value of ETFC estimated at $30 per share!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345066132000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345066193000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Clown, my research/knowledge talks&gt;&gt; Ah - yes - knowledge and research..... wait ..... aren't you Conservatives allergic to both ??? How else would you conjure this gem? http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_E/threadview?m=ts&amp;bn=24619&amp;tid=2036256&amp;mid=2036256&amp;tof=5&amp;frt=1</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345066193000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345066216000-83</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only are you STUPID, but most of all you are DESPICABLE, DISRESPECTFUL and UNEDUCATED! One day you will be OLD too, if your bird brain makes it. Don't you respect your parents (if you have any) which I assume are aging too or are you just a little stupid 18 year old BIMBO which finally learned how to operate a key board - are you old enough to vote jet?????? ROWDY You are digging yourself in deeper, because you are to stupid to think before you post and have NO CLUE on life!</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345066216000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345066784000-84</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;too old to be of any use... just "waiting to exit"&gt;&gt; I guess you still live in the twentieth century with Vice President Biden. BTW, you need to reframe from childess name calling...“Civilized men are more discourteous than savages because they know they can be impolite without having their skulls split, as a general thing.”</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1345066784000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345067194000-85</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing like freezing your market - telling them to wait for the next thing. this screams - "hey we don't sell enuf volts to care - but we like our government cheese - so general public you should wait to buy a car until we have a viable battery." brilliant</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1345067194000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:46:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345067222000-86</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biddermoon, My Repugnican friends want me to tell you "NUTS." Californians, whether Dem or Pub, love their state and wouldn't live anywhere else. They have nice beaches, beautiful mountains, gorgeous lakes, and useful streams and rivers. biddermoon, you are known in this board as an angry Pub and you need to lighten up before they pick you up.</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345067222000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345067777000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Poor Pubs</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1345048264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 12:31:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Surprised at the silence"......because I find facts (Phone calls to insurance and GM dealer) and $$$# first before I post - not just running the mouth like your uneducated, dim minded, OBIMBO blinded garbage! (Our dealership, the largest in the Twin cities area and here has currently NO PARTS and trained technicians to fix the lemon VOLT, if it quits - nice car!!!) ROWDY (Now I am e-mailing Gov. Walker, Sen. Sheila Harsdorf to freeze the use of Ethanol in WI - another loser - wrecking small and older car engine, less mpg and more expensive to produce! (An other stupid law) Also congratulated Tommy (I met him at a Packer game in Green BAY in the luxury box when he was governor, got the pass from Brett Favre) on his election to senator to be elected in Nov. to take back congress from the OBIMBOS!) (P.S. Thrump will hold a CLOWN ROAST)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345067777000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 17:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345068953000-88</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rampant ....I liked CA when I lived there in the 70s, except for the riots, when we had to open fire down Western Ave across Wilshire BLVD to keep the ni$$ers from overrunning us, but with my military training and our neighbors from the hardware store, (Asian, you might have seen him opening fire with his AK47 on TV, if you are old enough), we blew them right back down to Adams Blvd. My last residence after moving away from Laguna Niguel was Laurell Canyon Drive in the Hills! Then I moved and lived ever since in the Northland and I wouldn't trade it for the now broke, dopy, left wing (9th disrict court, SF) state. Go Jerry Brown - Freedown Fighter for fruit flies! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345068953000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 18:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345070499000-89</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rampant..........yes I did like my favorite place, Lake Arrowhead and Big Bear where I had a cabin on. (Now I suppose with all the fires it might be gone???) I liked Laguna Niguel, Escondido, also Santa Barbara with their great Spanish food and driving up the hills to the Ronney Ranch! I liked Beverly Hills and dining in the Brown Derby! (When we fly back to LA we always stay at the Beverly Hilton - that's whats her name croaked lately?) Taking our yacht from San Pedro to Avalon and stayed in hotels up in the hills! I loved to dine at Redondo Beach on the board walk, the Cattleman and the Polonaisian right on the corner. I traveled every spot in that state, the Redwoods were great and bought lots of stuff made from Myrtle Wood in Cuze Bay, OR and went all the way back down on 101 to San Diego! Life was and is still good! ROWDY (Look up "Fred &amp; Fuzzy's bar and grill, WI", watch the slide show and see the sunset from our cabin window, now that's a pretty beach too! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1345070499000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 18:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345071007000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Brak guts Medicare---&gt; Steals it from most frail among us</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345028525000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 07:02:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here it all is. Brak's own words on tape. Continue to carry his water if you want. It just shows you are no better than the president wif all of your perpetuating and condoning of his lies. http://townhall.com/tipsheet/guybenson/2012/08/15/video_obama_admits_he_cut_billions_from_medicare_to_fund_obamacare</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345071007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 18:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345071198000-91</Id><Title>freiburg should pay the investors</Title><Msg>he shouldn't get anything for the poor performance investors received!!!!cut the board members pay to make up for it!They hired the dead weight!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1345071198000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 18:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345071322000-92</Id><Topic><Title>13 miion charge in Q3 for firing..</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1345061808000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:16:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get rid of the board and save the salaries they do nothing but make mistakes!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1345071322000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 18:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345071781000-93</Id><Title>YAHOO Jacking With the Format Again...</Title><Msg>Take a look at the CSCO and YHOO boards....If they do that to All the boards...even JB will Stop Posting!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345071781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:03:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345072575000-94</Id><Topic><Title>YAHOO Jacking With the Format Again...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345071781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The libtarts will like it once they figure out how to stick all those thumbs up theirasses.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1345072575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345073901000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Gap to $8.53 filled!! New Support at $8.50!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345061126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 16:05:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should I buy etfc in ah now?</Msg><Username>joe_the_plumber_trader</Username><Timestamp>1345073901000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345074523000-96</Id><Topic><Title>YAHOO Jacking With the Format Again...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1345071781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:03:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Pukes don't know what is what! Poor Repukes!</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1345074523000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345074939000-97</Id><Topic><Title>More insiders will add at this low price!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345059614000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 15:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ask is 8.60 but I would love to get in at 8.49 or lower. It seems that I will buy 10000 etfc shares for a longer term tomorrow.</Msg><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1345074939000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:55:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345078244000-98</Id><Title>Has anyone tallied</Title><Msg>the amount paid to our last 5 or so failed CEOs? This is getting pathetic. May I suggest we hire any one of hundreds of qualified young MBAs who would love the chance to do a better job. Little or no experience preferred. Salary mostly based on stock price performance during their tenure. Clawbacks apply. Jeez, what a chump outfit his has become.</Msg><Username>anitaz22</Username><Timestamp>1345078244000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 20:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345079261000-99</Id><Topic><Title>California Pubs Party Going Bankrupt</Title><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1345007369000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 01:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bitter biddermon is still in the 18th century. He can't abide these newfangled electric cars. And he hates America. Wants to see it destroyed.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1345079261000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 21:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345079865000-100</Id><Title>If ETFC cross $8.77 tomorrow, we will see $9 on Friday!!</Title><Msg>If ETFC cross $8.77 tomorrow, we will see $9 on Friday!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345079865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 21:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345080125000-101</Id><Topic><Title>If ETFC cross $8.77 tomorrow, we will see $9 on Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345079865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 21:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you stuck your nose between my but checks you could taste my bung hole. What a idiotic comment!!</Msg><Username>wiffmyanus</Username><Timestamp>1345080125000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 21:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345083404000-102</Id><Topic><Title>Caution Must Be Maintained</Title><Username>dellysxr145</Username><Timestamp>1345074546000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 19:49:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>abigaelbqt737</Username><Timestamp>1345083404000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 22:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345084697000-103</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Has No Job Experience</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344971364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot, again. UC Law School statement: Several times during his 12 years as a professor in the Law School, Obama was invited to join the faculty in a full-time tenure-track position, but he declined. Furthermore, Obama was not merely an "instructor" As a "senior lecturer," Obama was in good company: The six other faculty members with the title include the associate dean of the law school and Judge Richard Posner, who is widely considered to be one of the nation’s top legal theorists or UC Law School statement2 : The Law School has received many media requests about Barack Obama, especially about his status as "Senior Lecturer." From 1992 until his election to the U.S. Senate in 2004, Barack Obama served as a professor in the Law School. He was a Lecturer from 1992 to 1996. He was a Senior Lecturer from 1996 to 2004, during which time he taught three courses per year. Senior Lecturers are considered to be members of the Law School faculty and are regarded as professors, although not full-time or tenure-track. The title of Senior Lecturer is distinct from the title of Lecturer, which signifies adjunct status. Like Obama, each of the Law School’s Senior Lecturers have high-demand careers in politics or public service, which prevent full-time teaching.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1345084697000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 22:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345086704000-104</Id><Topic><Title>If ETFC cross $8.77 tomorrow, we will see $9 on Friday!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345079865000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 21:17:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Futures are rising up as Asian market is rallying!!!!!! http://www.cnbc.com/id/17689937/site/14081545/ ETFC is well positioned at this price level. Next move-up will be coming on Friday!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1345086704000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345088162000-105</Id><Title>Wimp surrogates still lying</Title><Msg>"MSNBC host Chuck Todd and Iowa Gov. Terry Branstad (R) butted heads on Wednesday after Branstad accused President Barack Obama of undermining welfare reform. “The biggest problem I think a lot of people have is the massive expansion of the food stamp program,” Branstad said. “We have more people on food stamps than ever before. They’ve liberalized the rules and a lot of people think they need to tighten that up — just like we reformed welfare in the 1990s, now the Obama administration is trying to undo the work requirement. We think that we need to, instead of trying to put more people on –” “Well, wait a minute,” Todd interrupted. “Gov. Branstad, I can’t let that go. They haven’t done that. They haven’t undone the work requirements… Where did you get your information?” But Branstad insisted it was “absolutely true” that the Obama administration had waived the work requirement in the Temporary Assistant for Needy Families (TANF) program. He said liberals and President Barack Obama had “always hated” the work requirement in the law. “Every charge that has been leveled about this welfare reform order that this President signed — every accusation that has been leveled by some Republicans have been proven to be not true,” Todd said. The Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) last month encouraged states to experiment with better ways to administer the TANF program, informing state officials that the department was willing to grant waivers to states that wished to opt-out of provisions of the welfare law. Romney and other Republicans have claimed that the waivers were an attempt to undermine the welfare program’s work requirement. But PolitiFact rated those claims “Pants on Fire,” noting that the waivers were actually “designed to improve employment outcomes.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345088162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345088439000-106</Id><Topic><Title>Wimp surrogates still lying</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345088162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:36:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This one's ignorant to boot! Romney Adviser ‘Embarrassed’ He Doesn’t Know When Romney Would Balance Budget, But Shouldn’t Be Source: Think Progress Romney Adviser ‘Embarrassed’ He Doesn’t Know When Romney Would Balance Budget, But Shouldn’t Be By Aviva Shen on Aug 15, 2012 at 5:18 pm Senior Romney adviser Ed Gillespie was caught off guard Wednesday when CNN’s Wolf Blitzer asked him how long Romney’s budget proposal would take to balance the national budget: BLITZER: How many years would it take for the Romney budget to result in a balanced budget? GILLESPIE: Uh…Wolf, I’m not sure of that myself, actually. I’ll get that to you though and I’m sure it’s on our website. I should know it and I’m embarrassed on your air that I don’t have that number at the top of my head. I didn’t know we were going to talk about that today. I apologize. I should have prepared for that question. I didn’t know you were going to ask.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345088439000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:40:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345088747000-107</Id><Topic><Title>Wimp surrogates still lying</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345088162000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:36:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney steps away from Paul Ryan's Medicare cuts Source: LA Times COLUMBUS, Ohio – Mitt Romney on Wednesday unequivocally disavowed more than $700 billion in Medicare spending cuts proposed by his new running mate, Rep. Paul D. Ryan of Wisconsin. --- “First of all, Congressman Ryan has joined my campaign, and his campaign is my campaign now, and we’re on exactly the same page,” Romney said in response to anchor Anthony Mason’s question. “And my campaign has made it very clear: The president’s cuts of $716 billion to Medicare – those cuts are to be restored if I become president and Paul Ryan becomes vice president.” --- Ryan’s plan to revamp Medicare – which included Obama’s $716 billion in cuts to the projected growth of Medicare – was a central feature of a federal budget proposed by the congressman and passed by the Republican-controlled House in April. Romney has said he would sign it as president. The voucher system would begin in 10 years. --- In his 59-point economic plan, Romney praised Ryan’s Medicare plan, saying it “makes important strides in the right direction by keeping the system solvent and introducing market-based dynamics.” Romney’s economic plan says the Republican presidential candidate would share Ryan’s objectives on Medicare, but that his own revamping of the program would differ in unspecified ways. --- The Obama cuts, which are aimed at financing some of the president’s healthcare program, reduce reimbursements for hospitals and other care providers, but do not directly affect coverage of care for the elderly.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345088747000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:45:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345089312000-108</Id><Title>Aussies just figuring it out!!</Title><Msg>Wed Aug 15, 2012, 07:40 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) Source: The Guardian Leading Australian politicians and former defence chiefs are demanding an independent investigation, along the lines of the Chilcot inquiry in Britain, into their country's role in the invasion of Iraq. They say an independent inquiry must investigate the circumstances that led the then National-Liberal coalition to participate in the US-led invasion in 2003 in which Australia contributed 2,000 troops, including special forces. It must also conduct a review of the war powers of the government, and draw lessons for the future. Demands for an inquiry are led by former Liberal prime minister, Malcolm Fraser, former defence secretary, Paul Barratt, and former chief of the Australian Defence Force, General Peter Gration. Read more: http://www.guardian.co.uk/world/2012/aug/15/australian-politicians-inquiry-iraq-invasion If Australia were still a penal colony, this story headline would read: Australia indicts Bush!</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1345089312000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345089457000-109</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan Has No Job Experience</Title><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1344971364000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting how the board Log Cabin morons avoid the original post. Ryan has no job experience. They've been hammering Obama on that issue for years now. While Ryan has even less experience. He been a socialist s/lut living on taxpayers his entire career.</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1345089457000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-15 23:57:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>