<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354599185519-1</Id><Title>Unethical and Potential Account Violations by E*TRADE</Title><Msg>I am writing this to request input/suggestions on a recent problematic transaction made by E*TRADE, and to see if others have been similarly impacted. I am a Platinum IRA customer who had November options expiring on 11/16/12. On that day I had two orders in to sell the option, one of which was at the bid price. At 4:00 PM I tried to place an order to sell at market, however it does not even show up. On Tuesday 11/20 at about 11:00AM I received a call from E*TRADE indicating that my IRA account had a negative balance and they would be liquidating the position purchased via the option at 2:00PM if I did not do so by then. I questioned how could I have a negative balance in an IRA account since I did not have a margin account, could not sell uncovered options , could never make any purchase which would put me even a dollar over my available funds, etc. I was told that since the stock for which I had an option on was two cents in the money they exercised the option. When questioned why they would exercise the option when I had orders in to sell it, I had no money to pay for the stock in my IRA, it was only two cents in the money, I was a Platinum customer who received numerous sales calls but heard nothing about the exercise, why I was first being advised three days after it being exercised, etc. I was advised by numerous representatives and a supervisor that E*TRADE was 100% correct and could exercise the option, put my IRA account into a negative position, and sell my shares. It appears that E*TRADE sold my shares at 2:40PM not the 2:00PM several people advised they would. Between 2:00 AND 2:40 the stock declined further. A day or two later I realized they did not sell the entire position, but about 75% to cover the negative balance….while the stock declined further. I spoke to several representatives to resolve the situation but was initially only offered $150 and one hundred free trades (excluding option orders) if I would maintain my account with them. I told the representative that I would not agree to keep the account there and the offer was withdrawn. I was advised that they would escalate the matter to four senior offices and get back with me and to hold off moving the account since they would make me whole. On Friday 11/30 the matter was still not resolved so I told the representative I’m moving my account. He indicated to wait another day or two and he would go back to senior management. I told him I was concerned that if I didn’t move my account now it would be in flux prior to the expiration of some December options. I WAS ADVISED THAT IF I POSTPONED MOVING MY ACCOUNT ETRADE WOULD MEET THE LOWEST PRICED OPTION PRICING TO ENSURE I COULD EXERCISE MY DECEMBER OPTIONS PRIOR TO TRANSFER. I agreed based on the guarantee provided. Today, 12/4/12, I was called and offered $500 if I opened another account and 100 free non-option trades to resolve the matter. I indicated that was unacceptable and the rep. who promised to meet the pricing of the lowest competitor re: the sale/rolling over of my December options said that since I’m moving my account “I will not pay anything out of my commissions to help you”. Bottom line…..he outwardly lied to me. Has anyone experienced this type of situation? Also, while I have a list of many regulatory agencies, government officials, business channels, and social networks to contact, does anyone have any other thoughts on who I may contact? Thanks!</Msg><Username>bgood12338</Username><Timestamp>1354599185519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 00:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354635185328-2</Id><Topic><Title>Unethical and Potential Account Violations by E*TRADE</Title><Username>bgood12338</Username><Timestamp>1354599185519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 00:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My issue is that they exercised an option in a IRA account with no cash balance, which after speaking with six other firms is not allowed. If no funds are available inan IRA, they must either sell the option or let it expire. Do yu have any information indicating that is not the case in an IRA account? Thanks for responding.</Msg><Username>bgood12338</Username><Timestamp>1354635185328</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 10:33:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354647149876-3</Id><Title>I like the cliff</Title><Msg>I am with Govenor Dean, lets all go over the cliff together...cuts across the board, tax increases on everyone and especially the rich...hey, a lot of the so called rich voted for the man who wants to rise their taxes... On three, lets hold are collective noses and jump! Might want to buy some PUTS on the SPX for good measure.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1354647149876</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 13:52:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354668701641-4</Id><Topic><Title>Unethical and Potential Account Violations by E*TRADE</Title><Username>bgood12338</Username><Timestamp>1354599185519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 00:33:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have tried to buy an option at the Ask Price before only to see the ask get moved up away from my Entered Order!... That was back when everything was rum through Kenny Boys' Citadel. I couldn't believe my eyes when it happened Twice! I have Never touched an option through Etrade Again!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1354668701641</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-04 19:51:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>