<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350620889300-1</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT'S DIARY</Title><Msg>Thu Oct 18, 2012 at 06:00 PM PDT The Chronicles of Mitt: Oct 18, 2012 by Hunter pen on paper: 'Dear diary' Hello, human diary. It is I again, Mitt Romney, your better. I am very angry with my advisers today, Mr. Diary. Turning on the television today, I have heard nothing but my staff, surrogates, and assorted other hangers-on discussing my opinions on various issues. Ed G. apparently told the press I did not support a certain bill regarding wages for females. He then stated I did support it. Then another staff member said I mostly did, but partly did not. Then someone else said I did not, but that I supported the principle of it, or at least the part of the principle that I did support but not the part that I did not support. This is why I do not watch the television very often. I finally could take no more of it, and summoned my staff and advisers for an urgent conference call, which I used to angrily demand members of my campaign stop claiming to the press that I had opinions on various important issues facing the nation. I do not have opinions on various important issues facing the nation, I am running for office for Pete's sake. I do not remember ever expressing an opinion on any issue, I reminded them, other than wealthy Americans like myself deserve a large tax cut. And by tax cut, I currently mean that it would not be a tax cut, but merely an adjustment of the rates of various taxes in such a way as to achieve no actual tax cut, unless by coincidence a wealthy American happened to have most of their income invested in the various places that I intend to cut taxes. So it is not even accurate to say that I support lowering taxes, because I do not, I merely favor a multivectored tax adjustment that will accomplish nothing in particular. I then sent my staff out with the instruction that my opinion on very large tax cuts that will not cut taxes is the only issue that they may state I have an opinion on. I am beginning to fear all of these people are as dull as the commoners are. It is true that none of them are as wealthy as I am, but still—many of them are at least slightly wealthy. One would think they would be able to keep track of these things.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1350620889300</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 00:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350622075408-2</Id><Title>A Little Knowledge Is Dangerous</Title><Msg>In May 2009, my son was in a horrific accident, 3 months in intensive care, and I made some investments for him, forseeing a long recovery. Etrade was one of them, it was $1.50#$%$ the time, , and although I knew about the mortgage end of the business, i figured they'd work it off over time (18 months I thought). Also, given that Citadel had come to their rescue, I figured they had the backing of a pretty smart hedge fund. Well............I was wrong on all points. The bad bank side was far worse than I thought, we are now down to 90 cents/sh (pre-reverse split), and Citadel really hasn't done much for shareholders except for themselves as they probably short the stock. Today's $50 million debacle was a shocker, and eye opener for me. And, to make it worse, a failed CEO walks away with a $13 million severance package. That's the worst stick in the eye. I simply didn't understand the complexities or severity of these bank bad lending issues, a little knowledge is dangerous. Thankfully,.I made some good investments too for my son, and it looks like Etrade is going to be nothing more than a tax loss writeoff against those profits. Lessons learned.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1350622075408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 00:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350649388320-3</Id><Title>SELL SELL Delinquent Loans Portfolio still HUGE!!!!! $7.50 Coming!! ANALIST Downgrades Coming $7!</Title><Msg>Watch</Msg><Username>fuhcitichien</Username><Timestamp>1350649388320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 08:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350659118281-4</Id><Title>Report totally sucks, but didn't some insiders recently buy???</Title><Msg>That is the only positive I see for the near/mid-term. That $50MM "oops" was totally effing #$%$, but I can't believe they would buy thinking the future was not bright. Then again...these clowns have been screwing this up for 3 years now. Damn...I am just hoping to get an offer of $10 on a buyout so I can offset some of the bleeding. Yesterday was a hatchet job. Almost as bad as a drive by.</Msg><Username>max_gain_etfc</Username><Timestamp>1350659118281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350660118218-5</Id><Title>Obama officially wants America to be weak cut and paste link</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/mbview/threadview/?&amp;bn=d2eca4c5-5b34-3610-ab26-099a8670910a&amp;tid=1350442566169-3a110fa8-dca0-47e0-8f3f-6403d2996d9c&amp;tls=la%2Cd%2C3</Msg><Username>rivalmoney</Username><Timestamp>1350660118218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350660400613-6</Id><Title>Programs Helping Big Guys Bail</Title><Msg>Loks like large firms are using computers to assist them in bailing at mininmal loses. Litle guys have no chance.anymore.</Msg><Username>mtpocket</Username><Timestamp>1350660400613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:26:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350660702349-7</Id><Topic><Title>Obama officially wants America to be weak cut and paste link</Title><Username>rivalmoney</Username><Timestamp>1350660118218</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:21:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is an understatement, that link says he does not even understand the situation and he wants America defenseless</Msg><Username>dripshark</Username><Timestamp>1350660702349</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 11:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350664117465-8</Id><Title>long term buy</Title><Msg>based on the trends in the write downs and the size of their mortgage portfolio I figure Etrade needs to set aside another billion dollars for bad mortgages in the next 5 years. They are going to on average set aside 70 million a quarter for the next few quarters and at the end of 5 years I figure they'll be down to 20 to 30 million. It's a long slog but at the end of 5 years thy'll be making at least $1 a share.</Msg><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350665951030-9</Id><Title>Major Downgrades Will Come!! $7 is coming!!!</Title><Msg>I think ETFC is half-toasted and will sink big again next week to low $7s with analysts major downgrades!!! Wait until I give you a "Buy" signal!! Now is "Strong Sell"!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350665951030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350666268958-10</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They'll probably make at least 2 billion over the 5 years (they are currently grossing a little more than 400 million a year before write downs) before the 1 billion of write downs.. More if interest rates go up and trading volumes return to historic levels</Msg><Username>dpsheehy</Username><Timestamp>1350666268958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350668836984-11</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile, ETFC will have 2 Reverse Stock Splits.... After 5 years, ETFC will be still trading at $7 per share with 2 R/S/S. Good Luck!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350668836984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:47:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350669027754-12</Id><Title>Sell-Offs Continue Next Week!! Don't Buy!!</Title><Msg>ETFC has to hit low $7s first before stabilizing again... Major sell-offs will continue for a while even as market seems negative with not-so-good earnings..... Don't buy!! Sell if you can now!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350669027754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350669543652-13</Id><Topic><Title>Sell-Offs Continue Next Week!! Don't Buy!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350669027754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree! Hard to find a reason at all to buy with management that doesn't even know they are short 50 million in bankruptcies. What is the CFO paid for? Sounds lik e fraud? Where is the sec? Why are these yokels still working and why are they not saying. Ho didn't report on time? Stinks just like the management! IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1350669543652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350670207450-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sell-Offs Continue Next Week!! Don't Buy!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350669027754</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 13:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huge "Sell-Offs" next week!!! Maybe next Monday will become a "Black Monday"!!!! Sell everything today!!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350670207450</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350670353033-15</Id><Topic><Title>Major Downgrades Will Come!! $7 is coming!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350665951030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you the same st_loon_2000 that chirps non-stop about "...close today at $10...", "...strong buy until $9.50...", etc. I am amazed you still have two nickels to rub together. My guess is you have bought at the high and have sold at the low. Give it a rest.</Msg><Username>whistlerbc3peat</Username><Timestamp>1350670353033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:12:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350670660039-16</Id><Topic><Title>Major Downgrades Will Come!! $7 is coming!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350665951030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. I am not the same person.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350670660039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350670754335-17</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even if it did make $1 normalized eps 5 years from now, that put the value at $10-12 max in 5 years (no one would pay more than 10x-12x earnings for this trash playing in a deteriorating brokerage market). At todays price that would give you a 3.5%-8.2% annualized return on this pos investment. In other words, what kind of a buy is this??? Dont touch this trash until it touches $5 in a year or so.</Msg><Username>skiselev81</Username><Timestamp>1350670754335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350670822192-18</Id><Title>$8.55 and continue dropping.... Black Monday is coming!!!!</Title><Msg>Looks like ETFC will close under $8.40 today and will hit $7s next week!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350670822192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350671172674-19</Id><Topic><Title>Major Downgrades Will Come!! $7 is coming!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350665951030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:59:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>E*Trade Financial (ETFC) was downgraded by Wells Fargo (WFC) from outperform to market perform with a price target of $9 to $10, after it missed EPS estimates. Shares are lower by about 8.7 percent. Marvell Technology Group (MRVL) was downgraded by Oppenheimer (OPY) from buy to hold with a price target of $9 after it missed earnings this quarter and the fact that the CFO left the company. Shares are lower by about 14 percent.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350671172674</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:26:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350671395879-20</Id><Topic><Title>$8.55 and continue dropping.... Black Monday is coming!!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350670822192</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:20:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is sinking........... DOW will sink 20~30% in a year!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350671395879</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350671550692-21</Id><Title>$8.46 and sinking fast!!!!!! Get out!!!</Title><Msg>ETFC is like a Titanic ship..... It will continue sinking...... Get out!!!!!! $5 is on the horizon!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350671550692</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:32:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350671780985-22</Id><Title>perhaps $7's today?</Title><Msg>wow what a disaster!!! I think KG will finally give up this time, its over. That should take it to $5 in the near term.</Msg><Username>skiselev81</Username><Timestamp>1350671780985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350671965730-23</Id><Title>Just spiffy</Title><Msg>They managed to set their recovery back by three quarters. Wonderful. At least I got some cheep shares out of it.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1350671965730</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350673470941-24</Id><Topic><Title>Military Donations Much Higher for Obama, not Draft Dodger Mittens</Title><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1350596773721</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-18 17:46:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Yeah, and in 2008, Bush said the economy was just fine** That's ancient history...were you freezed dried or doing hard time</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350673470941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350673550174-25</Id><Title>Lifetime Democrat Endorses Romney</Title><Msg>After a lifetime of voting for and supporting Democrats — and even declining appointment to the U.S. Senate from a Democratic governor — Lee Iacocca Thursday endorsed Republican Mitt Romney for president.</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350673550174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350673596721-26</Id><Topic><Title>perhaps $7's today?</Title><Username>skiselev81</Username><Timestamp>1350671780985</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:36:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simply laughable. I bet they use hand puppets with each other during conference calls. Estimates lowered to .09 cents and they LOSE .10 cents. Are they so stupid to not see there is zero credibility with them by the investment community?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1350673596721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350673718751-27</Id><Title>President Romney is beating Obama.in all polls</Title><Msg>PA: R 49% O 45%... VA: R 50% O 47%... FL: R 51% O 46%...</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350673718751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350674418506-28</Id><Title>Salt Lake Tribune endorses BO</Title><Msg>Too many Mitts Obama has earned another term First Published 56 minutes ago • Updated 28 minutes ago Nowhere has Mitt Romney’s pursuit of the presidency been more warmly welcomed or closely followed than here in Utah. The Republican nominee’s political and religious pedigrees, his adeptly bipartisan governorship of a Democratic state, and his head for business and the bottom line all inspire admiration and hope in our largely Mormon, Republican, business-friendly state. But it was Romney’s singular role in rescuing Utah’s organization of the 2002 Olympics from a cesspool of scandal, and his oversight of the most successful Winter Games on record, that make him the Beehive State’s favorite adopted son. After all, Romney managed to save the state from ignominy, turning the extravaganza into a showcase for the matchless landscapes, volunteerism and efficiency that told the world what is best and most beautiful about Utah and its people. Photos In short, this is the Mitt Romney we knew, or thought we knew, as one of us. Sadly, it is not the only Romney, as his campaign for the White House has made abundantly clear, first in his servile courtship of the tea party in order to win the nomination, and now as the party’s shape-shifting nominee. From his embrace of the party’s radical right wing, to subsequent portrayals of himself as a moderate champion of the middle class, Romney has raised the most frequently asked question of the campaign: "Who is this guy, really, and what in the world does he truly believe?" The evidence suggests no clear answer, or at least one that would survive Romney’s next speech or sound bite. Politicians routinely tailor their words to suit an audience. Romney, though, is shameless, lavishing vastly diverse audiences with words, any words, they would trade their votes to hear. More troubling, Romney has repeatedly refused to share specifics of his radical plan to simultaneously reduce the debt, get rid of Obamacare (or, as he now says, only part of it), make a voucher program of Medicare, slash taxes and spending, and thereby create millions of new jobs. To claim, as Romney does, that he would offset his tax and spending cuts (except for billions more for the military) by doing away with tax deductions and exemptions, is utterly meaningless without identifying which and how many would get the ax. Absent those specifics, his promise of a balanced budget simply does not pencil out. If this portrait of a Romney willing to say anything to get elected seems harsh, we need only revisit his branding of 47 percent of Americans as freeloaders who pay no taxes, yet feel victimized and entitled to government assistance. His job, he told a group of wealthy donors, "is not to worry about those people. I’ll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives." Where, we ask, is the pragmatic, inclusive Romney, the Massachusetts governor who left the state with a model health care plan in place, the Romney who led Utah to Olympic glory? That Romney skedaddled and is nowhere to be found. And what of the president Romney would replace? For four years, President Barack Obama has attempted, with varying degrees of success, to pull the nation out of its worst financial meltdown since the Great Depression, a deepening crisis he inherited the day he took office. In the first months of his presidency, Obama acted decisively to stimulate the economy. His leadership was essential to passage of the badly needed American Recovery and Reinvestment Act. Though Republicans criticize the stimulus for failing to create jobs, it clearly helped stop the hemorrhaging of public sector jobs. The Utah Legislature used hundreds of millions in stimulus funds to plug holes in the state’s budget. The president also acted wisely to bail out the auto industry, which has since come roaring back. Romney, in so many words, said the carmakers should sink if they can’t swim. Obama’s most noteworthy achievement, passage of his signature Affordable Care Act, also proved, in its timing, his greatest blunder. The set of comprehensive health insurance reforms aimed at extending health care coverage to all Americans was signed 14 months into his term after a ferocious fight in Congress that sapped the new president’s political capital and destroyed any chance for bipartisan cooperation on the shredded economy. Obama’s foreign policy record is perhaps his strongest suit, especially compared to Romney’s bellicose posture toward Russia and China and his inflammatory rhetoric regarding Iran’s nuclear weapons program. Obama’s measured reliance on tough economic embargoes to bring Iran to heel, and his equally measured disengagement from the war in Afghanistan, are examples of a nuanced approach to international affairs. The glaring exception, still unfolding, was the administration’s failure to protect the lives of the U.S. ambassador to Libya and three other Americans, and to quickly come clean about it. In considering which candidate to endorse, The Salt Lake Tribune editorial board had hoped that Romney would exhibit the same talents for organization, pragmatic problem-solving and inspired leadership that he displayed here more than a decade ago. Instead, we have watched him morph into a friend of the far right, then tack toward the center with breathtaking aplomb. Through a pair of presidential debates, Romney’s domestic agenda remains bereft of detail and worthy of mistrust. Therefore, our endorsement must go to the incumbent, a competent leader who, against tough odds, has guided the country through catastrophe and set a course that, while rocky, is pointing toward a brighter day. The president has earned a second term. Romney, in whatever guise, does not deserve a first.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1350674418506</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350674609652-29</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Romney will deliver a 'Teachable Moment' to Dumbo. IT IS OVER!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350674609652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350674662582-30</Id><Title>looks like lots of stocks headed back to retest bottoms</Title><Msg>the elections are making everyone freak out</Msg><Username>counter_insurgency_buff</Username><Timestamp>1350674662582</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:24:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350675724979-31</Id><Topic><Title>Lifetime Democrat Endorses Romney</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350673550174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:05:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ohhh it's Iacocca ! For second I thought homobobo woke up to a reality.</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1350675724979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350675809503-32</Id><Title>Fidel Castro had a stroke.</Title><Msg>Will Hussein Obomba declare a national day of mourning ?</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1350675809503</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:43:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350676421698-33</Id><Title>Last post on this board...I'm out after years of hope</Title><Msg>Sold at a huge loss. It will completely offset my huge gains in AAPL. What a dog and what a sad event as I had high hopes for this POS. But when management keep doing their same tricks and the BOD allows it and with the long-term negative views on ETFC, the downgrades today, interest rates staying low until 2014, etc. - it is time for me to hang it up. Good luck to all of the longs. I won't turn into one of those azzh0les who sells and comes back to the board and says this is going to BK, you should have sold, etc. Quite the contrary...I wish all of you good luck and I hope you get the buyout the long-time investors deserve. Good luck to all.</Msg><Username>max_gain_etfc</Username><Timestamp>1350676421698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:53:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350677023489-34</Id><Topic><Title>Last post on this board...I'm out after years of hope</Title><Username>max_gain_etfc</Username><Timestamp>1350676421698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:53:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you. to bad the board of directors are so incompetent that they keep hiring the worst of the worst to be ceo!! after 2 failures do you think they will ever find a good one? Problem is investors suffer for their failure to do the right thing!it would be better if they sell the company because after this last fiasco it shows management has NO CLUE!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1350677023489</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:03:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350677457128-35</Id><Topic><Title>Last post on this board...I'm out after years of hope</Title><Username>max_gain_etfc</Username><Timestamp>1350676421698</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:53:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck, I dumped RSH at a huge loss this year because their CEO lied about maintaining the dividend, and I wasn't alone there. With this one though I have to admit that all negative outcomes so far except the surprise due to the one loan servicing company were fairly predictable. I did except a bit better than we did this quarter, but I still think in the long term, as long as they get a CEO backed by a good CTO, they have a chance. If they keep making their site worse and worse, then they're going to go down the tubes to a competitor who offers better online tools.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1350677457128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350679360748-36</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMTD is trading at 15x earnings. $1 a share assumes their earnings before mortgage write downs and loan refi remains the same. I don't believe that is the case, their earnings should grow as much as AMTD's earnings do. Even if they only go back to what they earned in 2011 before writedowns they would be making 1.20 or more a share. At 15x earnings that is close to $20.</Msg><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350679360748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 16:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350681440675-37</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one will touch this POS to buy.... GLTY!! I expect further drops on Monday to high $7s and continue sliding down to low $7s.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350681440675</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:17:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350681901289-38</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney is beating Obama.in all polls</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350673718751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Noooooooooooooooooo !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>delusional_left</Username><Timestamp>1350681901289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 17:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350686520255-39</Id><Topic><Title>Too much bubbles on the Price.</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350502965792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-17 15:42:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It happened just like what I said. I got out at $9.50+ several weeks ago and I have no position in ETFC. I will not add until ETFC falls under $7.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1350686520255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350686612023-40</Id><Topic><Title>long term buy</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1350664117465</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 12:28:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no way ETFC deserves a similar multiple as AMTD first of all. One has a real management that understands its core business the other one is vehicle of wealth redistribution from the shareholders to the constantly rotating management team (nice revlving door as we call it). Second of all, the core brokerage business is in a really bad spot here. there is a severe oversaturation in the industry (there is going to be less demand for brokers as the population continues to get poorer). Therefore there has to be strong consolidation in the industry. It will first start with a wave of bankruptices of smaller brokers around the US (that wave has already started), followed by powerful multiple contraction as growth opportunities diminish, and lastly, end with a wave of large M&amp;A transactions as the stronger players scoop up the weaker ones at very low valuations. I argue this will unfold within the next 3-5 years. At that point I expect for the stronger players to trade at 10x-12x and weaker players have no earnings and be sold at 0.2x-0.3x book multiples. That is the likely scenario for this dog, to be acquired at 0.3x BV at $5-$6 per share. i've seen this and analyzed this before during the many years I've been an analyst. Nothing different here.</Msg><Username>skiselev81</Username><Timestamp>1350686612023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 18:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350689517460-41</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney is beating Obama.in all polls</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1350673718751</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 15:08:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are idiots who voted for the leaderless liar in '08 and there are still bigger idiots who will vote for the leaderless liar again. Doubtful you'd find much success trying to waterboard the stupid out of these people.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350689517460</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 19:31:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350691514198-42</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It might be prudent for someone to take inventory of the bath towels upon the first family's WH final departure.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350691514198</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 20:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350697805491-43</Id><Title>Government Grants for Perpetual Motion Machines</Title><Msg>all you have to do is donate money to the right political candidate</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350697805491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 21:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>