<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355205049335-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama offers to cut AFDC</Title><Username>grope_this_sportivo</Username><Timestamp>1355179878385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 17:51:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Simple math "? Didn't offer any math. A bunch of hot air, as usual. 2003 $374B 2004 $413B 2005 $319B 2006 $248B 2007 $161B - record $2.7T revenue. 2008 $454B 2009 $1.4T 2010 $1.27T - Obama signs extension for Bush's tax cuts for the rich!!! 2011 $1.56T 2012 $1.1T This is not math. Just numbers. It used to be unpatriotic debt accumulation when Obama was Senator from Illinois. So, accelerating deficit 3x times makes it somehow patriotic when he occupied Oval Office. Who do you want to prove with 1,2,3,4? It is math, but for kindergaten. What fiscal cliff? Just raise tax on evil rich and continue spending as usual. Oh! Another $150B stimulus and extend unemployment benefits. A president doesn't care, we are at the point of no return. But his math is apparently stuck on the kindergarten level. So is yours. It isn't what Obama's predecessor did or didn't do. It is what Obama did and does. Yeah. Playing politics.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1355205049335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 00:50:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355250991469-2</Id><Topic><Title>The worst cursed message board!!!</Title><Username>muyjk1</Username><Timestamp>1355239100087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 10:18:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMAHA, Neb. (AP) -- Online brokerage TD Ameritrade said Tuesday that the average number of client trades per day in November fell 10 percent from the prior-year period. But the company said that the average of 341,000 clients trades a day last month was up 3 percent from October. William Katz of Citi Investment Research said in a client note that TD Ameritrade's trading was a bit soft in November, coming in below his 350,000 estimate. The analyst said that the figure may have been hurt a bit by Superstorm Sandy, as about 25 percent to 30 percent of the daily average number of client trades come from the region where the storm hit. Still, Katz said that TD Ameritrade's trading remains generally sluggish and is below management's forecast for full-year trading between 355,000 and 410,000. TD Ameritrade said that total client assets were $475.1 billion as of Nov. 30. That's an 18 percent increase from a year earlier and a 1 percent rise from October. Average fee-based balances climbed 28 percent year over year to $99.4 billion. The balances were up 1 percent from October. Average spread-based balances rose 8 percent from the prior-year period to $79 billion. This was a 2 percent increase from October. Katz said that the results for client assets, spread- and fee-based balances were in line with estimates. Shares of TD Ameritrade Holding Corp. added 25 cents to $16.59 in midday trading.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1355250991469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 13:36:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355254613237-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama offers to cut AFDC</Title><Username>grope_this_sportivo</Username><Timestamp>1355179878385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-10 17:51:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a nick on a boulder. If they put some money into enforcement and started maxing out people who defraud these programs of any felony amount, then they'll be able to cut it further. Get caught trading credits for other crap, go to jail, buyer or seller, and the waste in the program will vanish.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1355254613237</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 14:36:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355257365432-4</Id><Title>Greetings From Michigan</Title><Msg>[waves American flag] Greetings from Illinois [waves Beretta}</Msg><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1355257365432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 15:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355287542850-5</Id><Title>Board</Title><Msg>with this bored :)</Msg><Username>tenor4</Username><Timestamp>1355287542850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-12-11 23:45:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>