<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346904032310-1</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats booed God and Jews</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346884674847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell da truth, only 60% of em booed Gawd &amp; Israel, and Gawd knows who they are. Israel may have a little problem though. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Jews vote 70% for Democrats. They know they're unloved, but, they can buy their support there and they know it. Da Pubs, on da other hand, praise em to no end, begging for their vote and money. Pubs wouldn't bother, but, they're usually desperate for votes and they'll be happy with da rich 30% who hate Gawd and Israel too. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1346904032310</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:00:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346905092894-2</Id><Topic><Title>MOO-shell Commie crapola!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346850440289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodentrat, Are you old and dumb or dumb and old? There are five guys in the Willard Mittin family and none of them have served in the military and this is outrageous. And you want to criticize the President! Give me abreak, you ignorant schmoo!!!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1346905092894</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346905269331-3</Id><Topic><Title>MOO-shell Commie crapola!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346850440289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My dear fellow, The truth as spoken by the First Lady will set you free!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346905269331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:21:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346906018390-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Lies Lies!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346792757451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will you in the heck splain what it is your yapping about??? The DNC convention is the most successful ever. No one was hiding anything from anyone. Many of the speakers received standing ovations and people were fired up. RNC convention was practically dead on arrival.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346906018390</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346906276493-5</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats booed God and Jews</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346884674847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer my dear, Are you phantacizing again - that's a no, no.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1346906276493</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346906276610-6</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats booed God and Jews</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346884674847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:37:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer my dear, Are you phantacizing again - that's a no, no.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1346906276610</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:37:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346927991321-7</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout Price Ranged at $12~15 Per Share!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346883678734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That number is strongly dependent on who the buyer may be. There are two parts to that hypothesis. 1) Scale, where TD would be the only potential candidate with one-for-one stock swap. Forget about Scottrade, they lack the capital to be a broker in the first place. And 2) For smaller players such as Fidelity or perhaps JPM, the stock could be worth significantly more.</Msg><Username>convergent_series</Username><Timestamp>1346927991321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 06:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346938522222-8</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout Price Ranged at $12~15 Per Share!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346883678734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait till they screw the investors with a shelf offering!!IMHO nothing but bad news here</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346938522222</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346939307857-9</Id><Topic><Title>Buyout Price Ranged at $12~15 Per Share!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346883678734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:21:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why the hell would they do that?</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346939307857</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346939813851-10</Id><Title>Moonie what's the problem here?</Title><Msg>The entire market is screaming higher and this turd is only up 6 pennies and could easily end up red very soon. No volume, no buyers, simply dead meat.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346939813851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346940437714-11</Id><Topic><Title>Moonie what's the problem here?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346939813851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Etrade has always been unpredictable intra day but it always seems to do what it's suppose to do relative to the overall market by the end of the day. Strong uptrend.</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346940437714</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:07:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346941579055-12</Id><Title>Thats what i'm talking about!!</Title><Msg>yeeeehaa</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346941579055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:26:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942464438-13</Id><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Msg>...and they trot out old Billy Clinton like a lawyer trying to defend his guilty client. If Obama was a coach broght into turn around a team, and after 4 losing seasons he would be fired...plain and simple. You Obama followers can't seem to come to terms with that fact. You are emotionaly attached and won't admit you made a mistake when you bought his hipe of Hope and Change. It is OK to let go.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346944507508-14</Id><Topic><Title>Moonie what's the problem here?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346939813851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you looked at the short interest here lately? As of 8/15 it was as high as I have ever seen it. 8/15/2012 11,572,277 7/31/2012 11,192,316 7/13/2012 9,747,035 6/29/2012 9,086,847</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346944507508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346944973740-15</Id><Title>GOP's witness protection program</Title><Msg>Mon Sep 3, 2012 8:44 AM EDT 37 Over the weekend, Bill Maher presented a worthwhile new rule about the Republican Party and its reluctance to acknowledge the most recent GOP president. "Republicans don't have to accept evolution, economics, climatology, or human sexuality, but I just watched a week of their national convention, and I need them to admit the historical existence of George W. Bush," Maher explained. "If your party can run the nation for eight years and then have a national convention and not invite Bush, Cheney, Rumsfeld, Colin Powell, Karl Rove, or Tom DeLay, you're not a political movement, you're the witness protection program." To borrow a Homer Simpson line, it's funny because it's true. Bush is the only former president from either party in 40 years to stay away his first national convention after leaving office, and for the most part, Republicans pretended he doesn't exist. But before the political world completely shifts its attention from Tampa to Charlotte, it's worth pausing to appreciate the fact that Bush and Cheney may be carefully hiding from public view, and the GOP may seem largely ashamed of them, but their influence hasn't faded at all. Who did we hear from at the party's convention? Prime time slots went to Bush's Secretary of State, Bush's brother, and Romney's running mate -- who voted for Bush's tax cuts, Bush's wars, Bush's Medicare expansion, Bush's Patriot Act, Bush's No Child Left Behind law, and Bush's Wall Street bailout. Politico ran a piece last week on who would likely join a Romney/Ryan cabinet, and according to campaign insiders, the vast majority of the choices would be Bush/Cheney veterans. Indeed, we don't even have to wait until after the election -- Karl Rove is pulling party strings behind the scenes, Dan Senor and John Bolton are top campaign officials, and loyal Bushies are helping run the campaign. What's more, Matt Yglesias looked for meaningful policy differences between Romney's agenda and Bush's, and couldn't find anything. Even Republican National Committee spokespersons concede a Romney administration would effectively be the same thing as a Bush administration, "just updated." We may not see Bush, and the party may now perceive Bush as the name that must not be spoken, but that doesn't mean he's gone.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346944973740</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:22:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346947117553-16</Id><Topic><Title>Moonie what's the problem here?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346939813851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Combine normally slow seasonal DARTs with an unexpected Mgt. shakeup and you could have expected an even bigger jump in shorts enthusiasm.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346947117553</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:58:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346949371942-17</Id><Title>Obama logic</Title><Msg>"Fathom the hypocrisy of a government that requires every citizen to prove they are insured, but not everyone must prove they are a citizen." Now add this: "Many of those who refuse, or are unable, to prove they are citizens will receive free insurance paid for by those who are forced to buy insurance because they are citizens." This makes perfect sense to Obama.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346949371942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950150899-18</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMFAO - your analogy of a president to a coach, and the US economy to a sports team shows how puny your understanding of national economics is. It also shows, as is true with most pubs, a vast, vast, inability to grasp what -9% gdp means.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346950150899</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950205421-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama logic</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346949371942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not true, you're amking this stuff up.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346950205421</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346950684655-20</Id><Title>reagan and gop logic..... the Bushcare mandate</Title><Msg>The Emergency Medical Treatment and Active Labor Act, 1986 reagan and gop senate created what became known as Bushcare at the ER ........... this act: requires hospitals to provide care to anyone needing emergency healthcare treatment regardless of citizenship, legal status or ability to pay. There are no reimbursement provisions. gop wants to defeat the ACA so the middleclass can continue to pay for Bushcare at the ER with higher health insurance premiums. Bushcare at the ER adds over $1500 a year to each family's health insurance. the hidden gop healthcare tax amounts to about 4% for a family making $40K, and about .003% for a romney type making $45 million.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346950684655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346951463185-21</Id><Title>low volume manipulation</Title><Msg>back to 8.50 sooner then 9 IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346951463185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346952053019-22</Id><Title>Bubba blows 'em away</Title><Msg>Thu Sep 06, 2012 at 07:32 AM PDT Media mostly applaud what may have been Bill Clinton's best speech ever (and that's saying a lot) by Meteor Blades Secretary of State Hillary Clinton in East Timor, watching former President Bill Clinton delivering keynote at the Democratic National Convention in Charlotte, North Carolina attribution: State Department Secretary of State Hillary Clinton in East Timor, watching former President Bill Clinton delivering keynote at the Democratic National Convention. Negative responses to Bill Clinton's speech in Charlotte Wednesday night were few and far between in the traditional media and major on-line media. Some got in some digs at President Obama by saying some version of the idea Clinton made a better case for Obama than Obama himself has done. The Washington Post collected numerous responses from its staff, including opinion writers in a section headlined: Say What: Bill Clinton makes case for Obama. Among the details: Dan Balz and Philip Rucker: Former president Bill Clinton delivered a spirited defense of President Obama’s handling of the nation’s struggling economy here Wednesday night, criticizing the agenda and philosophy of Mitt Romney and accusing the Republican Party of ideological rigidity and an unwillingness to compromise. [...] Clinton said the most important question voters should ask is what kind of country they want in the future. “If you want a winner-take-all, you’re-on-your-own, you should support the Republican ticket,” he said. “If you want a country of shared prosperity and shared responsibility — a we’re-all-in-this-together society — you should vote for Barack Obama and Joe Biden.” Naturally, Mitt Megaphone Jennifer Rubin found nothing good in the speech (though she admitted it was the best of the evening) and spouted remarkable claims such as: No empathy or bitten lip is shown for [people in poverty], or for the more than 8 percent of unemployed Americans (and millions more underemployed or who have stopped looking for work). Under the headline of Bill Clinton: Trust Me, the Jobs Are Coming, Josh Barro at Bloomberg wrote: Bill Clinton offered a brilliant and detailed defense of Barack Obama’s record on economic policy tonight. The speech was long and had almost bizarre levels of detail on job training, Medicare, Medicaid, welfare reform, and most every other major area of the federal budget. [...] The conventional wisdom is that Medicaid is a losing issue for the Democrats. But Clinton’s case for Medicaid is succinct, sympathetic and persuasive, and I expect to start hearing it more often. At Politico, John F. Harris and Jonathan Martin wrote How Bill Clinton does it: Some of the effective elements of Clinton’s address were impossible to miss—his ease on stage, the sheer theatricality of the performance. But Clinton scored in Charlotte for reasons that go beyond superficial style and reflect the essence of the Clinton political brand. The speech was a vivid illustration of why Clinton survived so many disasters in office, and, even 12 years out of power, remains more effective than most politicians of the succeeding generation. At the Weekly Standard, beneath the headline Clinton Delivers Bang-Up Address, Fred Barnes wrote: In his fondest dreams, President Obama couldn’t have imagined getting any more from Bill Clinton than he did last night at the Democratic convention. Rather than pull Obama toward his centrist policies, Clinton embraced Obama’s hyper-liberalism—at least for one night. Despite his well-known differences with Obama, Clinton made a stronger case for the president’s reelection than either Obama or his campaign have been able to muster. Joe Klein at Time on The Clinton Speech: Bill Clinton talks about policy–about the substance of governing–better than any other politician I’ve ever heard. He keeps it simple and he keeps it accurate. He can make Medicare as dramatic as warfare. He did a major demolition job on the Republican Party’s economic policy tonight. He held it to the light of the facts. And it crumbled, as those of us who follow these things knew it would. After all, we’ve had 30 years of data: supply-side economics don’t work, tax cuts for the wealthy are more likely to encourage the purchase of dressage horses than the creation of new jobs. He did Barack Obama a service tonight, but he also did his country a service by making crystal clear the baloney-slicing at the heart of the Republican argument. In a round-up piece headlined Democratic National Convention Night 2: Winners and Losers, Chris Cillizza at The Fix: He was the explainer-in-chief without seeming too preachy. He was full of Southern aphorisms without being hokey. And, perhaps most importantly of all, Clinton was quite clearly having a very good time — and he let it show. He adlibbed. He played with the crowd. He smiled and laughed. And, yes, he went on a little too long. Aaron Blake wrote Bill Clinton: The smiling assassin: Littered throughout Clinton’s speech were sharp jabs at the GOP. And each one of them was delivered with an easy smile on his face that belied the stark charges. At The New Republic, Tim Noah noted under the headline, Clinton is Better Than Obama at Explaining Why Obama is Better Than Clinton: The underlying awkwardness here is that Obama, even if he never gets re-elected, has already achieved more--simply by passing Obamacare—than Clinton did in eight years. In his speech, Clinton waited too long to make the health care argument for Obama's re-election, but when he made it, he made it intelligently and forcefully. Bill Clinton Forms Barack Obama's More Perfect Union wrote John Nichols at The Nation: It was a remarkable performance by a political wunderkind turned senior statesman. And it provided a powerful reminder that in the ex-president competition—and there is an ex-president competition—Bill Clinton has defeated George Bush, overwhelmingly. Where two weeks ago, Bush was the former president whose name dare not be spoken at his party’s national convention, Clinton was more than a revered elder returning to the warm embrace of his party’s convention: he was a defining figure.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346952053019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:20:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952572344-23</Id><Topic><Title>low volume manipulation</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346951463185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:11:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These lower volumes day after day seems more like consolidation before a breakout to me. 9+ tomorrow with good news and the conference coming up and a excellent CEO pick with a buyout state of mind will act as short term Catalyst before even better news at the next earnings call.</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346952572344</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346952732045-24</Id><Title>GOP assault on voters at taxpayers expense</Title><Msg>from the Dallas Morning News: WASHINGTON — Texas has now spent more than $2 million defending its law to require photo identification to vote and its redrawing of political boundaries, officials said after federal judges sided against the state in both cases last week. And taxpayers’ outlays will grow as Texas Attorney General Greg Abbott appeals both cases to the U.S. Supreme Court. -snip- Luis Vera, general counsel for the League of United Latin American Citizens, called the legal fight a “solid waste of money.” “It’s continuous, nonstop litigation, and each and every time the courts find that the Legislature intentionally discriminates against Latinos and African-Americans,” Vera said.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346952732045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346954171040-25</Id><Topic><Title>low volume manipulation</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346951463185</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:11:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ETFC will cross $9.10 tomorrow!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346954171040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346955479881-26</Id><Topic><Title>Moonie what's the problem here?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346939813851</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:56:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most likely someone hedging their position on the Kenny pop.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346955479881</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346955924658-27</Id><Title>Rapist Bubba</Title><Msg>Juanita Broderick, Arkansas Secretary of State for Rapist Bubba gave, under oath a horrific, violent testemony of Rapist Bubba RAPING HER!!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346955924658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346958138315-28</Id><Title>GOP again caught lying</Title><Msg>Disillusioned Obama Supporter In Romney Ad Is Actually GOP Staffer Pema Levy- Republicans debuted a new ad Thursday in which a frustrated former Obama supporter expresses her disappointment with the president. The only problem: The woman in the video is actually an RNC staffer. The new ad features Republican National Committee Director of Hispanic Outreach Bettina Inclan, who in the ad purports to be an average woman voter who supported Obama in 2008. She describes her disillusionment with the president in the ad as a romantic relationship gone awry. The RNC says its ad, which first appeared on television Thursday is not dishonest. Inclan began her current RNC post in January 2012, and has worked in Republican politics since well before Obama’s 2008 election. She did Hispanic outreach for Rick Scott’s 2010 Florida gubernatorial race worked on Capitol Hill for Rep. Lincoln Diaz-Balart (R-FL), Rep. Thaddeus McCotter (R-MI) and as national executive director of the Republican National Hispanic Assembly. In addition to this EPIC FAIL, she's talking to a chair!</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346958138315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346958225117-29</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan the COMMIE (per the gop mantra)</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346851573980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:26:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- Reagan's tax cut was the biggest in history too and much more drastic than tax increase a year later. - Reagan grew defense not government entitlements. - Reagan didn't create SS, FDR did. Reagan put an effort to save SS in order to keep the promise made by FDR's New Deal and headed to fail. Once created the SS program belongs to current and future generations of US citizens, it isn't up to US President to abolish it, it is rather any President responsibility to keep it running. Reagan didn't deliberately fail to protect Federal laws, Obama did. DOMA is just one example. You're making idiotic statements. Go back to school, learn what Comunisim is.</Msg><Username>formykidsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1346958225117</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346958724049-30</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's victims speak out</Title><Msg>September 5, 2012, 9:52 PM 5556 CHARLOTTE — Employees at three companies that went bankrupt after being taken over by Bain Capital spoke at the Democratic convention on Wednesday, accusing Romney’s firm of exploiting workers for profit. President Obama has spent months attacking Romney’s business career, which the Republican nominee has put at the top of his political resume, using stories from the companies whose laid-off workers were represented onstage. The most dramatic tale came from Randy Johnson, a former worker at Bain-owned Ampad in the 1990s, who described how the private equity group took over the company, fired its workers, then invited them to reapply for jobs with lower benefits. “What affected me most was having guys the age I am now come to my desk, and cry; guys who had nothing to fall back on,” Johnson said. Ampad eventually went bankrupt. But Bain made about $100 million off the deal through management fees and the sale of its stock. “I don’t think Mitt Romney is a bad man,” Johnson, a longtime Romney critic across multiple campaigns, told the audience. “I don’t fault him for the fact that some companies win and some companies lose. That’s a fact of life. What I fault him for is making money without a moral compass. I fault him for putting profits before people like me.” “But that’s just Romney economics,” he said. David Foster, a former steelworker at GST Steel in Kansas City, accused Bain of fatally damaging the company for its own gain. “When Romney and Bain took over the mill, they loaded it up with millions in debt — and within months, they used some of that borrowed money to pay themselves millions,” Foster said. “Within a decade, the debt kept growing and was so large the company was forced into bankruptcy.” GST’s story is more controversial. Romney claims he shouldn’t be considered responsible for it since it went under in 2001, and he says severed all day-to-day ties with the company in order to run the Olympics. But Romney’s name still appeared on numerous SEC documents from the period that referred to him as “sole stockholder, chairman of the board, chief executive officer and president,” which Democrats claimed was more than enough to tie him to the company’s actions. A former worker at Bain-owned medical supply company Dade Behring, Cindy Hewitt, recounted how the firm laid off workers and loaded the company with debt. It went bankrupt in 2002, while Romney’s firm collected $242 million in profits. The company later was bought and recovered under a new name. “When Mitt Romney talks about his business experience, remember — it is not experience creating good-paying jobs,” Hewitt said. “It is experience cutting jobs. It is experience shutting plants. It is experience making millions of dollars by making life tougher for hard-working Americans.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346958724049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959331747-31</Id><Topic><Title>MOO-shell Commie crapola!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346850440289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 09:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moo-Shell special 'repent' sessions...hmmm like the 'Killing Fields'. Freedom is NOT what Moo-shell is slingin'!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346959331747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959437887-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Lies Lies!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346792757451</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-04 17:05:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ly-apoolza tonight!!!! Composite frekazoid stories for some super rediculously too long belchola!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1346959437887</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:23:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959998446-33</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is funny though that THE ONLY president present at this GOP convention was the "invisible Obama". No matter how deep they dug - they could not find a GOP president or vice president that they would dare bring in front of the voters.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1346959998446</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346960082176-34</Id><Title>Seems like unlimited supply of shares @$8.85</Title><Msg>May be the top for the day?</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346960082176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346960133361-35</Id><Title>Lyin' Ryan's history of perfidy</Title><Msg>9/4/12 Since When Did Paul Ryan Become a Liar? By Jonathan Chait GLEN ALLEN, VA - AUGUST 17: Republican U.S. Vice Presidential candidate Rep. Paul Ryan (R-WI) speaks to supporters during a campaign rally at West Springfield High School August 17, 2012 in Springfield, Virginia. Rep. Ryan continued to campaign for the upcoming general elections. (Photo by Alex Wong/Getty Images) Who are you gonna believe -- me or your Ryan eyes? Those eyes... so blue... A week ago, Paul Ryan’s political assets included — alongside his chiseled torso, plainspoken Midwestern demeanor, and the unshakable loyalty of the entire Republican Party — a firm reputation for honesty among the mainstream media. That reputation has suffered a massive, swift erosion. News stories about his speech at the Republican National Convention focused on its many rhetorical sleights of hand. Over the weekend, the revelation that he dramatically misstated a marathon time added a crucial, accessible piece of evidence to the indictment. Now liberals are calling him “Lyin’ Ryan” — a nickname that, a few weeks ago, would have seemed silly, like “Wimpy Palin.” Now mainstream pundits are defending Ryan with versions of the “well, all politicians fib” defense. Given that this constituency was once portraying Ryan as unusually honest, this represents a huge retreat for his political brand. What happened? Here’s what has not happened: Paul Ryan did not begin telling an unprecedented series of lies that suddenly exposed a predilection for shading the truth. His marathon boast is certainly odd and may well be a deliberate lie, but it could also be a simple failure to recall. The New Yorker’s Nicholas Thompson, arguing for the prosecution, contends that “for someone who does run seriously,” missing a marathon time by as a vast a level as Ryan does is nearly impossible. On the other hand, given that the race occurred in 1990 and was Ryan’s only marathon, perhaps the explanation is that Ryan just isn’t a serious runner. And Ryan’s Tampa speech, while pretty dishonest, was not especially so by Ryan’s standards. Here you can see why Ryan must view the sudden attack of the truth squad so bewilderingly. Ryan has been saying things like this, and worse, all along. The bit where he sadly shakes his head and blames President Obama for the failure of the Bowles-Simpson deficit commission that Ryan killed himself has been a staple of the Ryan shtick for two years. Reporters usually bat their eyes and coo sympathetically. Now it has become evidence of his duplicity . Ryan seems to have fallen victim to circumstances he didn’t quite foresee. The Romney campaign has spent the last several weeks practically daring the national press corps to call out its lies. Well beyond the usual exaggerations of a national campaign, Romney has built its entire message around two accusations — “you didn’t build that” and “just send them a check” — that are obviously false. A day before Ryan’s speech, a Romney adviser told reporters, “We're not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers.” The media that had spent the last two and a half years nuzzling gently in Ryan’s lap had been prodded with sharp sticks and reacted in the predictable fashion, though probably not predictable to Ryan himself. The thing about Ryan is that he has always resided in a counter-factual universe. He is a product of the hermetically sealed right-wing subculture. Many of the facts taken for granted by mainstream economists have never penetrated his brain. Ryan burst onto the national scene with a dense, fact-laden attack on the financing of Obama’s health-care bill that was essentially a series of hallucinations, pseudo-facts cooked up and recirculated by conservative apparatchiks who didn’t know what they were talking about or didn’t care. His big-think speeches reflect the influence of fact-free conservatives and collapse under scrutiny. During the last couple of years, Ryan took his act to the big city, expanding beyond his Washington conservative movement base and pitching himself to a broader audience as a straight-talking avatar of fiscal responsibility. That he managed to pull off the feat was completely incredible. Ryan’s entire career had been rooted in the “Reagan proved deficits don’t matter” wing of his party, and he spent the Bush administration consistently pushing for even more fiscally irresponsible policies than even George W. Bush could bear, and then spent the Obama administration relentlessly killing any effort to ameliorate those deficits. The genuine Paul Ryan is a man deeply devoted to reducing tax rates for Job Creators, and staunchly opposed to universal health insurance and other social spending. He is not a deficit hawk. The tension between Ryan’s policy goals and the persona he crafted was strained to the breaking point. When the press corps finally applied even the slightest pressure to it, it immediately and inevitably snapped.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346960133361</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346960861658-36</Id><Title>"Land of opportunity" , maybe not so much</Title><Msg>Exceptional Upward Mobility in the US Is a Myth, International Studies Show from sciencedaily dotcom The rhetoric is relentless: America is a place of unparalleled opportunity, where hard work and determination can propel a child out of humble beginnings into the White House, or at least a mansion on a hill. But the reality is very different, according to a University of Michigan researcher who is studying inequality across generations around the world. "Especially in the United States, people underestimate the extent to which your destiny is linked to your background," says Fabian Pfeffer, a sociologist at the U-M Institute for Social Research (ISR). Pfeffer is the organizer of an international conference on inequality across multiple generations being held September 13 and 14 in Ann Arbor. "Research shows that it's really a myth that the U.S. is a land of exceptional social mobility." Pfeffer's own research illustrates this point based on data on two generations of families in the U.S. and a comparison of his findings to similar data from Germany and Sweden. The U.S. data come from the ISR Panel Study of Income Dynamics, a survey of a nationally representative sample that started with 5,000 U.S. families in 1968. He found that parental wealth plays an important role in whether children move up or down the socioeconomic ladder in adulthood. And that parental wealth has an influence above and beyond the three factors that sociologists and economists have traditionally considered in research on social mobility -- parental education, income and occupation. --- more at link</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346960861658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961086089-37</Id><Topic><Title>Rapist Bubba</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346955924658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope Rapist Bubba likes the heat! Hell is waiting...</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346961086089</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961593715-38</Id><Topic><Title>Rapist Bubba</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346955924658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sure he's very worried about Hades and not getting your vote.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346961593715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346961757077-39</Id><Title>Needs an illuminating public debate!!!</Title><Msg>Schumer: Senate should vote soon on Ryan budget Source: AP CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — Sen. Chuck Schumer says he wants the Senate to vote soon on the Ryan budget to put Republicans, including presidential running mates Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan, on the defensive. The New York Democrat told The Associated Press Thursday that another public discussion and vote, this time on the Senate floor, would force the Republican ticket mates and GOP congressional candidates to defend the proposal's changes to government aid to seniors and the poor. Said Schumer of Republicans: "Let 'em embrace it again."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346961757077</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346961760209-40</Id><Title>Needs an illuminating public debate!!!</Title><Msg>Schumer: Senate should vote soon on Ryan budget Source: AP CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) — Sen. Chuck Schumer says he wants the Senate to vote soon on the Ryan budget to put Republicans, including presidential running mates Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan, on the defensive. The New York Democrat told The Associated Press Thursday that another public discussion and vote, this time on the Senate floor, would force the Republican ticket mates and GOP congressional candidates to defend the proposal's changes to government aid to seniors and the poor. Said Schumer of Republicans: "Let 'em embrace it again."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346961760209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961950647-41</Id><Topic><Title>Seems like unlimited supply of shares @$8.85</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346960082176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope... God I hope tomorrows report is somewhat good</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346961950647</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:05:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346962178943-42</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What I do understand is that your blind devotion to a failed Presiedent is kind of creepy. It is the same principal rather its sports, business, or the economy, If you can't cut it your gone. Asked what he will do in his second term, more stimulus and government spending on infrastructure, which is his pay back to the public and private unions as before. He has no plan, has not past a budget since becoming President, and has no plan for out of control entitlement spending, and adds the mother of all entitlemets...Obamacare. BTW, good luck with that hip replacement when you need it.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346962178943</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346962389941-43</Id><Topic><Title>Needs an illuminating public debate!!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346961760209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell chuck to have another vote on Obama's budget...last time it did not recieve even one vote, not even chukies.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346962389941</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346962524537-44</Id><Topic><Title>Seems like unlimited supply of shares @$8.85</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346960082176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:34:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on the action of the broad market and financials in particular, don't you think this stock should be much higher? Low beta schw is creaming this today and bac is up 5%. When you drop from $16 to $7, you only get a bounce back to $8.85 with 300 S&amp;P points higher? Just seems set up to plunge to me. Shorts are all over this one.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346962524537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346963385555-45</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Jimmy Carter scheduled to give a speech on Democratic convention? I am sure he has a lot to share.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346963385555</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:29:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346963486552-46</Id><Title>Woman delegate threatens Romney</Title><Msg>I won't be surprised if she is not offered a speaking slot at the convention. She has all the quilifications, she a minority, and she ignorant. Secret Service looking into DNC delegate who wants to ‘kill’ Romney CHARLOTTE, N.C. — A spokesman for the Secret Service told The Daily Caller that the agency is aware of video showing a delegate at the Democratic National Convention expressing a desire to “kill” Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney. “We are aware of it,” Secret Service spokesman George Ogilvie told TheDC on Thursday. He said the department is “taking the appropriate follow-up steps” with the woman. Video surfaced on Wednesday of a woman identifying herself as New York delegate Julia Rodriguez telling The Blaze, “If I see him” — in reference to Romney — “I would like to kill him.” In the video, Rodriguez says she’s from Puerto Rico but she now lives in New York. She expressed her desire to kill the Republican nominee after saying “Romney will destroy this country.”</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346963486552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346963916616-47</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No what you simply fail to understand, because you do not grasp what -9% gdp means, is that we are actually in a pretty good place given how horrible, HORRIFIC the state of the union was when Bush left office . Here is a clue, if you add up the contraction %s of the 5 previous recessions, you stil do not get -9% gdp the fact that you pubs think this train wreck you created can be fixed in 4 years is laughable.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1346963916616</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346964048475-48</Id><Title>$9.10+ tomorrow!!</Title><Msg>A huge buying block of 157,500 at $8.86 in AH trading at 16:26. ETFC will rally into $9s from tomorrow!! $11~12 is coming within 3 months!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346964048475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:40:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346966169985-49</Id><Topic><Title>Woman delegate threatens Romney</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346963486552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's Fluke'd up!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1346966169985</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:16:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967174725-50</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ! They've been trotting out Reagan's corpse for the last 10 years !!!!</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1346967174725</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967174741-51</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ! They've been trotting out Reagan's corpse for the last 10 years !!!!</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1346967174741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967380715-52</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you notice not even one mention of the dreaded 'Bush' name ? Bush means failure.</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1346967380715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:36:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346968906368-53</Id><Topic><Title>$9.10+ tomorrow!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346964048475</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:40:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will have one more rally day tomorrow! Futures are up now and I expect Asia and Europe will follow US rally!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346968906368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:01:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346969825778-54</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heck, they trootted out the swimmer's corpse the other night at the Dem convention. Dead people can't make gaffs like good old Joe(ya'all)Biden.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346969825778</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:17:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346970666585-55</Id><Topic><Title>Needs an illuminating public debate!!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346961760209</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:02:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone know that "budget vote" was pure theater, NOTE THAT BOTH RESOLUTIONS WERE INTRODUCED BY GOP PARTISANS: By Jake Tapper May 16, 2012 6:48pm House and Senate Unanimously Reject Obama Budgets — Or Do They? The White House today reacted to news that representations of President Obama’s budget had been voted down by the House and Senate by decrying the introduction of the amendments, by Republicans, as “gimmicks.” “Gimmicks are not solutions,” White House press secretary Jay Carney emailed to ABC News. “The American people overwhelmingly support a balanced approach to our long-term budget challenges. That’s the approach the President supports. The sooner Republicans drop their intransigence and join the American people in supporting a balanced approach, the sooner Congress will be able to come together and reach a compromise.” Sen. Jeff Sessions, R-Miss., introduced a budget amendment representing the president’s budget request; the Sessions amendment was voted down 99-0. (You can read it HERE.) A similar effort from Rep. Mick Mulvaney, R-SC, was rejected in the House 414-0. Sessions told reporters that it was “stunning” that no one voted for the version of the Obama budget he put forward. “A sitting president of the United States, seeking reelection, can’t lay out a plan that will gain a single vote in the House or Senate for the financial future of America,” he said. “It speaks volumes While the Sessions and Mulvaney bills put forward the same topline numbers as those in the president’s budget, neither offered any specifics. The Sessions legislation was 56 pages long; actual budgets are closer to 2,000 pages long. Thus, a White House official said, the Sessions proposal was a “shell that could be filled with a number of things that could hurt our economy and hurt the middle class,” a White House official said. “For example, rather than ending tax breaks for millionaires his budget could hit the revenue target by raising taxes on the middle class and rather than ending wasteful programs, his budget could hit its spending target with severe cuts to important programs.” “This is the president’s budget,” said the top Democrat on the Senate Budget Committee, Sen. Kent Conrad of South Dakota, indicating the voluminous budget proposal President Obama offered. “This is what Sen. Sessions has presented as being the president’s budget,” he said, indicating the much slimmer document. “I think it’s readily apparent there is a big difference between the president’s budget, which I hold in my hands, and what Sen. Sessions has presented as being the president’s budget. This is not the president’s budget. So, of course, we’re not going to support it. It’s not what the president proposed.” The White House official said the Sessions and Mulvaney’s bills were mere GOP stunts to get Democrats on record opposing ‘the President’s budget’” as well as distracting from what the House Republican budget would do, which the official described as “protect(ing) massive tax cuts for millionaires and billionaires while making the middle class and seniors pay.” -Jake Tapper</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346970666585</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346972254646-56</Id><Title>Fox continues to deceive viewers</Title><Msg>"Another Fox News Contributor Isn't Disclosed As A Member Of Romney's Campaign ERIC HANANOKI Fox News contributor Elaine Chao has recently appeared on Fox Business to criticize Obama over the economy and push the falsehood that he stripped the work requirement from welfare. During these appearances, Fox didn't disclose that Chao is a national chair of Mitt Romney's presidential campaign. Fox News has made it a regular practice to not disclose some of its frequent guests' ties to the Romney campaign. In an August 2 press release announcing her appointment, Chao stated that she is "honored that Governor Mitt Romney asked me to serve as the national chair of Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders for Romney" and that "it will take new leadership to put this country on a path to prosperity and full employment." News Corp., the parent company of Fox News, recently nominated Chao to join its Board of Directors. Chao is married to Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-KY). Fox News contributors John Bolton and Walid Phares, and Fox regular Jay Sekulow, have all appeared on the network to criticize Obama without disclosing they're Romney advisers. Fox News contributor Pete Snyder is the chairman of the Republican Party of Virginia's 2012 coordinated committee. And Fox News contributor Karl Rove is the co-founder and adviser for the super PAC American Crossroads, which is spending tens of millions of dollars to defeat Democrats."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346972254646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:57:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346983870313-57</Id><Topic><Title>This stock capitalizes on a strong Dollar &amp; weak Euro, ETFC</Title><Username>luvr_n</Username><Timestamp>1345488854000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-20 14:54:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any company that doubles its revenues is worth a look IMHO</Msg><Username>tech.guy45</Username><Timestamp>1346983870313</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 22:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346988725100-58</Id><Topic><Title>Woman delegate threatens Romney</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346963486552</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:31:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Secret Service does not talk to an online rag such as the Daily Caller!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346988725100</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>