<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347509010795-1</Id><Title>Defining a conservative</Title><Msg>"The modern conservative is engaged in one of man's oldest exercises in moral philosophy... the search for a superior moral justification for selfishness. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347509010795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 00:03:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347514799861-2</Id><Topic><Title>Wing nuts turning on each other</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347496651018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wed Sep 12, 2012 at 05:48 PM PDT Joe Scarborough eviscerates Mitt Romney by Bonsai66 Wow! Just Wow. It looks like the flood gates have opened now that Mark Halperin has sanctified the CW among the villagers that Mitt Romney is toast. Joe Scarborough takes Romney to the woodshed this afternoon over at Politico. Voters who like moderates can’t trust him. Conservatives who are desperate for victory don’t believe him. And the election Republicans should be winning seems to be slipping further from their grasp. And that is about the nicest thing Joe has to say about Mitt in a very long opinion piece. More highlights beneath the fold. How can it be that this man who turned around countless businesses, saved the 2002 Olympics and ran Democratic Massachusetts like a pro be the head of such a disastrous campaign? Who was responsible for burying his moving convention video behind the bumbling bluster of Clint Eastwood? Who told Mr. Romney to issue a political broadside against the commander in chief the day after a U.S. ambassador was murdered? And who decided that Romney would use his general election campaign to stand for absolutely nothing? Ouch! It gets better. THE NATIONAL DEBT: The United States of America is racing towards an eventual default. And yet Mitt Romney refuses to lay out a plan to balance the budget before 2040. He doesn’t specify cuts, he doesn’t propose eliminating agencies and he doesn’t explain how his tax cuts will be offset. When it comes to balancing the budget, Mr. Romney has no plan. ... DEFENSE SPENDING: The U.S. military-industrial complex is bloated beyond belief, and yet all Mitt Romney can do is promise bigger budgets and longer wars. Today the United States spends more on its military than all other countries combined. This does not make America safer. This puts us deeper in debt and poses a far greater threat to America’s long-term health than Russia and China combined. Romney’s penchant for one-upmanship on seemingly every foreign policy issue that arises would stretch our military thin and limit our ability to neutralize real threats coming from countries like Iran. Ahhh. The long knives have now been unsheathed. And the lesson is clear: If we want to win the battle of ideas in the long term, we should be willing to face the fact that Mitt Romney is likely to lose — and should, given that he’s neither a true conservative nor a courageous moderate. He’s just an ambitious man. To sum up... Instead, we have a nominee who represents the worst of both worlds. Any swing voter attracted by moderate Republicanism can’t vote for a man who ran away from his core convictions. And conservative voters don’t believe Romney has any core convictions. This has all the makings of a Greek tragedy, all playing out on C-SPAN. Well, I guess that there is something that conservatives and liberals can finally agree on: We don't think that Mitt Romney has any core convictions either.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347514799861</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 01:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347538493910-3</Id><Topic><Title>whazzzzzzzz happening bored odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347498100971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:01:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would it be possible for you odumbomites try to get your bretheren across the pond to calm down....you guys do way too much recipe sharing</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347538493910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 08:14:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347542182662-4</Id><Title>QE or no QE?</Title><Msg>Anyone care to guess?</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1347542182662</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347543953619-5</Id><Title>easy to see that pugs are wrong about unions, teachers and quality of education</Title><Msg>The top rated public schools for science and math are NOT TEXAS and other red union hating states......... Texas is rated BELOW average......... here are the 2011 rankings: Well Above Average 1Massachusetts 2Minnesota 3New Jersey 4New Hampshire 5New York Above Average 6Virginia 7Maryland 8Connecticut 9Indiana 10Maine Average 11Florida 12Illinois below average 31 Texas 32 North Dakota far below average 49West Virginia 50Mississippi</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347543953619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347545767791-6</Id><Topic><Title>Wing nuts turning on each other</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347496651018</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Steve "The Bullet" Schmidt has said it best on Romney's smirking Libya statement ... Thu Sep 13, 2012, 08:13 AM "There are legitimate criticisms to be made but you foreclose on your ability to make them when you try to score easy political points. And the American people, when the country is attacked, whether they're a Republican or Democrat or independent, want to see leaders who have measured responses, not leaders whose first instinct is to try to score political points." If the man who chose Sarah Palin as McCain's running mate thinks you screwed up, well, ouch.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347545767791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347546357772-7</Id><Topic><Title>easy to see that pugs are wrong about unions, teachers and quality of education</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347543953619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2012 Top 20 High Schools - Look how TX dominates the top 20 - with barely a mention of any Northeast schools. That liberal "peanut butter" metric you posted is just the dumbing down of the smartest. Look at the list below - that is where the next generation of leaders will come from: Academy of Mathematics and Science in Kentucky Bowling Green KY S 100 4.7 100 2010 31.2 16 4.3 4.51 2 The School for the Talented and Gifted Magnet Dallas TX M 100 3.7 100 1810 27.7 32 3.1 3.33 3 Basis Scottsdale Scottsdale AZ C 100 3.1 100 1951 28.3 0 4.1 3.23 4 School of Science and Engineering Magnet Dallas TX M 100 3.8 100 1742 25.9 63 2.6 3.15 5 Basis Tucson Tucson AZ C, O 100 2.6 100 1932 30.3 0 3.7 2.71 6 Jefferson County International Baccalaureate School Birmingham AL S 100 2.2 100 1897 29.5 14 3 2.37 7 Signature School Evansville IN C, O, L 100 2.3 100 1811 27.2 9 3 2.34 8 Stanton College Preparatory School Jacksonville FL M, S, L 99 2.6 100 1824 27 15 2.8 2.33 9 Suncoast Community Riviera Beach FL M 100 2.6 97 1712 24.8 24 3.1 2.19 10 Thomas Jefferson for Science and Technology Alexandria VA S 100 1.9 100 2200 3 4.5 2.1 11 City Honors School at Fosdick -Masten Park Buffalo NY M 100 2.3 99 1771 25.4 31 2.8 2.01 12 School for Advanced Studies Miami FL S 100 2.4 100 1774 25.8 39 2.9 1.97 13 Andrew Carnegie Vanguard Houston TX S 100 2.1 100 1849 27.7 27 3 1.94 14 Uplift Education North Hills Preparatory School Irving TX C, L 100 1.8 100 1830 27 4 2.7 1.86 15 Pine View School Osprey FL S 100 1.7 100 1968 29.2 10 4 1.81 16 Maggie L. Walker Governor's School for Government and International Studies Richmond VA S 100 1.6 99 2084 29.7 0 4.2 1.78 17 Early College at Guilford Greensboro NC S 100 1.5 100 1930 29.5 7 4.3 1.77 18 Westlake Academy Westlake TX C, O, L 100 1.6 100 1758 27.1 1 3.5 1.72 19 Oxford Academy Cypress CA S 100 1.7 100 1903 28.6 28 3.4 1.68 20 Biotechnology Freehold NJ S 100 1.4 100 2001 28.1 3 5 1.62</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347546357772</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347546417511-8</Id><Title>HEY ROMNEY, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRASSING YOURSELF, WHERE ARE YOUR TAXES?</Title><Msg>"As a tax-paying, voting citizen of the United States of America, I demand that you show us your tax records to prove you are fit for consideration as our President. I doubt it will help you at all, though."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1347546417511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:26:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547138098-9</Id><Title>HEY DUMBO, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRESSING YOURSELF, WHERE IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?</Title><Msg>FELONY FRAUD! Why does your Connecticut issued Social Security number fail 'E-Verify"?? Who the 'F' are you??</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347547138098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347547832139-10</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DUMBO, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRESSING YOURSELF, WHERE IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347547138098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not the smartest cookie in the jar - are you qbike...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1347547832139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:50:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347547883317-11</Id><Title>Doing the Dipshidiot dance!</Title><Msg>September 12, 2012 Romney Fails the Commander-in-Chief Test. Again. If there were any lingering doubts about Mitt Romney's unfitness to serve as Commander-in-Chief, his shameful response to the killings of four Americans at a U.S. consulate in Libya should have put them to rest. Romney didn't know the facts. He didn't know the timeline of events. He didn't know who was responsible for the embassy breaches in Cairo and Benghazi. Yet even before Americans had learned of and could mourn their deaths, Governor Romney used their murdered countrymen to slander the President of the United States. When the proverbial 3 A.M. phone call came, Romney let it go to voice mail, where his pre-recorded message called the President "disgraceful" and charged that Obama "sympathize[d] with those who waged the attacks." Of course, it shouldn't have taken this appalling episode for Mitt Romney to disqualify himself in the eyes of so many. He long ago proved he lacks the judgment, temperament and steadfastness needed to guide the United States during times of crisis. Consider, in no particular order, the following examples: Thanks to multiple deferments, Mitt Romney avoided combat duty in the rice fields of Vietnam by instead serving his church in the tony 16th arrondissement of Paris. But while Time reported in 2007 that "he felt guilty about the draft deferment," during his Senate run in 1994 Mitt acknowledged "he did not have any desire to serve in the military during his college and missionary days." (Ironically, the mockery of France would become a centerpiece of Romney's planned campaigns against Hillary Clinton in 2008 and Barack Obama in 2012.) Regardless, four decades after his time in France, he told Iowa voters in 2007 that his own five sons had a higher calling than the U.S. armed forces in Iraq: "My sons are all adults and they've made decisions about their careers and they've chosen not to serve in the military and active duty and I respect their decision in that regard. One of the ways my sons are showing support for our nation is helping me get elected because they think I'd be a great president." And five years ago, would-be President Romney had a message about a potential nightmare facing the United States. Echoing Glenn Beck, Romney warned that "It's this century's nightmare, jihadism - violent, radical Islamic fundamentalism. Their goal is to unite the world under a single jihadist caliphate." And Romney's "they," it turned out, conflated virtually every Muslim, friend or foe, into one, undifferentiated threat: "But I don't want to buy into the Democratic pitch, that this is all about one person, Osama bin Laden. Because after we get him, there's going to be another and another. This is about Shia and Sunni. This is about Hezbollah and Hamas and al Qaeda and the Muslim Brotherhood. This is the worldwide jihadist effort to try and cause the collapse of all moderate Islamic governments and replace them with a caliphate." And asked about that "one person, Osama Bin Laden," Mitt Romney was of two minds. In late April 2007, he announced, "It's not worth moving heaven and earth spending billions of dollars just trying to catch one person." But just days later, Romney reversed course and declared of Bin Laden, "He's going to pay, and he will die." And thanks to President Obama, die he did. But during his first run for the White House, Mitt Romney opposed the very kind of unilateral U.S. strike in Pakistan candidate Barack Obama promised to carry out against Bin Laden and other high value Al Qaeda targets. Of course, after Bin Laden was killed, Romney repeatedly insisted "I think other presidents and other candidates, like myself, would do exactly the same thing." Put another way, if Mitt Romney gets that phone call at 3 A.M., he'd give you a different answer at 3:15. That was hardly Romney's first foreign policy turnabout. Four years ago Mitt Romney felt pretty good about killing Saddam Hussein, too. As Byron York noted, during a January 2008 GOP debate, Romney was asked, "Was the war in Iraq a good idea worth the cost in blood and treasure we have spent?" Mitt's response? "It was the right decision to go into Iraq. I supported it at the time; I support it now." But despite no new evidence in the intervening three years, by 2011 Multiple Choice Mitt was not so sure: "Well, if we knew at the time of our entry into Iraq that there were no weapons of mass destruction -- if somehow we had been given that information, why, obviously we would not have gone in." Amazingly, Al Qaeda never topped Mitt Romney's list of national security threats to the United States. In March 2012, Romney surprised both parties by declaring, "Russia is without question our number one geopolitical foe." (In 2010, a shocked Fred Kaplan skewered Romney's grandstanding, declaring, "In 35 years of following debates over nuclear arms control, I have never seen anything quite as shabby, misleading and -- let's not mince words -- thoroughly ignorant as Mitt Romney's attack on the New START treaty.") But just the month before, Romney wrote an op-ed titled, "How I'll Respond to China's Rising Power." The previous October, he told a GOP debate audience, "If you are not willing to stand up to China, you are going to get run over by China." Yet in October 2009, the Republican nominee in waiting penned another screed exclaiming: "Iran: Biggest Threat Since Soviets" And for years, Mitt Romney's line towards Iran has pretty much been whatever his friend and former Boston Consulting Group colleague Benjamin Netanyahu said it should be. But while Romney has crowed "we can almost speak in shorthand," those messages haven't worked out so well with the American public. After all, in 2007, Romney took up Bibi's campaign for U.S. pension funds to disinvest from companies doing business with Iran. Mitt's failed effort lasted exactly 24 hours, or about as long as it took the AP to document that his former employer, Bain &amp; Company, was profiting from deals with the mullahs in Tehran. Romney's response? "This is something for now-forward. I wouldn't begin to say that people who, in the past, have been doing business with Iran, are subject to the same scrutiny as that which is going on from a prospective basis." (In 2012, Americans similarly learned that Bain Capital, from whom Mitt Romney still earns millions annually, bought the video surveillance division of Chinese company that is a major supplier to the government in Beijing.) Governor Romney's on-going crusade demanding the United Nations indict Iranian President Mahmoud Ahmadinejad on war crimes charges hasn't gone much better. As Mother Jones detailed last year, there are a host of legal barriers to Romney's gambit. For starters, "U.S. policy has been to not honor the International Criminal Court; we are not a signatory to the Rome Treaty." And as MoJo reported: It's widely interpreted that a statement supposedly egging on genocide is not legally considered a tool of genocide, unless it can be taken into evidence as proving direct intent and premeditation. Furthermore, it would be unprecedented to indict a foreign leader for a genocide that hasn't even taken place yet. Regardless, Mitt Romney has insisted that "we must not allow Iran to have a nuclear weapon." And, he has said repeatedly, "If I'm president that will not happen. If we reelect Barack Obama it will happen." Apparently, that development would not only be more dire than the Soviet nuclear threat ever was, but one he said in June President Romney could militarily pre-empt without the authorization of Congress: "I can assure you if I'm president, the Iranians will have no question but that I will be willing to take military action if necessary to prevent them from becoming a nuclear threat to the world. I don't believe at this stage, therefore, if I'm president that we need to have a war powers approval or special authorization for military force. The president has that capacity now. I understand that some in the Senate for instance have written letters to the president indicating you should know that a containment strategy is unacceptable. We cannot survive a course of action which would include a nuclear Iran we must be willing to take any and all actions." That may seem like an odd position for Romney to be taking. After all, just three weeks ago one of top national security advisers Elliott Abrams called for Congress to authorize the use of force against Iran. And back in 2007, Romney gave MSNBC's Chris Matthews and his GOP debate audience a much different answer. Asked "if you were president of the United States, would you need to go to Congress to get authorization to take military action against Iran's nuclear facilities," Mitt answered: "You sit down with your attorneys." Five years later, Mitt Romney has instead promised, "I'd get on the phone to my friend Bibi Netanyahu and say, 'Would it help if I said this? What would you like me to do?'" And when he traveled to Jerusalem in June, Romney delivered on his pledge that "we will not have an inch of difference between ourselves and our ally Israel." With Bibi by his side, Mitt ignored U.S. policy about preventing Iran from actually building a nuclear weapon and instead endorsed Netanyahu's murkier red line "to prevent the ayatollahs from possessing the capability" to develop one. (That wasn't the first time this year that Mitt Romney flouted the long-standing convention that "politics stops at the water's edge." In June, Romney economic adviser Glenn Hubbard published an op-ed in Germany criticizing the Obama administration's position on austerity policies in Europe.) Of course, Mitt Romney would do better to formulate a position of his own on Afghanistan, a war about which he expressed only silence during his acceptance speech at the Republican National Convention. (His stunning June 2011 statement that "I also think we've learned that our troops shouldn't go off and try and fight a war of independence for another nation" left Democrats and Republicans alike confused.) Looking at the upheaval in the Middle East, Romney bizarrely suggested in July that the Arab Spring might never have happened had George W. Bush's "freedom agenda" not been prematurely halted by President Barack Obama. As for his continuing evolution on Libya, ABC News documented five different positions Romney has held. All of which is why, especially after his disgusting performance over the past 24 hours, Mitt Romney never the hold of the position of Commander-in-Chief of the United States of America.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347547883317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347548479040-12</Id><Title>Mitt Romney asked Paul Ryan for one decade of tax returns</Title><Msg>hu Sep 13, 2012 at 07:30 AM PDT by Jed Lewison Chart showing Mitt Romney has only released one tax return in last two decades. attribution: Hey, remember the tax return issue? It's back: As part of its vetting, the Romney campaign required at least some of the candidates on the short list—including the eventual winner of the GOP veepstakes, Ryan—to submit fully 10 years of tax returns, according to a knowledgeable source. Actually, this isn't just the tax return issue it's also the one set of rules for Mitt, another set of rules for everyone else issue. It's bad enough that Mitt Romney doesn't want to follow President Obama's lead and allow the public to see his tax returns. But by insisting on seeing the returns of his vice presidential candidates, Romney is implicitly acknowledging that even he thinks they are an important part of the hiring process for this job. And by not releasing that information to the public, he's implicitly acknowledging that he doesn't give a damn about the ability of regular Americans to make informed decisions about their vote this November. He only cares about himself. 7:30 AM PT: "For Mitt's VP vetters, 10 yrs tax returns were good for the goose, but they still won't give America a gander at HIS!" davidaxelrod</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347548479040</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:01:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347550239192-13</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DUMBO, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRESSING YOURSELF, WHERE IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347547138098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey birther billie, you go girl!</Msg><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1347550239192</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:30:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347551567735-14</Id><Topic><Title>easy to see that pugs are wrong about unions, teachers and quality of education</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347543953619</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 09:45:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the measure of a public school system is how it performs as a whole , and not that some have set up btw, a few schools that are top notch......this YEAR THE top HS in the USA is in NY ,see below. So, the list i showed ranked the USA PUBLIC schools from best to worst for science and math education.. AS A WHOLE, the quality of service it offers to ALL... and the ranking was done by scientists: Statistical Research Center at the American Institute of Physics and physicist Paul Cottle of Florida State University. The ranking i gave is verified by the SAT score rankings of the students from each state who go on to college: State Education Rankings: SAT Scores (Total) 5. Illinois: 1775 12. Oklahoma: 1703 44. Florida: 1475 45. Texas: 1467 State Education Rankings: SAT Scores Math Illinois Math SAT Score: 604 (Ranking 4) texas Math SAT Score: 506 (Ranking 38) it is also interesting to note that Texas also has one of the LOWEST per capital incomes of the states besides its below average public schools. here is THE top award winner in the USA this year: New York School Wins Top Honors at Intel Schools of Distinction Awards Nation’s Most Innovative Math and Science Schools Celebrated as Intel Schools of Distinction • Ossining High School from Ossining, N.Y. won the top award of $100,000 Press Release: Intel Corporation – Mon, Sep 10, 2012 WASHINGTON--(BUSINESS WIRE)-- Ossining High School in Ossining, N.Y. took top honors Monday in the Intel Schools of Distinction Awards. The Intel Schools of Distinction Awards recognizes K-12 schools that have some of the most successful educational programs in the country.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347551567735</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 11:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347552142452-15</Id><Title>Do you guy's think maybe</Title><Msg>If a video of an odumbomite male humping an odumbomite female on you tube could result in a mob of odumbomites rushing and attacking google headquarters...you know how sensitive they are about their sexuality..................</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347552142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:02:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347552275147-16</Id><Title>Romney Reveals Character With Deaths in Lybia</Title><Msg>U.S. ambassador from Davis, 3 other Americans die in Libya consulate attack. The horrific tragedy in Libya provides a crucial window into the readiness, competency and steadiness of Gov. Mitt Romney in his desire to become President. I believe his remarks expressing sympathy for those Americans killed were sincere but his naked politicization of President Barack Obama's foreign policy was shameful, and opportunistic.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1347552275147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347552670480-17</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DUMBO, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRESSING YOURSELF, WHERE IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347547138098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>q4bike, Kindergarden is next door - hurry, hurry, hurry ----------------------------</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1347552670480</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:11:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347556902931-18</Id><Topic><Title>Technical Chart Shows Upside on E*TRADE Financial Corporation</Title><Username>imaconnerley</Username><Timestamp>1347553453267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:24:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know - for once I would like to see such #$%$ "technical chart shows" actually say something that could be of value AHEAD of time. Seems to me like "technical charts" are showing upside on the SOLIDLY positive days, they show downward pressure on the days the stock is already in the gutter and, amazingly, show no upside or downside on the flat days. So please stop advertising this #$%$ we#$%$ite with these #$%$ "technical charts" because, quite frankly, my daily horoscope has more to say on that topic.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1347556902931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558185989-19</Id><Title>Is There Another CEO Etrade Can Fire?</Title><Msg>This beyotch rises like the Phoenix when KG fires people. Line up the exectuive team and fire them one at a time til it hits $25. Then fire some more......</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347558185989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347558788895-20</Id><Title>How's E*bank doing</Title><Msg>Does etrade still have the bank, last I heard it was to be mothballed..</Msg><Username>hellasmusic</Username><Timestamp>1347558788895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347558836599-21</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reveals Character With Deaths in Lybia</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1347552275147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Romney "jumps the gun" not knowing what happened following his comments. Obama though, knowing all details after tragic events in Lybia, same day continues raising money shooting at his his rival. Yeah, this guy is sooooooo compassionate! I am really impressed!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347558836599</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559068710-22</Id><Topic><Title>Do you guy's think maybe</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347552142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ah - look - returnusmaximus - the elite GOP member - had a thought of his own and felt the need to share.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1347559068710</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347559129676-23</Id><Topic><Title>HEY DUMBO, IF YOU'RE DONE EMBARRESSING YOURSELF, WHERE IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER?</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1347547138098</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 10:38:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP has decided that fact checking is un-American and never seems to make them look smart or honest. So they decided to boycott fact checking. Let's let Snopes set them straight anyway: snopes DOTCOM Home Politics Barack Obama Birthers Stolen Security Stolen Security Claim: Barack Obama uses a Social Security number belonging to man born in 1890. FALSE Example: [Collected via e-mail, June 2011] An investigation has revealed the identity of the man whose Social Security number (SSN) has been illegally used by Obama: Jean Paul Ludwig, who was born in France in 1890, emigrated to the United States in 1924, and was assigned SSN 042-68-4425 in or about March, 1977. Ludwig lived most of his adult life in Connecticut. His SSN begins with the digits 042, which are among those reserved for Connecticut residents. Obama never lived or worked in that state, so there is no reason for his SSN to start with the digits 042. Now comes the best part. Ludwig spent the final months of his life in Hawaii, where he died. Conveniently, Obama's grandmother, Madelyn Payne Dunham, worked part-time in the Probate Office in the Honolulu Hawaii Courthouse, and therefore had access to the SSNs of deceased individuals. The Social Security Administration was never informed of Ludwig's death, and because he never received Social Security benefits there were no benefits to stop and no questions were raised. The suspicion, of course, is that Dunham, knowing her grandson was not a U.S. citizen — either because he was born in Kenya or became a citizen of Indonesia upon his adoption by Lolo Soetoro — merely scoured the probate records until she found someone who died who was not receiving Social Security benefits, and "selected" that SSN for Obama. Origins: This fantastical tale about President Barack Obama's having used a Social Security number (SSN) issued to a French immigrant named Jean Paul Ludwig, born in 1890, is easily debunked. As can be verified through the Social Security Death Index (SSDI), a database of death records created from the United States Social Security Administration's Death Master File Extract, the Social Security Administration was in fact informed of Ludwig's death, and the Social Security number assigned to him was not, as claimed, the same as that assigned to Barack Obama (042-68-4425), but rather a completely different number (045-26-8722). Ludwig also didn't pass away until 1981, by which time Barack Obama had long since been assigned a Social Security number of his own: The premise of this claim is also flawed in concept, as Barack Obama was born in United States and thus there would have been no reason for his grandmother to appropriate someone else's Social Security number for use by him. (And since non-citizens can legally obtain Social Security numbers the issue is irrelevant, as possession of a Social Security number is not in itself an indicator of citizenship.) Likewise, the claim that Social Security numbers beginning with 042 are "reserved for Connecticut residents" is false. As explained by the Social Security Administration, the area number portion of a SSN does not (and never did) necessarily correspond to the state in which an applicant was born or resides; it simply reflects the mailing address which the applicant has requested his newly issued card be sent to. That mailing address does not have to be the same as the applicant's residence address: it can be the address of a friend, relative, employer, rented post office box, or anyone else authorized to receive mail on his behalf: The Area Number is assigned by the geographical region. Prior to 1972, cards were issued in local Social Security offices around the country and the Area Number represented the State in which the card was issued. This did not necessarily have to be the State where the applicant lived, since a person could apply for their card in any Social Security office. Since 1972, when SSA began assigning SSNs and issuing cards centrally from Baltimore, the area number assigned has been based on the ZIP code in the mailing address provided on the application for the original Social Security card. The applicant's mailing address does not have to be the same as their place of residence. Thus, the Area Number does not necessarily represent the State of residence of the applicant, either prior to 1972 or since.. Why Barack Obama's Social Security card application might have included a Connecticut mailing address is something of a curiosity, as he had no known connection to that state at the time, but by itself that quirk is no indicator of fraud. The most likely explanation for the discrepancy is a simple clerical or typographical error: the ZIP code in the area of Honolulu where Barack Obama lived is 96814, while the ZIP code for Danbury, Connecticut, is 06814. Since '0' and '9' are similarly shaped numbers and are adjacent on typewriter keyboards, it's not uncommon for handwritten examples to be mistaken for each other, or for one to be mistyped as the other (thereby potentially resulting in a Hawaiian resident's application mistakenly being routed as if it had originated from Connecticut).</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347559129676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347560633761-24</Id><Topic><Title>Do you guy's think maybe</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347552142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Use of the terms "GOP" and "member" in the same sentence is discouraged as it provokes the Log Cabin crowd to uncontrollable giggles.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347560633761</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347561837022-25</Id><Topic><Title>Do you guy's think maybe</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347552142452</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:02:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crown of camel's azzses...you and stockturder are the best....Elite caddys for bammy during his everlasting leisure time....always polishing his shaft and washing his balls....so..are ye both spitters or swallers...my gues would be swallowers...bammy would never allow for that right foot plant to slip on a drive tee off</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347561837022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347562638611-26</Id><Title>Bernanke's read on the economy... in the tank!</Title><Msg>This is the biggest money printing in American history. What does he see coming that has possed him to do such QE. Knowing this will cause commodites to rise on the low and middle class, punish retirees with low rates now till 2015, create hyper inflation to be sure, the answer is........he knows the economy is heading into the tank! He is following in Greenspans shoes, creating a bubble in equities, drawing folks into the risky markets to obtain any kind of return...as usual the retail investor is going to get fleeced once the bubble burst. If they are long they won't be able to get out fast enough. History to repeat it self again, it's just the way of things, the little guy always gets hosed by the professional crooks on Wall Street.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347562638611</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347563114162-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke's read on the economy... in the tank!</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347562638611</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep...and they're buying the bags like there's a fire sale...bwahahahaha...folks....i don't care how they manipulate interest rates.........play the bond game so forth and so on......bottom line...we still have an incompetent government running the united states....we still have bankrupt banks loaning to bankrupt countrys globally...ECB...bwahahahahaha..here's a bag for ye....bwahahahaha</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1347563114162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565539312-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reveals Character With Deaths in Lybia</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1347552275147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, You missed the point - I have not mentioned anything about compassion. Most Republican leaders in Congress declined to follow Romney's lead as he assailed the Obama administration, and by the end of the day, many analysts concluded that he had hurt himself by jumping in precipitously. He should have waited 12 to 24 hour and put out a more comprehensive statement, said Rep. Peter King, R-N.Y., the chairman of the Homeland Security Committee By Wednesday morning,when news of the four deaths became public, Romney's initial statement looked clumsy and badly timed to many, and Republicans like Peggy Noonan, WSJ columnist, and John Sununu, the former senator, publicly criticized it. McCain's long time adviser, Mark Salter, chastised Romney "unfair and hyperbolic sound bites." Romney said, "It's disgraceful that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize wit those who waged the attacks." But Romney came under withering criticism for distorting the chain of events overseas and appearing to try to gain political advantage from an episode that claimed American lives. pacifican, Sooner or later, Romney will regret his outlandish statements.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1347565539312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565539468-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reveals Character With Deaths in Lybia</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1347552275147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, You missed the point - I have not mentioned anything about compassion. Most Republican leaders in Congress declined to follow Romney's lead as he assailed the Obama administration, and by the end of the day, many analysts concluded that he had hurt himself by jumping in precipitously. He should have waited 12 to 24 hour and put out a more comprehensive statement, said Rep. Peter King, R-N.Y., the chairman of the Homeland Security Committee By Wednesday morning,when news of the four deaths became public, Romney's initial statement looked clumsy and badly timed to many, and Republicans like Peggy Noonan, WSJ columnist, and John Sununu, the former senator, publicly criticized it. McCain's long time adviser, Mark Salter, chastised Romney "unfair and hyperbolic sound bites." Romney said, "It's disgraceful that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize wit those who waged the attacks." But Romney came under withering criticism for distorting the chain of events overseas and appearing to try to gain political advantage from an episode that claimed American lives. pacifican, Sooner or later, Romney will regret his outlandish statements.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1347565539468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347565539522-30</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Reveals Character With Deaths in Lybia</Title><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1347552275147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 12:04:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, You missed the point - I have not mentioned anything about compassion. Most Republican leaders in Congress declined to follow Romney's lead as he assailed the Obama administration, and by the end of the day, many analysts concluded that he had hurt himself by jumping in precipitously. He should have waited 12 to 24 hour and put out a more comprehensive statement, said Rep. Peter King, R-N.Y., the chairman of the Homeland Security Committee By Wednesday morning,when news of the four deaths became public, Romney's initial statement looked clumsy and badly timed to many, and Republicans like Peggy Noonan, WSJ columnist, and John Sununu, the former senator, publicly criticized it. McCain's long time adviser, Mark Salter, chastised Romney "unfair and hyperbolic sound bites." Romney said, "It's disgraceful that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize wit those who waged the attacks." But Romney came under withering criticism for distorting the chain of events overseas and appearing to try to gain political advantage from an episode that claimed American lives. pacifican, Sooner or later, Romney will regret his outlandish statements.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1347565539522</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347566322724-31</Id><Topic><Title>Bernanke's read on the economy... in the tank!</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347562638611</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 14:57:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth be told if the so called "legacy assets" were still on the books of most banks they would be insovent. Almost every commodity will be the place to invest...sad state of affairs.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347566322724</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 15:58:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347568403200-32</Id><Title>What is wrong with Obama's thinking?</Title><Msg>Today the appeaser in-chief Obama called the libyan leader to thank him for his suppurt as well as the Egypts leader. If you are an American this Presidents actions are disgraceful. I am surprised he did't thank him for only killing 4 people... liberalism is a mental disorder.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347568403200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:33:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347569928304-33</Id><Title>Andrew Sullivan comments on the Dipshidiot's faux pas</Title><Msg>The right has decided - surprise! - that the whole Romney mess over Libya and Egypt is a function entirely of media bias. Eric Erickson complains that "the media wanted to focus on Mitt Romney" yesterday. Scott Galupo makes the obvious point: The media focused on Mitt Romney yesterday because Mitt Romney asked them to. If he had merely issued a formal statement expressing outrage at the mobs in Cairo and Benghazi, the media would have focused on the aspects of this ongoing story that Erickson finds so interesting — effectively, as Daniel Larison observed via Twitter, it would have done Romney’s work for him. Fred Kaplan spells out what Romney should have done: Imagine if Romney had called President Obama, asked how he could be of assistance in this time of crisis, offered to appear at his side at a press conference to demonstrate that, when American lives are at risk, politics stop at the water’s edge—and then had his staff put out the word that he’d done these things, which would have made him look noble and might have made Obama look like the petty one if he’d waved away these offers. But none of this is in Romney. He imagined a chink in Obama’s armor, an opening for a political assault on the president’s strength and leadership, and so he dashed to the barricades without a moment of reflection, a nod to propriety, or a smidgen of good strategy. Romney has all the affect of a traditional, patriotic, mild-mannered Republican, like Reagan or the first Bush. But he isn't. He's just Cheney with better hair and even fewer scruples.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347569928304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347576185267-34</Id><Topic><Title>Leg O' Bear, today would be a good day for you to comment.</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1347567913183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leg O Bear is recovering from a brain fart. After the stock didn't hit his cherished $7.01, he escaped back the world of booze and pot. He forgot to cover his short position. Bye bye bear</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347576185267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:43:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347576391059-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is There Another CEO Etrade Can Fire?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347558185989</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:43:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you suggesting some sort of sacrificial ritual? I would agree. They should have a lottery in the company every month and send the chosen one to slaughter. A festival of blood and gore.</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347576391059</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347576756312-36</Id><Title>We shall soon begin the Ritual of Channeling the Great Brandish.</Title><Msg>Oh great spirit, we beseech thee to bring forth BRANDISH. HEAR OUR CALL, OH BRANDISH.... COME FORTH AND EXPOUND GREAT THINKING UPON OUR SELVES. BRANDISH BRANDISH BRANDISH</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347576756312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577023470-37</Id><Title>HMMMMMM HMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMM HMMMMMMM HMMMMMM</Title><Msg>GREAT BRANDISH HEAR OUR VOICE........... HMMMMMMMMMMMMM BRANDISH..............................................BRANDISH.................HMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOONG............BRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAANNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNDISHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347577023470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 18:57:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577217204-38</Id><Title>BRANDISH ...... COME TO THE LIGHT.......... WALK TO THE LIGHT.....................</Title><Msg>We sense you are near, OH BRANDISH. COME TO THE LIGHT.........</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347577217204</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:00:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577470263-39</Id><Title>The Light is fading.......... Brandish, come back..... come to the light....</Title><Msg>MMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMm OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO hMMMMMMMMMMMMM Dueces tecum OIIIIi Oh Great Brandish, who come from the land so far....... come hither........ HMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM HMMMMMMMMMMM</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347577470263</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:04:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577702150-40</Id><Title>BRANDISH..... THERE IS MUCH THAT CAN BE DONE..... Oh great one... COME TO THE FORE.</Title><Msg>BRANDISH COME FORWARD....... MMMMMMMMMMMMMM OHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH ooooooooooooooooooooo ooooooooooooooooooooo ooooooooooooooooooooo OHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347577702150</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347577897018-41</Id><Title>IN THE NAME OF THE GREAT YAHOOOOO - ORDERED BRANDISH TO APPEAR</Title><Msg>I SENSE BRANDISH IS NEAR......COME HITHER............ WE BESEECH THEE TO APPEAR..... WE SEEK YOUR ASSHOLERY</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347577897018</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578014496-42</Id><Title>BRANDISH...... FIREFOX DOESN'T PLAY WELL WITH THE NEW YAHOOOOOO.......</Title><Msg>Use another browser hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347578014496</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:13:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578236663-43</Id><Title>OHHHH More Management bad habits for BRANDISH TO EXPOSE.... .COME TO THE LIGHT</Title><Msg>Hmmmmmmmmm brandish come to the fore with thy saber and shield...... We must confront more miscreant management and get another leg up. hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm ooooooooooooooooooooo uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu oooouaayyyyyyyyyyyy</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347578236663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:17:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578353814-44</Id><Title>BRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAANNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNDIIIIIIISSSSSSHHHHHHHHHHH</Title><Msg>Last call before the bear game................ Come to the light...... hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347578353814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578448518-45</Id><Title>OOOHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH BRAAAAAAAAAAAAANNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNNDISHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH</Title><Msg>Arise, come forth, be heard i order ye in the name ofthe geat yahoooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347578448518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347578607151-46</Id><Title>BRAAAANDISH..... THE COMMONWEAL OF SHAREHOLDERS BESEECES THEEEEEEEE..</Title><Msg>COME FORTH!!</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347578607151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:23:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347579121595-47</Id><Title>OOOOOOOOOMMMMMMMMM OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOMMMMMMMMMMMMMM</Title><Msg>Brandish.......... Before the bear game starts...... Mmmmmmmmmmmmm oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347579121595</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:32:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347579470144-48</Id><Title>OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO</Title><Msg>One more big one for BRANDISH</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1347579470144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 19:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347581167609-49</Id><Title>Nothing emboldens the wicked like a coward</Title><Msg>That is why our embassies in the Middle East are on fire</Msg><Username>alien_frikin_abduction</Username><Timestamp>1347581167609</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:06:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347581841543-50</Id><Topic><Title>How's E*bank doing</Title><Username>hellasmusic</Username><Timestamp>1347558788895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:53:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is E*bank.. Is it related to E*trade.. ;--)</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1347581841543</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582006656-51</Id><Topic><Title>What is wrong with Obama's thinking?</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347568403200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:33:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing is wrong with Obama 's thinking.. You on the other hand are a war mongering idiot. Get over yourself.</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1347582006656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347582638045-52</Id><Topic><Title>Andrew Sullivan comments on the Dipshidiot's faux pas</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347569928304</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 16:58:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney 's hiden agenda is to grow Mormon membership and turn America to his view of the garden of eden... Minus the apple tree.. Keep that knowledge for the elite. Just fooling! Point is, Romney is dangerous for America.</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347582638045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 20:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347586175702-53</Id><Title>KANSAS REDNECKS GONE WILD</Title><Msg>Classic example of power crazed, knuckle dragging , GOP governance. Topeka — Kansas officials want more information before deciding whether to remove President Barack Obama from the state's November ballot. The State Objections Board heard arguments Thursday on a claim from a Manhattan resident that Obama is not eligible to be president because his father was from Kenya. The resident, Joe Montgomery, also questions whether Obama has a valid birth certificate. The president released a copy of his long-form birth certificate last year, and Hawaii officials have verified his citizenship repeatedly. But the Kansas board — made up of Secretary of State Kris Kobach, Attorney General Derek Schmidt and Lt. Gov. Jeff Colyer — said Thursday it wants certified documents from Hawaii and two other states where similar questions about Obama's citizenship have been raised. The board plans to meet again Monday and may rule then.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347586175702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 21:29:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347588061813-54</Id><Title>Dipshidiot savaged by editorial boards across the country</Title><Msg>Thu Sep 13, 2012 at 11:45 AM PDT Editorial boards across America savage Mitt Romney's bungled response to Libya attack by PorridgeGun New York Times: "An extraordinary lack of presidential character" Mitt Romney, who wants Americans to believe he can be president but showed an extraordinary lack of presidential character by using the murders of the Americans in Libya as an excuse not just to attack Mr. Obama, but to do so in a way that suggested either a dangerous ignorance of the facts or an equally dangerous willingness to twist them to his narrow partisan aims. Washington Post: "A discredit to his campaign" Mr. Romney’s first rhetorical assault came Tuesday night in response to a statement by the U.S. Embassy in Cairo, which was also besieged by demonstrators Tuesday. His statement claimed that the administration’s first response was “to sympathize with those who waged the attacks.” In fact the embassy statement was issued before the protests began; referring to an ugly anti-Islam film that was the focus of demonstrators, it condemned “those who abuse the universal right of free speech to hurt the religious belief of others.” Los Angeles Times: "An outrageous exercise in opportunism." His statement on the anti-U.S. violence in Libya and Egypt was outrageous and ill-conceived. In reacting to the killing of the U.S. ambassador to Libya and three other Americans, President Obama, Secretary of State Hillary Rodham Clinton and some Republican members of Congress appropriately focused on mourning the dead and honoring their patriotism. Mitt Romney thinks he has a better idea: capitalizing on the attack to shore up his dubious campaign narrative that Obama is soft on radical Islam and apologetic about American values. It's an outrageous exercise in opportunism. Boston Globe: "His statement was offensive on many other levels…Romney’s actions raise more doubts about himself than Obama." Not much is known about Romney’s views on foreign policy, and he benefits from the perception that, because he is bright and well-informed on other issues, he therefore would be a responsible steward of American diplomacy. But his actions on the campaign trail belie this image. He has been only too eager to revive the Bush-era approach of tough talk and military action as the default responses to threats in the world — an approach that proved utterly ineffective at thwarting guerrilla actions such as the one that killed US Ambassador Christopher Stevens and three others in Libya. Romney’s actions raise more doubts about himself than Obama. Philadelphia Inquirer: "Mitt Romney didn't wait for expert assessments to use the four diplomats' deaths to launch his own verbal assault." Unfortunately, because it is election season, Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney didn't wait for expert assessments to use the four diplomats' deaths to launch his own verbal assault. Miami Herald: "Profoundly inappropriate" Predictably, the attacks were quickly mired in political controversy at home. Candidate Mitt Romney jumped the gun in attacking Mr. Obama as an “apologist” because of a statement issued by the U.S. Embassy in Cairo before the assaults took place. Reacting to the death of U.S. diplomats by seeking to take political advantage is profoundly inappropriate. This is a time for unity, as much as it was when Americans rallied behind President Bush 11 years ago. Wednesday’s events are reminders that the war that began on 9/11 is far from over. Tampa Bay Times: "The Republican nominee continued to exploit the situation" There are unanticipated turns of events in every political campaign that provide insights about the candidates, their judgment and their grace under pressure. Romney's factual mistake, exploitation of an evolving situation in which Americans were killed, and poor timing is one of those moments. South Florida Sun Sentinel: "Irresponsible. And totally unwarranted." There are still almost two months left in the presidential campaign — plenty of time for Romney and other Republicans to make their points, and criticisms, of American foreign policy. There will be upcoming debates, where Romney can directly challenge the president on his actions. That's fair game. But the immediate hours after a horrendous attack on American citizens abroad is not the time to further divide the American people in an attempt to push up poll numbers. Irresponsible. And totally unwarranted. Sarasota Herald-Tribune: "Prematurely lobbed off-base criticism" When terrorists struck America on Sept. 11, 2001, the nation grieved together. Eleven years later, in the wake of another 9/11 attack -- which Tuesday claimed the lives of a U.S. ambassador and three other brave Americans at a consulate in Libya -- that spirit of unity was missing. In its place was partisan finger-pointing by Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney, who prematurely lobbed off-base criticism at the wording of the U.S. diplomatic response. He would have been wiser to reserve judgment for another time. Cleveland Plain Dealer: "Mitt Romney's trigger finger was so quick that he didn't even get it right" Republican nominee Mitt Romney's trigger finger was so quick that he didn't even get it right. Tuesday night, his campaign released a statement calling it "disgraceful" that the Obama administration's first reaction was "to sympathize with those who waged the attacks," but erroneously based that on a U.S. embassy statement in Cairo that had preceded the assault. Far from sympathizing, the statement was a simple expression of religious tolerance aimed at defusing tensions. It was not, as Romney repeated Wednesday, "akin to apology." Akron Beacon Journal: "Unfortunately, Mitt Romney chose to ignore the distinction." So it made sense that Americans facing the mob in Cairo issued a statement that signaled an understanding of what triggered the protests. That statement may have reflected fear. It certainly attempted to bring calm, the message similar to that issued by the Bush White House when protests followed Danish cartoons mocking Islam. What shouldn’t be missed is that the statement was released long before the attack and the killings in Benghazi. Unfortunately, Mitt Romney chose to ignore the distinction. In a statement, the Republican presidential candidate expressed outrage at the attacks and the death of an American consulate worker. He then cudgeled the White House for a “first response” that did not condemn but showed sympathy “with those who waged the attacks.” The idea of any American president, Republican or Democratic, taking such a stance is ludicrous. As it is, Romney strained in grabbing the moment to press a familiar campaign theme. Boulder Daily Camera: "For someone whose campaign has been studded with tone-deafness abroad, this was stunning, undiplomatic and undemocratic rhetoric." Leading Republicans including House Majority Leader Eric Cantor (R-Va.), Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.), Sen. John McCain (R-Ariz.), and House Speaker John A. Boehner (R-Ohio) -- some of the most strident voices against Obama's bid for a second term -- stood together as Americans. They decried the violence, mourned the dead, and expressed the resolve to continue to work for democratic peace in the region. That democratic peace relies on tolerance of people with different beliefs. Without that tolerance for other beliefs, it all falls to pieces. That couldn't be more clear in the wake of the deaths in Libya. And stating that commitment to one of our core values is not an "apology" as candidate Mitt Romney tried to portray it. Not only irresponsibly, when he was clueless as to the extent of the attack but even the next morning when more information was available to him. For someone whose campaign has been studded with tone-deafness abroad, this was stunning, undiplomatic and undemocratic rhetoric. Milwaukee Journal Sentinel: "Yes, it was sad and pathetic to see such callous and uninformed statements from politicians who couldn't wait until they had the facts to use an international incident for political gain." Mitt Romney, the Republican nominee for president, was quick to criticize President Barack Obama, noting Tuesday night that he was "outraged by the attacks" and that it was disgraceful that "the administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions but to sympathize with those who waged the attacks." The chairman of the Republican National Committee, Reince Priebus of Wisconsin, tweeted: "Obama sympathizes with attackers in Egypt. Sad and pathetic." Sad and pathetic? Yes, it was sad and pathetic to see such callous and uninformed statements from politicians who couldn't wait until they had the facts to use an international incident for political gain. The former Massachusetts governor doubled-down during a news conference on Wednesday even as leading Republicans refused to play politics over the deaths of four Americans. Denver Post: "Romney's reaction was out of line." Republican candidate Mitt Romney was out line when he criticized the embassy statement for "sympathizing" with rioters. U.S. diplomats obviously have no sympathy for such criminals, and the statement doesn't imply they do. Romney later stood by his hasty reaction, but he should back off. Four good public servants are dead — and no decent American sympathizes with the perpetrators.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347588061813</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 22:01:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>