<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353182558016-1</Id><Title>The facts are in on the golden state, and they ain't pretty</Title><Msg>No denying what the Democrats have done to the "golden state". They now have a super majority to continue their reign of terror on working folks. Three groups of folks left...rich, poor, and public sector employees. Congratulation on a job well done. California Now Officially Leads Nation in Poverty The Golden State has fallen on hard times, with a poverty rate that is now twice as bad as West Virginia’s and substantially worse than the rates of poverty in Mississippi, Alabama, Arkansas and Texas, according to a new measure of poverty developed by the federal Census Bureau. Democrat-run California earned its last-place rank under the federal government’s new measure of poverty, which incorporates more detailed analyses of welfare payments and the local costs of food, gasoline and housing. The state’s costs are boosted by its environmental and workplace regulations, and by 38 million residents’ competition for housing close to the sea.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1353182558016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:02:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353186953874-2</Id><Topic><Title>upgrade with a 8.50$ arget price!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1353074973597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>to all of you,in 2013 etfc will be sold fo $ 16</Msg><Username>make10</Username><Timestamp>1353186953874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 16:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353196969494-3</Id><Topic><Title>The facts are in on the golden state, and they ain't pretty</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1353182558016</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 15:02:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are suspending reality for your own ideology...you can't argue with the articule. You need to be more objective to have any crediability on any issues you raise. In California the Democrats have controlled the legislation for decades, thus the state has had rapant illegal benefits, lavash public sector benefits and pensions, and the highest percent in the nation of welfare recipients. Them are the facts, and now the state for all purposes has turned into a cesspool of government and third world parasites.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1353196969494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-17 19:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>