<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348378694984-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer darling, Haven't you read and heard that the AG was absolved of any wrongdoing in regard to Fast &amp; Furious??? slayer honey, Eric Holder is not a criminal!. We Dems don't watch much TV, we get our News on the internet. On TV we watch only selected programs.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348378694984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 01:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348379407071-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifica, Keep on watching Faux News, Rushbo, crazy Hannity, etc. Gov. Chris Christie gets distracted everytime he sees someone in the audience eating icecreme or a hamburger. His state is going down the tubes and he criticizes Jerry Brown and California. This fat guy is nuts!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348379407071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 01:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348379407171-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifica, Keep on watching Faux News, Rushbo, crazy Hannity, etc. Gov. Chris Christie gets distracted everytime he sees someone in the audience eating icecreme or a hamburger. His state is going down the tubes and he criticizes Jerry Brown and California. This fat guy is nuts!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348379407171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 01:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348405748115-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your desperate tone is pathetic. maybe you should just pack your bags and move to Israel where they do it your way...... well, except for the universal healthcare with free abortions and the socialism and so forth......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348405748115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348406196519-5</Id><Topic><Title>Mitten's windowdressed tax return is a joke</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348346945707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 16:49:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are so lame. for all your weaseling blather, the fact is Mitt is hiding his tax returns, he has only submitted 2 returns and the latest is obviously and aburdly windowdressed. And he is such a hypocrite that he required his vp candidates to submitt 10 years, just like his dad ...... but Mitt is too special and fluffy to have to put up with the rule he imposed on others.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348406196519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:16:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406731416-6</Id><Title>Ryan's Mother is a 47% er?</Title><Msg>she is on moocher "collectivist" "socialist" entitlements...... what about Romey's dad and granddad? by now you have seen the video of his mom telling about them being on welfare: Lenore Romney: "You know we've only owned our home for the last four years. He was a refugee from Mexico. He was on relief, welfare relief for the first years of his life. But this great country gave him opportunities." from 1962 interview and what about your mom or grandmom? are they like Ryan's mom? Doesn't this make you want to denounce them as mooches to a crowd of the weathy at a $50,000 per plate gop gathering?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348406731416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348407494130-7</Id><Title>gop killed a veterans jobs bill</Title><Msg>why did the gop have to kill a 1 billion dollar veterans jobs bill (paid for) when they never bothered to pay for W's $ trillion dollar iraq invasion and occupation? ( instead they gave tax cuts to the rich) the gop is 100% for sending the troops to war but only 2% for a jobs bill for them when they return? Maybe Romney can bring it up among the wealthy people he talks to in private denouncing half of Americans as mooches......... ."It makes sense for the 99 percent of Americans to find new ways to pay their debt to the 1 percent who serve in uniform"......... does it not?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348407494130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348417577377-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer darling, The AG was absolved of any connection or wrongdoing in regard to "Fast &amp; Furious." Eric Holder is not a criminal and that irks you does it not, slayer honeybunch? Or don't you believe Darrell Issa?</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348417577377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348420959108-9</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's mental instability</Title><Msg>Romney Univision tantrum part of pattern, including 1981 arrest for disorderly conduct by mikepridmore As mentioned here, there is a trending twitter theme about the temper tantrum a Republican said Mitt Romney threw at the recent Univision taping. Here is the Buzzfeed snippet. Romney took issue with the anchors beginning the broadcast that way, said Salinas, and he refused to go on stage until they re-taped the introduction. (One Republican present at the taping said Romney "threw a tantrum.") Five years ago Romney got caught in a lie by Glen Johnson of AP and angrily approached Johnson after the presser was over. As Keith Olbermann noted later, Johnson was completely correct about the fact that Romney was telling a bold-faced lie. Eric Fernstrom tried to end the presser abruptly and afterward accused Johnson of being unprofessional. Yes, pointing it out when Romney tells a lie is... "unprofessional." The embed code of that video has been disabled by request (wonder whose request that was?) but here is the link. Note the anger on Romney's face when challenging Johnson. As I wrote earlier here, Mitt Romney lost his cool multiple times during the time he was in charge of the 2002 Winter Olympics. There was one incident where he blew up at a teenager charged with directing traffic: Romney found himself stuck in a huge traffic backup on the road to the men’s downhill ski area, because some buses had not received the proper security-clearance placards and were being prevented from proceeding. Romney, who had organized the Salt Lake Olympics, jumped out to take charge. He started directing traffic, over the objections of a sheriff’s deputy, Kodi Taggart; she later filed a report on Romney’s interference. And he lit into an 18-year-old volunteering as a security officer, Shaun Knopp. Knopp told reporters that Romney had asked “who the #$%$ he was and “what the #$%$ he was doing and had then told him, “We got the Olympics going on, and we don’t need this sh-t going on.” Romney denied this at the time, saying he had not used such language since high school. “I would not, have not, and never would use the f-word,” he said. The worst word he used with Knopp, he said, was “H-E double hockey sticks.” .... In the days after the incident, the state’s top law enforcement official decided against an investigation. But the officer in charge of security at the downhill site, Weber County Sheriff’s Office Captain Terry Shaw, said a police sergeant from Colorado working under his command had corroborated Knopp’s account, and Shaw demanded an apology from Romney. This incident put Romney at odds with those in public safety positions: Police were angered that Romney denied shouting the expletive and were further miffed when Romney later offered a partial apology to a sheriff's captain but not to Knopp. ''There were a lot of people in public safety who were extremely angry,'' said Peter Dawson, a lawyer today who served as an intern in a communications center at the time. ''The general consensus was, 'I hope he doesn't need any help from us because we aren't going to respond very quickly.'.'' Romney also had "clashes" with others while at Salt Lake, times when he seemed more menacing, and times that bring to memory previous stories like his attack of a fellow student. Romney tolerated little dissent from trustees who aggressively questioned his decisions. While his many admirers in Salt Lake City viewed him as pristine, amiable, and self-effacing, he developed an alternate image among a group of dissenters: petty, vindictive, and self-aggrandizing. His chief foe was Ken Bullock - no relation to Romney's friend and COO Fraser Bullock. Ken Bullock served on the organizing committee and also was executive director of the Utah League of Cities and Towns. .... Garff, the organizing committee chairman whose association with Romney went back to childhood, believed Romney inappropriately tried to silence Bullock. ''Mitt saw him as an agitator,'' Garff said, ''and I saw him as a watchdog who needed to be heard.'' Romney showed little sympathy for another trustee who criticized his performance. When Lillian Taylor, a small-business consultant, questioned why the committee continued to retain a pricey law firm that had acknowledged losing documents related to the scandal, Romney, who at the time said he had no problem with her raising the issue, sat silently while the board's attorney aggressively dismissed her complaint. Yahoo News notes four other episodes, including a 1981 arrest for disorderly conduct: In 1981, Romney was putting the family boat into Lake Cochituate, an hour outside of Boston, when a park officer told him he couldn't because the license looked painted over. If he launched, he'd face a $50 fine. "I was willing to pay the fine," Romney told The Boston Globe. But the officer returned as Romney put the boat in and, visibly angry at being ignored, handcuffed Mitt, who was "dripping wet in a bathing suit," and booked him for disorderly conduct. Romney contested the arrest in court, threatened to sue, and got the arrest dismissed and sealed. The other three events mentioned in the Yahoo News article included Putting Rick Perry in a "Vulcan neck pinch," Sparring with party rockers LMFAO, and yelling at a radio host over his gay marriage record. There is also the attack on his classmate in 1965 when Romney was in prep school. That story is here. And those are just the stories we know about.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348420959108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:22:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348422408367-10</Id><Title>GOP admits BO's success</Title><Msg>Bill Kristol: ‘Obama team turned around’ Bush’s financial meltdown Source: The Raw Story Weekly Standard editor Bill Kristol says that Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney is going to have a tough time winning if the election is a referendum on President Barack Obama’s first term. “They need to focus on the next four years,” the conservative columnist told Fox News host Chris Wallace on Sunday. “If this election is just about the last four years, that’s a muddy verdict.” “Bush was president during the financial meltdown, the Obama team has turned that around pretty well,” he explained. “He’s got to make it a referendum on the choice about the next four years, and explain what Obama would do over the next four years that would be bad for the country and what he would do would be good for the country.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348422408367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348423544661-11</Id><Title>Chance of a life time</Title><Msg>OMG, get out your check books, don't let this opportunity pass you by...just imagine being able to lunch with these two luminaries. Donate To Dems And Win Lunch With Gore And Pelosi Former Vice President Al Gore has been entirely absent from President Barack Obama’s campaign this year and was nowhere to be seen at the Democratic National Convention earlier this month. But it appears he’s ready to resurface and help out his party. The Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee announced Saturday that people who donate money to it could win a free trip to New York City, and lunch with Gore and House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.).</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423544661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348423874809-12</Id><Topic><Title>Chance of a life time</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423544661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lunch with Pelosi could reveal very good stock tips. But since you live in ugly Riverside and live off the govt, the only stock you see is livestock. Mostly chickens.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1348423874809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348423961076-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Criminally Negligent and Dishonest on Benghazi</Title><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1348356814176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 19:33:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**What was Obama lying about?** If you truely don't no the answer to that question..that is scary.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423961076</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348424267877-14</Id><Topic><Title>Chance of a life time</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423544661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey weasel, I noticed you never answered the question about where you live in California. Why is that?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348424267877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348425409447-15</Id><Topic><Title>Topic #1: Why is it taking this company so long to find a new CEO?</Title><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348341815259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I have a tendency to agree with your intelligent thought. Despite ETFC's problems, it would not be difficult to find a talented individual who would chomp at the bit to take the reins. It would be a very lucrative and rewarding position, and the winning cnadidate would gain to awesome exposure. But as you so eloquently express, who would join a company that would sell in a short period of time. I will add further that the board of directors would be foolish to hire on a CEO as the termination package would be costly. They already dumped Strategic Steve and perhaps the dumping was part of the master plan. They already know that they will pay him a severance package and he probably was being obstructionist to a sale - so off he goes. So lucky. Steve probably added a good amount of value in cleaning up the loan portfolio and wHaTeVeR, so his usefulness is over. I'd like to think that the buyer for ETFC has been located and the deal is getting teed up for a fourth quarter event, springer call, loan sale, sale transaction all in one shot. MMs are collecting shares, and all this frantic political posting here has nothing to do with Obama, and everything with collecting shares.</Msg><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348425409447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348427082819-16</Id><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Msg>"The Republican base knows they're being lied to. They don't mind. They know there's no voter impersonation problem to solve via voter ID. They will admit, privately, that they don't think "those people" should be allowed to vote. They know public employees aren't overpaid, but they've been taught to hate public employees, so slashing public employee wages and benefits feels good to them. They know there's no threat justifying our enormous defense budget. They just like being the strongest bully. They know unions spend a tiny pittance on politics compared to corporations, but they're happy denying that because they've been taught to hate "union thugs" and "union bosses". They know that Wall Street has rigged the system, but that's OK as long as they get to see the "Occupy hippies" pepper-sprayed. They know their Party doesn't give a sh-t about them, but they've been taught to hate the other Party as a "bunch of takers". They know there is no "liberal media" but also know that claiming there is one helps back up their other comfortable lies. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348435455291-17</Id><Topic><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the site.."Democraticunderground"... You can't Think for Yourself?... Not a Surprise!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1348435455291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:24:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348436021461-18</Id><Title>JB!...GROW UP!...</Title><Msg>Pick an I.D. and Stick with it... Hell...My 6 year old makes You look Immature!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1348436021461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348438592852-19</Id><Topic><Title>JB!...GROW UP!...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1348436021461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:33:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who calls himself junglebob and then has tee-shirts made up in the case that he forgets who he is? I doubt even tarzan lord of the jungle ever felt the need to put his name on any of his apparel.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348438592852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348438792840-20</Id><Topic><Title>it doesn't take multiple pages of scrolling for one post of a topic</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348277330957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:28:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer, Didn't you mooch Larry Craig's kok?I call that some mooching!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348438792840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348438793752-21</Id><Topic><Title>it doesn't take multiple pages of scrolling for one post of a topic</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348277330957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:28:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer, Didn't you mooch Larry Craig's kok?I call that some mooching!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348438793752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:19:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348439004185-22</Id><Topic><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dike...why you be so paranoid....you'll still get something in the mailbox monthly even if bammy don't win......if the post office can survive him another couple monrhs that is.........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348439004185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348440725531-23</Id><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan: Contraception Mandate 'Will Be Gone' On 'Day 1' GOP vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan sees no place for the Obama Administration's contraception mandate. At a Saturday campaign event in Orlando, Fla., the Associated Press reports that Ryan was asked about whether he would press Vice President and fellow Catholic Joe Biden on his views in relation to the 2012 Democratic Party platform. Ryan's answer turned straight to the piece of Obamacare providing birth control access. He vowed to remove that requirement for insurance providers, including Catholic hospitals and universities, on "day one." "It will be gone," Ryan told onlookers at the University of Central Florida. "I can guarantee you that." Back on February 10, Ryan offered similar criticisms of Obama's contraception plan. In a statement released on his website, the Wisconsin congressman deemed it an "affront to religious liberty."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348440725531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348440905956-24</Id><Topic><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**They know public employees aren't overpaid** You can't be this stupid. The inflated income and benifits of public sector workers with like jobs don't lie, but you have no problem lying to make a point. BTW, why are you a self hating white. I have a suggestion, move out of your white neighborhood and relocate to the hood... you won't because you don't want to get dead.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348440905956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348449010129-25</Id><Title>Romney the epitome of everything wrong with the US</Title><Msg>A thieving , hedge-fund parasite, money worshipping, fake religious , outsourcing , soulless liar</Msg><Username>serpa666</Username><Timestamp>1348449010129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:10:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348449507320-26</Id><Topic><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pay attention dipstick,we've been over this before: ".....let's first dispense with some widespread misunderstandings about our federal workforce. 1. Federal employees are overpaid compared with private-sector workers. The notion that federal workers consistently earn higher salaries than comparable private-sector workers has become an accepted truth. Conservative think tanks, including the Cato Institute, make much of data that does not offer fair comparisons of similar public-sector and private-sector jobs or account for how experience and education affect pay. A pediatrician with a small practice in Des Moines and a doctor at the National Institutes of Health who is leading a team of 50 researchers trying to cure cancer both provide health care, for example, but we shouldn't expect that they be paid the same. Though some critics question their accuracy, government analyses show that federal employees make on average 24 percent less than their private-sector counterparts. The Congressional Research Service reported in 2009 that private industry pays higher salaries than the government for PhD-level employees in computer science, information science, mathematics, statistics, biological sciences, environmental life sciences, chemistry, economics, and civil, architectural, electrical and computer engineering. In addition, the average private-sector salary in 2010 for a recent college graduate was $48,661. Entry-level federal workers start at $34,075, or $42,209 for candidates with superior academic achievement. On the other hand, some federal blue-collar and clerical workers are paid more than those in the private sector. The ongoing debate about federal pay, however, does not address the root problem: The government does not have a pay system flexible enough to recruit the best talent and pay in accordance with the market. 2. The federal workforce is bigger than ever. Not including the U.S. Postal Service, the federal government employs 2.1 million people. The workforce is now slightly smaller than it was in 1967, at the height of Lyndon Johnson's Great Society, and today there are 100 million more Americans to serve. Even during the Reagan administration, when small government was a political mantra, there were still between 2.1 and 2.2 million federal workers. In fact, there was an increase of about 95,000 federal employees between 1981 and 1989. In the 1990s, Bill Clinton reduced the workforce by nearly 350,000 to 1.8 million. Under George W. Bush, the federal workforce grew predominantly because of post-9/11 homeland security demands and the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. Today, two out of three federal civilian employees work for the Departments of Defense, Homeland Security, Veterans Affairs or Justice. The vast majority of government hiring since 2003 has been in these four departments. 3. You can't fire a federal worker. In the 2009 fiscal year, 11,275 federal employees were fired for poor performance or misconduct. In addition, a survey of federal managers by the U.S. Merit Systems Protection Board suggests that besides those who are formally terminated, there are a sizable number of employees who voluntarily leave after they are counseled that their performance is unacceptable. Still, the myth persists that incompetent federal workers cannot be fired. Unfortunately, even federal managers buy into it, often believing that there is little they can do to deal with a poorly performing subordinate. The primary causes of this misunderstanding are that managers do not feel supported by top leadership and do not have clear performance expectations for their employees. Though the process is complex, there are rules in place across government allowing for the dismissal of workers not passing muster -- and they should be used. 4. Most federal workers are paper-pushing clerks. The vast majority of federal workers hold white-collar professional, administrative and technical jobs, and aren't just college dropouts archiving triplicates of your tax return. Approximately 20 percent of federal workers have a master's degree, professional degree or doctorate, vs. 13 percent in the private sector. Fifty-one percent of federal employees have at least a college degree, compared with 35 percent in the private sector. Remarkably, more than 50 current or former federal employees have received Nobel Prizes. In fact, about one in four American Nobel laureates have been federal workers. Their contributions have included the eradication of polio, the mapping of the human genome and the harnessing of atomic energy. Federal employees protect our food and drug supplies, manage airline traffic, foil terrorist attacks, care for our wounded veterans, and make sure the elderly and those with disabilities get their Medicare and Social Security benefits. This is hardly paper-pushing. 5. Pay or hiring freezes would help slash the federal budget. Clearly, hard choices are needed to restore our nation's fiscal health. But across-the-board pay and hiring freezes avoid tough strategic decisions. The real question is not what can we cut, but how can we best save money. History has taught us that arbitrary, broad hiring and pay freezes don't return significant cost savings. When the Clinton administration cut government jobs, overall federal spending still increased. Reagan's 1981 hiring freeze fell apart when routine exemptions were granted to fill urgent demands, such as for VA doctors or military support personnel. How much will the government save by cutting 10 percent of the federal workforce -- about 200,000 employees -- as recommended by the president's deficit commission? If the work of federal employees is simply contracted to the private sector, the savings could be minimal or the move could even cost us more. If government employees are not replaced and their salaries are returned to the Treasury, the government would save at most $20 billion annually, or roughly 0.5 percent of total budget outlays. Bottom line: We cannot come close to balancing the budget simply by cutting federal staffers or their salaries. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348449507320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:18:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348449800563-27</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's "tax evaviseness"</Title><Msg>"The Obama campaign has released a new video attacking Mitt Romney for not releasing more tax returns. "What else is he hiding?" the video asks, noting that "from his 2010 release, we knew about his Swiss bank account, and we knew he owned a corporation in Bermuda." The video attacks Romney for overseas investments and "betting against the U.S. dollar." "He's still failing to match the precedent set by other presidential candidates," the video's narrator says, going on to list the number of tax returns George Romney, George H.W. Bush, Bill Clinton and George W. Bush released during their presidential runs. Obama previously called on Romney to release his tax returns at a surprise news conference in August. "This isn't overly personal here, guys," Obama said. This pretty standard stuff. I do not think we are being mean to ask him to do what every other presidential candidate has done." Romney released his 2011 tax return Friday afternoon. HuffPost's Zach Carter reported earlier: Mitt Romney paid an effective tax rate of 14.1 percent in 2011, according to a tax return filed on Friday, a relatively low tax rate resulting from exotic deductions, the special tax treatment for his Bain Capital retirement package and the low tax rate on capital gains. Romney also opted not to deduct millions in charitable contributions from his tax bill in order to maintain a pledge from August that he has paid at least 13 percent in federal income taxes for each of the past 10 years. Despite choosing to not take the deduction for charitable contributions, Romney can recoup that money after the election. HuffPost's Ryan Grim reports: If the American people reject him at the polls in November -- and even if they don't -- Romney would be fully within his legal rights to file an amended return, requiring the Treasury to cut him a substantial check. "It's noble," said Boston College tax law professor Brian Galle of Romney's generous, if temporary, gift to the Treasury. "It also doesn't prevent him from taking that deduction in an amended return if he were to file it after the election."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348449800563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348449956108-28</Id><Title>Romney dyed his face for Univision interview !!! LMFAO</Title><Msg>See huffing ton post article, what an effin phony</Msg><Username>serpa666</Username><Timestamp>1348449956108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:25:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348450265115-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot's "tax evaviseness"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348449800563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:23:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are probably one of the 47% that don't pay taxes at all and talk about the working class paying all your taxes. Romney does like every other wealth person He will take advantage of all tax breaks.That is not tax evasion. It is the democrates that would not do away with the loop holes.They had both houses and the presidency for 2 years and did not help the latinos , black or middle class but gave us a obama care that will break the country..</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1348450265115</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348450518775-30</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on women</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348440725531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:52:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure what assault you are talking about but we know that Kennedy drowned his girl friend, Clinton played cigar tag with Monica, John Edwards was crewing a girl while his wife died. The democrate for NY resigned because he was crewing some girl in his office. Not sure what assult you are talking about for the republicans.??</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1348450518775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348451180353-31</Id><Title>$8.50 is coming this week! Asia is down big!</Title><Msg>Don't add above $8.50. ETFC will go under $8 within a month!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348451180353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348453974487-32</Id><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Msg>You need 60 solid votes in the Senate to overcome filibusters. Dems never had more than 58. Add in the two Senate "independents" and you might reach 60 but one of them is Lieberman, not reliable at all. And then there's the actual, real time period where if EVERYTHING miraculously fell in place, the Dems had 60 votes: ------- Did The Democrats Ever Really Have 60 Votes In The Senate, And For How Long? Doug Mataconis · Sunday, June 17, 2012 · 11 Comments Once again in the wake of the President’s immigration policy announcement on Friday, one refrain you’re hearing from critics is that the President never pursed comprehensive immigration reform when had a Democratic Congress. Of course, as we all know too well, having majority control of both house of Congress doesn’t necessarily mean much if the opposition in the Senate decides to filibuster your legislation, and without a consistent caucus of 60 votes to overcome a cloture vote, legislation can be effectively blocked. That leads to the question of how long the Democrats actually had a filibuster proof majority in the 111th Congress. As this chart from Wikipedia reveals, it wasn’t for a very long period of time at all: What this shows is is that there were only two time periods during the 111th Congress when the Democrats had a 60 seat majority: From July 7. 2009 (when Al Franken was officially seated as the Senator from Minnesota after the last of Norm Coleman’s challenges came to an end) to August 25, 2009 (when Ted Kennedy died, although Kennedy’s illness had kept him from voting for several weeks before that date at least); and From September 25, 2009 (when Paul Kirk was appointed to replace Kennedy) to February 4, 2010 (when Scott Brown took office after defeating Martha Coakley); For one day in September 2009, Republicans lacked 40 votes due to the resignation of Mel Martinez, who was replaced the next day by George LeMieux So, to the extent there was a filibuster proof majority in the Senate it lasted during two brief periods which lasted for a total of just over five months when counted altogether (and Congress was in its traditional summer recess for most of the July-August 2009 time frame). It’s important to keep this fact in mind when discussing what could have happened in the 111th Congress, I think, and it’s probably something I haven’t kept in mind myself in the past.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>