<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-18"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347942327855-1</Id><Title>Exposed Dipshidiot responds</Title><Msg>UPDATE, 10:53 p.m. ET: Mitt Romney held a brief news conference Tuesday evening to address his comments. The AP reports: Republican Mitt Romney says a video clip in which he called nearly half of Americans "victims" was "not elegantly stated" and was "spoken off the cuff." But he says President Barack Obama's approach is "attractive to people who are not paying taxes." ... The Republican nominee did not disavow the comments but said they were made during a question-and-answer session. He said it was indicative of his campaign's effort to "focus on the people in the middle." During the press conference, Romney called for the full video to be released. "Mitt wants the full video huh? Well don't worry, there's more to come," Mother Jones reporter Adam Serwer tweeted in response. WASHINGTON -- The overwhelming majority of voters who back President Barack Obama do so because they are "dependent on government" and "believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing," Mitt Romney told a closed-door gathering of about 30 major donors earlier this year, according to video of the event that has surfaced on the Internet. The person who uploaded a series of potentially inflammatory videos from the fundraiser has claimed authorship of them in an email exchange with The Huffington Post. The source said he or she wishes to remain anonymous for professional reasons and to avoid a lawsuit. The videos, which have created a buzz on the Internet, were blurred and at times blacked out to obscure the location of the filming, the source said. "I have obviously degraded the quality to attempt to camo the location," said the clandestine filmmaker. The original, which has not been posted in full, is very high quality, the source said. The source has given the full video to Mother Jones' David Corn, the source said. The videos capture Romney speaking loosely about Obama supporters, immigrants, privilege and a host of other controversial issues. The candidate seems unguarded and displays the sense of humor that is often mentioned by those close to him, but is so rarely on public display. It's Romney's remark about the president's backers that might have the most potential to undermine his candidacy, however, as Romney seeks to persuade people who voted for Obama in 2008 to switch this time. "There are 47 percent of the people who will vote for the president no matter what," Romney says in one clip. "All right -- there are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent on government, who believe that, that they are victims, who believe that government has the responsibility to care for them. Who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing." Romney's comments on the video go a step beyond his August claim, made in public, that the Obama administration's state-by-state welfare waivers were an effort to "shore up his base." In the behind-closed-doors speech to donors, Romney seems to be suggesting that nearly half of Americans expect to have all their needs supplied by the government. "[M]y job is not to worry about those people. I'll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives," Romney also said in the video, according to Mother Jones. As for the other 53 percent? Romney may have been referencing a meme started by conservative blogger Erick Erickson, who has noted that only 53 percent of Americans pay federal income taxes. Erickson argued that the rest of the country, and in particular the Occupy Wall Street movement, should "suck it up you whiners." The notion that Democrats hope to ride dependency to political power is one that has no shortage of adherents among conservatives. “We are reaching the tipping point where the majority of Americans are recipients of government programs,” columnist George Will said recently on Laura Ingraham's radio show. "Heavens, one in seven of Americans is on food stamps today. The gamble -- it's really not a gamble, the tactic -- of the Democratic Party is to run up the dependency ratio in this country until you get 50-60 percent of Americans dependent on the government in at least one or often in multiple ways, at which point they figure the party of government will always win." But there are a few problems with the idea of the overburdened "53 percent." Many Americans don't pay federal income taxes, in part, because of deductions like the child tax credit that have been championed by conservatives and progressives alike. Almost all of the "47 percent" do pay other federal taxes in the form of Social Security and Medicare payroll deductions and gas levies, as well as a variety of state and local sales and property taxes that aren't dependent on income. "Mitt Romney wants to help all Americans struggling in the Obama economy. As the governor has made clear all year, he is concerned about the growing number of people who are dependent on the federal government, including the record number of people who are on food stamps, nearly one in six Americans in poverty, and the 23 million Americans who are struggling to find work," Romney spokeswoman Gail Gitcho said in a statement responding to the video's release. "Mitt Romney's plan creates 12 million new jobs in four years, grows the economy and moves Americans off of government dependency and into jobs." A separate video clip that featured Romney addressing deplorable conditions at a Chinese factory began making the rounds on the Internet last month. In that video, he contrasted the conditions he witnessed on a business trip to China with conditions in the United States, where he said, "Ninety-five percent of life is set up for you if you were born in this country." Commentators have seized on the assertion that people are mostly set if they're born in the U.S. In fact, tens of millions of Americans are jobless or living in poverty. The notion also cuts against one of Romney's campaign themes, which is that those who are successful have gotten to where they are on their own. In addition, the video is notable for Romney's recounting of conditions he saw at the factory. By his own telling, he seemed satisfied when the factory owner told him the barbed wire was to keep job-seekers out, not to keep workers in. Romney may have been referring to conditions at Global Tech Appliances Inc., a Chinese manufacturer, in which Bain Capital invested, that was fined $2.65 million for ripping off a deep-fat fryer design, according to Boston Globe reporter Matt Viser. There are at least 10 of these videos, each allegedly clipped from the same fundraiser. A YouTube link to the Chinese factory clip, it turns out, was initially posted in May in the comments section of The Huffington Post under the handle romneyexposed. The commenter posted a link to a YouTube account by the same name, which includes a version of the factory video and three others. Six more videos exist under another account. In one of the other videos, Romney lamented, in a joking way, that he would have a better chance of being elected if his father had been ethnically Mexican, rather than born to white parents living in Mexico. "My dad, as you probably, know was the governor of Michigan and was the head of a car company. But he was born in Mexico ... and, uh, had he been born of, uh, Mexican parents, I'd have a better shot at winning this," Romney said. "But he was unfortunately born to Americans living in Mexico. ... I mean I say that jokingly, but it would be helpful to be Latino." In a separate video, Romney talks about his success. "Both my dad and [wife] Ann's dad did quite well in their lives. But when they came to the end of their lives and passed along the inheritance to Ann and me, we both decided to give it all away. So I have inherited nothing. Everything that Ann and I have, we earned the old-fashioned way." Romney's parents did pay for his boarding school, his college, his graduate school and his first home. He got closer to the truth in another clip. "There's a perception that all of you were born with a silver spoon. You know, you never had to earn anything and so forth," Romney said to the donors. "Frankly, I was born with a silver spoon, which is the greatest gift you can have -- which is to get born in America." Brad Shannon contributed reporting This story was updated to add context from a fuller version of the video posted by Mother Jones, and to add a response from the Romney campaign.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347942327855</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347942716333-2</Id><Title>An added, delicious touch of irony</Title><Msg>Mon Sep 17, 2012 at 06:10 PM PDT Jimmy Carter's Grandson Made the Mitt Romney Video Viral (Special Appearance by Daily Kos) by FiredUpInCA New York magazine traced the story behind the Mitt Romney Youtube video that has been around for a few months but only became wildly viral today. Here's the crux of the report: The damning video of Mitt Romney telling a room of wealthy donors how he really feels about the free-loading 47 percent of Americans "who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it," among other candid things, has been floating around online in bits and pieces for three months, but didn't hit the big time until it was published by David Corn at Mother Jones today. Credited as a "research assistant" on the story is James Carter IV, the grandson of former President Jimmy Carter, who has been toiling online as an opposition researcher and is "currently looking for work," according to his Twitter bio. "I've been searching for clips on Republicans for a long time, almost every day," said Carter this evening. "I just do it for fun." But by connecting Corn with the mysterious uploader of the clip, Carter has uncovered his biggest story yet, one that could potentially affect the outcome of the election. (And get him a job.) Carter told Daily Intel that he first noticed a portion of the video in which Romney discusses using Chinese labor while working at Bain Capital. That clip, uploaded by a YouTube user named "Rachel Maddow" in late May, has since been deleted, but eventually made it to Buzzfeed and Daily Kos. American Bridge has incorporated the video into an ad (I presume a web ad) here. Hat tip to Susan from 29: Wouldn't it be ironic if they guy who takes such glee in denigrating the legacy of Jimmy Carter, has his political career ended by the literal legacy of Jimmy Carter?</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347942716333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347975559530-3</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot caught on tape</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347915563510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't be hatin' on the rich folks junglebob.. In it's stead, aspire to become successful in your own right.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1347975559530</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347976505460-4</Id><Title>Quite the Performance</Title><Msg>being put on here. Down 7% in about 7 hours of trading in a slightly down tape. I would hate to see what would happen with a full blown market correction. Nothing has changed.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1347976505460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347978297712-5</Id><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Msg>Obama campaign manager Jim Messina releases a statement on the newly surfaced video of Mitt Romney telling wealthy campaign donors that nearly half of all Americans are worthless freeloading moochers who don't pay any taxes: It's shocking that a candidate for President of the United States would go behind closed doors and declare to a group of wealthy donors that half the American people view themselves as ‘victims,’ entitled to handouts, and are unwilling to take ‘personal responsibility’ for their lives. It’s hard to serve as president for all Americans when you’ve disdainfully written off half the nation.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347978758302-6</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Krugman - New York Times Blog September 17, 2012, 5:10 pm The Real Romney Oh, my. Mother Jones has what it says is a video of Mitt Romney talking to donors; it sure looks and sounds real. And it reveals a candidate who despises half the country: There are 47 percent of the people who will vote for the president no matter what. All right, there are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent upon government, who believe that they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it. That that’s an entitlement. And the government should give it to them. And they will vote for this president no matter what…These are people who pay no income tax. Actually, if you look at the facts, you learn that the great bulk of those who pay no income tax pay other taxes; also, many of the people in the no-income-tax category are (a) elderly (b) students or (c) having a bad year, having lost a job — that is, they’re people who have paid income taxes in the past and/or will pay income taxes in the future. The idea that half of Americans are just grifters is grotesque. If this is real, it’s very, very ugly.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978758302</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347980632005-7</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot caught on tape</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347915563510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he's (apparently) an investor, so at least he's realized you don't get rich without putting your own money at risk. That's a big first step.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1347980632005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:03:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347980799708-8</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, those on welfare programs are not going to vote for Romney. Darn right, it is hard after 4 years of moral destruction and decay, trying to win hearts of another half of the country is a mountain to climb. Romney was talking only about winning up coming election. Obama doesn't count on those who have strong sense of personal responsibility for their lives and and have 2nd part of the brain. Who do you think Obama addresses saying "fair shot, fair share"? Millions of us never buy this concept. So, arrogant Obama implicitly discards a category which strongly disagree. But he would never say it openly. I would prefer him to be honest. But apparently, too much to ask.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347980799708</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347982806554-9</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dipshidiot is exposed now as the candidate OF and FOR the super rich. It's on tape and conclusive. GOP only hope is suppressing the vote.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347982806554</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347983048824-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot caught on tape</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347915563510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:59:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Strickland: Romney speaks "with such disdain about so many Americans" (CNN) Strickland says, “Well, it wasn’t a bump in the road, it was a deep chasm, in my judgment. And quite frankly, what the Governor said is very significant because it reveals something about his value system. For him to speak with such disdain about so many Americans and he wants to be our President? Some of those people that he was talking about, Soledad, are soldiers that are risking their lives at this very moment in Afghanistan. Some of those people he was talking about in such a disdainful way are older people. How can this man who wants to be president talk in such a disdainful way about half of the American people, and then hope to pull this country together and to be our president.” He continues, “He’s very sly…. Many people don’t pay income taxes because they’re so poor they don’t make enough money to be able to pay income taxes. But they pay payroll taxes, they pay state taxes, they pay excise taxes. This man apparently feels that if you’re not a part of his social class or you don’t have his economic status, that somehow you’re a parasite.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347983048824</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 11:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347987098555-11</Id><Topic><Title>An added, delicious touch of irony</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347942716333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bless those Carters!</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1347987098555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 12:51:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347988994605-12</Id><Title>Mitt:: "it's not my job to worry about those people" (enough to worry about the 1% , right?)</Title><Msg>(mittens whines about gop tax cuts......while kissing billionaire rear end and promising THEM tax cuts) "You can’t have it both ways—cut taxes then blame the opposition for not paying taxes. Ronald Reagan successfully pushed the Earned Income Tax Credit, which gives working class people money back as an incentive for working. The Earned Income Tax Credit was expanded by Newt Gingrich on the way to welfare reform Bill Clinton signed in 1997. Republican-favored tax credits to the elderly, passed with winning states like Florida in mind, eliminated millions of elderly tax payers from the tax rolls. George W. Bush’s massive 2001 tax cuts eliminated millions of lower-income people off the tax rolls. His massive 2003 tax cut, much of which directed at the wealthiest Americans by way of exempting investment income, lowered the tax liabilities of another chunk (Romney was in that batch). The expansion of the child tax credit eliminated millions more (7.8 million, according to the Tax Foundation). A good many millionaires, too, pay no income taxes: 4,000 ...."</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1347988994605</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347991390611-13</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thw whole Democratic Covention was parading crack pot 47%ers in front of the nation...69% of Democrats think government should have more involvement in their lives...so what is the surprise here.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347991390611</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347992249523-14</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% GOP is so proud of their past GOP presidents that they were ashamed to show any one of them to the nation lest the memory returns of the damage they made and are likely to cause once again if elected.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1347992249523</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347992822228-15</Id><Title>The world will love us because...</Title><Msg>...of my Obamaness. Where does anyone get this kind of hubris from... answer: All his life folks have been kissing his behind because as Joe(you'all)Biden said, he is a articulate clean blackman. The whole Obama middle east doctrine is on its head. These people hate us and Democracy, they feel that their prophet Muhammad is the way...end of story. For some junior senator and community organizer to think different is at best navie, and at worst maniacal. "I truly believe that the day I'm inaugurated not only does the country look at itself differently, but the whole world looks at America differently". "If I'm reaching out to the Muslim world they understand that I've lived in a Muslim country, and I may be a Christian, but I understand their point of view." "My sister is half Indonesian. I traveled there all the way through my college years so I am intimately concerned with what happens in these countries and the cultures and perspectives these folks have."</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347992822228</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347993040382-16</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If that is true then why wasn't Jimmy(I'll never lie to you)Cater speaking at prime time?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347993040382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347993643604-17</Id><Topic><Title>'It's hard to serve as president for all-when you’ve written off 1/2 the nation'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347978297712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 10:24:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you define a 53% of the country, as super rich? Well, no surprise. You never lived in China. Didn't you?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1347993643604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 14:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347995329546-18</Id><Title>Dipshidiot, the sneering plutocrat, the real class warrior</Title><Msg>Yesterday at 10:26 PM 401Comments The Real Romney Captured on Tape Turns Out to Be a Sneering Plutocrat By Jonathan Chait LOS ANGELES, CA - SEPTEMBER 17: Republican presidential candidate, former Massachusetts Gov. Mitt Romney addresses the U.S. Hispanic Chamber of Commerce's 33rd annual national convention on September 17, 2012 in Los Angeles, California. Romney's campaign staff says it plans to retool their message by being more specific of Romney's policies. (Photo by Kevork Djansezian/Getty Images) Presidential campaigns wallow so tediously in pseudo-events and manufactured outrage that our senses can be numbed to the appearance of something genuinely momentous. Mitt Romney’s secretly recorded comments at a fund-raiser are such an event — they reveal something vital about Romney, and they disqualify his claim to the presidency. To think of Romney’s leaked discourse as a “gaffe” grossly misdescribes its importance. Indeed the comments’ direct impact on the outcome of the election will probably be small. Romney repeated the wildly misleading but increasingly popular conservative talking point that 47 percent of Americans pay no income taxes. The federal income tax is, by design, one of the most progressive elements of the American tax system, but well over 80 percent of non-retired adults pay federal taxes. But most people hear “income taxes” and think “taxes,” which is why the trick of using one phrase to make audiences think of the other is a standard GOP trick when discussing taxes. For that very reason, it won’t strike many voters as an insult: Most people who don’t pay income taxes do pay other taxes, and fail to distinguish between them, and thus don’t consider themselves among the 47 percent scorned by Romney. Instead the video exposes an authentic Romney as a far more sinister character than I had imagined. Here is the sneering plutocrat, fully in thrall to a series of pernicious myths that are at the heart of the mania that has seized his party. He believes that market incomes in the United States are a perfect reflection of merit. Far from seeing his own privileged upbringing as the private-school educated son of an auto executive-turned-governor as an obvious refutation of that belief, Romney cites his own life, preposterously, as a confirmation of it. (“I have inherited nothing. Everything I earned I earned the old fashioned way.”) It is possible to cling to some version of this dogma and still believe, or to convince yourself, that cutting taxes for the rich or reducing benefits for the poor will eventually help the latter, by teaching them personal responsibility or freeing up Job Creators to favor them with opportunity. Instead Romney regards them as something akin to a permanent enemy class — “I’ll never convince them that they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives.” Romney explained to reporters tonight that his remarks were not "elegantly stated," but did not repudiate them as his true beliefs. In fact, it was quite eloquently stated. The Romney speaking to fund-raisers was not the halting, smarmy figure so frequently on public display but an eloquent and passionate orator. He had no reason to believe his donors needed to hear him denounce the poor — they would have been perfectly satisfied with a bromide about how cutting taxes on the rich will create opportunity for one and all. Instead he put himself forward as the hopeful president of the top half of America against the bottom. Some pundits have likened Romney’s comments to Barack Obama’s 2008 monologue, also secretly recorded at a fund-raiser, about his difficulties with white working class voters in rural Pennsylvania. But the spirit of Obama’s remarks was precisely the opposite of Romney’s. While Obama couched his beliefs in condescending sociological analysis about how poor small town residents vote on the basis of guns and religion rather than economics, the thrust of Obama’s argument was that he believed his policies would help them, and to urge his supporters to make common cause with them: But the truth is, is that, our challenge is to get people persuaded that we can make progress when there's not evidence of that in their daily lives. You go into some of these small towns in Pennsylvania, and like a lot of small towns in the Midwest, the jobs have been gone now for 25 years and nothing's replaced them. And they fell through the Clinton administration, and the Bush administration, and each successive administration has said that somehow these communities are gonna regenerate and they have not. So it's not surprising then that they get bitter, they cling to guns or religion or antipathy to people who aren't like them or anti-immigrant sentiment or anti-trade sentiment as a way to explain their frustrations. Um, now these are in some communities, you know. I think what you'll find is, is that people of every background — there are gonna be a mix of people, you can go in the toughest neighborhoods, you know working-class lunch-pail folks, you'll find Obama enthusiasts. And you can go into places where you think I'd be very strong and people will just be skeptical. The important thing is that you show up and you're doing what you're doing. Obama was aspiring to become president of all of America, even that part most hostile to him, in the belief that what they shared mattered more than what divided them. Romney genuinely seems to conceive of the lowest-earning half of the population as implacably hostile parasites. The revelations in this video come to me as a genuine shock. I have never hated Romney. I presumed his ideological makeover since he set out to run for president was largely phony, even if he was now committed to carry through with it, and to whatever extent he’d come to believe his own lines, he was oblivious or naïve about the damage he would inflict upon the poor, sick, and vulnerable. It seems unavoidable now to conclude that Romney’s embrace of Paul Ryanism is born of actual contempt for the looters and moochers, a class war on behalf of his own class.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347995329546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347995893905-19</Id><Title>Let that be the last time you force that cheap kibble on me!!!</Title><Msg>ARE dogs taking over the world? Two men, on opposite sides of the world, have been shot by their alleged best friends. One man's shooting trip in Utah, US took a surprise turn when he was shot in the buttocks - by his own dog. Meanwhile in France, a 55-year-oldd hunter had to have his right hand amputated after his dog accidentally shot him has said he doesn't blame the pet, which he still considers "adorable". The 46-year-old American (naturally) took his best buddy along on a duck hunt in Utah, before his four-legged pal "accidentally" stepped on a shotgun. The man was rushed to hospital but avoided any serious injuries, the Telegraph (UK) reports. How did it happen? The man was getting out of his boat when the dog shot across the bow, as it were. Kevin Potter, the Box Elder County Sheriff's deputy, who wasn't shot, said: "(The dog) did something to make the gun discharge. I don't know if the safety device was on. It's not impossible the dog could have taken it off safety." It just boils down to this: dog shoots owner. In the butt. Hahahahahahahahahahahahaha. That felt good. The French hunter, identified only as Rene, told France Bleu radio the dog accidentally pulled the trigger of his shotgun when he jumped on him while they were hunting on Sunday in the Dordogne region. Rene said he was hunting with three dogs when two of them ran off after a deer while the youngest stayed behind. "He jumped on top of me for a cuddle" and accidentally fired the gun, shooting him in the right hand, Rene said. The hunter was taken by helicopter to a hospital in Bordeaux but the damage was too serious and the hand had to be amputated. "It wasn't the dog's fault," Rene insisted. "And he's adorable! I should have left the (gun's) safety on, that's all." PS. Were they really accidents? TRUST NO ONE.</Msg><Username>hooveredbyndavis</Username><Timestamp>1347995893905</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348001622510-20</Id><Topic><Title>As I 've been explaining to you dummies for years now.....</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347928733900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Robert Frank | CNBC – Mon, Sep 17, 2012 11:00 AM EDT Cutting taxes for the wealthy does not generate faster economic growth, according to a new report. But those cuts may widen the income gap between the rich and the rest, according to a new report. A study from the Congressional Research Service -- the non-partisan research office for Congress -- shows that "there is little evidence over the past 65 years that tax cuts for the highest earners are associated with savings, investment or productivity growth." In fact, the study found that higher tax rates for the wealthy are statistically associated with higher levels of growth. The finding is likely to fuel to the already bitter political fight over taxing the rich, with President Obama and the Democrats calling for higher taxes on the wealthy to reduce the deficit and fund spending. Mitt Romney and the GOP advocate lower marginal tax rates for top earners, saying they fuel investment and job creation. The CRS study looked at tax rates and economic growth since 1945. The top tax rate in 1945 was above 90 percent, and fell to 70 percent in the 1960s and to a low of 28 percent in 1986. The top current rate is 35 percent. The tax rate for capital gains was 25 percent in the 1940s and 1950s, then went up to 35 percent in the 1970s, before coming down to 15 percent today - the lowest rate in more than 65 years. Lowering these rates for the wealthy, the study found, isn't aligned with significant improvement in any of the areas it examined. Pushing tax rates down had a "negligible effect" on private saving, and while it does note a relationship between investing and capital gains rates, the correlations "are not statistically significant," the study says. "Top tax rates," it concludes, "do not necessarily have a demonstrably significant relationship with investment." The study said that lower marginal rates have a "slight positive effect" on productivity while lower capital gains rates have a "slight negative association" with productivity. But, again, neither effect was considered statistically significant. Do higher taxes on the rich lead to faster economic growth? Not necessarily. The paper says that while growth accelerated with higher taxes on the rich, the relationship is "not strong" and may be "coincidental," since broader economic factors may be responsible for that growth. There is one part of the economy, however, that is changed by tax cuts for the rich: inequality. The study says that the biggest change in the distribution of U.S. income has been with the top 0.1 percent of earners - not the one percent. [ More From CNBC: One Percent Gives Up Ground -- to the Five Percent ] The share of total income going to the top 0.1 percent hovered around 4 percent during the 1950s, 1960s and 1970s, then rose to 12 percent by the mid-2000s. During this period, the average tax rate paid by the 0.1 percent fell from more than 40 percent to below 25 percent. The study said that "as top tax rates are reduced, the share of income accruing to the top of the income distribution increases" and that "these relationships are statistically significant." In other words, cutting taxes on the rich may not grow the economic pie. But the study found that those cuts can effect "how that economic pie is sliced."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348001622510</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348001975686-21</Id><Title>GOP Senate candidates denounce Dipshidiot</Title><Msg>GOP Sen. Scott Brown denounces Romney comments Last edited Tue Sep 18, 2012 Source: the hill Sen. Scott Brown (R-Mass.) came out in opposition to GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney's controversial comments that were made public last night, an attempt to distance himself from a candidate that remains deeply unpopular in Massachusetts. The candidate joins Republican candidate for Senate in Connecticut Linda McMahon in coming out against the statements, making them thus far the only two Republican candidates for Senate to denounce Romney's remarks on the "47 percent." "That’s not the way I view the world. As someone who grew up in tough circumstances, I know that being on public assistance is not a spot that anyone wants to be in. Too many people today who want to work are being forced into public assistance for lack of jobs," he said in the email.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348001975686</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 16:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348002102242-22</Id><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Msg>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage, and now he denounces those who make that wage and who are too poor to pay income taxes as bums and mooches..........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348007709834-23</Id><Topic><Title>An added, delicious touch of irony</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347942716333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing I will give Jimmy(I'll never lie to you)Carter, he was the best friend to folks on fixed incomes...CD @16%. Unfortunately if your were trying to buy a home mortgage rates were also at 16%. That was the beggining of the negative amortization loans.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348007709834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348008582515-24</Id><Topic><Title>Quite the Performance</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1347976505460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are u holding any positions?</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1348008582515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 18:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348010899825-25</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's host</Title><Msg>When Mitt Romney at a private fundraiser dismissed all Barack Obama voters as moochers and victims—showing disdain for nearly half of the American electorate—he was speaking at the home of controversial private equity manager Marc Leder in Boca Raton on May 17, 2012. (It was Romney's second fundraising event in Boca that day.) This is evident from references made by Romney within the full video recording of the event that has been reviewed by Mother Jones. When Mother Jones first disclosed secret video of Romney's remarks, we were obliged to not reveal details regarding the time and place of the event. That restriction has been lifted, as the story has garnered attention throughout the media. At the fundraiser, Romney was asked how he could win in November, and he replied: There are 47 percent of the people who will vote for the president no matter what. All right, there are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent upon government, who believe that they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it. That that's an entitlement. And the government should give it to them. And they will vote for this president no matter what…These are people who pay no income tax…[M]y job is is not to worry about those people. I'll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives. Romney made those remarks before donors who had paid $50,000 a plate to attend the dinner at Leder's swanky house. Leder has long been a fan of Romney. In January, the New York Times reported: Years ago, a visit to Mr. Romney's investment firm inspired Mr. Leder to get into private equity in the first place. Mr. Romney was an early investor in some of the deals done by Mr. Leder's investment company, Sun Capital, which today oversees about $8 billion in equity. The paper noted that Leder is something of a poster boy for private equity—and not in a good way: Mr. Leder personifies the debates now swirling around this lucrative corner of finance. To his critics, he represents everything that's wrong with this setup. In recent years, a large number of the companies that Sun Capital has acquired have run into serious trouble, eliminated jobs or both. Since 2008, some 25 of its companies—roughly one of every five it owns—have filed for bankruptcy. Among the losers was Friendly's, the restaurant chain known for its Jim Dandy sundaes and Fribble shakes. (Sun Capital was accused by a federal agency of pushing Friendly's into bankruptcy last year to avoid paying pensions to the chain's employees; Sun disputes that contention.) Another company that sank into bankruptcy was Real Mex, owner of the Chevy's restaurant chain. In that case, Mr. Leder lost money for his investors not once, but twice. But Leder does differ from Romney in one significant fashion: how he likes to have a certain sort of fun. In August 2011, the New York Post reported, It was as if the Playboy Mansion met the East EBond at a wild party at private-equity titan Marc Leder's Bridgehampton estate, where guests cavorted nude in the pool and performed sex acts, scantily dressed Russians danced on platforms and men twirled lit torches to a booming techno beat. The divorced Sun Capital Partners honcho rented a sprawling beachfront mansion on Surf Side Road for $500,000 for the month of July. Leder's weekly Friday and Saturday night parties have become the talk of the Hamptons—and he ended them in style last weekend with his wildest bash yet. Russell Simmons and ex-wife Kimora Lee attended a more subdued party thrown by Leder—who's an event chair for Simmons' Art For Life charity—on July 29 together. But the revelry hit a frenzied point the next day before midnight when a male guest described as a "chubby white meathead" and a "tanned" female guest stripped and hopped into the pool naked. At Romney's fundraiser at Leder's Boca Raton home, not a single sex act was recorded.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348010899825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348011393240-26</Id><Topic><Title>An added, delicious touch of irony</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1347942716333</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 00:31:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Worth finding on youtube: Keith Olbermann's EPIC Special Comment on Romney's videotape disaster</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348011393240</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:36:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348012709776-27</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot, the sneering plutocrat, the real class warrior</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347995329546</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 15:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Posted at 07:00 PM ET, 09/17/2012 Mitt Romney trashes the 47 percent By Jonathan Capehart Back in February, Mitt Romney stuck his ample silver foot in his mouth when he told CNN’s Soledad O’Brien, “I’m not concerned about the very poor.” He went on to say, “We have a safety net there. If it needs repair, I’ll fix it. I’m not concerned about the very rich, they’re doing just fine. I’m concerned about the very heart of the America, the 90, 95 percent of Americans who right now are struggling, and I’ll continue to take that message across the nation.” Late Monday, Mother Jones released several video clips of a fundraiser where Romney (R-1 percent) tells weatlhy donors exactly what he thinks of those supporting President Obama. In one clip, he contradicts that botched expression of concern for the middle class. In fact, what the Republican presidential nominee said is reprehensible and unbecoming a man who claims to want to be president of all Americans. There are 47 percent of the people who will vote for the president no matter what. All right, there are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent upon government, who believe that they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it. That that's an entitlement. And the government should give it to them. And they will vote for this president no matter what. And, I mean, the president starts off with 48, 49 [percent], he starts with a huge number. These are people who pay no income tax. Forty-seven percent of Americans pay no income tax. So our message of low taxes doesn’t connect. So he’ll be out there talking about tax cuts for the rich. I mean, that’s what they sell every four years. And so my job is is not to worry about those people. I’ll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives. What I have to do is convince the five to 10 percent in the center that are independents, that are thoughtful, that look at voting one way or the other depending upon, in some cases, emotion, whether they like the guy or not . . . Mother Jones said it did not reveal the date of the fundraiser or its location in order to protect its source. But nothing should protect Romney from the avalanche of criticism already coming his way. As Greg Sargent notes, “[T]he ranks of the oft-discussed 47 percent, many of whom pay no federal income taxes but do pay state and local taxes, are swelled with working class voters and seniors, and many of them are obviously Romney supporters — and hardly think of themselves as Big Government freeloaders.” That one-minute-seven-second clip lays waste to Romney’s concern “about the very heart of America, the 90, 95 percent of Americans who right now are struggling.” Worse, it reveals it to be a lie. He couldn’t care less about them, it seems. That condescending clip shows a contempt for half the country that demands an explanation from Romney.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348012709776</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 19:58:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348013009634-28</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you ever work for minimal wage? Do you know anyone who works for minimal wage all his/her life? Don't try to find one. They don't exist. Visit McDonalds for once. See how many old wrinkled faces you'll find there behind cachier stand. Oh, by the way, those on minimal wage have more reasons to vote for Romney, because they are looking up in their carrier ladder, not stuck in the mud like now. Romaney promiss to give them jobs with decent salaries, not government assistance.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348013009634</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:03:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348015294783-29</Id><Title>Who are the 47% ?</Title><Msg>September 17, 2012 Behind the ‘People Who Pay No Income Tax’ By ANNIE LOWREY Mother Jones has published a video of Mitt Romney at a private fund-raiser making incendiary remarks about Obama voters – and, well, about half of the electorate. “There are 47 percent of the people who will vote for the president no matter what,” Mr. Romney said. “There are 47 percent who are with him, who are dependent upon government, who believe that they are victims, who believe the government has a responsibility to care for them, who believe that they are entitled to health care, to food, to housing, to you-name-it, that that’s an entitlement. And the government should give it to them. And they will vote for this president no matter what.” “These are people who pay no income tax,” he added. I’ll address just that last part in this post. Mr. Romney is absolutely correct that about half of American households do not pay federal income tax. (He is also tapping into a now long-running vein of conservative anger at those households.) But he is missing some crucial context on why they do not pay federal income tax. The nonpartisan and highly respected Tax Policy Center derived the 47 percent number – it is actually 46 percent, as of 2011 – and published an excellent analysis of it last summer. It found that about half of the households that do not pay federal income tax do not pay it because they are simply too poor. The Tax Policy Center gives as an example a couple with two children earning less than $26,400 a year: The household would pay no federal income tax because its standard deduction and other exemptions would simply erase its liability. The other half, the Tax Policy Center found, consists of households taking advantage of tax credits and other provisions, mostly support for senior citizens and low-income working families. Put bluntly, these are not households shirking their tax liabilities. The pool consists mostly of the poor, of relatively low-income working families and of old people. The tax code is specifically designed to reduce the burden on them. Indeed, the recession and its aftermath have left tens of millions of workers out of a job or underemployed, removing more households from payment of federal income taxes. Moreover, the Bush tax cuts – the signature Republican economic policy of the 2000s, which doubled the child tax credit, increased a number of other deductions and exemptions, and lowered marginal tax rates – erased millions of families’ federal income tax liabilities. It is also worth noting that though tens of millions of families do not pay federal income taxes, there are virtually no families that do not pay any taxes – between payroll taxes, sales taxes, state and local taxes, and on and on. For much more detail on the 46 (or 47) percent, read my colleague David Leonhardt’s 2010 column or my 2011 piece for Slate.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348015294783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348015486497-30</Id><Topic><Title>Who are the 47% ?</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348015294783</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lowrey on 10-11-2011: "What is going on with that other 47 percent? Why are so few people paying income taxes? For the answer to that question, we turn to the nonpartisan Tax Policy Center, which released a study on the subject this July. (The TPC also put out the initial report with the 53 percent number.) The short answer is: deductions and poverty. About half of households within that 47 percent do not end up paying federal income tax because they qualify for enough breaks to cancel their tax obligations out. Of that group, 44 percent are claiming tax benefits for the elderly, like an exemption for Social Security payments. And 30.4 percent are claiming credits for “children and the working poor,” like the child-care tax credit. The remainder get breaks for investment income, spending on education, itemized deductions, and a mish-mash of other things. When combined, it’s all enough to cancel out their income tax requirements. In short, it is not that they are not paying their taxes. It is that the country’s tax structure lets them off the hook. Indeed, you can draw a straight line between the Bush tax cuts and the growing number of households exempted from income tax. For instance, the 2001 cuts, extended under the Obama administration, doubled the child tax credit from $500 to $1,000 and expanded eligibility for the Earned Income Tax Credit among married taxpayers. Additionally, the Bush tax cuts lowered income taxes in every bracket, making it easier for a household’s liability to get fully offset by deductions and credits. And on top of all that, the stimulus bill introduced a host of further tax cuts. That covers about half of the households that don’t pay any federal income taxes. The other half of households are just too poor to pay them. The Tax Policy Center provides a handy example: A couple with two children earning less than $26,400 per year pays no income tax if it takes standard deductions and common exemptions, for instance. “The basic structure of the income tax simply exempts subsistence levels of income from tax,” TPC’s Roberton Williams writes. That pool of too-poor households has grown much bigger because of the recession and its aftermath: Average incomes have kept on declining even though the recession has officially ended, and millions of households have lost one or both of their wage-earners. Households are earning about 10 percent less than they did in 2007. About 12 percent of families live in poverty. That means a lot of folks simply aren’t eligible for income tax. So what of the claim that the 53 percent are subsidizing the 99 percent? Well, just because 47 percent of households do not pay federal income tax does not mean that they do not pay any federal taxes. Indeed, almost everyone pays some: There are federal taxes for Social Security and Medicare, on gas, alcohol, and cigarettes. Plus, there are also state and local taxes, and property taxes. You’d have to be freegan to escape paying any tax at all.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348015486497</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348015916928-31</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fyi, a lot of jobs pay the minimum wage or close to it, and those working people are all part of the 47 % Mitt says it's not his job to represent, since they are , you know, mooches and bums. and btw, mitt's mooches and bums include jr enlisted in the miliary, for example and e-4 with 3 yrs makes $25884...... if that person had a dependent wife and 2 kids , their income tax would be ZERO making them some of gthe 47% of Americans who are bums, parasites and mooches seeking welfare according to mitt..........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348015916928</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 20:51:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348021077396-32</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't read the word I said. "those working people" are NOT all part of the 47 %. 47% Romney is talking about are those who want governement assistance and they belong to all income spectrum. Warren Buffet is in this group too. And you would be surprised to learn how many of those who make $25884 don't want Obama even near Oval Office. "bums, parasites and mooches seeking welfare" are clearly Obama voting block. What about other 53%? are they all rich?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348021077396</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348023304214-33</Id><Title>Mittens ist kaput, finished, fertig, toast!!!</Title><Msg>Mittens stuck his foot into his mouth again.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348023304214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:55:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348026035529-34</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens ist kaput, finished, fertig, toast!!!</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1348023304214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 22:55:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he has a shoe permanently implanted in his #$%$</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1348026035529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348026370937-35</Id><Title>Mittens Gets His Foriegn Policy from Sarah Palin !</Title><Msg>Mittens should be wearing a short skirt and and glasses !</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1348026370937</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 23:46:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>