<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348469912659-1</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats HAD 60 votes to pass Obamacare in December 2009. "just over five months" is way too much time to pass comprehensive immigration reform if it would be of priority. Problem is, the issue DIDN'T EVEN CAME UP into discussion! Stop looking for exuses! Obama didn't even bother to raise the topic in 2009 when he had 100% shot to pass it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348469912659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 02:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348490795861-2</Id><Title>there is no evidence that tax cuts spur economic growth says Congressional Research Service</Title><Msg>(but blind faith gop says just do more bush tax cuts....... and nevermind that the decade since those tax cuts has been one of the worst in USA history and there no evidence that tax cuts are correlated with economic growth and so says the non-partisan Congressional Research Service..........) "The results of the analysis suggest that changes over the past 65 years in the top marginal tax rate and the top capital gains tax rate do not appear correlated with economic growth. The reduction in the top tax rates appears to be uncorrelated with saving, investment, and productivity growth. The top tax rates appear to have little or no relation to the size of the economic pie." from Taxes and the Economy: An Economic Analysis of the Top Tax Rates Since 1945 Congressional Research Service &amp; as commented on in the business insider: "According to a new study by the Congressional Research Service (non-partisan), there's no evidence that tax cuts spur growth. In fact, although correlation is not causation, when you compare economic growth in periods with declining tax rates versus periods with high tax rates, there seems to be evidence that tax cuts might hurt growth. But we'll leave that possibility for another day."</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348490795861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 08:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348492660468-3</Id><Topic><Title>$8.50 is coming this week! Asia is down big!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348451180353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the advice. You are one of the only people on this board closely tracking Etrade.</Msg><Username>doubledown</Username><Timestamp>1348492660468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348493563719-4</Id><Topic><Title>$8.50 is coming this week! Asia is down big!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348451180353</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:46:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paid pumpers like 'Moon and 'Precious' like playing games...</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1348493563719</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348496005020-5</Id><Topic><Title>Topic #1: Why is it taking this company so long to find a new CEO?</Title><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1348341815259</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 15:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imposter. Not Brandish_Mow it is is Brandish_Now</Msg><Username>invlongtrm</Username><Timestamp>1348496005020</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348496718573-6</Id><Title>think things are bad now!</Title><Msg>wait till they dump more shares to pay off the springers!! this is just a piggy bank for the hedge funds to manipulate. they will leave the investors holding the bag with no darts and little interest money with lower rates. Thats why no one will buy a DEAD horse. fire the bunch!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1348496718573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348497133407-7</Id><Title>E*TRADE sitting on low end of the pullback! GET IN NOW!</Title><Msg>Etfc is a strong buy at $9 to $9.20 price range! Sitting on the low end of a healthy (etfc style) pullback. When it moves up its going to go fast and strong, expect movement up anytime from now into next week!</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1348497133407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 10:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348500910432-8</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems never had more than 58. How hard is that to grasp? and how long did they work on 'Obamacare' to get a consensus? And who threw them under the bus at at the end, Lieberman. Here is what it hard for the pubs to grasp, since they vote as one mind, the dems actually have varying opinions and getting 100% consensus is still a complicated task. The concerns of a New York senator on immigration might vary greatly from the concerns of an Arizona senator.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1348500910432</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:35:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348501853002-9</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Factoring in Congressional vacations in 2009, there were effectively only 25 days when Dems had control and that assumes a cooperative Lieberman (he wasn't very).</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348501853002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:50:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348502259146-10</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lieberman and the healthcare vote proved that Lieberman was not a dem. Period.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1348502259146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 11:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348502414565-11</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Democrats HAD 60 votes to pass Obamacare in December 2009. " That Obamacare, which nearly 60% of the country did not want. Comprehensive immigration reform never came up during Democrats majotity in Congress. Suddenly, few weeks before election, it became a serious issue. What a coincidence!. Your consensus nonsense is an excuse of doing NOTHING.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348502414565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:00:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348502960538-12</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty sure the 60 votes were not all Democratic senators, right? They had to deal with Lieberman to get it done and it ended upo being a VERY different bill than if dems actually had a 60 vote majority. See 58 != 60, still too hard to grasp? "consensus nonsense is an excuse of doing NOTHING" So does this hold true for the republican held congress?? Because their lack of ability to build a consensus with the democratic held senat sure makes them look like a do nothing congress.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1348502960538</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:09:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348504517585-13</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dude, it's not that the Dems are killing things on the voting floor, no, that isn't the case at all, instead they are killing them in committee or holding up the House/Senate reconciliation process. The filibuster is something the MINORITY party uses, not the majority, the majority party in the Senate does not NEED to filibuster.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1348504517585</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:35:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348504643028-14</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot's "tax evaviseness"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348449800563</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:23:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>| You are probably one of the 47% that don't pay taxes | There is a reason ALL GOP leaders (including Romney) are trying to distance themselves from those idiotic comments of their wanna-be-leader. They do it to survive. We can only hope that the dumb republican masses will keep on reviving it with comments like yours. That will practically ENSURE across the board win for the DEMS. So yea - revodcam - keep repeating that insult as much as you can - and when you have a chance - find out who really is a member of this 47%, and you will see that you are not only offending the Dems, but the independents AND republicans alike.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348504643028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348505342073-15</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The discussion never came up for all 4 yerars of Obama administration in ANY form. There was nothing to look cosensus for. Pretend to be dummy?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348505342073</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 12:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506425459-16</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lieberman voted for final version of Obamacare. Get a grip. Is Ben Nelson Democrat? He didn't like public option either. What about consensus?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348506425459</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506767078-17</Id><Topic><Title>Chance of a life time</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423544661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd love to have lunch, especially with Gore. Gore created the internet, or at lease the internet of Today. Don't laugh, just look up "High Performance Computing Act of 1991". And also, he's got that "Climate Change" thing going on. What a facinating man. I wish he had been elected instead of Bush. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348506767078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:12:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348506912795-18</Id><Topic><Title>Chance of a life time</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348423544661</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From the wikipedia: Among the many technological achievements that resulted from the funding of the Gore Bill, was the development of Mosaic in 1993,[5][10] the World Wide Web browser software which is credited by most scholars as beginning the Internet boom of the 1990s: Gore's legislation also helped fund the National Center for Supercomputing Applications at the University of Illinois, where a team of programmers, including Netscape founder Marc Andreessen, created the Mosaic Web browser, the commercial Internet's technological springboard. 'If it had been left to private industry, it wouldn't have happened,' Andreessen says of Gore's bill, 'at least, not until years later.' [11]</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1348506912795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348508800916-19</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The ACA then passed by a vote of 60–39 on December 24, 2009, with all Democrats and two Independents voting for, all but one Republican voting against and one senator (Jim Bunning, R-Ky.) not voting.[167]" Public opinion can best be characterized as "confused", IMO owing to a steady GOP campaign to denigrate the plan: Public opinion Polls indicated that a majority of Americans did not support the overall law, although specific elements were very popular across the political spectrum, with the notable exception of the mandate to purchase insurance. Democrats favored the law, while Republicans and Independents did not. For example, a Reuters-Ipsos poll during June 2012 indicated the following: 56% of Americans overall were against the law, with 44% supporting it. By party affiliation, 75% of Democrats, 27% of Independents, and 14% of Republicans favored the law overall. 82% favored banning insurance companies from denying coverage to people with pre-existing conditions. 61% favored allowing children to stay on their parents' insurance until age 26. 72% supported requiring companies with more than 50 employees to provide insurance for their employees. 61% opposed requiring all U.S. residents to own health insurance. By party affiliation, 19% of Republicans, 27% of Independents, and 41% of Democrats favored the mandate that all Americans buy health insurance.[239] Other topics receiving majority support among all three affiliations included: creation of insurance pools so small businesses and the uninsured had access to insurance exchanges to take advantage of large group pricing benefits; and providing subsidies on a sliding scale to aid individuals and families who cannot afford health insurance.[240][241] Other specific ideas that showed majority support, such as purchasing drugs from Canada, limiting malpractice awards, and reducing the age to qualify for Medicare, were not enacted.[242] Public opinion supported healthcare reform proposals in 2008, but turned negative when the plan changed in 2009, and remains opposed to the final version that was signed in 2010.[243][244] Though in 2008 then-Senators Barack Obama and Joseph Biden campaigned against requiring adults to buy insurance;[245] in 2009 President Obama reportedly changed his mind and agreed with insurance industry and Democratic Congressional proposals to include an individual mandate.[246][247] Public opinion of the legislation turned negative when the individual mandate proposal was announced, and remains opposed by a margin of 10 percentage points.[243][244][248] In March 2010, pollsters probed the reasons for opposition. In a CNN poll, 62% of respondents said PPACA would "increase the amount of money they personally spend on health care," 56% said the bill "gives the government too much involvement in health care," and only 19% said they and their families would be better off with the legislation.[249] In The Wall Street Journal, pollsters Scott Rasmussen and Doug Schoen wrote, "One of the more amazing aspects of the health-care debate is how steady public opinion has remained... 81% of voters say it's likely the plan will end up costing more than projected [and 59%] say that the biggest problem with the health-care system is the cost: They want reform that will bring down the cost of care. For these voters, the notion that you need to spend an additional trillion dollars doesn't make sense."[250] USA Today found opinions were starkly divided by age, with a solid majority of seniors opposing the bill and a solid majority of those younger than 40 in favor.[251] A September 2010 Politico article reported that five House Democrats had run political ads highlighting their "no" votes on the bill, while there had not been any political ads highlighting a "yes" vote since April, when Harry Reid ran one. The article also reported a Kaiser Family Foundation poll "which showed 43 percent of the public supports the overhaul and 45 percent are opposed. Much of the disagreement falls along party lines."[252] As of February 2012, 72% of registered voters believe PPACA's individual mandate is unconstitutional, while 20% say it is permissible.[253] By a margin of 50% to 39%, Americans say the Supreme Court should overturn the entire statute.[254] The Supreme Court hearings occasioned public demonstrations including prayer vigils coordinated by the White House[255] and Tea Party Protests.[256] A June 2012 Reuters-Ipsos poll indicated that much of the opposition to the law was because Americans wanted more reform, not less. About one-third of Republicans and independents who oppose the law did so because it did not go far enough to fix healthcare. 71% of Republican opponents reject it overall, while 29% believed it did not go far enough, while independent opponents are divided 67% to 33%. Among Democratic opponents, 49% reject it overall, and 51% wanted the measure to go further.[239] A poll released in July 2012 showed that "most Americans (56%) want to see critics of President Obama's health care law drop efforts to block it and move on to other national issues."[257]</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348508800916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 13:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348515141494-20</Id><Title>A major pullback is due and coming soon as Q3 eps disappoints investors!</Title><Msg>ETFC will go down to $8 per share sooner than you think! Don't add anything until you see $8.0s! 99% accuracy with 10 years of trading only in ETFC!! GLTA!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348515141494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348516079015-21</Id><Title>Dipshidiot b--tchslaps Joe Sixpak</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney: It's fair I pay a lower tax rate than people making $50,000 by Jed Lewison He is the gift that keeps on giving: Pelley: Now, you made on your investments, personally, about $20 million last year. And you paid 14 percent in federal taxes. That's the capital gains rate. Is that fair to the guy who makes $50,000 and paid a higher rate than you did? Romney: It is a low rate. And one of the reasons why the capital gains tax rate is lower is because capital has already been taxed once at the corporate level, as high as 35 percent. Pelley: So you think it is fair? Romney: Yeah, I think it's the right way to encourage economic growth, to get people to invest, to start businesses, to put people to work. In Mitt Romney's world, the only people that matter are the people that start businesses. The poor schlubs who shop at them just don't count. And before you complain about him wanting business owners to pay lower taxes than their customers, just pause for a moment and be glad he's willing to pay any taxes at all. Mitt looks like he's having a meltdown in that clip.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348516079015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 15:47:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348517636371-22</Id><Title>Dipshisiot remains clueless</Title><Msg>Romney Now: In his interview with CBS News’ “60 Minutes” that aired Sunday night, Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney pointed to emergency rooms as a form of health care for people without insurance. “Well, we do provide care for people who don’t have insurance,” Romney told interviewer Scott Pelley. “If someone has a heart attack, they don’t sit in their apartment and — and die. We pick them up in an ambulance, and take them to the hospital, and give them care. And different states have different ways of providing for that care.” Romney Then: But Romney’s position is a shift from 2010, when he told MSNBC that part of the impetus for the Massachusetts health-care law was to keep people out of the ER. “It doesn’t make a lot of sense for us to have millions and millions of people who have no health insurance and yet who can go to the emergency room and get entirely free care for which they have no responsibility,” he said. ------------------------ Mr. Romney - On Behalf of ER Doctors and Nurses Everywhere... Last edited Mon Sep 24, 2012, 12:20 PM USA/ET - Edit history (1) I'd just like to tell you, stop now. Enough is enough. Of all the asinine, morally objectionable, ethically wrong-headed and just downright IGNORANT statements you have made (just in the past week!), this one takes the cake. The ER is not designed for Universal Care. It is designed for life-threatening emergencies. And yes, I know you were speaking of a "heart attack", but good God man, don't you realize people already use the ER for primary care? Don't you realize that's why people die in ERs, why people die every day, why the doctors and nurses are so overworked they can barely take care of the hordes of UNINSURED sick people streaming through the door as it is? Do you think ER care is free? Have you ever seen an ER bill? Do you know how many people have filed bankruptcy over an ER bill and/or uninsured hospital stay? How out-of-touch with reality are you, really? Now you tell us, "this is how we take care of our uninsured"? Even when you were Governor, you realized what a burden this put on the health care system. How much it raised costs on EVERYBODY, on the state, on the facilities. In the name of all that is right and good, is there nothing you won't say to get elected? Is there no end to your utter stupidity? If I sound angry, I am. Because I *am* an ER nurse. I know how wrong you are...and so do you.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348517636371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:13:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348518503914-23</Id><Topic><Title>The party of frightened old white men</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1348427082819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**We cannot come close to balancing the budget simply by cutting federal staffers or their salaries."** It is a great place to start. For every government employee eliminated, that's one less regulation added to the backs of folks in the private sector, along with less use of broadban for internet porno surfing on the job. BTW, how is that house hunting in the Hood going?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348518503914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348518985090-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshisiot remains clueless</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348517636371</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:13:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**If I sound angry, I am. Because I *am* an ER nurse. I know how wrong you are...and so do you** I hope he speak Spanish, and don't expect to get payed a single paso from those free loaders.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348518985090</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 16:36:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348523832958-25</Id><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Msg>Benghazi = Tehran Obama lied; Americans died.</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348525874553-26</Id><Title>Calipornia is turning in to a New Jersey ?</Title><Msg>Everyone is leaving California in search of a job, or to state with no income tax. Soon only the Leftwing parasites will remain. Thank you Prezidunce Obomba !</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348525874553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348526692499-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our Supreme Leader, Prezidunce. Obomba Husseini. is doing to the whole Middle East what Carter did to Iran in 1979. We, Left-wing Parasites call this "SOCIAL JUSTICE". Now everybody bend over and say Allahu akbar and god bless the Supreme Leader Prezidunce Obomba Husseini !!!</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348526692499</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:44:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348535975765-28</Id><Title>Mitt Romney a bush rerun..... bushalloveragain....</Title><Msg>Bush : trust me on the WMD and the tax cuts ,we're on the road to riches! details later, trust me! Romney: trust me on the tax cuts on top of the Bush tax cuts and on the increased military spending, i call all this deficit reduction..... trust me...... specifics later!! (So, if Romney wins, I get a huge tax cut......Plus full AS IS social security and medicare....... and defense spending will be increased.......... and all this is "deficit reduction"..........specifics on how it will work not given though........ this is all on blind faith? trusting a guy who offshores jobs, offshores his money to the caymans, refuses to submit 10 years of tax returns the same as he asked his vp candidates to do, and who windowdressed his 2011 return.........a guy who says it's not even his job to represent all Americans??)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348535975765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 21:19:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348539657907-29</Id><Topic><Title>Debunking the GOP myth that the Dems had complete control of Congress</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348453974487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:32:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have control of both the house and Senate. If you don't know how to introduce a bill in a manner that allows it to be passed you are called a democrate. Obama never tried to help the middle class. He never tried to pass a new tax bill .. All he and Nancy did was talk about how pretty they were and spend our money..Nancy got her just reward and now it is Obama's time.</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1348539657907</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348540666664-30</Id><Topic><Title>Romney dyed his face for Univision interview !!! LMFAO</Title><Username>serpa666</Username><Timestamp>1348449956108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:25:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What will he do to persuade log Cabin pubs to join him? LOL</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1348540666664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348541968140-31</Id><Title>Benghazi 4 days after the attack</Title><Msg>A CNN reporter walks into the wrecked embassy and picks Ambassador Stevens's diary up off the floor. Hello, Obama, you aren't even mailing it in anymore! Google the name Philippe Reines to see how much this administration cares about the deaths and how much it cares about covering its #$%$ Another story that Yahoo won't cover.</Msg><Username>quiveringpileofpoop</Username><Timestamp>1348541968140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348542638334-32</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi 4 days after the attack</Title><Username>quiveringpileofpoop</Username><Timestamp>1348541968140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give State Department's Philippe Reines a Break You may heard have that the State Department's Philippe Reines sent off an email with profanity to a member of the press as he responded to questions to the member of the media about the State Department's handling of the Libya crisis. Some are jumping him for losing his temper. Give Philippe a break. I know Philippe. He works hard for the American people. He is a good guy. He just got angry. Don't forget -- these are very, very difficult times for people at the State Department for many reasons, including that many of them knew the ambassador who was murdered and feel a huge loss beyond what we may realize. Yes, Philippe used profanity in responding to the media but who hasn't used profanity in his or her life, right? And if you haven't used it, and especially with the media, you might have thought about using it, right? Don't forget: the shoe was on the other foot recently. Governor Mitt Romney's traveling press secretary Rick Gorka lost his temper and cursed out the media in Poland. Big deal --who cares that Rick Gorka lost his temper and cursed out the media (the media can be annoying...)? So Rick lost his temper. And yes, so did Philippe. So what. It happens. People get angry. You might get angry. I do. Bottom line -- Philippe works hard (and so does Rick). They both are probably exhausted with no sleep and much pressure. So, can we move on?</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1348542638334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348542638852-33</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi 4 days after the attack</Title><Username>quiveringpileofpoop</Username><Timestamp>1348541968140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 22:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give State Department's Philippe Reines a Break You may heard have that the State Department's Philippe Reines sent off an email with profanity to a member of the press as he responded to questions to the member of the media about the State Department's handling of the Libya crisis. Some are jumping him for losing his temper. Give Philippe a break. I know Philippe. He works hard for the American people. He is a good guy. He just got angry. Don't forget -- these are very, very difficult times for people at the State Department for many reasons, including that many of them knew the ambassador who was murdered and feel a huge loss beyond what we may realize. Yes, Philippe used profanity in responding to the media but who hasn't used profanity in his or her life, right? And if you haven't used it, and especially with the media, you might have thought about using it, right? Don't forget: the shoe was on the other foot recently. Governor Mitt Romney's traveling press secretary Rick Gorka lost his temper and cursed out the media in Poland. Big deal --who cares that Rick Gorka lost his temper and cursed out the media (the media can be annoying...)? So Rick lost his temper. And yes, so did Philippe. So what. It happens. People get angry. You might get angry. I do. Bottom line -- Philippe works hard (and so does Rick). They both are probably exhausted with no sleep and much pressure. So, can we move on?</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1348542638852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348544062185-34</Id><Topic><Title>Obama = Carter</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1348523832958</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 17:57:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cheney/Bush lied - Americans died. 4,500 American soldiers died in Iraq because Cheney, Bush, Rice, Rumsfeld, etc. lied.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1348544062185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348545494168-35</Id><Title>Dipshidiot's "tax evaviseness"</Title><Msg>"More Questions Than Answers About Romney &amp; Taxes On Friday, Mitt Romney belatedly released just a single additional tax return — his 2011 filing — and a cryptic summary of the previous two decades. The summary featured no details about any individual year. And as for the 2011 return, it was cooked to produce a higher tax rate — and more favorable headlines — for Romney, calling into question what else in this and other returns was manipulated to produce a more favorable appearance. Here’s ten questions about his taxes that Mitt Romney still needs to answer: 1. After the election, when the subject of your tax returns is outside of the public glare, will you file an amended tax return to claim your full deduction of charitable contributions? Was the tax rate you reported for other years similarly manipulated? 2. Why was your 2011 income $7 million lower than you estimated it to be in January? How does someone overestimate their income by $7 million? 3. Financial disclosures show that you have as much as $82 million in your tax-deferred Individual Retirement Account, despite the fact that tax rules limited contributions into such accounts to $30,000 per year. Did you lowball the value of the assets you put into your IRA, as tax experts suspect? And did you do the same with gifts into your sons’ trusts? 4. What was the purpose of your Swiss bank account and the myriad offshore entities shown on your return, based in countries like the Cayman Islands and Luxembourg, if not to avoid taxes? 5. Can you explain what one tax expert has called a “mysterious one-time infusion of foreign tax credits” in 2008? 6. You have not disclosed any foreign bank account reports (FBARs). Did you file all FBARs on all of your offshore accounts with the Treasury Department by the legal deadlines each year? 7. You claim to have paid an average tax rate of 20 percent over the last 20 years based on a flawed calculation. What was your real tax rate? 8. Your 14 percent tax rate –- not to mention the approximately 10 percent tax rate you would have paid had you not inflated it — is less than what many middle-class Americans pay. And you paid just 0.2% of your income in payroll taxes, while most Americans pay about 15%. Do you think that is fair? 9. Your tax returns show that the Marriott Corporation paid you $260,390 in directors’ fees in 2011. When you were the company’s audit committee chair in the 1990s, were you aware that the company was abusing a notorious illegal tax shelter? 10. You say you’ve made a “commitment to the public” that your tax rate should not be below 13 percent. If you believe that the richest Americans shouldn’t be paying an exceptionally low tax rate, why don’t you support President Obama’s “Buffett Rule”? In fairness, Romney actually did answer question number eight during a 60 Minutes interview that aired last night. Romney argued that it is indeed “fair” for him to pay a lower tax rate on millions in investment income than a middle class worker pays on $50,000 in wages: Pelley: Now, you made on your investments, personally, about $20 million last year. And you paid 14 percent in federal taxes. That’s the capital gains rate. Is that fair to the guy who makes $50,000 and paid a higher rate than you did? Romney: It is a low rate. And one of the reasons why the capital gains tax rate is lower is because capital has already been taxed once at the corporate level, as high as 35 percent. Pelley: So you think it is fair? Romney: Yeah, I think it’s the right way to encourage economic growth, to get people to invest, to start businesses, to put people to work. Not only does none other than Ronald Reagan disagree with Romney, but his economic argument is also wrong. The Bush tax cuts for the wealthy ushered in the weakest job growth in decades. Lower taxes on the wealthy do not lead to job growth. In fact, the opposite appears to be true. BOTTOM LINE: It’s time for Mitt Romney to come clean about both his tax returns and plans to increase taxes on the middle class while slashing them even further for the wealthiest Americans."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348545494168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348545494171-36</Id><Topic><Title>Calipornia is turning in to a New Jersey ?</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348525874553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What kind of an idiotic Puke are you? You're criticizing New Jersey whose governator is Republican Chris Christie, the fat guy who likes hamburgers and icecreme. N.J. is #48 in regard to its economy, jobs, and balanced budget. Christie is a darling of the GOP because of his big mouth. Unenployment is rampant in N.J. The fat guy criticized California and its governor Jerry Brown. After China and Brasil, California is the largest economy in the world. Anyway, I like it when Pubs go at each other.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348545494171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348545495266-37</Id><Topic><Title>Calipornia is turning in to a New Jersey ?</Title><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1348525874553</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 18:31:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What kind of an idiotic Puke are you? You're criticizing New Jersey whose governator is Republican Chris Christie, the fat guy who likes hamburgers and icecreme. N.J. is #48 in regard to its economy, jobs, and balanced budget. Christie is a darling of the GOP because of his big mouth. Unenployment is rampant in N.J. The fat guy criticized California and its governor Jerry Brown. After China and Brasil, California is the largest economy in the world. Anyway, I like it when Pubs go at each other.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1348545495266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 23:58:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>