<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344313064000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Joe Biden</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344307533000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden is better looking and alot smarter than Dan Quale ever was!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1344313064000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:17:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344313371000-2</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slayer-darling, You've got it all wrong again just like pacifican! For your info, the Rednecks are among the Teapartiers.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1344313371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344313802000-3</Id><Title>Let's be honest for once</Title><Msg>" It was fine when the GOP was intensely speculating whether or not President Clinton was a drug trafficker, or whether or not Hillary Clinton had some guy killed because of something-something-travel-receipts, or which war heros were or were not really war heroes based on this guy who said that one thing one time or a bit more recently when we were determining whether the first non-white president was really even an American, given that he seems so suspiciously, you know, non-white, or which members of the House of Representatives were secretly in league with terrorists. Talking about a rich person's taxes, though—that's just too much. Mitt Romney has at this point gone to the barricades to keep the voting public from knowing how much money he made over the years, or how, or how much tax he paid on it, and I think we all can agree that only a monster would suggest that maybe if this guy wants to be president of These United States and come up new budgets and be in charge of the military and maybe help enforce laws against Wall Street types doing Wall Street things and other businesses doing other business things that maybe, just maybe, how he has conducted his own business dealings over recent years ought maybe to be a thing that the nation has a right to know, or at least has the right to be inherently suspicious of if it's not forthcoming. The defense offered is that the rich business guy who wants to be president is the real victim here. Since he is not legally obliged to tell us his past financial dealings, too bad for yous: If nothing else, this definitely shows Mitt's true Wall Street expertise, an industry in which anything not explicitly illegal is fair game, and the illegal things are fair game too if you think you won't get caught. Now that he's clammed up tighter than if he'd been caught in bed with a dead gay hooker, the rumors are flying, and Harry Reid says he had one of Romney's old business associates tell him this certain rumor, and that, my friend, is the true abomination. Or something. You know what? I don't even care anymore. Whatever's in Mitt Romney's old taxes, whether it be zero-tax years or Swiss tax amnesties or non-tithing or that he made several million dollars on a new product called Fetus Chow, it's apparently so bad that America wouldn't vote for the rich business guy if they saw it. At this point, that's bad enough. I realize that in Mitt Romney's circles accusations as gauche as "did this donkey even pay taxes at all?" are usually farmed out to Super PACs or mid-level rodent-haired surrogates, but I think America will survive the Senate Majority Leader making a nasty comment to a reporter during an election year. I am sorry the bad man insulted your money, Mitt. I am sorry the bad man insulted someone else's money, Reince. I can only imagine the pain your entire party must be in right now." mostly by Hunter</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344313802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344315007000-4</Id><Topic><Title>I didnt see those a-holes crying at the</Title><Username>hardbrownbone</Username><Timestamp>1344306807000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 22:33:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent post. Very true.</Msg><Username>froglegsaregreen</Username><Timestamp>1344315007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344316475000-5</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Why are you switching now to defend a abvious potential CRIMINAL &gt;&gt; Reading and comprehension issues? Dementia setting in ? I do not defend anyone - I'm attacking GOP, NRA and NEO-CON stupidity. Also attacking you personally for trying to put blame for messed up gun laws in this country- GOP and NRA lifetime achievement- on LIBERALS. It does not surprise me coming from a tax evading crook like you - your kind is always in need to put blame elsewhere. "yeah, I'm rowdy - like our GOP leader - I too evade taxes whenever I can - no - not my fault there is a budget deficit. Its those poor people on minimum wage not paying taxes that cause this problem." "yeah - I'm rowdy - I collect medicare, Social Security, and pensions - but it's the other scum collecting benefits that is ruining the country" Right rowdy?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344316475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 01:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344316591000-6</Id><Title>The "Killer Wimp"</Title><Msg>Was killing Leola Anderson "a distraction" ? (3+ / 0-) The more we get into any one area of interest, the more likely we are to find this Mitt Romney fellow lying. Every time he tweaks the facts dishonestly to get him an advantage. The worst "tweak" was a blatantly anti-Catholic Team Lying extravaganza dating all the way from 1968. Mitt Romney's Driving Killed Leola Anderson. His Cover-Up Tale is Proved Dishonest Romney misread a roadway going north on N524 through Beaulac. He drove head-on into the southbound Left Turn lane and caused an accident that killed Mrs. Leola Anderson. A visit in hospital by the American Ambassador, Sargent Shriver, eased him into not being prosecuted. Originally aimed at his own family and the Anderson family, Romney invented a preposterous tale that the other driver was a "drunk priest" named "Albert Marie" speeding on a "mountain road" at "120 kph" and "swerving" out of his lane to hit them. Imaginary witnesses were created by the dozen. We now know from photographic evidence and then personal accounts that the other driver was Bishop Jean Vilnet, later president of the Council of Bishops of France. Today he is 90 and lives at Saint-Dié-des-Vosges. He was at no time blamed for this accident. (Jean-Felix-Albert-Marie Vilnet, b. 1922 in Chaumont.) Michael Kranish and Scott Helman wrote "The Real Romney." (2007) Mitt Romney's crew of thugs lied to them directly, repeatedly and did such as presenting a falsified Sud Quest newspaper article. Lying, simply, is evil. Apparently Mr. Romney never learned that lesson. He lies about every single event under the Heavens while his dearest friends, the Republicans, care about that only when he gets caught in a felony. Cheney, Palin, now Romney -- amazing what pops to the top combining hypocrisy with not doing competent background checks ! by bontemps2012 on Mon Aug 06, 2012 at 10:09:16 AM PDT</Msg><Username>slayen98_1</Username><Timestamp>1344316591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 01:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344318116000-7</Id><Title>Upgrade: ETFC Mean Recommendation to 2.69</Title><Msg>In the last 24 hours, the Reuters Research Mean Recommendation Changed from 2.71 to 2.69. ETFC will jump big soon!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344318116000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 01:41:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344324115000-8</Id><Title>$8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!! $8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!!</Title><Msg>$8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!! $8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!! $8.22!!!!! $8.22!!!!! $8.22!!!!! $8.22!!!!! $8.22!!!!! $8.22!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344324115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 03:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344335516000-9</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I'm attacking".......................................... Just your Normal state of Being... Dang...Just lok in the Mirror, and take a Rest!...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344335516000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 06:31:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344335718000-10</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Also attacking".................................................. WOW.... There it is Again in the Same Post! Some people just use a Dog and get the Same Results!...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344335718000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 06:35:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344340407000-11</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crownie the clown wants the people to become sheep so he has a place to put hispenis. Or he want to let the country go to the dogs so he have something to eat.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344340407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 07:53:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344343354000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Romney use oiuja board to talk to Reagan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344030391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the ouija board spelled out how Mittens can cut taxes, increase military spending and balance the budget, or so he says, the session was done in secret. the ouija board did ask what Mitt was hiding from Americans by refusing to show more than 2 window dressed years of tax returns.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344343354000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 08:42:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344345517000-13</Id><Title>The unemployed are sick of Obama's lies</Title><Msg>Everybody is sick of Obama's lies. tears</Msg><Username>robert_carr_donk</Username><Timestamp>1344345517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>28</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344346819000-14</Id><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Msg>Brak went there, right? Did stray dogs come up mysteriously missing during that time period? There is no evidence of that that I can find. http://www.theblaze.com/contributions/obama%e2%80%99s-college-classmate-the-obama-scandal-is-at-columbia/</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>30</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344348673000-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney use oiuja board to talk to Reagan</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344030391000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 17:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wimp hasn't completely released even ONE year, 2010 is incomplete. To assure Americans that he's not a crook, Wimp needs to release '99-2002 returns and '08 &amp; '09 returns, at a minimum.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344348673000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 10:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344350830000-16</Id><Topic><Title>$8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!! $8.22!!!!! Repeat After Me!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344324115000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 03:21:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This move up looks too controlled. I don't see $8.22 happening today, unless the shorts give it up. They love to beat her once the bruises start to fade.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1344350830000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 10:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344351043000-17</Id><Topic><Title>The unemployed are sick of Obama's lies</Title><Username>robert_carr_donk</Username><Timestamp>1344345517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so why did the gop sabotage the recovery 2011 feb........220,000 jobs added mar......246,000 jobs apr........251,000 GOP BEGINS ITS SABOTAGE over the debt ceiling, threatening default. may..... less than 100K jobs added june...less than 100K july...less than 100K august... less than 100K jobs added debt ceiling resolved SEP OVER 200,000 JOBS ADDED nice work gop ! Your sabotage cost several hundred thousand jobs.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344351043000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 10:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344353757000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Referring to the author of that wingnut piece of... "In your gut you know he's nuts."</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1344353757000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 11:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>30</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344354490000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Obama has a big skeleton in his closet. It’s his college records. Call it “gut instinct” but my gut is almost always right. Obama has a secret hidden at Columbia- and it’s a bad one that threatens to bring down his presidency." I have a gut instinct that the members of this msg board could each give me $50,000 and I have a gut instinct that I could double their money by digging for gold in my back yard. Any takers? That guy is stoopid. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1344354490000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 11:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344354671000-20</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lackof........thank you and I hope you did stop at TITLETOWN bar and grill with the football statue outside the converted train station into a bar and grill with a micro brewery and made it to the Packer stadium/proshop too! We stay always at Paradise when we going to the MI-U.P. and then work our way down to Benton Harbor. We take the Ferry and then stay in Port Washington, WI to avoid Chicago and Milwaukee. I always stayed at the resort by Smyrna on Peachtree when I had business with Turners staff, took his private boat from his office to his house, what a palace and the security!!! Is that place now sold, it was on the market for 40 million, when I last was in Atlanta? Have a good one and good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344354671000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 11:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344354700000-21</Id><Topic><Title>Corrective Move Stepping in</Title><Username>farrandtuy902</Username><Timestamp>1344342797000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 08:33:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Thanks</Msg><Username>leontineqel752</Username><Timestamp>1344354700000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 11:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344355782000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Tomorrow: Close over $8.12!! Mark this!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344283552000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 16:05:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It already hit $8.15 today... Let's see we can go to $8.22 today!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344355782000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:09:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344356056000-23</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>project.....don't tell this to the board CROWN clown, he will be all over you! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344356056000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:14:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344356330000-24</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Just your Normal state of Being...&gt;&gt; Eradicating stupidity and ignorance should be the goal of everyone. Has this stroke a vibe with you? GOP attacks progress and science - neo-cons would want to take us back 100-200 years (at least) so that being a white male would be enough to make them important. Progress and knowledge CAN be hindered - GOP is doing a great job there - but it cannot be stopped.....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344356330000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344356531000-25</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt; sheep ... a place to put ......&gt;&gt; Ah - Slayer on his favorite topic of animal stuffing again....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344356531000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344356569000-26</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lackof.......don't waste your time on the CLOWN, I hope he takes my advice and sees a shrink! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344356569000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:22:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344356751000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;blaze.com&gt;&gt; Slayer - your trash addiction is scary...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344356751000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344357140000-28</Id><Topic><Title>The unemployed are sick of Obama's lies</Title><Username>robert_carr_donk</Username><Timestamp>1344345517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:18:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hypo......bottom line is "8.3% UNEMPLOYMENT" not even counting the ones that dropped out or under are employed, not to mention the switch to "Disability"!!! Lot's of those are "moon lighting" and now pay NO TAXES at all! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344357140000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 12:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344359752000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate going around and disillusioning people especially clowns, --- you already know that. BUT I just got done listening to Andrew Wilcow on sirius sat. radio. He interviewed this Root guy and during this interview Root said a person from Breitbart dot com is over in Jakarta and he has IN HIS HAND, right now, definitive proof that Brak was an Indonesian citizen. He went on to say how this story can easily be the one historians say.. brought down a US presidency.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344359752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 13:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>21</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344360877000-30</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter what they find out about Barry Soetoro it won't matter. He has already pulled off the biggest fraud in American history, and the media is an accessory to the crime and cover up. How does a self admitted pothead and cocaine user in school get the grades to attend Columbia University, and who paid for it? Best answer, he applied as a foreign student. Release the transcrips and prove me wrong, NOW!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344360877000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 13:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344361135000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Woweee!!! hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahhahahahahaha</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1344361135000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344361244000-32</Id><Title>Why no WS prosecutions under Obama</Title><Msg>Not one of those WS crooks went to jail under the community organizers administration, not one. Answer... A new report finds that President Barack Obama’s and Attorney General Eric Holder’s failure to criminally charge any top Wall Street bankers is likely a result of cronyism inside the Department of Justice and political donations made to Obama’s campaign. Despite Obama’s and Holder’s “heated rhetoric” against Wall Street (in 2009, Obama blamed the 2008 financial collapse on “reckless speculation of bankers” while Holder charged that “unscrupulous executives, Ponzi scheme operators and common criminals alike have targeted the pocketbooks and retirement accounts of middle class Americans”), they haven’t “filed a single criminal charge against any top executive of an elite financial institution,” GAI wrote in its report, exclusively obtained by The Daily Caller. GAI argues that the Obama administration’s decision to not go after Big Finance is due to senior DOJ leadership Holder, Associate Attorney General Tom Perrelli, Associate Attorney General Tony West, Assistant Attorney General Lanny Breuer, Deputy Attorney General James Cole and Deputy Associate Attorney General Karol Mason — who “all came to the DOJ from prestigious white collar defense firms where they represented the very financial institutions the DOJ is supposed to investigate.” The report details how Holder and Breuer both came to the DOJ from Covington &amp; Burling, a “toptier Washington law firm” with a client list that includes financial firms like Wells Fargo, J.P. Morgan Chase, Bank of America, CitiBank, Deutsche Bank, Goldman Sachs, ING, Morgan Stanley, UBS and Wilmington Trust. GAI said that President Obama’s decision to choose Holder, “a white-collar defense attorney from Covington,” as his attorney general, over a “more fiery prosecutor,” appears to have sent “a subtle signal to the financial community” that this administration isn’t going to actually do anything, despite the harsh words. Cole, the report outlines, was with Bryan Cave LLP, “a white-shoe firm with A-list clients” before becoming Holder’s right-hand man at the DOJ. One of Cole’s clients while at Bryan Cave LLP, the GAI report shows, was insurance and financial giant AIG. Cole had done $20 million worth of work for AIG between 2004 and 2008, but his close ties with the company which was “at the heart of the financial crisis largely because of its noncompliance in regulatory and compliance</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344361244000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 13:40:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344364575000-33</Id><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Msg>"The ‘Missing Evidence’ In Romney’s Tax Records (Joe Conason) There is a legal doctrine that applies to Romney’s current behavior, as Indiana attorney John Sullivan points out – and it doesn’t place the burden of proof on Reid: "At law, if a person in control of evidence refuses to produce the evidence, then the jury is instructed that there is a presumption that the evidence would be against the party failing to produce. It is called the 'Missing Evidence' instruction." The missing evidence is in Romney’s grasp, yet he insists that he will never produce it. Does anyone need instruction from a judge to make the correct inference? "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344365332000-34</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;"At law, if a person in control of evidence refuses to produce the evidence, then the jury is instructed that there is a presumption that the evidence would be against the party failing to produce. It is called the 'Missing Evidence' instruction."&gt;&gt; Hey knuclehead, this is not in a court of law. I think Barry was a foreign student at Columbia, prove me wrong...realese his transcrips, NOW!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344365332000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344365636000-35</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this a matter before the court? Such logic only applies there. You know two things: 1) romney paid taxes, 2) you want to get your dirty mitten on his tax returns because they would provide excellent material for you to demagogue. Harry Reid should release his tax returns and explain how a guy with a paltry salary can become filthy rich. Both harry and Nancy need to give up all their tax returns so they can explain how it was they were able to become filthy rich by employing Vietnamese children to assemble trade goods. Harry should also demonstrate that he did not make any money on the Mexican coke trade or in dealing automatic weapons for cash, or cash for gats as he might explain.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344365636000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:53:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344365734000-36</Id><Title>This should spike the ratings</Title><Msg>I think that night I will be busy rearranging my sock drawer. Jimmy(I'll never lie to you)Carter to speak by video at Dem convention Former president Jimmy Carter won't be attending the Democratic National Convention in Charlotte, but he'll address the gathering by videotape. "Rosalynn and I regret that we will be unable to be at the Democratic Convention this year in Charlotte. However, we remain steadfast in our support for President Obama and the progress he will make in the next four years," Carter said in a statement released by the Democratic convention.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344365734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344365770000-37</Id><Topic><Title>Why no WS prosecutions under Obama</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344361244000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 13:40:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Left this bit out: "A new report from the conservative Government Accountability Institute (GAI)" Well I'm shocked, shocked I tell you, that a conservative think tank would conclude it was collusion rather than other practical considerations. Believe it or not, almost all of the practices that led to the crisis were LEGAL. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Financial_Crisis_Inquiry_Commission</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344365770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344365881000-38</Id><Title>Harry Reid unable to disprove he sold drug and guns</Title><Msg>to illegal aliens and terrorists. A shame on Harry.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344365881000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344365975000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Happy for E*TRADE Financial Corporation (NasdaqNM: ETFC) - I think we are in the Hole Stretch..</Title><Username>paulmccarthy384</Username><Timestamp>1344342755000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 08:32:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This stock never let me down, it always give me lot of money beyond my expectation.</Msg><Username>carrollraymundo473</Username><Timestamp>1344365975000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344366200000-40</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem with your arguments is the growing chorus of GOP luminaries who also believe the Wimp is WRONG in not being transparent. The point of the legal standard is to equate an election with a trial. BO's returns are public record, Wimp can legally hide his but the electorate will then have the right to draw implications from his suspicious behavior. Simple really!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344366200000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:03:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344366434000-41</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(.)( . ) ........jungleobimbo nice job - got your tit's out of the wringer, I think the LEFT one is bigger??? ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344366434000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344366692000-42</Id><Topic><Title>Let's be honest for once</Title><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344313802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny stuff, Z!!!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344366692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:11:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344366891000-43</Id><Topic><Title>This should spike the ratings</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344365734000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:55:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biddermon.....Carter is a smart man - he doesn't want to go down as the worst president in History of the US, he wants OBIMBO to claim that title!!! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344366891000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344366911000-44</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Harry Reid is a hustler, pimp, drug and gun dealer, and he employs vietnamese children to roll cigarettes. UNless Harry can prove otherwise, he remains.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344366911000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344367013000-45</Id><Title>Harry Reid sold AK-47s and other War Equipment</Title><Msg>To indigent nations and other nations known to breathe oxygen.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344367013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:16:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344367071000-46</Id><Title>Harry Reid sold vast amounts of drugs</Title><Msg>to pirates and mercenaries.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344367071000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344367127000-47</Id><Title>Harry reid is a One-eyed Pirate</Title><Msg>Who commits rape on high-kicking cheerleaders.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344367127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344367264000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Harry reid is a One-eyed Pirate</Title><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344367127000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:18:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just in, Harry ain't running for anything. The Wimp IS!!!!!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344367264000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:21:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344367370000-49</Id><Topic><Title>NOT A Assault rifle!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344293249000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 18:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is called 2nd amendment, stupid. Like we don't have enough gun restrictions yet.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1344367370000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344367586000-50</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hammer...............right on especially OBIMPOLOSI with HER/HIS foreign bank accounts and investments in China, Asia and other far east countries - some enemies of the USA!!! Hope she falls down the steps to her wine cellar and breaks her friggn neck! Terrorist wont even take money to take her out because she does the job for them - to ruin the USA! Harry is just plain a bumbling stupid order taker of OBIMBO, just like Biden! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344367586000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344367629000-51</Id><Title>So KCG turned down 500mil from KG</Title><Msg>Looks like Citadel offered 500mil to KCG and they turned it down to get the 400mil from others. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2012-08-07/knight-is-said-to-have-spurned-500-million-citadel-loan.html</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344367629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344367967000-52</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The point of the legal standard is to equate an election with a trial. BO's returns are public record, Wimp can legally hide his but the electorate will then have the right to draw implications from his suspicious behavior.' Wimp's suspicious behavior extends to his time as Governor. He had every computer removed from his office in MA. The Wimp just gives the impression of a guy that's hiding things. http://www.reuters.com/article/2011/12/06/us-usa-campaign-romney-computers-idUSTRE7B500X20111206</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344367967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:32:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344368307000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Let's be honest for once</Title><Username>lackofzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1344313802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 00:30:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here is a list of some prominent Republicans who have so far urged the Wimp to release more tax returns: * Columnist George Will * Former Mississippi Gov. Haley Barbour * Weekly Standard editor Bill Kristol * Rep. Pete Sessions * Rep. Ron Paul * The editors of National Review * Texas Gov. Rick Perry</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344368307000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344368461000-54</Id><Topic><Title>Columbia University Class of 1983</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344346819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 09:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayer......what's scary is that the CLOWN is marching in front of his beloved OBIMBOCRAT party and doesn't know that he has the flag upside down - SOS (Save Our Sickos) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344368461000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:41:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344368611000-55</Id><Title>Willard cheated the Italians?</Title><Msg>http://www.examiner.com/article/new-charge-that-romney-s-bain-capital-avoided-italian-taxes-emerges</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1344368611000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344369007000-56</Id><Topic><Title>So KCG turned down 500mil from KG</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344367629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:27:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After seeing the deal KG gave ETFC, I'm surprised Knight even let him in the door.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344369007000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:50:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344370126000-57</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;"The point of the legal standard is to equate an election with a trial. BO's returns are public record&gt;&gt; How many years did the community organizer release when running for president. More importantly, what does tax returns have to do with 1 1/2 GDP growth, 8.3 unployment, 5 trillion in new debt, 1 trillion wasted on a bogus stimulus package, etc...answer: nothing. This losser can't run on his failed record so he has stogges like you changing the subject. This dope had no experiance at running anything, no resume to be president, but it didn't stop angry disinfranchised folks like from casting a vote for an empty suit. BTW, how is your house value fairing under the pamphlet distributors reqime.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1344370126000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344371866000-58</Id><Title>Josh Margolin - NY Post</Title><Msg>OBIMBO is worried that the stadium for the convention won't be filled with OBIMBOCRATS! They have little raffles and other events and prises to coax in the sheep! Since it is an open stadium, I hope the weather is going to be like it was at NASCAR yesterday! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344371866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344372106000-59</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2008, BO released SEVEN YEARS of returns back to 2000. Wimp's employment at Bain is at issue. Voters need to see his 1999-2003 returns and at least the 2008-present years. Why was he willing to show McCain 23 years but the American public can't even get ONE FULL YEAR??</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344372106000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344372735000-60</Id><Title>Etfc management prepares for shareholder action</Title><Msg>Etfc board elected to not sell at the pps of $18. Pps now $8 and management continues to demonstrate a lack of direction. Silent Steve and Audacious Audette continue to execute a plan that takes the company no where. Supposedly they presented a capital plan to the regulators. I shudder to think what that plan consists of. Either its all good or all bad. Fact of the matter is the info vacuum has imploded the stock.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344372735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344372959000-61</Id><Topic><Title>Josh Margolin - NY Post</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344371866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He, along wif help from the msm, is also trying to put together a composite crowd. A crowd similar in its composition to the composite girlfriends the counterfeit one dreamed up and lied about in his book.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344372959000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344373247000-62</Id><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Msg>Romney’s wind energy stance puts him at odds with key Iowa Republicans Iowa, which is home to more wind energy jobs than any other state in the country. And it unsettled many of Romney's top Iowa supporters, who publicly complained they had been caught off guard by his campaign's policy decision Republican Rep. Tom Latham, R-Iowa, noting that nearly 7,000 Iowans work in the wind industry, assailed the Romney campaign for "a lack of full understanding of how important the wind energy tax credit is for Iowa and our nation." Iowa's senior senator, Chuck Grassley, told reporters he didn't believe Romney really opposed the extension, and he joined five other GOP lawmakers in voting for it in the Senate Finance Committee.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344373263000-63</Id><Topic><Title>So KCG turned down 500mil from KG</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344367629000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 15:27:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe KCG turned down Citadel when the word "springing lien" came up?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344373263000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:01:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344373631000-64</Id><Title>Free ETF's from Scotttrade....</Title><Msg>being shuttered due to a lack of interest. Imagine that, free etf's that on one is interested in buying? http://www.marketwatch.com/story/scottrade-to-liquidate-focusshares-etfs-2012-08-07</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344373631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:07:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344374670000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you tell the whole story? Southern MN did not issue any more permits for wind generators, because the left wing bleeding hearts together with the "Sierra Club" stated that it kills the birds with their blades and IA is following the same crap - a eagle was killed - big deal! Also ND told MN (EXEL) to stay out of their state and scrapped the wind farms! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344374670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:24:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344374967000-66</Id><Topic><Title>Josh Margolin - NY Post</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344371866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 16:37:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ewww. Just got another wif of billie/slayer's racism.</Msg><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1344374967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344375013000-67</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;same crap - a eagle was killed - big deal&gt;&gt; Rodent - why don't you lay off the anger pipe and go back to smuggling money??? You are old - you may consider upping your number of trips back to Germany while you still can....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344375013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344375337000-68</Id><Title>$8.31, Repeat After Me!! $8.31, $8.31!!</Title><Msg>$8.31, Repeat After Me!! $8.31, $8.31!! $8.31, $8.31!! $8.31, $8.31!! $8.31, $8.31!! Coming tomorrow!!!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1344375337000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344375485000-69</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;this is not in a court of law&gt;&gt; no - this is a job that will shape the future of the country - including Supreme Court Justice nominations etc. This is much more then a court of law....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344375485000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344375507000-70</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously some places are better suited for wind than others and the fact is wind power is the source of thousands of jobs in Iowa and mittens wants to kill them. http://www.emagazine.com/earth-talk/bird-friendly-wind-power</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344375507000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344375598000-71</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Harry Reid is a hustler, pimp, drug and gun dealer&gt;&gt; desperate to point finger elsewhere?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344375598000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344375764000-72</Id><Title>Gasoline!</Title><Msg>With the small fire in OK and now the BIG ONE in CA the West Coast Gasoline Prices might jump to or over $4! If OBIMBO would have authorized the long overdo permits to build new refineries, he would be a HERO!!! I must say that all presidents since the 70s should have done so, but HE didn't invest in refineries and pipelines for "shovel ready jobs", he missed his calling terrible by screwing around with loser green projects wasting billions!!! Watch out if there is another mishap and/or a strong winter for change and the refineries shut down for winter gasoline conversion in early Oct.!!! Hello Romney are you listening, that's your ticket for election!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344375764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344375794000-73</Id><Title>Etrade Board Members review D&amp;O Policies</Title><Msg>Just making certain they are covered when the SHTF on this whole sell issue.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344375794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344375982000-74</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Hope she falls down the steps to her wine cellar and breaks her friggn neck!&gt;&gt; Probably should notify the authorities and put ROWDYRODENT on a "suspicious persons" list. He is currently only expressing THE WISH for certain political figures to die. But just like the other Wisconsin dude - that can quickly turn to mass murder.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344375982000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376047000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First of all, I am not a Romney fan. But let's be honest. Romney wants to stop subsidizing industries, he is not "against" wind farms. He is just against providing a government-backed advantage to them. That is the free market.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1344376047000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376325000-76</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Why was he willing to show McCain 23 years &gt;&gt; and why after seeing those returns McCain opted to ask a witless bimbo (that thought Paris was a country in Europe) to be his VP instead? How scary were those returns????</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344376325000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376494000-77</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown...don't worry about me - this ex pilot is in excellent shape and sound mind and we taking all the trips we want, (money is NO objective) while you sitting at home getting a heart attack over the OBIMBO Party! (Just had my physical paid for by MEDICARE and BCBS while it still lasts!) ;o) How about you, have you followed my recommendation and see a head shrink jet??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344376494000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376733000-78</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"This is more then a court of law." Yep, right now it's a CLOWN CLUB CIRCUS run by a clown club organizer! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344376733000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:58:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376767000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Gasoline!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344375764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;If OBIMBO would have authorized the long overdo permits to build new refineries, he would be a HERO!!!&gt;&gt; You are totally clueless on most topics - but dead wrong on this one. You cannot rekindle in 21st century economy with ideas from middle of 20th century. I understand that you are fond of those times: you were younger and probably more productive, and think if we only turn the clock back and start another cold war all would be better - but that's just your senile old brain talking...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344376767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:59:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344376903000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Free ETF's from Scotttrade....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1344373631000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:07:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not too surprising. Scottrade isn't big enough to pull off something like that. Only works for Chuck because they are so large.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1344376903000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 18:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344377302000-81</Id><Topic><Title>"Missing Evidence" standard</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344364575000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown....I hope air force one crashes with OBIMBO on board, but let the pilots live - now what you going to do??? ;o) Matter of fact at the local water hole, many asked why so many presidents got shot but no terrorist takes him out - I told them, that he does so much damage to the country that you couldn't pay a terrorist enough to take him out! ;o) Have a nice day at the shrink! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344377302000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 18:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344377967000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Board Members review D&amp;O Policies</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344375794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm ignorant to such things. please enlighten me.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1344377967000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 18:19:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344378048000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gora.....a good level headed post. Problem is we have to fight up here the environmentalists and the Sierra club on every thing! Complaints about bird killing, complaints about blade noise if built close to housing and what have you! Same crap with the Stillwater bridge across the St. Croix, between MN and WI, finally signed and approved by Obama (one good thing he did), but now 12 years later and 150 million more in cost to build - what a waste of tax payer money! Our ex governor the democrat never did anything till Walker came into the picture together with the new republican house/senate and ran that idiot out of town! Even democrat gov. Dayton and senator Klobuchar together with Bachman of MN can see eye to eye with our republican senators and governor! That's the way it should be!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1344378048000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 18:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344383418000-84</Id><Title>what did you lazy azzse odumbomites</Title><Msg>accomplish today...huh..?...anything?...would you be willing to have your whiney assze strapped on top of public service vehicles?...you'd make good sirens..wah wah wah wah wah wah..</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344383535000-85</Id><Topic><Title>what did you lazy azzse odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya mean like Mitten's dog ?</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1344383535000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:52:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344383848000-86</Id><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Msg>Mon Jul 16, 2012 at 07:52 AM PDT Romney Demanded to See Ted Kennedy's Tax Returns by Morgan Sandlin This will be a short diary but I found this amusing and another example of Mitt Romney's utter inability to be consistent in his principles or representations. During his losing Senate run against Ted Kennedy Romney demanded that Ted Kennedy provide his tax returns on the basis of the public's right to know: "It's time the biggest-taxing senator in Washington shows the people of Massachusetts how much he pays in taxes," Romney said in April of 1994, according to a report in the Boston Globe. In 2002 Mr. Romney also demanded that his opponent (who had released her tax returns whilst Mr. Romney declined to provide his returns) provide her spouse's return. ...and this morning, in defense of his refusal to be forthcoming with the American voter, Romney used as a defense that John Kerry's SPOUSE had not provided her tax returns, totally ignoring that Senator Kerry had provided numerous returns. At this point I'm not so sure that it is the failure to provide tax returns that will do the most damage to Mr. Romney, but it will be the exposure of his lack of character and consistency which will inflict the most damage. This man's principles and ethics are simply a mess. *As for taking Mr. Romney's word that there's nothing to be concerned about, to just trust him to tell the truth the linked Boston Globe article has a nifty little example of how Mr. Romney misrepresented his residency filing and then went back and amended his filing when the situation became uncomfortable. Boston Globe Anyone else noticing a pattern here?</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344383934000-87</Id><Topic><Title>what did you lazy azzse odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'm sure you'll work out if ya sound like mittens dog....</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383934000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:58:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344384867000-88</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COLUMBUS, Ohio -- One of Ohio's top Republican leaders says GOP presidential candidate Mitt Romney should release more tax returns because it's become a distraction in the campaign. Romney has faced repeated criticism for refusing to release several years' worth of tax returns. Several Republicans have joined in the call for more transparency, including several U.S. senators and Texas Gov. Rick Perry. Ohio House Speaker William Batchelder said in a taped television interview that the issue has become a problem for the candidate, and that Romney should release the forms so he can move on to other topics. Batchelder has been a state lawmaker in the presidential battleground off and on since the 1960s.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344384867000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 20:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344385873000-89</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George Will. On ABC’s “This Week,” Will, a long-time conservative commentator and Washington Post columnist, said, “The costs of not releasing the returns are clear, therefore he must have calculated that there are higher costs in releasing them.” At one point, he even played devil’s advocate to Republican consultant Mary Matalin, who was defending Romney.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344385873000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 20:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344386693000-90</Id><Topic><Title>what did you lazy azzse odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rodent - Be nice or I will stop paying into your medicare and your social security. And if 3m decided to "renegotiate" your pension citing that "it is choking their ability to turn profit" all you will have left is the money you smuggle from Germany.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1344386693000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 20:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344387484000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Kristol. “Here’s what he should do,” said Kristol, another conservative commentator, on Fox News. “He should release the tax returns tomorrow. This is crazy… you’ve got to release 6, 8, 10 years of back tax returns. Take the hit for a day or two. Then give a serious speech on Thursday.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344387484000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 20:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344387999000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Take the hit for a day or two" LOL. Romneyhood is likely like a lot of rich people, many of the schemes that they get into to save money on taxes are illegal. He might just be trying to avoid being the first presidential candidate to spend election day in jail. JMO, ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1344387999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344388306000-93</Id><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Msg>Chicago style sleaze! For every failed policy Brak implimented there are 10 lies and there are a crapload of failed policies. People are so sick of his crap, NOV caint get here soon enough. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ "This election Obama is offering sleaze and viciousness" http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/08/07/Obama-SuperPac-Releases-One-of-the-Most-Ugly-Misleading-Ads-in-Campaign-History</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344388735000-94</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nonsense Slayer, this is the cleanest presidency maybe EVER. NO MAJOR SCANDALS. NO CRIMINAL CONVICTIONS. Compare and contrast with Bush and Reagan years.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344388735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344388914000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ron Paul. Unitl just days ago, Paul was the other Republican presidential candidate. He is also one of those calling for Romney to release the returns. Paul told Politico today, “Politically, I think that would help him. …In the scheme of things politically, you know, it looks like releasing tax returns is what the people want.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344388914000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:21:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344389946000-96</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you forget to read the article? CNN fact checked the Ad and found a bunch of lies. And what kind of husband is that Soptic guy if he caint get a freakin job after 6 years time to provide for his family? His wife probably got sick of the whole mess and decided to check out early just to get away from her lazy b'terd of a husband..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344389946000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:39:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344390100000-97</Id><Title>ROMNEYHOOD</Title><Msg>Mittens Tax Policy is Robin Hood in reverse = Romneyhood http://www.politico.com/blogs/burns-haberman/2012/08/obama-its-romneyhood-131270.html?hp=l3</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1344390100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344390208000-98</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you live?? He presently is withholding information about the gun running deal with Holder. He gave billions to Solondyra one of his contributors. He paid Rev. Wright to shut up and lied about it. He will go down as the worst president including Jimmy Carter..</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1344390208000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344390547000-99</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ad is from a Super PAC. By law they can't even communicate with BO. This is a consequence of Citizens United, the SCOTUS decision your GOP is so proud of. This will be the ugliest campaign ever thanks to a rightwing SCOTUS. Enjoy!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344390547000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:49:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344390767000-100</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dummy, where are the indictments? You cite trumped up ,wannabe scandals. By this time in the Bush and Reagan administrations, their staffs were being fitted for prison stripes.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344390767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344390791000-101</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Alabama Gov. Robert Bentley. The Alabama Governor actually went further than others in suggesting that perhaps Romney is hiding something by not releasing his tax returns. “If you have things to hide, then maybe you’re doing things wrong,” he told the AP. “I think you ought to be willing to release everything to the American people.“</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344390791000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344390799000-102</Id><Topic><Title>CNN: Brak's superpac Ad lying and misleading</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344388306000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:11:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You shouldn't end your sentence wif a preposition. You know better than that.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1344390799000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:53:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344391194000-103</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michael Steele. The former chair of the Republican National Committee is pushing for release. He claims it will help voters trust Romney, especially since he claims there is nothing to see in the returns: “If there’s nothing there, there’s no ‘there’ there, don’t create a ‘there.’ Put out as much information as you can. Even if you don’t release 12 years worth of tax returns, at least three, four, five.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344391194000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:59:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344391479000-104</Id><Topic><Title>BO still squeaky clean!!!</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1337090691000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-05-15 10:04:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Record still running.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1344391479000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 22:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344391563000-105</Id><Topic><Title>Iowa gop turns against Romney the job killer</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1344373247000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:00:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, &lt;&lt;&lt;Dayton and senator Klobuchar together with Bachman of MN can see eye to eye with our republican senators and governor! That's the way it should be!!!&gt;&gt;&gt; God help anyone who sees eye to eye with Walker and Bachmann. Bachmann the crazy nutcase who even Republicans despise and Walker who is disliked by the Workers in WI. rodent, Again, are you getting dumber or older which ist it???</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1344391563000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 22:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344391986000-106</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Board Members review D&amp;O Policies</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344375794000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 17:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go enlighten yourself. You owe it to yourself.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1344391986000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 22:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344393775000-107</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Walter Jones. In an interview with CNN, the Republican Congressman from North Carolina said, “I think he should release his financial records and I think if he does it in July it would be a lot better than in October. …whenever you are asking for the vote of the American people you need to fully disclose what your holdings are, if you have any.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344393775000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 22:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344394097000-108</Id><Topic><Title>what did you lazy azzse odumbomites</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344383418000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:50:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't have a choice.... You socialist have locked yourselves in. Il be wiping my adzes on that paultry little fee you are forced to pay</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1344394097000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 22:48:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344394941000-109</Id><Title>Brak loses out on SCotUS nominations</Title><Msg>Yes his strict adherence to a radical ideology has blocked his opportunity to nominate more. Too late now, an election is coming. And roof is going to croak soon.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344394941000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344394979000-110</Id><Title>''Trickle-Down Fairy Dust" &amp; "Romney Hood</Title><Msg>http://www.usnews.com/news/blogs/Ken-Walshs-Washington/2012/08/07/romney-hood-and-trickle-down-fairy-dust-romneys-economic-strategy-under-fire</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1344394979000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:02:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344395591000-111</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEYHOOD</Title><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1344390100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Elks member, what part of an elks member are you ??? If you get your opinion from "politigo" ... You must have an elks member up your A$$ ...</Msg><Username>bigtimeusa</Username><Timestamp>1344395591000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:13:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344395653000-112</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ana Navarro. “He should just release the stupid taxes and eliminate the Obama campaign tactic of insinuating he’s got something to hide,” the former adviser to John McCain said. “The Obama people are going to keep the issue alive and it has the potential of mushrooming into a bigger issue. …It’s time to just pull off the band-aid.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344395653000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344397548000-113</Id><Title>Texas Executes a Republican !</Title><Msg>Marvin Wilson Execution: Texas Puts Man With 61 IQ To Death They need him on the Pub voter rolls.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1344397548000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:45:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344397735000-114</Id><Topic><Title>Brak loses out on SCotUS nominations</Title><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1344394941000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:02:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayerdarling!!! hammerstein doesn't suit you at all!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1344397735000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:48:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344397764000-115</Id><Topic><Title>Hypocrisy, thy name is Willard!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344383848000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 19:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Pete Sessions. Sessions (R-TX) leads the National Republican Congressional Committee, and even he called Romney’s tax returns “fair game” and a “legitimate question.” In an interview with CNN, Sessions said that “[Romney's] personal finances, the way he does things, his record, are fair game.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344397764000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344397933000-116</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEYHOOD</Title><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1344390100000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 21:41:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get lost!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!?????</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1344397933000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-07 23:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>