<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353048677123-1</Id><Title>Obama phoney Empire crumbling</Title><Msg>By the minute...By the day... The Emperor has no clothes...</Msg><Username>krisspcritter_da_1</Username><Timestamp>1353048677123</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 01:51:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353074973597-2</Id><Title>upgrade with a 8.50$ arget price!</Title><Msg>group do you think ETFC has hit it's bottom for the year?</Msg><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1353074973597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:09:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353079446643-3</Id><Topic><Title>upgrade with a 8.50$ arget price!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1353074973597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOT an upgrade. Initiated with a "Neutral" rating and PT of $8.50. Flacid at best........</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1353079446643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 10:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353081546782-4</Id><Title>This must be what revenge looks like</Title><Msg>The obama azzblasting continues. tears</Msg><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1353081546782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 10:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353089967690-5</Id><Title>Fire Freiberg......</Title><Msg>wait they already did that. Refi the high interest debt. wait they already did that. Wind down the toxic mortgages wait they are doing that. Reality is the stock price is $7.80 or .78 cents........</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1353089967690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 13:19:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353097280774-6</Id><Title>Obama lied, Americans died</Title><Msg>He was doing Susan Rice in the SItuation Room.</Msg><Username>nofatchixplease</Username><Timestamp>1353097280774</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:21:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353097665550-7</Id><Topic><Title>upgrade with a 8.50$ arget price!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1353074973597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, ETFC was downgraded with lower price target. ETFC will go under $7 before the year-end. Watch and learn!! My target price is $5.50.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1353097665550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 15:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353099837706-8</Id><Topic><Title>upgrade with a 8.50$ arget price!</Title><Username>jondow69</Username><Timestamp>1353074973597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 09:09:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are clueless Moon. Flat clueless......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1353099837706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 16:03:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353102919317-9</Id><Title>Bring back Layton!</Title><Msg>The man with the plan!</Msg><Username>etardedlongs</Username><Timestamp>1353102919317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 16:55:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353108556668-10</Id><Title>It's an outrage...where my Twinkies</Title><Msg>** Hostess Brands disclosed plans on Friday to liquidate its assets and lay off most of its 18,500 workers** How can a couple of hedgefunds do this to these hard working union folks during the holidays...what about the children. I don't know about you but this kind of capitialist greed needs to end, and it needs to end now. These money changers on WS didn't build that, it was the collective society that made it possible for this company to prosper. I say that the Justice Department needs to force these rats to continue funding this company until the Obama administration can step in and redistribute the stock and bonds to the unions. This company needs to be bailed and the union jobs that will be lost...If we taxpayers can bailout those fatcats bankers we can sure as hell help these hard working union working men and women. Call, email you representative and tell them to save this iconic company from those greedy 1%ers, and remind them that the folks spoke in November 2012...and that elections matter! Hostess Brands disclosed plans on Friday to liquidate its assets and lay off most of its 18,500 workersThe End of Hostess as We Know It Failing to persuade striking employees to return to work, Hostess Brands disclosed plans on Friday to liquidate its assets and lay off most of its 18,500 workers, bringing the 82-year-old maker of Wonder Bread and Twinkies to the end of its line. The painful decision to wind down the Irving, Texas.-based private company follows a nationwide strike that Hostess said severely constrained its operations. Hostess said delivery of its products, which include Ding Dongs and CupCakes, will continue and its retail stores will keep their lights on for several days to sell already-baked products. “We deeply regret the necessity of today’s decision, but we do not have the financial resources to weather an extended nationwide strike,” Hostess CEO Gregory Rayburn said in a statement. As a result of the liquidation, Hostess said it will “move promptly” to lay off “most” of its 18,500 employees and focus on “selling its assets to the highest bidders.” The company will now be forced to close its 33 bakeries, 565 distribution centers, 5,500 delivery routes and 570 bakery outlet stores throughout the U.S. The Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers International Union pushed back against the Rayburn blaming the liquidation on the unions.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1353108556668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 18:29:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>