<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-19"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348027274963-1</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT'S DIARY</Title><Msg>Tue Sep 18, 2012 at 06:15 PM PDT The Chronicles of Mitt: Sept 18, 2012 by Hunter pen on paper: 'Dear diary' Hello, human diary. It is I, Mitt Romney, your better. Much has happened. The staff is currently locked in heated discussion as to whether or not to announce that I am suffering from a terrible episode of laryngitis, thus rendering me unable to speak until perhaps after the election. Eric F. feels this is too extreme, and perhaps we should say I have merely been drunk for the past few months, but am fine now. After an hour or so of this I fled the room, telling the staff to get back to me with their recommendations when they have some. That was some time ago, so there still seems to be no resolution. I am not sure what precisely the current issue is, but it seems to revolve around one of my many meetings with fellow wealth units. I was explaining the difficulties of promoting my policies vis-a-vis lowering taxes on wealthy Americans, and happened to mention that most commoners were lazy slackabouts who hardly earned any money at all, and who were therefore ignorant of the plight of the wealthy. I do not believe any of this is new information. Suddenly, however, the press is very interested in my theories as to the inherent laziness of the poor. I am not sure why, but is this not a good thing? We have continually labored to explain these things to the press, and now that the press has finally taken interest in them, now my advisers are expressing concern? Should we not be taking this opportunity to further highlight my messages as to how our nation oppresses its most wealthy, and coddles the poor? I will never understand campaign politics, that is for certain. There is much more to write about, but for now I should probably check on my staff. Things have gotten quieter now, which either means that they are nearing a satisfactory conclusion or, possibly, that Eric F. has once again beaten recalcitrant staff members with a chair. That fellow tries my patience at times—I am not made of chairs, Eric. Those things cost money.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348027274963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 00:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348059180687-2</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice of you to explain what Romney meant by denoucing the 47% of Americans who pay no income tax...."47% of the people who "pay no income tax," he said........... and THAT 47% of people does include the working poor and military personnel as i described..............and get this .... the bottom 40% of American's income is LESS a % of the nation's total income than what the top 1% takes in.......... so basically Romney was denouncing the poor to his wealthly crowd of $50,000 a plate donors..... in the mansion of a sex orgy loving vulture capitalist, btw.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059180687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 08:53:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348059893696-3</Id><Title>if not for the 47% and their cayman island bank accounts we could have a bigger military budget!</Title><Msg>if not for the 47% and their tax evasion cayman island bank accounts the USA would have no debt problem! the bush tax cuts for the poor are the ruination of the nation, so let the child tax credits that have added so many to the 47% expire, but keep the tax cuts for the rich and give them more!</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059893696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348062752429-4</Id><Title>Romney Totally Incompetent</Title><Msg>His campaign is falling apart. Republicans lining up behind Obama</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348062752429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348062907939-5</Id><Topic><Title>if not for the 47% and their cayman island bank accounts we could have a bigger military budget!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059893696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do real Americans hide their taxes with foreigners ?</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1348062907939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348063952576-6</Id><Title>stockc</Title><Msg>can you guys talk obout etfc and not politics.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1348063952576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:12:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348064715151-7</Id><Topic><Title>stockc</Title><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1348063952576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't wait for November to be over!</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1348064715151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:25:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348065140153-8</Id><Topic><Title>stockc</Title><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1348063952576</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:12:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>amen to that.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1348065140153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348065946346-9</Id><Title>Sector woes</Title><Msg>EW YORK (TheStreet) -- The Charles Schwab Corp. (SCHW) was cut to "Neutral" from "Buy" by Goldman Sachs in a report published Wednesday that was bearish on the discount brokerage sector as a whole. In downgrading Schwab, Goldman analysts cited a decline in yields on residential mortgage backed securities (RMBS) issued by Fannie Mae (FNMA)and Freddie Mac (FMCC) following the Federal Reserve's announcement last week that it would buy long-dated RMBS in an effort to boost the housing market. So called "agency" RMBS make up 70% of Schwab's securities portfolio, according to Goldman, and the decline in yields may encourage pre-payments and "headwinds" in net interest margins. Net interest margins refers to the difference between a company's cost of capital and the rate it earns through lending. Goldman's analysts see Schwab outperforming E Trade Financial (ETFC) and Ameritrade (AMTD), but still believe "upside in the stock is limited." Shares of Schwab were down by 1.15% a few minutes after the opening bell Wednesday. Ameritrade and E Trade shares were also lower. -- Written by Dan Freed in New York.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348065946346</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348066015853-10</Id><Topic><Title>Quite the Performance</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1347976505460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 09:55:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Goldman out with a note today pummeling the OLB space. Downgrade schw, and reiterated sell on amtd. QE3 no good for brokers. The fed is buying agency MBS which is exactly where etrade reinvest the loan roll off proceeds. Those rates are going down and thus NIM will be pressured further. Darts are hitting multi year lows at the same time. October 9 puts purchased on Friday.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1348066015853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 10:46:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348069988503-11</Id><Topic><Title>if not for the 47% and their cayman island bank accounts we could have a bigger military budget!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059893696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>47% who don't pay income tax are just as tax evaders as those who put their money on Cayman Islands. Both categories do nothing illegal. The difference is that those who "hide" their money on Cayman Islands contribute 40% of federal income tax, while 47% contrubute NOTHING. Most of those in 47% have cell phones. Can they be patriotinc and pay taxes instead? Are those 47% tax evaders?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348069988503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:53:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348070812902-12</Id><Topic><Title>if not for the 47% and their cayman island bank accounts we could have a bigger military budget!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059893696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"47% who don't pay income tax " how can you stand to by so dishonest? Everyone knows that 46% of americans pay zero income tax, but most of those are poor working families who don't have much to spare. YOU are a disgrace to humanity to compare their situation to the rich billionaires. and fyi, you can credit the bush tax cuts for adding a lot people to the 46% , he doubled the child tax credit and right there a poor woman with kids who would have paid a few %, a few hundred dollars in income taxes ended up paying zero...... the rich of course benefited much more by hundreds of thousands of dollars and many % more than the poor.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348070812902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348071207196-13</Id><Topic><Title>if not for the 47% and their cayman island bank accounts we could have a bigger military budget!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348059893696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 09:04:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pacifican and slayer are the board's local racists - they would vote for Putin if that would kick Obama out of the office. To them anyone voting for a black president is a traitor...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348071207196</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 12:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348075831884-14</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens bragged he vetoed a proposal to raise the minimum wage</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348002102242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 17:01:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still don't get it. - TRUE: "bums, parasites and mooches seeking welfare" are bought by Obama, won't vote for Romney; - FALSE: 53% Romney relys on, are rich; - TRUE: there is large enough block among those who pay no income tax today which WILL vote for Romney because they don't want wellfare for life, they want JOBS, and Romney is the one who more likely to create them.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348075831884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:30:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348076282726-15</Id><Title>Even the Mormons disowning the Dipshidiot, getting ugly out there!!!</Title><Msg>By Gregory A. Prince, Ph.D. Mitt Romney Is Not the Face of Mormonism Posted: 09/19/2012 1:12 pm When the news of Mitt Romney's Florida video broke on Monday evening, I was incensed -- but not for its political implications. His arrogant and out-of-hand dismissal of half the population of this country struck me at a visceral level, for it sullied the religion that he and I share -- the religion for which five generations of my ancestry have lived and sacrificed, the religion whose official mantra is "to take care of the poor and needy throughout the world." My first impulse was to rent an airplane towing a banner: "Mitt Romney is Not the Face of Mormonism!" I was a supporter of Romney 1.0. That was in late 2007, when we had far more in common. We are both Mormons and we both served foreign missions for our church at the same time, he in France and I in Brazil. Some of my best friends had been some of his best friends for decades. Although I am a registered Democrat, his accomplishments as Governor of Massachusetts appealed to me. I contributed the maximum amount to his early presidential primary bid. I also became an emissary to him, presenting what I felt was an attractive proposition. Helen Whitney, who had recently completed a four-hour PBS documentary, "The Mormons," was also intrigued with Romney, enough that she asked that I propose to him one hour of national coverage on PBS if he would allow her to interview him only about his religion. "It's a good religion," she said to me, "but he is hiding from it. He needs to own it." I delivered the proposal in person. He declined, stating that he and his advisors had concluded that the issue of his religion would simply go away. It didn't, but his candidacy did. Early in 2008, to my dismay, Romney 1.0 became Romney 2.0 by moving far enough to the right to lose my support. He has kept moving ever farther to the right. He has made this move in a successful attempt to gain the nomination, and in an ongoing attempt to persuade no more than 53 percent of the country that he should be the next President. The issue of Romney's Mormon faith has never gone away, although its presence has waxed and waned as other issues have come and gone. How -- or if -- he chooses to use his religion as part of his public biography is up to him, but the fact that he is the only Mormon ever to be the nominee for the Presidency of a major political party makes it inevitable that even if people do not judge him because of his religion, they will judge his religion because of him. Given the unfolding news of this week, I regret to say that Mitt Romney is not the face of Mormonism. Romney 1.0 was that face. Having been a missionary myself, I know the formative power of two years of missionary service. Having served as an assistant to one bishop and four stake presidents -- and Romney served as bishop and stake president -- I know the even greater formative power of those offices. I understand completely what his father George meant when he said, "I am completely the product of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints." That face of Mormonism is the one that calls on some of its members, particularly bishops and stake presidents, to devote as many hours gratis to their church jobs as they do to their professional jobs. It is the one that summons up extraordinary acts of love, compassion and generosity, often in response to the deepest tragedies of life -- and death. But it is not the one that dismisses out-of-hand half the population of the United States by saying, "My job is not to worry about those people. I'll never convince them they should take personal responsibility and care for their lives." As a bishop and stake president, Romney worried about those very people. Indeed, he worried far more about them, and spent far more time and means in assisting them, than the others in his flock who were more fortunate. The very basis of Mormon community, stretching back to the earliest years of Mormonism nearly two centuries ago, is that the more able have a sacred obligation to assist the less able. That sense of physical community was institutionalized in the Church's Welfare Program, which sprang out of the Great Depression as an exemplary and effective means of combining church and government assistance not only to give to those in need, but also to help them to help themselves. Any who have visited Welfare Square in Salt Lake City, as did the producers of a recent "Rock Center" documentary on MSNBC, cannot help but be impressed with what we have attempted, for over seven decades, to accomplish through what is now an international network of church facilities and volunteers. Judge Mitt Romney as you will, and vote for or against him as you will; but do not judge Mormonism on the basis of the Mitt Romney that was unveiled to the public this week. He is not the face of Mormonism.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348076282726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348076701720-16</Id><Title>Peggy Noonan calls for an "intervention"</Title><Msg>"I think there is a broad and growing feeling now, among Republicans, that this thing is slipping out of Romney’s hands. Today at a speech in New York with what seemed like many conservatives and Republicans in the audience, I said more or less the above. I wondered if anyone would say, in the Q&amp;A, “I think you’ve got it wrong, you’re too pessimistic.” No one did. A woman asked me to talk about why in a year the Republicans couldn’t lose, the Republican candidate seems to be losing. I said pre-mortems won’t help, if you want to help the more conservative candidate, it’s a better use of your time to pitch in with ideas. There’s seven weeks to go. This isn’t over, it’s possible to make things better. Republicans are going to have to right this thing. They have to stabilize it. It’s time to admit the Romney campaign is an incompetent one. It’s not big, it’s not brave, it’s not thoughtfully tackling great issues. It’s always been too small for the moment. All the activists, party supporters and big donors should be pushing for change. People want to focus on who at the top is least constructive and most responsible. Fine, but Mitt Romney is no puppet: He chooses who to listen to. An intervention is in order. “Mitt, this isn’t working.” Romney is known to be loyal. He sticks with you when you’re going through a hard time, he rides it down with you. That’s a real personal quality, a virtue. My old boss Reagan was a little colder. The night before he won the crucial 1980 New Hampshire primary—the night before he wonit—he fired his campaign manager, John Sears. Reagan thought he wasn’t cutting it, so he was gone. The economist Martin Anderson once called Reagan genially ruthless, and he was. But then it wasn’t about John Sears’s feelings or Ronald Reagan’s feelings, it was about America. You can be pretty tough when it’s about America. Romney doesn’t seem to be out there campaigning enough. He seems—in this he is exactly like the president—to always be disappearing into fund-raisers, and not having enough big public events. But the logic of Romney’s fundraising has seemed, for some time, slightly crazy. He’s raising money so he can pile it in at the end, with ads. But at the end will they make much difference? Obama is said to have used a lot of his money early on, to paint a portrait of Romney as Thurston Howell III, as David Brooks put it. That was a gamble on Obama’s part: spend it now, pull ahead in the battlegrounds, once we pull ahead more money will come in because money follows winners, not losers. If I’m seeing things right, that strategy is paying off."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348076701720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:45:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348077767300-17</Id><Title>Mitts disgusting attack on half of America even has Mormons disowning him</Title><Msg>By Gregory A. Prince, Ph.D. Mitt Romney Is Not the Face of Mormonism Posted: 09/19/2012 1:12 pm When the news of Mitt Romney's Florida video broke on Monday evening, I was incensed -- but not for its political implications. His arrogant and out-of-hand dismissal of half the population of this country struck me at a visceral level, for it sullied the religion that he and I share -- the religion for which five generations of my ancestry have lived and sacrificed, the religion whose official mantra is "to take care of the poor and needy throughout the world." My first impulse was to rent an airplane towing a banner: "Mitt Romney is Not the Face of Mormonism!"</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1348077767300</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348078138262-18</Id><Title>"Thumpers" even turning on the Dipshidiot!!!</Title><Msg>What Would Jesus Say to Mitt Romney? Posted: 09/19/2012 1:02 pm My heart sank when I heard Mitt Romney's videotaped comments to a group of wealthy campaign donors. I had wanted to believe that he was a good, kind, spiritual man -- even though I disagree with his politics. I think Jesus' heart must have sunk, too, to hear such cold, condemning words from the lips of someone who professes to be a Christian. But apparently Romney prefers to just worship Jesus, rather than follow Him. I understand. Every Christian knows it's much easier to worship than follow. It's easy to say "God bless America"; it's hard to go into the military and put your life on the line for her. It's easy to write checks to your church; it's hard to extend your generosity to the thousands of people whose jobs you outsourced. It's easy to help out friends and neighbors in times of need; it's hard to be compassionate to the millions of needy people you don't know personally. It's easy to act pious in public; it's hard to really be Christ-like when you're hanging out with your über-rich friends behind closed doors. What would Jesus say? I'm not a biblical scholar, but I do know that Jesus has a lot to say about the poor, hungry and needy. Jesus tells me that I AM brother's keeper -- it is my job to help those who may have lost their way and ended up homeless, hopeless and poverty-stricken, no matter how they got there. Jesus tells me to judge not, lest I be judged -- it is my job to help others, not judge them as "victims" who refuse to take responsibility for their lives. Jesus tells me to love my neighbor as myself. And He doesn't just mean my literal neighbors; he means everyone. There is no doubt about Jesus' message when He says, "What you did not do for the least of these you did not do for me." Jesus has strong words for those who profess to be men of faith but don't walk their talk. Consider Luke 11:37-52, notably verses 42-44: "Woe to you Pharisees, because you give God a tenth of your mint, rue and all other kinds of garden herbs, but you neglect justice and the love of God. You should have practiced the latter without leaving the former undone. Woe to you Pharisees, because you love the most important seats in the synagogues and respectful greetings in the marketplaces. Woe to you, because you are like unmarked graves, which people walk over without knowing it." This last verse is especially harsh, basically saying that "anyone who comes into contact with you defiles himself just by your presence."* Jesus offers explicit advice for those who aspire to power and leadership: He tells us that the meek shall inherit the earth -- it is a leader's job to be humble, not arrogant. Jesus tells us that those who seek to lead people must serve them. And Jesus cautions us against personal, ego-driven ambition: "What do you benefit if you gain the whole world but lose your soul?" Alas, Mitt, the more you talk -- in public and in private -- the more we see who you really are. Makes me sad. I want to cry when I hear your cold, cruel comments about those who don't make enough money to pay income taxes -- the elderly, students, soldiers fighting overseas, the working poor, single-parent families, the long-term unemployed, the disabled. I think Jesus must be crying, too. Mitt, oh Mitt, have you learned nothing from all your years in church? Years ago, when I was traveling in North Carolina on business, I noticed the marquee in front of a little white church, and its message has stuck with me ever since: "Those who deserve love least, need it the most." So I'm trying to love you, Mitt, I'm really trying -- even though you don't seem to love the 47 percent of Americans who need it the most. I love you, Mitt, because Jesus tells me to love you as my brother -- but I'm praying you never make it to the White House. 2012-09-18-9781571746481.jpg *Special thanks to Brian Wendt for contributing the Bible verses from Luke. BJ Gallagher is the author of 'If God Is Your Co-Pilot, Switch Seats' (Hampton Roads).</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348078138262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348078884548-19</Id><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Msg>He actually belives that he can change the world just on his Obamaness. Where does anyone get this kind of hubris from... answer: All his life folks have been kissing his behind because as Joe(you'all)Biden said, he is a articulate clean blackman. The whole Obama middle east doctrine is on its head. These people hate us and Democracy, they feel that their prophet Muhammad is the way...end of story. For some junior senator and community organizer to think different is at best navie, and at worst maniacal. "I truly believe that the day I'm inaugurated not only does the country look at itself differently, but the whole world looks at America differently". "If I'm reaching out to the Muslim world they understand that I've lived in a Muslim country, and I may be a Christian, but I understand their point of view." "My sister is half Indonesian. I traveled there all the way through my college years so I am intimately concerned with what happens in these countries and the cultures and perspectives these folks have."</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348079832148-20</Id><Title>Dipshidiot imperiling GOP Senate races</Title><Msg>* Democrats target Republican's "shocking comment" * Republican sees comments as "one- or two-day story" By Thomas Ferraro WASHINGTON, Sept 18 (Reuters) - Two Republican U.S. Senate candidates in close races disowned Mitt Romney's "47 percent" comments on Tuesday, signaling concern about the impact of his words on Republican fortunes beyond the presidential race. Democrats, sensing a new opportunity to influence congressional contests, were busy trying to link Republicans generally with Romney's remarks. The Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee showered dozens of districts with news releases tying specific Republican candidates to Romney's "shocking comment." Linda McMahon, Republican Senate candidate in Connecticut, was worried enough to issue a statement criticizing Romney. "I disagree with Governor Romney's insinuation that 47 percent of Americans believe they are victims who must depend on the government for their care. I know that the vast majority of those who rely on government are not in that situation because they want to be," her statement said. McMahon, who lost a 2010 Senate bid in Connecticut, is in a close race against former U.S. Representative Chris Murphy. Massachusetts Senator Scott Brown, running a tight race against Harvard Law professor Elizabeth Warren to retain his seat in a traditionally Democratic state, sounded a similar theme. In statement to The Hill, a publication specializing in Congress, he said of Romney's views: "That's not the way I view the world. As someone who grew up in tough circumstances, I know that being on public assistance is not a spot that anyone wants to be in. Too many people today who want to work are being forced into public assistance for lack of jobs." In the video, the first part of which was published on Monday by the liberal Mother Jones magazine, Romney told donors that 47 percent of Americans would back Obama no matter what and "my job is not to worry about those people." In theory, at least, Romney's comments had the potential to offend millions of voters directly. About 46 percent of U.S. households paid no federal income tax in 2011, according to the bipartisan Tax Policy Center, although almost two-thirds of those paid an employment tax to support the Social Security and Medicare programs. 'SECOND THOUGHTS' It is axiomatic that a strong presidential nominee can boost the chances for other party candidates, particularly those in close U.S. Senate races. But the presidential candidate can also hurt those farther down the ticket. While a single comment might not alter particular races, a lagging campaign could. Republican Representative Steven LaTourette of Ohio, who is retiring from Congress, defended Romney's remarks, but said they "don't help i n swing districts like mine." "People were ready to throw Obama over, like dumping a boyfriend, and were ready to be courted by a new boyfriend," he said. "But now they're having second thoughts," LaTourette said. Republican Representative Tom Cole of Oklahoma called Romney's remarks "an unfortunate choice of words," but predicted the comments would be "a one- or two-day story." "The election is going to turn on the economy," Cole said. University of Virginia political scientist Larry Sabato, whose "Crystal Ball" blog closely tracks congressional races, said Romney's performance would be particularly influential in Senate races in Virginia, Connecticut, Montana, North Dakota and Florida. "Scott Brown can't survive much more undertow in Massachusetts," he said. George Allen, the Republican Senate contender in Virginia, "depends on a Romney win," Sabato added. "As I go through the states, I'd say Romney's performance will help to determine most of the close Senate contests," he said in an email interview. "It's going to be very difficult for Republicans to take over the Senate if Romney doesn't capture the White House. That's a different evaluation than a year ago when the GOP looked to be a good bet to grab the Senate."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348079832148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:37:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348080249086-21</Id><Title>Sermon on the Mitt?</Title><Msg>Blessed are the 1% who whine about their taxes, for they shall be comforted Blessed are their Cayman island bank accounts...........................</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348080249086</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:44:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348080324930-22</Id><Title>38% of the working poor vote for the GOP</Title><Msg>Their standard bearer, the Dipshidiot" , has just informed them that he considers them irrelevant. They could deduce a GOP win won't result in much help from Washington. In fact, things they count on for survival like food stamps, Medicaid , Medicare , public education and SS may be imperiled.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348080324930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348080886530-23</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Mormons disowning the Dipshidiot, getting ugly out there!!!</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348076282726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 13:38:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sometimes making some one uncomfortable is not a bad thing. If forces one to evaluate there situation and do something about it. To keep enabling people and forcing them to rely on the government can lead to just as much harm.</Msg><Username>deepwater531</Username><Timestamp>1348080886530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:54:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348081368721-24</Id><Topic><Title>38% of the working poor vote for the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348080324930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They realize that Obama will just "spend" the country into destruction and then they will have no one to help them when they need it.</Msg><Username>deepwater531</Username><Timestamp>1348081368721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348081849087-25</Id><Topic><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeap. It not the MOVIE, stupid!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348081849087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348084585377-26</Id><Topic><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**"If I'm reaching out to the Muslim world they understand that I've lived in a Muslim country"** Oh, something like I can see Russia from here that the left likes to ridicule....now what sounds more idiotic?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348084585377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 15:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348084978415-27</Id><Topic><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. Once he was inaugurated the country and the world DID have a better view of America. I know you choose not to remember that - but that's your personal problem. 2. Reaching out to others, is integral to dialog - I know the concept of dialog is beyond your limited comprehension - but again - that's your personal problem 3. I know you have issue with well versed, well traveled, knowledgeable people - but that - again - is your personal problem.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1348084978415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348087298687-28</Id><Topic><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right, Muslim "world DID have a better view of America". Because Muslim world thought Obama is "their" guy. Than Obama allowed to execute Osama and bragged about it. And hell broke loose. Now Obama is a traitor despite being well travelled. Seems like Obama has personal problem. Boy! May be it is still Bush' fault?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348087298687</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348087482026-29</Id><Title>$8.25 is a good buying point!</Title><Msg>WIth low trading activities and uncertain economy, market may tumble big. I am glad that I sold out all of my ETFC position last Friday. Looking for a buying entry at $8~8.25 again.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1348087482026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 16:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348088727868-30</Id><Title>GOP voter fraud</Title><Msg>Republican U.S. House Staffer Pleads 'No Contest' to 5 Election Fraud Counts The year of GOP election and voter fraud continues... By Brad Friedman on 9/19/2012, 7:51am PT No doubt Fox 'News' is going wall-to-wall with this today, so you've got no need for us to tell you about it, right? ... What? They're not? Huh. How strange. Well, then, if you haven't heard, Lorianne O'Brady, a former staffer to Congressman Thaddeus McCotter (R-MI) has pleaded "no contest" to five misdemeanor counts of election fraud yesterday, related to creating and submitting fraudulent signatures in a failed conspiracy to qualify McCotter for the ballot this year. O'Brady is just one of four of top McCotter aides who were charged last month with a total of 36 federal felony and misdemeanor election fraud-related counts in the alleged ballot petition forgery scheme. McCotter abruptly resigned last July as the scandal began to emerge. While U.S. House candidates in Michigan are required to submit just 1,000 valid voter signatures, McCotter's campaign turned in some 2,000. Investigators discovered, however, that just 244 of them were actually valid. The rest were forged or photo-copied from previous petitions. Submitting false signatures is the same thing that Fox "News" has spent years falsely claiming the community group ACORN was engaged in. The difference, of course, is that ACORN was the one to have discovered and turned in the handful, among their tens of thousands of voter registration workers, found to have defrauded them in such schemes. ACORN itself was never found to be involved in such fraud, and in every case, it was ACORN themselves who discovered the fraud and sought prosecution for the workers. McCotter's campaign was hardly the only Republican team involved in submitting fraudulent signatures in hopes of winning a place on the ballot this year. As The BRAD BLOG reported exclusively last January, the Presidential campaign of former U.S. House Speaker Newt Gingrich was being investigated by the Virginia State Attorney General after the former GOP Presidential candidate's campaign was discovered to have turned in fraudulent signatures in their failed bid to qualify for the Republican Presidential Primary Election in VA, Gingrich's home state. Gingrich was caught on tape claiming to a supporter, after the forgeries were discovered by the state Board of Elections: "We turned in 11,100 --- we needed 10,000 --- 1,500 of them were by one guy who, frankly, committed fraud." In May of this year, it was discovered that Momentum Political Services, a group hired by the Sacramento GOP and headed by a "professional con artist" to carry out their voter registration campaign for Rep. Dan Lungren (R-CA), had turned in thousands of fraudulent voter registrations as part of a $50,000 bounty paid for Republican-only voter registrations. That is, of course, exactly what ACORN was falsely accused of, even though --- unlike in the Sacramento GOP case, and in a very similar scheme by a firm hired by the California Republican Party in 2008, where the head of the firm itself pleaded guilty to charges of voter registration fraud --- the former four-decade old community organization was never actually involved in. For more on the McCotter staffers charged with 36 election fraud-related counts, see our August coverage. As an added bonus, that article also includes a quick round-up of more than 10 recent cases of alleged and confirmed voter fraud and election fraud by a number of very high-profile Republicans, including Gingrich, Mitt Romney, Todd Akin, James O'Keefe, the Sec. of State of Indiana and, yes, the high priestess of GOP Voter Fraud, Ann Coulter. Of course, none of the fraud detailed above would have been prevented by the disenfranchising polling place Photo ID restriction schemes Republicans are enacting around the country under the guise of deterring "voter fraud" --- not even Coulter's, since she also committed a felony to create a fraudulent drivers' license with the faked address she submitted to election officials when she committed fraud on her voter registration form, before later, knowingly, voting at a precinct in an area where she did not live in Florida. That, even though there are just 10 known cases of in-person voter impersonation --- the only type of voter fraud that can possibly be deterred by polling place Photo ID restrictions --- in the entire country, out of hundreds of millions of votes cast since 2000.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348088727868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348088859125-31</Id><Topic><Title>In Obama's own words</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1348078884548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh god, my sides hurt. To think you actually think these two comments are similar. In the first the person has actually LIVED in the country he is making a comment about, lived shoulder to shoulder with its citizens. Conversed with its citizens, lived among its culture.... The other is a fool saying she can see the border of a country next door (compounded b by the fact that as a state governor she would have NO relationship with the Russian govt at all with). I could have even bought her garbage a bit, if it was a populated area of Alaska next to a populated area of Russia, but it is barren, next to barren. Too funny, you are now in a contest with pacifican to see who is the biggest fool?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1348088859125</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348089072876-32</Id><Title>Small biz overwhelmingly favors BO!!!!</Title><Msg>Can't wait for Mitt's take on this one: Small business owners favor Obama (47%) over Romney (39%) Austin Business Journal: Obama leads Romney among small biz owners, survey says Tuesday, September 18, 2012, 7:36am CDT President Barack Obama leads Mitt Romney among small business owners, according to one new survey. The economy and job creation is the most important issue in this election for almost half of small business owners polled in a new survey, which also found that President Barack Obama leads Republican challenger Mitt Romney by 47 percent to 39 percent.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348089072876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:11:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348089615709-33</Id><Topic><Title>38% of the working poor vote for the GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348080324930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:45:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for the fact that thats basically impossible unless someone really screws up. The government isn't a household, they don't need to balance their budget ever. The deficit is only about 6% of GDP, not that big a deal. The 15 Trillion in debt will never be paid back, and thats a good thing because thats 15 Trillion in assets that people like you and me now have. The fact that people think we'll pass on the debt to our children and they'll have to pay it all back is laughable. Government debt isn't some magical thing that they owe to some mystery person who is outside of the economy, its owed primarily to the citizens of the US, what some would call "savings". The real thing you should be worried about is our trade deficit, over 500 billion a year. That means the first 500 billion of government deficit is just to compensate for the outflow of dollars to the rest of the world. If they didn't spend at least that much, eventually we'd run out of dollars in America. This was actually one of the causes of so many people taking on debt in the late 90s and early 2000s, which partially lead to the housing bubble. The government deficit was smaller than the trade deficit, thus the American people had negative savings rates during that time and increased debt burdens. Unlike the government, you and I can't constanly increase our debt because we don't control the currency. Its the same reason all those countries in Europe are going under, they don't control their own currency.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1348089615709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:20:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348098188516-34</Id><Title>hey odumbomites..woot woot!</Title><Msg>NEW YORK (Reuters) - The net worth of the richest Americans grew by 13 percent in the past year to $1.7 trillion, Forbes magazine said on Wednesday, and a familiar cast populated the top of the annual list, including Bill Gates, Warren Buffett, Larry Ellison and the Koch brothers. The average net worth of the 400 wealthiest Americans rose to a record $4.2 billion, up more than 10 percent from a year ago, while the lowest net worth came in at $1.1 billion versus $1.05 billion last year, the magazine said. Seven in ten of the list's members made their fortunes from scratch</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1348098188516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 19:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348099499109-35</Id><Title>DETERIORATING</Title><Msg>Arctic ice shrinks 18% in a year, sounding climate change alarm bells Scientists and environment groups say the fall is unprecedented and the clearest signal yet of global warming John Vidal in Longyearbyen, Svalbard guardian.co.uk, Wednesday 19 September 2012 14.09 EDT Arctic melting ice : Icebergs, Disko Bay, Greenland 'Our response [so far] has not been alarm, or panic, or a sense of emergency. It has been: ‘Let’s go up there and drill for oil’. There is no more perfect indictment of our failure to get to grips with the greatest problem we’ve ever faced,' says author and environmental campaigner Bill McKibben. Sea ice in the Arctic shrunk a dramatic 18% this year to a record low of 3.41m sq km, according to the official US monitoring organisation the National Snow and Ice Data Centre in Boulder, Colorado. Scientists and environment groups last night said the fall was unprecedented and the clearest signal yet of climate change. The data released showed the arctic sea beginning to refreeze again in the last few days after the most dramatic melt observed since satellite observations started in 1979. This year's sea ice extent was 700,000 sq km below the previous minimum of 4.17m sq km set in 2007. "We are now in uncharted territory," said Nsidc director Mark Serreze. "While we've long known that as the planet warms up, changes would be seen first and be most pronounced in the Arctic, few of us were prepared for how rapidly the changes would actually occur." Julienne Stroece, an Nsidc ice research scientist who has been monitoring ice conditions aboard the Greenpeace vessel Arctic Sunrise, said the data suggested the Arctic sea ice cover was fundamentally changing and predicted more extreme weather. "We can expect more summers like 2012 as the ice cover continues to thin. The loss of summer sea ice has led to unusual warming of the Arctic atmosphere, that in turn impacts weather patterns in the northern hemisphere, that can result in persistent extreme weather such as droughts, heatwaves and flooding," she said. Arctic sea ice Arctic sea ice extent for September 16, 2012 was 3.41m sq km. The orange line shows the 1979 to 2000 median extent for that day. The black cross indicates the geographic North Pole. Photograph: National Snow and Ice Data Center Other leading ice scientists this week predicted the complete collapse of sea ice in the Arctic within four years. "The final collapse ... is now happening and will probably be complete by 2015/16," said Prof Peter Wadhams of Cambridge University. Sea ice in the Arctic is seen as a key indicator of global climate change because of its sensitivity to warming and its role in amplifying climate change. According to Nsidc, the warming of Arctic areas is now increasing at around 10% a decade. Along with the extent of the sea ice, its thickness, or volume, has also significantly decreased in the last two decades. While this is harder to measure accurately, it is believed to have decreased around 40% since 1979. The collapse of the ice cap was last night interpreted by environment groups as a signal of long-term climate warming caused by man. "I hope that future generations will mark this day as a turning point, when a new spirit of global cooperation emerged to tackle the huge challenges we face. We must work together to protect the Arctic from the effects of climate change and unchecked corporate greed. This is now the defining environmental battle of our era," said Kumi Naidoo, director of Greenpeace International. Other groups called on the UK government, and industries across the world to heed the warning signs from the Arctic and act "with urgency and ambition" to tackle climate change. Rod Downie, polar expert at WWF-UK said: "With the speed of change we are now witnessing in the Arctic, the UK government must show national and global leadership in the urgent transition away from fossil fuels to a low carbon economy. "This is further evidence that Shell's pursuit of hydrocarbons in the Arctic is reckless. It is completely irresponsible to drill for oil in such a fragile environment; there are simply too many unmanageable risks." Author and environmental campaigner Bill McKibben said: "Our response [so far] has not been alarm, or panic, or a sense of emergency. It has been: 'Let's go up there and drill for oil'. There is no more perfect indictment of our failure to get to grips with the greatest problem we've ever faced." Arctic sea ice follows an annual cycle of melting through the warm summer months and refreezing in the winter. It has shown a dramatic overall decline over the past 30 years. Sea ice is known to play a critical role in regulating climate, acting as a giant mirror that reflects much of the sun's energy, helping to cool the Earth. The UN Environment programme warned that the extra shipping and industry likely to result from the thawing of sea ice could further accelerate sea ice melting. "There is an urgent need to calculate risks of local pollutants such as soot, or black carbon, in the Arctic. Soot darkens ice, making it soak up more of the sun's heat and quickening a melt," said UNEP spokesman Nick Nuttall in Nairobi.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348099499109</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:04:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348100246770-36</Id><Title>Also deteriorating</Title><Msg>Mitt is down; out looms next By: Roger Simon September 19, 2012 04:32 AM EDT The wheels are not coming off the Mitt Romney campaign. They came off some time ago. The press is just beginning to notice. The Romney campaign is skidding along on its axles and scraping its muffler. Soon it will be down to the dog on the roof. I hate to say I told you so. No, scratch that. I love to say I told you so. I just don’t get to do it very often. But as I have been saying for a while now, Mitt Romney is a deeply flawed candidate who got the Republican nomination by beating a ludicrously weak field. Don’t believe me? You know who came in second? Rick Santorum. Newt Gingrich was third, and Ron Paul was fourth. That’s not a field; that’s a therapy group. Romney’s defects as a nominee, which I will get to in a moment, were obvious, but considered unimportant because he really did not have to attract voters. Instead, voters would flock to him. They would be driven to him by a bad economy and a lack of jobs, jobs, jobs. The latter was the Romney campaign’s magical incantation that would make up for any of its own faults and deficiencies. Did Team Romney face a well-funded incumbent, an inspirational orator, who had assembled an experienced, battle-hardened campaign staff that understood the electoral map as well as any in history? Well, yes. And did Team Romney understand that as much as the media dismissed conventions as meaningless, the Democrats would use their convention to rebrand the party as one that was strong on defense, big on determination and deeply concerned about our fighting forces? Well, no. Jobs, jobs, jobs, the Romney team chanted. That would solve everything. That would make voters desert Obama in droves. And it did not matter that the evidence suggested otherwise. Unemployment has been above 8 percent for every month of the Obama campaign and he has beaten Romney in the polls in every month of his campaign. With its tunnel vision, the Romney campaign assumed an economic downturn would mean Americans would want to elect a businessman to the presidency. Yet the economic downturn was caused in part by shady business practices, runaway greed and outright dishonesty at the highest reaches of America’s corporate community. Did Americans really want to elect the guy on the cover of the Monopoly box or throw him in jail? So how does a wheeler-dealer financier like Romney gain the public trust? By refusing to release a meaningful number of his back tax returns! Just trust him, he says. Because we know the Masters of the Financial Universe are always trustworthy, don’t we? But wait. Does Romney trust his own vice presidential nominee? No, he does not. Romney demanded 10 years of Paul Ryan’s back tax returns before he selected him. So why should we show Romney the trust he would not show his own running mate? Ronald Reagan had a simple formula: “Trust, but verify.” We are told to trust Romney about his tax records and his Swiss bank accounts and all the rest. But how do we verify? We can’t. And there is another thing that troubles me even though some dismiss it as trivial. I am still bothered by Romney attacking that gay kid and cutting off his hair with a pair of scissors when they were in prep school. A ghetto kid does that and he gets booked for assault with a deadly weapon. But what does the son of a governor get? A law degree from Harvard. Republicans accuse Obama of wanting to wage class warfare, but who is more class conscious than Romney? I can summarize what Romney said to a bunch of wealthy donors at a May fundraiser: America is divided between the deserving rich and bums who want a handout. Vote for me, and I’ll keep you rich. Thank you very much. Enjoy the chicken. And when David Corn of Mother Jones obtained the video of those remarks and Romney was forced to hold a news conference, how did he explain them? “That’s something which fundraising people who are parting with their monies are very interested in,” Romney said. No kidding. But no matter. We still have the debates in October, and the debates can save Romney. Not that he is a masterful debater. At a debate last December, he decided to attack the hapless Rick Perry by betting him that he was wrong. “Rick, I’ll tell you what,” Romney said, sticking out hand, “ten thousand bucks? $10,000 bet?” As I wrote at the time: That’s right, Mitt. Remind the American people that $10,000 is chump change to you. Romney won most of his primary debates, however, by staying above the fray and looking presidential. But that won’t work against Obama, who is, after all, an actual president. Since Romney can salvage his campaign only by a stunning victory in these debates, he is going to have to attack Obama relentlessly. But you can bet on two things: Romney will be intensely uncomfortable in that role, and Obama will be well prepared for it. I do not want to give the impression that Romney and Obama are polar opposites. They are not. Both are politicians. Both want power. But after Nov. 6, only one of them is going to have any. Roger Simon is POLITICO’s chief political columnist.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348100246770</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348102061136-37</Id><Title>It's clear that Romney &amp; Ryan are just more Bush, so why isn't W on board and pumping R&amp;R?</Title><Msg>......................If Romney and Ryan are advocating more neo-con Mideast policy (see Iran), and less regulation of Wall Street, and lower taxes on the well-to-do, all of which they support, then why is George W not being touted??? These are largely an extension of policies that the Bush regime was pushing. Where's George W , their role-model?...............</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1348102061136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 20:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348104341727-38</Id><Topic><Title>Small biz overwhelmingly favors BO!!!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348089072876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:11:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's ridiculous junglebob.. one survey? Seems you'll believe anything in your old age.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1348104341727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:25:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348106167185-39</Id><Topic><Title>Small biz overwhelmingly favors BO!!!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348089072876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 17:11:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are so crazy..are you part INDIAN? the only small business owner that likes obama are the drug dealer and marijuana stands in Colorada... Real business supports Romney....</Msg><Username>revodcam</Username><Timestamp>1348106167185</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 21:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348106626977-40</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT'S DIARY</Title><Msg>Wed Sep 19, 2012 at 05:30 PM PDT The Chronicles of Mitt: Sept 19, 2012 by Hunter pen on paper: 'Dear diary' Hello, human diary. It is I again, Mitt Romney, your better. I honestly do not know what these people are going on about. I merely observed that approximately one half of the nation was made up of slackers and ne'er do wells, dull and lazy persons who would never amount to anything but who nonetheless are allowed to vote as if they were productive human beings. This is common conversation during every dinner party I have ever attended, so what, precisely, is the difficulty this time around? Politics continues to confound me.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348106626977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348107118319-41</Id><Title>GOP Senators kill Vet's job bill</Title><Msg>Wed Sep 19, 2012 at 01:30 PM PDT Senate Republicans kill veterans jobs bill by Joan McCarter McConnell: No jobs for vets. In their short work week before heading out of town, Senate Republicans decided to give the finger to veterans, using a procedural vote to kill the Veterans Jobs Corp Act, 58-40. The Veterans Jobs Corp Act would have created new job-training programs to help veterans find work in targeted fields such as national park conservation, historic preservation projects, police work and firefighting, among others. The unemployment rate for Iraq, Afghanistan and Gulf War II-era Veterans—those who would have most benefitted from the bill—is now at 10.9 percent, but Republicans blocked this bill because they don't want anything that could remotely help anyone to happen under President Obama's watch. That, and they don't really give a crap about veterans, much like Mitt Romney, who called the men and women fighting in Afghanistan items on a laundry list. That's just how Republicans are. 1:34 PM PT: The White House responds: No veteran who fought for our nation should have to fight for a job at home, but Republicans in Washington are blocking a common sense plan to create the Veterans Jobs Corps and put tens of thousands of veterans back to work. Working with Democrats and Republicans in Congress, the Obama Administration has already made real progress to help veterans find jobs. We passed tax credits to encourage employers to hire veterans and released new tools to connect veterans with employers. And thanks to the First Lady and Dr. Biden’s Joining Forces Initiative, more than 2,000 businesses have hired or trained more than 125,000 veterans and military spouses in the past year. But we can do more and Senate Republicans should not block legislation that includes many of their ideas and stand between veterans and good jobs protecting and preserving America.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1348107118319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 22:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348112999849-42</Id><Title>Fat boy gonna have a stroke!!!</Title><Msg>More bad news for New Jersey, and for Gov. Chris Christie: The latest dose of bad news was delivered by Standard &amp; Poor’s, which Tuesday lowered its credit outlook for New Jersey from stable to negative. While Standard &amp; Poor’s did not change the state’s AA- rating — one of the worst among the states — it warned the more drastic step of a lower rating loomed if Christie’s nearly 8 percent growth in revenue failed to materialize. [...] "We revised the outlook to reflect our view of the risk of revenue assumptions we view as optimistic, continued reliance on one-time measures to offset revenue shortfalls, and longer-term growing expenditure pressures," John Sugden, a credit analyst for Standard &amp; Poor’s, said. The optimistic revenue assumptions part is a direct reference to Christie's implausible budget assumptions, especially as it relates to his insistence that only further tax cuts can possibly cause the magical money unicorn to once again poop cash and rainbows across his great state. For Republicans, this was proof enough of Christie's seriousness to make him one of the keynote speakers at their recent convention. Which, as it turns out, seems to be a trend. After all, one of the people most responsible for the national credit downgrade was Paul Ryan and his merry band of fellow fiscal anarchists—and for his own valiant attempts in the field of completely implausible budget numbers, he was rewarded with the vice presidential slot on the Republican ticket. In the current Republican Party, gross fiscal incompetence has become a big selling point. And if your incompetence results in actual, real-world economic damage, you'll be considered as leadership material.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1348112999849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348113264241-43</Id><Title>Smal Business Abandons Romney Supports Obama</Title><Msg>More evidence that the roof is caving in on Mitt Romney came today from a poll of small business owners conducted by George Washington University School of Political Management, which found Obama leading Romney, 47%-39%. Not only is Obama leading Romney, but the George Washington University poll also found that small business owners thought President Obama was more supportive of them than Mitt Romney by 39%-31% margin, with 28% undecided. 6,415 small business owners were asked what their single most important issue was in their choice for president. Forty percent of them responded the economy and jobs. Fourteen percent listed corruption/honesty/ethics in government, six percent responded social/moral issues, and five percent said it was beating Romney/supporting Obama/electing Democrats. Obamacare, beating Obama/electing Romney/supporting Republicans, and the budget deficit all tied at 5%. Two staples of the Romney campaign, taxes was mentioned by 3%, and government regulation was not mentioned at all. The three most important issues to small business owners were unemployment and the job market (26%), the federal budget deficit (16%), and healthcare costs (10%). Small business owners listed self-employment taxes, the cost of gas, healthcare costs, and personal income taxes to be the biggest burdens. President Obama has cut taxes for small businesses anywhere from 16 to 18 times depending on how a small business tax cut is defined. In contrast Mitt Romney came up with a slogan, but the benefits of his tax plan are designed for corporations and people at the top. Romney’s plan would give the biggest corporations a $1 trillion tax cut.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1348113264241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 23:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>