<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346213935633-1</Id><Title>Unimpressive GOP rhetoric</Title><Msg>Romney and Christie's Hard Truth Problem By Josh Barro Aug 28, 2012 8:15 PM PT Facebook Share Tweet LinkedIn Google +1 0 Comments Print QUEUE Q The theme of Chris Christie’s Republican National Convention keynote address tonight was “hard truths.” The hard truths Chris Christie’s mother told, the ones he has told as governor of New Jersey, and the ones he says Mitt Romney will tell if elected president. But sometimes, when telling the hard truth is especially hard, Chris Christie dissembles. And Mitt Romney -- well, I will just note Christie’s use of the future tense. Christie promises Romney “will tell us the hard truths.” It would be hard to contend that he has done so in the past. I have no reason to doubt that Christie’s mother was a straight shooter. So, at least he went one for three in tonight’s speech. Christie’s record in New Jersey is mixed. He really has told some hard truths and defended some politically difficult positions, and the state is better off for it. He has put a focus on pay and benefits structures that have made public employment in New Jersey unaffordable, and has gotten good though imperfect reforms passed through a Democratically controlled legislature. Part of his 2010 budget plan was eliminating property tax credits -- effectively, raising New Jersey residents’ net property tax bills. This wasn’t popular in the state with the country’s highest property taxes, and it drew fire from the right and left, but it was a necessary part of addressing the state’s dire fiscal situation. Unlike most Republicans, Christie has declined to take the Americans for Tax Reform pledge against tax increases. And he has loudly defended Muslims against baseless attacks from some conservatives, even though doing so might hurt him in a future presidential primary. But a hard truth Christie absolutely will not tell is that every one of his budgets has been unbalanced by more than $2.5 billion. When Christie said tonight he has signed “three balanced budgets,” he wasn’t telling a hard truth -- he was using bad accounting to hide a hard truth. Each year, Christie has achieved “on paper” budget balance by making inadequate payments into the state’s pension fund, effectively borrowing from the fund. Christie has touted this year’s $1.03 billion pension fund payment as the largest in the state’s history. Too bad the state’s pension actuaries told him to deposit $3.74 billion. And Christie said tonight that his pension reforms will save the state $132 billion over 30 years. But those savings are backloaded. Pension costs will continue to rise over the coming years and squeeze out funding for public services. Even after reform, the hard truth is that New Jersey still has a defined-benefit pension system that is unaffordable and exposes taxpayers to excessive investment risk. Christie isn’t the first governor to underfund New Jersey’s pensions or to sign a budget that was “balanced” with gimmicks. And he’s not the only governor to brag about an inadequate pension reform -- New Jersey’s reforms are actually better than what most states have done in the last few years. But Christie claims to be a unique truth-teller, and in these key areas, he has not been one. As for Romney, his political career has been built around avoiding hard truths. He was a moderate when that was convenient and a conservative when that was convenient, always modifying his message to meet the demands of the audience. Mitt Romney needs hard truths like a fish needs a bicycle. Romney’s platform contains no discernable hard truths. At a time of record budget deficits, Romney is running on a plan to cut income tax rates by 20 percent. He says he will broaden the tax base to offset the revenue loss, but he won’t say how -- that would be a hard truth. Romney says Medicare is unsustainable, and yet he promises no changes to the program before 2022, even pledging to spend hundreds of billions of dollars more than President Obama would over the next decade. Saying that Medicare cuts have to start now, as they do in Obama's plan, would be a hard truth. Romney has a 59-point economic plan with no content about monetary policy or housing policy. The vast majority of the plan could have just as easily have been proposed in 2007, before the housing and financial crises rocked the economy. Saying what he would do about the specific economic problems of our time would probably involve telling some hard truths. Maybe Christie has reason to believe Romney will start telling hard truths if we first elect him president. I actually think that’s possible -- it’s closely related to my Secret Economic Plan hypothesis. And that’s the hard truth about Mitt Romney’s candidacy -- the only way to support him is on a leap of faith.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346213935633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346215206000-2</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo denies access to Googles Firefox browser</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346198110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean Google Chrome?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1346215206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346215344000-3</Id><Topic><Title>No, It aint right.</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346010627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must learn the difference between working for the government and "living off the taxpayer". There are, of course, similarities, but the differences are most important than those. Usually liberals have a hard time with this though exercise.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1346215344000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:42:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346215553000-4</Id><Topic><Title>Yahoo denies access to Googles Firefox browser</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346198110000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:55:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Firefox. Which is owned by google.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346215553000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:45:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346242660003-5</Id><Topic><Title>Unimpressive GOP rhetoric</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346213935633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey #$%$new this board is for etfc Not your #$%$new view of politics ... Get off this board and stay off !!!!</Msg><Username>bigtimeusa</Username><Timestamp>1346242660003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346244451000-6</Id><Title>E*TRADE Financial Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial Corporation looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in E*TRADE Financial Corporation http://STOCKMARKETEXPLAINED.INFO</Msg><Username>selinakingman</Username><Timestamp>1346244451000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346244582964-7</Id><Title>Frank J. Petrilli</Title><Msg>This guys past is full of affiliations with The Toronto-Dominion Bank, Waterhouse Investor Services, Inc., and TD Ameritrade, Inc my opinion is the communication channels most be wide open and that makes mergers much more likely</Msg><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1346244582964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:49:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346245157000-8</Id><Title>Technical Chart Shows Upside onE*TRADE Financial Corporation</Title><Msg>Im in shock!E*TRADE Financial Corporation is on the verge of a major change in trend. Check out this site http://FREEMOCKSTOCKTRADING.INFO</Msg><Username>dorotharaden</Username><Timestamp>1346245157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346249189000-9</Id><Topic><Title>No, It aint right.</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346010627000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-26 15:50:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please tell us what Ryan's job experience is.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1346249189000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346249876000-10</Id><Title>Is E*TRADE Financial Corporation about to plunge? I think I have figured it out</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial Corporation is on the verge of a major decline. Look what is about to happen! http://INSTANTSTOCKQUOTES.INFO</Msg><Username>perryguedjian</Username><Timestamp>1346249876000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:17:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346250302477-11</Id><Title>GOP's zero share of the black vote explained</Title><Msg>An attendee at the Republican National Convention in Tampa on Tuesday allegedly threw nuts at a black camerawoman working for CNN and said “This is how we feed animals” before being removed from the convention, a network official confirmed to TPM. Keep it classy, Republicans.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346250302477</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346250560434-12</Id><Title>Taibbi in Rolling Stone</Title><Msg>Greed and Debt: The True Story of Mitt Romney and Bain Capital How the GOP presidential candidate and his private equity firm staged an epic wealth grab, destroyed jobs – and stuck others with the bill Four years ago, the Mitt Romneys of the world nearly destroyed the global economy with their greed, shortsightedness and – most notably – wildly irresponsible use of debt in pursuit of personal profit. The sight was so disgusting that people everywhere were ready to drop an H-bomb on Lower Manhattan and bayonet the survivors. But today that same insane greed ethos, that same belief in the lunatic pursuit of instant borrowed millions – it's dusted itself off, it's had a shave and a shoeshine, and it's back out there running for president. ......................... "But what most voters don't know is the way Mitt Romney actually made his fortune: by borrowing vast sums of money that other people were forced to pay back. This is the plain, stark reality that has somehow eluded America's top political journalists for two consecutive presidential campaigns: Mitt Romney is one of the greatest and most irresponsible debt creators of all time. In the past few decades, in fact, Romney has piled more debt onto more unsuspecting companies, written more gigantic checks that other people have to cover, than perhaps all but a handful of people on planet Earth." "By making debt the centerpiece of his campaign, Romney was making a calculated bluff of historic dimensions - placing a massive all-in bet on the rank incompetence of the American press corps. The result has been a brilliant comedy: A man makes a $250 million fortune loading up companies with debt and then extracting million-dollar fees from those same companies, in exchange for the generous service of telling them who needs to be fired in order to finance the debt payments he saddled them with in the first place..." "If Romney pulls off this whopper, you'll have to tip your hat to him: No one in history has ever successfully run for president riding this big of a lie. It's almost enough to make you think he really is qualified for the White House."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346250560434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346250821000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>precious_krystal34</Username><Timestamp>1346244202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Promised Profit</Msg><Username>sherie_karin</Username><Timestamp>1346250821000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346253550066-14</Id><Topic><Title>Thought the GOP convention was supposed to be this week</Title><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1346196303113</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 19:25:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another STUPID American - you didn't build that! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346253550066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346253932111-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unimpressive GOP rhetoric</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346213935633</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 00:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But he is the FULL TIME LEFT WING IDIOT on this board - we can't afford to lose him because he is doing in OBIMBORAMA deeper and deeper, he even beats the CLOWN and JUNGLEBIMBO! (JB) YES, we built it! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346253932111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346253983975-16</Id><Topic><Title>Frank J. Petrilli</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1346244582964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only issue with amtd is the mortgage book. I don't care how good of a relationship he has with amtd, it's hard to convince them those loans are not full of crap. Buyers want stuff on the cheap. Amtd will use that to thier advantage on any disscussion.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346253983975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 11:26:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346257517000-17</Id><Title>Republicans Win</Title><Msg>For the most mind numbing 3 hours of total boredom. Chris Christie didn't mention Romney Ann Romney avoided any mention of Bain They have soooo much to fear. I'll bet not one poster here watched the process.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1346257517000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346258311000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>precious_krystal34</Username><Timestamp>1346244202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I singed up too...</Msg><Username>gerda_fern</Username><Timestamp>1346258311000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346259403135-19</Id><Title>A job no one wants, maybe the "toad" will take it?</Title><Msg>Struggling online brokerage firm says it's close to hiring executive search firm. E*Trade's trading babies FORTUNE -- E*Trade may have to pay its babysitter overtime. One of the top candidates to run the online trading firm, which is known for its trading baby television ads, says he isn't interested in the job. Greg Fleming, who heads Morgan Stanley's brokerage division and is overseeing its integration with Smith Barney, says he has no plans to leave his current position, according to sources close to Fleming.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346259403135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:56:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346259550000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>precious_krystal34</Username><Timestamp>1346244202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major Information Happening</Msg><Username>lavon_ina</Username><Timestamp>1346259550000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346259825652-21</Id><Topic><Title>A job no one wants, maybe the "toad" will take it?</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346259403135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 12:56:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i couldn't do any worse then the last no talent yahoo! first thing i would do is sell the company and give the money back to investors where it belongs!!!as you can see etfc has done nothing but milk investors for the last 5 years! imho</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346259825652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346260223280-22</Id><Title>Need to announce new strategy at Barclay's conf</Title><Msg>They made all this effort to throw out the bank president and CEO. They had better present their new strategy that warrants the expense of cleaning house.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346260223280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:10:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346260396660-23</Id><Topic><Title>Need to announce new strategy at Barclay's conf</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1346260223280</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:10:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it seems thier plan was to milk investors more by letting pertilli get 500k a month till they find another shill to fill the last one's spot. sell this god forsaken pos already!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346260396660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346260692000-24</Id><Title>New Analysis on E*TRADE Financial Corporation Suggests Drop</Title><Msg>Wow! E*TRADE Financial Corporation is not looking good right now. MUST READ! http://GUIDESTOCK.INFO</Msg><Username>geriweinzimer</Username><Timestamp>1346260692000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261061000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>precious_krystal34</Username><Timestamp>1346244202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see your pointThanks for sharing this.</Msg><Username>evie_aida82</Username><Timestamp>1346261061000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:24:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346261243954-26</Id><Topic><Title>Taibbi in Rolling Stone</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346250560434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good read! "Mitt Romney, it turns out, is the perfect frontman for Wall Street's greed revolution. He's not a two-bit, shifty-eyed huckster like Lloyd Blankfein. He's not a sighing, eye-rolling, arrogant jerkwad like Jamie Dimon. But Mitt believes the same things those guys believe: He's been right with them on the front lines of the financialization revolution, a decades-long campaign in which the old, simple, let's-make-stuff-and-sell-it manufacturing economy was replaced with a new, highly complex, let's-take-stuff-and-trash-it financial economy. Instead of cars and airplanes, we built swaps, CDOs and other toxic financial products. Instead of building new companies from the ground up, we took out massive bank loans and used them to acquire existing firms, liquidating every asset in sight and leaving the target companies holding the note. The new borrow-and-conquer economy was morally sanctified by an almost religious faith in the grossly euphemistic concept of "creative destruction," and amounted to a total abdication of collective responsibility by America's rich, whose new thing was making assloads of money in ever-shorter campaigns of economic conquest, sending the proceeds offshore, and shrugging as the great towns and factories their parents and grandparents built were shuttered and boarded up, crushed by a true prairie fire of debt. Mitt Romney – a man whose own father built cars and nurtured communities, and was one of the old-school industrial anachronisms pushed aside by the new generation's wealth grab – has emerged now to sell this make-nothing, take-everything, screw-everyone ethos to the world. He's Gordon Gekko, but a new and improved version, with better PR – and a bigger goal. A takeover artist all his life, Romney is now trying to take over America itself. And if his own history is any guide, we'll all end up paying for the acquisition."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346261243954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 13:27:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346263206000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade board of Directums</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346193643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 18:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dint get any stars on this. I dint get any stars on my beautiful ceo prognostications neither. Did yous see da newz today? Da morgan stanley candidate pulled out. He hates da board of directums</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346263206000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346263376000-28</Id><Topic><Title>No ceo? Sell the company. Easy.</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346192902000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-28 18:28:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets waste more time. Please pass the Jergens Lotion.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346263376000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346263401000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Be Leery!</Title><Username>precious_krystal34</Username><Timestamp>1346244202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:43:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>tressa_caitlin</Username><Timestamp>1346263401000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:03:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346264011324-30</Id><Topic><Title>Taibbi in Rolling Stone</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346250560434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 10:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not to even mention that he's not a Christian, unlike Obama. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346264011324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:13:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346264187132-31</Id><Title>no wonder they can't make money</Title><Msg>the fire ceo(good) but still have to pay him(bad) and then they pay chairman 500k a month(just plain stupid) to do his job. Sounds like bain capital milking the company and investors before they crash thge company!!!must be huge losses coming at quarter's end!!!! when will this pos just sell and get it over with!!! 10 million shares must have been short waiting for the fall!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1346264187132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346264864692-32</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney!!! (Done!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1345413053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging by the vein popping all the Progressive/Marxist/Liberals are having right now,......LANDSLIDE of historical proportions for President Romney!!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1346264864692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 14:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346268293878-33</Id><Topic><Title>Voter ID laws simply GOP voter suppression</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344745665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do the Democrats want no voter ID, answer....so they can vote early and offen.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346268293878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346268834956-34</Id><Topic><Title>On 'Lection day, get out there and vote for a good Christian!</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346101435665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote for Obama because he is a Christain, then according to your logic he is a child molester. The last time I check the Catholic Church is a Christain organization. BTW, why you lefties got religion all of a sudden...phonies, fakes, and frauds the lot of you.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346268834956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:33:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346269657360-35</Id><Title>Voter I.D. Laws protects your Vote!!!</Title><Msg>How the 'F' do people get to the polls without a Drivers License? If you are the one stupid ILLEGAL who can't find his Fake I.D., well look over by your crack pipe!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346269657360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346273038806-36</Id><Topic><Title>Voter I.D. Laws protects your Vote!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346269657360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 15:47:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Voter ID laws assume someone is going around trying to impersonate voters. Just not happening. South Carolina Voter ID Law Author Cannot Cite Single Example Of In-Person Voter Impersonation By Josh Israel on Aug 28, 2012 at 6:00 pm State Sen. George E. "Chip" Campsen, III (R-SC) State Sen. George E. "Chip" Campsen, III (R-SC) As a federal court considers whether to reinstate a South Carolina state voter identification law — denied pre-clearance by the U.S. Department of Justice for violating the Voting Rights Act — one of the bill’s authors took the stand Monday to defend the bill. But when pressed, state Sen. George E. “Chip” Campsen III (R) acknowledged that none of the isolated examples of possible voter fraud that he could identify would have been prevented by requiring a photo identification to vote in-person. The Associated Press reports: [Campsen] cited examples of fraud that he took into consideration while drafting early versions of South Carolina’s law. These included vote buying, voter rolls indicating a woman who showed up at the polls had already voted, and press reports of voters being registered in both South Carolina and North Carolina. But under questioning from Justice Department attorney Anna Baldwin, Campsen, a Republican, said the examples he gave did not involve the type of fraud that requiring photo identification would address. “None of the examples you gave in your testimony involved incidents of impersonation?” Baldwin asked. “Correct,” Campsen answered. He also said he could not find cases of voter impersonation in South Carolina, but added that the state lacks the tools to root them out. Last month, the Republican Attorney General of South Carolina also admitted that requiring a photo identification to vote would not actually prevent a determined voter impersonator from voting as someone else. But happily, as Campsen noted in his testimony, it almost never happens. In fact, it is so rare that a person is more likely to be struck by lightning than commit voter fraud of any kind. Even the Supreme Court could only identify one example of in-person voter fraud in the past 143 years in their 2009 decision upholding a voter ID law. By contrast, a recent Brennan Center report found that nearly 500,000 voters — mostly low-income and minority individuals — in states with voter ID laws stand to be disenfranchised. These voter ID laws continue to be at best a solution in search of a problem — and at worse, a scheme to disenfranchise elderly, urban, poor, and minority voters who are among the least likely to have a photo identification.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346273038806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346273165269-37</Id><Title>GOP assault on democracy</Title><Msg>"Last month, the Republican Attorney General of South Carolina also admitted that requiring a photo identification to vote would not actually prevent a determined voter impersonator from voting as someone else. But happily, as Campsen noted in his testimony, it almost never happens. In fact, it is so rare that a person is more likely to be struck by lightning than commit voter fraud of any kind. Even the Supreme Court could only identify one example of in-person voter fraud in the past 143 years in their 2009 decision upholding a voter ID law. By contrast, a recent Brennan Center report found that nearly 500,000 voters — mostly low-income and minority individuals — in states with voter ID laws stand to be disenfranchised. These voter ID laws continue to be at best a solution in search of a problem — and at worse, a scheme to disenfranchise elderly, urban, poor, and minority voters who are among the least likely to have a photo identification. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346273165269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346274535399-38</Id><Title>Nothing highlights the baser instinct and disdain for democracy of the GOP like the premeditated Voter ID law plot in conjunction with ALEC</Title><Msg>ALEC's Voter ID Laws Work to Overturn Hundreds of Years of Progressive Moves to Broaden Democracy Corporations, 1 percenters and Republicans are working to ensure you don’t vote because they honestly believe you don’t count. May 7, 2012 | Corporations, 1 percenters and Republicans want to take America back. And by that they mean all the way to the 1780s when wealthy white men controlled the nation. Because only they could vote. In the intervening 230 or so years, America became increasingly democratic, eventually awarding the vote to white landless males; Quakers, Jews and Catholics; black men; women; Native Americans, and 18-year-olds. The wealthy are nostalgic for the power they enjoyed when most states limited voting to landed gentry. Republicans are helping them return America to those plutocratic days by passing voter identification laws constraining suffrage by the 99 percent. Country club conservatives are converting voting from a universal right of citizenship to a privilege exclusive to select society members. Voter identification laws require citizens to provide specific documents before exercising their franchise. Depending on the state, these include a photo driver’s license, a passport or a permit to carry a concealed handgun. The Brennan Center for Justice and others have calculated that 11 percent of eligible voters do not have government-issued photo identification. That’s 21 million citizens. A survey by the Brennan Center showed that many Americans, primarily women, do not have proof of citizenship under their current name and certain groups, primarily the poor, elderly and minorities are less likely to possess the documents the new voter ID laws require. The U.S. Department of Justice barred implementation of voter ID laws in Texas and South Carolina after determining that the restrictions would disproportionately limit minority citizens’ access to the polls. Texas and South Carolina are among 16 states with records of discrimination, including voter intimidation and poll taxes. As a result, they are required by the 1965 Voting Rights Act to secure federal approval before changing voting laws. In March, a court in Wisconsin declared the Badger State’s voter ID law unconstitutional. And the American Civil Liberties Union plans to ask a Pennsylvania court this week to do the same in the Keystone State. But not all such suits are successful. The U.S. Supreme Court upheld Indiana’s restrictive voter ID law in 2008. And last year a nearly unanimous Georgia Supreme Court endorsed its voter limitations. Every judge except the first African American to sit on the Georgia Supreme Court bench approved restricting access to the polls. Thirty states will require voters to show identification in November, unless their laws are overturned. Limiting voter access to the polls is a Republican cause. In 2011 and so far in 2012, nine states passed new or stiffened old voter ID laws. Republican governors preside over all nine states. And in all but one, Republicans completely control the legislatures. Five other states with Republican-controlled legislatures passed voter ID bills last year. These will not take effect, however, because five Democratic governors vetoed them. Behind every voter-restricting Republican is corporate-sponsored ALEC. ALEC is the American Legislative Exchange Council, a right-wing group that sends conservative lawmakers on all-expenses-paid junkets where they are wined and dined on ALEC corporate sponsors’ dime while they develop “model” legislation, like the kill-at-will laws that the slaying of Trayvon Martin made infamous. ALEC gives corporations veto power over proposed “model” legislation, a fact that clearly illustrates who is in charge – the corporations that provide 98 percent of ALEC’s $7 million annual budget. Corporations embrace voter ID because democracy is downright annoying to them. The Supreme Court has deemed corporations to be people, which allows them to secretly spend unlimited money on political campaigns. But that doesn’t assure victory for candidates that corporations choose because corporations don’t have the right to actually make the choice – to vote. The best corporations can do is limit balloting by those likely to vote against corporate-sponsored candidates. That would be voters who historically have favored Democrats. Voter ID laws disproportionately disenfranchise those voters ­– the poor, minorities and those who actually recall the progressive, popular and successful administration of Franklin D. Roosevelt. The Republican backers of voter ID are completely unconcerned that the laws subjugate these citizens. Too bad, they say, for grandma, who has voted in every election for the past 65 years but doesn’t have a driver’s license anymore and because she was born at home does not have a birth certificate necessary to get a government-issued photo ID. Too bad, Republicans say, for the student whose driver’s license address differs from his university address and whose college photo ID does not have an expiration date. Too bad, the GOP says, for the urban single mother who does not have a driver’s license or the time or money to apply for a birth certificate with a raised seal required to apply at another office for a state identification card. Voter ID restrictions work for the rich. They’ve got birth certificates and photo driver’s licenses and passports. Or they can send a servant or secretary to apply for the documents. And the more rabble removed from the polls, the more weighty the votes of the wealthy. In the Halcyon Days of democracy, the unwashed masses were actually urged to vote with slogans like: “If you don’t vote, you don’t count.” Now corporations, 1 percenters and Republicans are working to ensure you don’t vote because they honestly believe you don’t count.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346274535399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346275237811-39</Id><Title>Voter I.D laws #$%$ off Losers!</Title><Msg>A Bunch of Stupid, RACIST Liberals (Nothing new!) A radical group funded by billionaire George Soros that has a history of biased research is primarily behind a national campaign to paint voter ID laws as racist. The voter ID data collected by the group, the Brennan Center for Justice, has been called into question by experts and has been contradicted by other credible studies. Yet the center’s information is cited widely by news media and even members of the Obama administration. Besides receiving a reported $7.4 million from Soros’ Open Society Institute since 2000, the Brennan Center was also the recipient of grants from the Joyce Foundation from 2000 to 2003. President Obama served on the Joyce board from 1994 through 2002. Get Aaron Klein’s “Fool Me Twice: Obama’s Shocking Plans for the Next Four Years Exposed,” autographed, at WND’s Superstore! The Brennan Center is located at New York University School of Law. Its primary focus is so-called voting rights and creating a “living constitution” as well as pushing for a “living wage.” In November 2006, the Brennan Center issued “Citizens Without Proof,” an extensive report that claimed voter ID policies will disfranchise millions of minority, elderly and low-income voters because those voting blocs are less likely to possess documentation than the general population. The report is routinely cited by news media and activists seeking to prove voter ID is racist. Just yesterday, MSNBC featured two segments citing the Brennan Center information as evidence the GOP is attempting to block minorities from voting by pushing ID laws. Articles this week by the Huffington Post, Bloomberg News and the Baltimore Sun also cited the Brennan research. The National Center for Public Policy Research notes that in its report on voter ID measures, the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, or NAACP, “relied heavily” on Brennan Center’s work. Also last month, Politifact used the Brennan Center’s 2006 report to support Attorney General Eric Holder’s claim that 25 percent of African-Americans lack government-issued photo ID. GroupSnoop.org, a website run by the National Center for Public Policy Research, recently posted a new profile of the Brennan Center that documents how its voter ID information is highly questionable and may be based on biased data. In August 2011, Hans A. von Spakovsky and Alex Ingram of the Heritage Foundation critiqued the Brennan report, finding it is “both dubious in its methodology and results and suspect in its sweeping conclusions.” According to the Heritage Foundation report, the Brennan Center used biased questioning to obtain their desired result concerning minority voters – a result that is actually contradicted by footnotes buried in the Brennan report itself. “By eschewing many of the traditional scientific methods of data collection and analysis, the authors of the Brennan Center study appear to have pursued results that advance a particular political agenda rather than the truth about voter identification,” write Von Spakovsky and Ingram. Heritage points out that the Brennan Center’s report was based entirely on one survey of only 987 “voting age American citizens.” However the report contained no information on how the survey determined whether a respondent was actually an American citizen. Heritage found the Brennan survey used the responses of the 987 individuals to estimate the number of Americans without valid documentation based on the 2000 Census calculations of citizen voting-age population. Those Census figures, noted Heritage, “contain millions of U.S. residents who are ineligible to vote, thus contributing to the study’s overestimation of voters without a government-issued identification.” Heritage charged the survey questions used in the Brennan Center’s report “are also suspect and appear to be designed to bolster the report’s biased findings.” Brennan, for example, did not ask respondents whether they had government-issued IDs, but instead asked whether respondents had “readily available identification.” “By asking whether such ID could be found ‘quickly’ or shown ‘tomorrow,’ the study seems to be trying to elicit a particular response: that those surveyed do not have ID,” noted Heritage. The Brennan study is undermined by some of its own footnotes. One footnote states that “[t]he survey did not yield statistically significant results for differential rates of possession of citizenship documents by race, age, or other identified demographic factors.” That footnote appears to contradict the very premise of the Brennan report. Another footnote relates that 135 respondents “indicated that they had both a U.S. birth certificate and U.S. naturalization papers. This most likely indicates confusion on the part of the respondents.” In other words, Heritage notes, nearly 14 percent of the respondents provided contradictory answers. The Brennan study further did not ask any of its participants whether they had student or tribal ID cards even though in some states like Arizona and Georgia, such cards are acceptable for the purpose of voting. Heritage cited numerous studies that directly contradict the Brennan report, studied not widely cited by the news media in the voter ID debate. Such studies include: •An American University survey in Maryland, Indiana, and Mississippi found that less than one-half of 1 percent of registered voters lacked a government-issued ID. Therefore, the study correctly concluded that “a photo ID as a requirement of voting does not appear to be a serious problem in any of the states.” •A 2006 survey of more than 36,000 voters found that only “23 people in the entire sample—less than one-tenth of one percent of reported voters” were unable to vote because of an ID requirement.” Brennan has a history of questionable research. The center was at the heart of a national scandal in 2002 after the U.S. Supreme Court upheld the McCain-Feingold campaign-finance act. The attorneys defending McCain-Feingold had reportedly based key portions of their case on research provided by the Brennan Center – research, Discover the Networks notes, that may have been “deliberately faked,” according to Weekly Standard editor David Tell. Tell quoted Brennan Center political scientist Jonathan Krasno admitting in his funding proposal to the Pew Charitable Trusts that the purpose of his group’s proposed study on campaign finance was for partisan political reasons. Wrote Tell: “‘Issue Advocacy: Amassing the Case for Reform,’ dated February 19, 1999, explained that `[t]he purpose of our acquiring the data set is not simply to advance knowledge for its own sake, but to fuel a continuous multi-faceted campaign to propel campaign reform forward.’ Dispassionate academic inquiry was so alien to the spirit of the thing that Brennan promised to suspend its work midstream, pre-publication, if the numbers turned out wrong. `Whether we proceed to phase two will depend on the judgment of whether the data provide a sufficiently powerful boost to the reform movement.’” Tell claimed Brennan researchers “deliberately faked” their results. With additional research by Brenda J. Elliott</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346275237811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:20:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346276375000-40</Id><Title>My name is Orland Kravitz. Extraordinarily talented</Title><Msg>Seer of the future. I care about things that become newz. I know that the company will only be able to hire a 70% character. Poo baby, poo</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346276375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:39:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346276574000-41</Id><Title>Who shall rule ETFC in the future?</Title><Msg>Biggest question yet. See yaz!</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346276574000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346277381516-42</Id><Title>New CEO stiffarm begins with MS guy</Title><Msg>Is this going to be another debacle on a CEO search? The last time took over a year and they ended up with Freiberg who costs them 20+ million and drove the stock price down over 50%. "One of the top candidates to run the online trading firm, which is known for its trading baby television ads, says he isn't interested in the job. Greg Fleming, who heads Morgan Stanley's brokerage division and is overseeing its integration with Smith Barney, says he has no plans to leave his current position, according to sources close to Fleming."</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1346277381516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:56:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346277590079-43</Id><Topic><Title>Voter I.D laws #$%$ off Losers!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346275237811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, if it keeps stupid legal and illegal Mexicans from voting for the community organizer so be it! Don't forget to go to the poles early and ofen and vote Rebublican.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346277590079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346277747515-44</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on democracy</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346273165269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 16:46:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whats got you lefties nervious is that if you can't gin up enough bogus votes your beloved Berry is in trouble...and you know it!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346277747515</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346278287265-45</Id><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Msg>What the pamphlet distributor meant to say was those Solendra powered cars are more efficient than steam driven ones. BTW, isn't one of Obama's dream energy solution thermo power...which is steam. He is beggining to give Joe(you'all)Biden a run for his money.... "Just yesterday my opponent called my position on fuel efficiency standards extreme. I don't know, it doesn't seem extreme to me to want to have more fuel efficient cars. Maybe the steam engine is more his speed."</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346278795483-46</Id><Title>between you odumbomites cyring all the time and isaac</Title><Msg>new orleans won't stand a chance...the levies won't be able to handle both of ya...</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346278795483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:19:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346279202000-47</Id><Topic><Title>My name is Orland Kravitz. Extraordinarily talented</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346276375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:39:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like everyone hauledass on ya. Or junglebub finally bored everyone to death.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1346279202000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346281466385-48</Id><Topic><Title>Voter I.D laws #$%$ off Losers!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346275237811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:20:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you don't like the Brennan Center even the GOP now admits there's no impersonation problem to fix: "Last month, the Republican Attorney General of South Carolina also admitted that requiring a photo identification to vote would not actually prevent a determined voter impersonator from voting as someone else. But happily, as Campsen noted in his testimony, it almost never happens. In fact, it is so rare that a person is more likely to be struck by lightning than commit voter fraud of any kind. Even the Supreme Court could only identify one example of in-person voter fraud in the past 143 years in their 2009 decision upholding a voter ID law." Then you cite these studies done BEFORE the new laws take effect that affirm voters were getting to vote, the new laws could only restrict that democratically desirable access. 'Such studies include: •An American University survey in Maryland, Indiana, and Mississippi found that less than one-half of 1 percent of registered voters lacked a government-issued ID. Therefore, the study correctly concluded that “a photo ID as a requirement of voting does not appear to be a serious problem in any of the states.” •A 2006 survey of more than 36,000 voters found that only “23 people in the entire sample—less than one-tenth of one percent of reported voters” were unable to vote because of an ID requirement.” And there's this: “I guess I really actually feel we shouldn’t contort the voting process to accommodate the urban — read African-American — voter-turnout machine,” said Doug Preisse, chairman of the Franklin County Republican Party and close adviser to Gov. John Kasich, in an email to The Columbus Dispatch on Aug. 19. The admission to racial politics was immediately picked up by state Democrats, reigniting the early voting controversy even more than the previous threats to fire Montgomery County Board of Election Democrats who refused to comply with Secretary of State Jon Husted’s demands for uniform early voting hours. The remark by Preisse was in defense of Husted’s actions. Husted had invoked uniform early voting hours in Ohio and the Democrats quickly jumped on the new uniform hours for not including weekend hours. Preisse admitted race was a factor while justifying why there would be no in-person early voting during the weekends. Unsurprisingly, the remarks quickly backfired. For many Democrats, the racism invoked feelings of Jim Crow laws, which suppressed the black vote until the Voting Rights Act of 1965. Blatantly admitting to suppressing black voters in a post-legal segregation era was immediately repulsive to Democrats. “Ohio Republican Party leadership and Kasich’s adviser need to wake up and remember we’re in the 21st century and that there’s never an appropriate time to talk about suppressing African-American voters,” said Jerid Kurtz, spokesperson for the Ohio Democratic Party, in a statement. But Preisse’s remarks don’t reveal anything new. For years, study after study have confirmed that voter suppression laws — meaning laws that require state-issued voter IDs and laws that diminish early voting opportunities — disproportionately hurt minorities. .........Preisse told BuzzFeed shortly after his email to The Dispatch. He denied racism, but then contradicted himself by saying his comments were simply honest: “I am asking the question, and I am indeed questioning how far this process of democratic, small ‘d,’ democratic voting process should be contorted to favor a political operation. I don’t think we should go overboard in doing that.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346281466385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 19:04:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346287412628-49</Id><Topic><Title>Frank J. Petrilli</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1346244582964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 08:49:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that ETFC stock will gap-up past $9 with the news of a new CEO, provided he is a stellar name. I have tried to establish a block position, in hopes that a buyout will take the stock price to $15......but this thing is a whipsaw.....won't stay still......so far the premium is approx. 70 cents, since the buyout rumor emerged earlier this month. Oct/12 earnings are for +0.09 cents.</Msg><Username>baxter12co</Username><Timestamp>1346287412628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 20:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346289561313-50</Id><Topic><Title>Voter ID laws simply GOP voter suppression</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1344745665000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-12 00:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folksnews...........take a rope and shoot yourself! How many POSITIVES have you gotten = ZERO!!!! I am going to try to vote in MN, since the ID law got turned down and I am from WI! Since I/we have property in MN/WI will see what happen! ROWDY (Keep up the good work to make a real OBIMBO FOOL out of yourself!)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346289561313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346290240209-51</Id><Title>GOP can't repress their racism</Title><Msg>CNN Goes On Air With Story About Incident Against Network’s Black Camerawoman DAVID TAINTOR 5:50 PM EDT, WEDNESDAY AUGUST 29, 2012 On air this evening, CNN's Wolf Blitzer called attention to the network's earlier report on two Republican National Convention attendees throwing nuts at a black CNN camerawoman and saying, "This is how we feed animals." The attendees were removed from the Tampa Bay Times Forum after the exchange. Blitzer called the incident "truly shocking" and said it "hit home" for everyone at the network. CNN political analyst Donna Brazile said during the segment she hopes the two attendees have their convention credentials revoked.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346290240209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346290533154-52</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing highlights the baser instinct and disdain for democracy of the GOP like the premeditated Voter ID law plot in conjunction with ALEC</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1346274535399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:08:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Neo-libs can try to distort the issue all you want! but the fact remains that every country on the planet (that has elections) requires that you have proper ID/ citizenship to participate in their elections. I challenge you to cross the boarder and try to Vote in Mexican elections as a US citizen. Give it up already! you may be getting traction with innercity folks and people that are trying to skirt the immigration process , but thats about it.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1346290533154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346290649000-53</Id><Topic><Title>My name is Orland Kravitz. Extraordinarily talented</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346276375000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 17:39:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An early weekend in the hamptons. Too bad the Directums are still here</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346290649000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346291202989-54</Id><Title>The face of austerity. GOP is advocating the same wrongheaded policies.</Title><Msg>Source: UK Guardian Britain's wealthiest people should face an emergency tax to avoid a breakdown in social cohesion as the country fights an "economic war" caused by a longer than expected recession, Nick Clegg has said. The intervention by Clegg, who is calling for a "time limited contribution" from the richest in society beyond the party's current policy for a mansion tax, came as the deputy prime minister marked his return to Britain after a two-week family holiday in Spain. Tory eyebrows are likely to be raised by Clegg's declaration that the rich must pay more as Britain copes with an economic downturn that is far deeper than anything he expected when he took a "collective gamble" to form Britain's first peacetime coalition in 70 years. "What people once thought might have been a short, sharp economic battle, a short, sharp recession, is clearly turning into a longer-term process of economic recovery and fiscal restraint. That begs big questions." The deputy prime minister said that new taxes should be drawn up which go beyond the Lib Dems' existing proposal to impose a mansion tax on properties worth more than £2m. Clegg fears for the cohesion of Britain unless the rich do more to help tackle the deficit.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346291202989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:46:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346293028082-55</Id><Title>ETFC will go down tomorrow! Back to $8.40s!</Title><Msg>Asia down deep now!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346293028082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346293468783-56</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP lives back in the olden days and clueless yes it is!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346293468783</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346296442269-57</Id><Topic><Title>The face of austerity. GOP is advocating the same wrongheaded policies.</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346291202989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:46:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't like the British example, substitute Spain, Italy, Ireland or Greece- none of those experiments in austerity are doing very well. Really dumb to think it will be successful here.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346296442269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:14:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346297120485-58</Id><Title>GOP lie machine, by Robert Reich</Title><Msg>How Romney Gets Away With So Many Lies Presumably the Romney campaign continues its false claims because they’re effective. But this raises a more basic question: How can they remain effective when they’ve been so overwhelmingly discredited by the media? The answer is the Republican Party has developed three means of bypassing the mainstream media and its fact-checkers. The first is by repeating big lies so often in TV spots – financed by a mountain of campaign money – that the public can no longer recall (if it ever knew) that the mainstream media and its fact-checkers have found them to be lies. The second is by discrediting the mainstream media – asserting it’s run by “liberal elites” that can’t be trusted to tell the truth. “I am tired of the elite media protecting Barack Obama by attacking Republicans,” Newt Gingrich charged at a Republican debate last January, in what’s become a standard GOP attack line. The third is by using its own misinformation outlets – led by Fox News, Rush Limbaugh and his yell-radio imitators, book publisher Regnery, and the editorial page of the Wall Street Journal, along with a right-wing blogosphere – to spread the lies, or at least spread doubt about what’s true. Together, these three mechanisms are creating a parallel Republican universe of Orwellian dimension – where anything can be asserted, where pollsters and political advisers are free to create whatever concoction of lies will help elect their candidate, and where “fact-checkers” are as irrelevant and intrusive as is the truth. Democracy cannot thrive in such a place. To the contrary, history teaches that this is where demagogues take root.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346297120485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346297598527-59</Id><Title>BO perfect on foreign policy, says Condi</Title><Msg>Condi Rice Can’t Name A Specific Obama Foreign Policy Failure By Ben Armbruster on Aug 29, 2012 at 10:40 am Condoleezza Rice Today on CBS’s morning show, former Bush administration Secretary of State and top Mitt Romney surrogate Condoleezza Rice could not offer any specific foreign policy failures made by President Obama. Romney’s allies, led by Rice and Sen. John McCain (R-AZ), are expected to attack Obama on national security grounds tonight in at the Republican National Convention in Tampa. But when asked to offer specifics this morning on CBS, all Rice could come up with was some vague attack on Obama’s Syria policy, which, host Norah O’Donnell noted, the president himself might agree with: O’DONNELL: Can you be specific about somewhere where you think President Obama has failed on foreign policy. RICE: What we should do tonight, is talk about what a President Romney would mean for America. It’s not a time to look back, it’s a time to look forward. We have real challenges out there, in the Middle East, in Asia, in Europe, with our allies. O’DONNELL: But if President Obama isn’t doing anything wrong, then why change things? RICE: It’s a question of what a President Romney would do and there is no doubt that the United States’ voice has been muted and when the United States’ voice is muted the world is a more dangerous place. O’DONNELL: How is the United States’ voice muted? RICE: Just look at the situation in Syria for instance. We have a circumstance in which Assad is butchering his people. The Iranians are helping him to do so. The United States seems to be mired in the Security Council. The Russians and the Chinese say no, no, no and we don’t have an answer. When that is the case, it’s a dangerous place. … O’DONNELL: But I think the president agrees with that as well. Having covered the White House, the question is whether … a President Romney would be willing to advocate and commit American troops, American lives, in a place like Syria right now. Watch the clip: So despite the fact that the GOP plans to attack Obama’s foreign policy, Rice has no interest in “looking back.” Instead, she said, she wants to “look forward,” yet she doesn’t have any idea what Romney’s international agenda is either. And on Syria, it turns out that the policy Romney has articulated thus far isn’t much different from the Obama administration’s. But as far as attacking Obama on foreign policy grounds goes, the Republicans are going to have a tough time. Poll after poll shows that Americans favor Obama over Romney in handling international issues. And the Wall Street Journal noted today that their recent poll “found 54% of voters approve of Mr. Obama’s handling of foreign policy, his highest score in more than a year and far better than what either George W. Bush or Bill Clinton fetched as they sought re-election.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346297598527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346298758000-60</Id><Title>How to be Really Stupid</Title><Msg>Throw a convention in hurricane alley, during hurricane season. Global warming deniers at their worst.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1346298758000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346298770380-61</Id><Topic><Title>BO perfect on foreign policy, says Condi</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346297598527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:33:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HEY, FUKNEW GET OFF THIS BOARD.... It's for ETFC comments not your foreign policy politico views ... YUUUUUUUUCKKKKKKKK !!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bigtimeusa</Username><Timestamp>1346298770380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>