<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343709020000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bought SWHC @ 10.04</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343660163000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 10:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should try the underlying security on that stock sometime. Cheaper and just as knee-strappy.</Msg><Username>jonrenr</Username><Timestamp>1343709020000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:30:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343709508000-2</Id><Title>Did Slayer Lose Another Yahoo ID ? LOL !!!!!!</Title><Msg>The gay hippie / Billie Homo keeps changing her ID's. Too bad she has nothing to say.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1343709508000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:38:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343709726000-3</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are really that dumb to think life expectancy in Chile or in Cuba, is as long as in this country due to equivalent health care services, I have one suggestion. MOVE. And live it. As for me, I left healthcare like Chilean in my past. I'd rather stay here and pay 10x more but expect highest quality services in entire world in return. We probably are having salaries 10x more than Chileans. Didn't that cross your mind?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343709726000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343709786000-4</Id><Title>Everyone Asks Mittens Why He's a Wimp ??!!!</Title><Msg>The whole world sees it. Like Bush, he's a wimpy little girlie man cheerleader. The world has no respect for a punk who beats up on gays, and needs 3 others to do it !.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1343709786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:43:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343710248000-5</Id><Title>$8 is Coming!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! EOM</Title><Msg>$8 is Coming!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! EOM</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343710248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343710373000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poland's Solidarity Union Rebukes Romney Upon Former Leader's Endorsement Source: Huffington Post Presumptive GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney may have earned an apparent endorsement from former Polish president Lech Walesa on Monday, but no such kind words were coming from Poland's storied Solidarnosc (Solidarity) trade union, which Walesa and others founded in 1980. Upon Romney's visit to the Gdansk shipyards, the site of historic Polish worker strikes during the Soviet era, Solidarnosc issued a press release saying it is "in no way involved" in the Romney meeting with Walesa and had no "initiative" to invite the American candidate to Poland. The union expressed dismay at Romney's anti-union stances in the U.S., saying it would stand alongside the AFL-CIO, the American labor federation that has endorsed Obama and remains highly critical of Romney. "Regretfully, we have learned from our friends in the American trade union central AFL-CIO representing over 12 million workers about Mitt Romney's support for the attacks against trade unions and labor rights," Andrzej Adamczyk, the head of the union's international department, wrote. "In this respect, I wish to express... our solidarity with American workers and trade unions. will always support the AFL-CIO in their struggle for the right of workers to organize and bargain collectively."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1343710373000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343712752000-7</Id><Topic><Title>$8 is Coming!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! EOM</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343710248000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 00:50:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Futures are up huge!!!!! +53 and rising!!!!! http://www.cnbc.com/id/17689937/site/14081545/</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343712752000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 01:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343714586000-8</Id><Topic><Title>NIM continues to erode YOY earnings comparisons</Title><Username>dswanhmsk</Username><Timestamp>1343680197000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 16:29:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NIM decreases but assets increase thus the reduction in revenues has not been severe for ETFC and SCHW.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343714586000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 02:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343720436000-9</Id><Topic><Title>What's wrong with this stock?</Title><Username>twentyonejumpst14</Username><Timestamp>1343268156000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-07-25 22:02:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their platform is great for charting and the execution is fast if you trade otcbb/pinksheet/nasdaq stocks.</Msg><Username>trader.phd65</Username><Timestamp>1343720436000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 03:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343738013000-10</Id><Title>chart analysis</Title><Msg>I've been watching the market closely now that I'm retired and I now understand how difficult it is to predict, even at the broad ETF level, especially at this particular point in time. The analysis they provide has been extremely helpful and maybe it can help you. http://TECHNICALSTOCKTRADER.INFO</Msg><Username>beauregardgsi187</Username><Timestamp>1343738013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 08:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343738833000-11</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Canada is 12th in life expectancy, USA is 50th. (they also now have universal healthcare, more jobs, less debt, higher net worths.....) the entire EU has higher life expectancy... all have universal healthcare, most have more jobs, less debt... ditto for Australia and New Zealand..... and many many other nations. maybe bushcare at the ER is a really stupid way to do healthcare, although the former ceo of the nations largest health insurer would say otherwise. "dollar" Bill Mcquire the ceo who attempted to give himself a $1.1 billion retirement package......not that his board of directors minded, since they also all got millions and millions in deals to rubber stamp his billions in deals. No wonder health insurers don't want any regulations and or forced transparency, or competition from a public plan. http://www.chron.com/business/steffy/article/Steffy-How-William-McGuire-earned-that-fat-1901786.php</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343738833000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 08:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343743609000-12</Id><Title>Shorted AXL @ 10.86</Title><Msg>but I could be wrong. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343743609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343743994000-13</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP’s hidden tax? Nonsense. Put it on your forehead: Obamacare imposes enormous tax on everyone who makes money. Buying health insurance is voluntary action. No one was forcing you to buy it before Obamacare came along. You are just WILLINGLY paying asking price. Now, thank you Obamacare, it makes it a tax. So, now everyone is paying this tax or go to prison. GOP never forced me to buy insurance. If I am young and healthy, I have a choice keepmy money in the bank or put them on health care account. I didn’t challenge $1502 overhaul we are paying for cost shifting. Although, the article link you bring is not a research result. It doesn’t say how many illegal immigrants we pay for in hospital emergency rooms. Shall we give illegal health coverage too to save money on their surgeries? I challenged the idiotic idea of cost effectiveness of colonoscopies as oppose to cancer surgery. Whoever gets “free” coverage is going to use it for multiple other procedures and tests which uninsured has no access to. Actual insurance holders are going to pay for all of that. It will raise the cost of coverage. So, if today we are only paying for accidental surgeries, tomorrow we’ll pay for whole range of services of those who don’t contribute a dime to the system and that will, of course, include colonoscopy along with multiple EKGs,MRIs,CTs,blood, urine tests and so on. And you are still saying it is going to cost us less? 15-20 colonoscopies which would find nothing(as expected) will cost as much as surgery. Did I make it too complicated for you?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343743994000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343745148000-14</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown - WRONG AGAIN, not on government payroll, but the pension I worked for and the SS I paid in! See - every time you type something - you SCREW UP - that's what you are!!! Get the FACTS right before you post! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343745148000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343745435000-15</Id><Title>"Wimp" get spiegeled</Title><Msg>German Media Writes Mitt's Obit: 'Romney Has Already Disqualified Himself' 'Romney Has Already Disqualified Himself' "Travel educates. As a result one should assume that Mitt Romney, the Republican challenger of Barack Obama, wants to learn something during his visit to Israel. Wrong! Almost everything that the candidate organized in Jerusalem fuels the impression that he doesn't want to try understanding how complicated the Middle East situation is. Instead, Romney paints the crisis region in black and white: Israel is good and the rest -- the Palestinians and the mullahs in Iran -- are lumped together." "This one-sided world view is less dumb than it is coldly calculated. Romney is soliciting campaign donations in Jerusalem (the minimum price for two plates at breakfast is $50,000.) And he is ensnaring Jewish voters at home." "The trip to Israel may help Romney in the short-term. But in the long-term the Republican has done damage. The Middle East needs the US as a mediator. As such, the presidential hopeful has already disqualified himself."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343745435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343745643000-16</Id><Title>etfc need to make news</Title><Msg>great one would be half of board members and ceo submit their resignations prior to buy out!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343745643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343745996000-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clown - that's the first one that I can agree with you - government (President/House/Senate) should have to adhere to the same insurance options/plan the citizen have, that would give them a different perspective when voting on Health care. Not only is their health care free for them, but their dependents for life time! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343745996000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343747315000-18</Id><Title>And now they even managed to anger the Poles</Title><Msg>Mitt's international trip starts to look like "rednecks gone wild" Now they even managed to anger the Poles by yelling obscenities at one of the most solemn Polish sites. http://news.yahoo.com/mitt-romney-spokesman-tells-reporters-kiss-polish-holy-110442318--abc-news-politics.html GOP is counting hours for the trip to be over, holding their breath and hoping Romney will be given no more chances to offend the world....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343747315000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:08:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343747522000-19</Id><Topic><Title>And now they even managed to anger the Poles</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343747315000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:08:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>China has joined the chorus of criticism.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343747522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343748298000-20</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;WRONG AGAIN, not on government payroll&gt;&gt; Currently - no - just most of your life. Now you are on a pension plan. And federal pension plans are paid for by taxpayers money, so yeah - you live off of handouts. &lt;&lt;but the pension I worked for&gt;&gt; Are you implying ONLY YOU worked to get your pension? EVERY pension recipient worked for it, yet in your self-absorbed folly, you think only YOUR pension is justified. Your description of other Wisconsin "parasites" that want their pension shows how detached from reality you really are. &lt;&lt;and the SS I paid in!&gt;&gt; SS is NOT a saving account - you don't pay-in for your own benefits - when you pay - you support it's current recipients, - when you reach the SS age - others are paying for your SS benefits. I'm currently paying for YOUR SS checks. and I'm told I will NOT get anything for it, because SS will not be there when I reach the age. Basically - you are taking MY money - with government assistance. You are doing it twice, collecting your pension funded by me and collecting social security, also funded by me. Still feeling superior? Come on - stick out your hand for more of the taxpayer dollars. &lt;&lt;Get the FACTS right before you post!&gt;&gt; Read up - and maybe you will realize that you post self-absorbed, self-justifying, self-worshiping fiction.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343748298000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 11:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343751239000-21</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>111 Congress, H. Res. 657 Expressing the sense of the House of Representatives that Members of Congress who participate in the Federal Employees Health Benefits Program (FEHBP) should be automatically enrolled in the public option and be subject to any personal income tax increases levied as a result of healthcare legislation, regardless of their annual gross income. Last Action: Referred to House Ways and Means on Jul 17, 2009 This proposal didn't get to the vote. It was blocked by Democrats who controlled the House at the time. If you have a reference to a different proposal, you are welcom to post it. It doesn't have to be a link.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343751239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343751729000-22</Id><Topic><Title>etfc need to make news</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343745643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO kidding. This is getting disgraceful. The company is ignoring shareholders in hopes of achieving some grand plan... time for them to go.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343751729000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343751815000-23</Id><Topic><Title>Video Forecast</Title><Username>kelcismp990</Username><Timestamp>1343742781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>audryluf495</Username><Timestamp>1343751815000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343752298000-24</Id><Title>From 2/24/2011...........................</Title><Msg>E*TRADE’s Secondary Drop Is Actually Good For Holders (ETFC, SCHW, AMTD, MS, GS) Posted: February 24, 2011 at 12:35 pm Print Email E*TRADE Financial Corporation (NASDAQ: ETFC) is getting hit hard today on news that Ken Griffin’s Citadel Investment Group has sold shares in the stock in a registered offering. Don’t be fooled by this initial reaction to the stock offering. This is “good dilution” if there can be such a thing with a $3.5 billion market cap. We just did a full review of E*TRADE’s Annual Report to find the hidden gems that investors overlook. After going back over t his finding and looking at today’s offering, this stock sale is actually good for E*TRADE and its holders even if the shares have fallen over 5% today to $15.80. Citadel, E*TRADE’s largest shareholder, sold 23.9 million shares and this took the implied ownership down substantially. The company still has ties to Citadel. For that long-expected buyout to come it has to be clear to a buyer that E*TRADE will stay independent for a while. As far as who will buy E*TRADE down the road, the most likely suitors are Charles Schwab Corp. (NYSE: SCHW) with its $22 billion in market cap or TD AMERITRADE Holding Corporation (NASDAQ: AMTD) with its near-$12 billion market cap. Who could ultimately be larger strategic acquirers could even end up being those “bank holding companies” which are not banks at all. That means Morgan Staley (NYSE: MS) or even Goldman Sachs Group Inc. (NYSE: GS), although neither would be as solid integrations as a Schwab or Ameritrade and they would be strategic moves in a new direction rather than discount and online broker market share-driven acquisitions. E*TRADE had noted in its annual report just this week that Citadel held about 9.9% of the common stock or approximately 27% of the common stock assuming conversion of convertible debentures it holds. Kenneth Griffin, President and CEO of Citadel, joined the E*TRADE board of directors on June 8, 2009. The reason that this is good for E*TRADE shareholders is that E*TRADE was without strong management of its own for quite some time during the recovery and it was Citadel’s investment that was one of the key events which effectively rescued E*TRADE during the financial meltdown. This also gave Citadel a hold on much of E*TRADE. While this is the lowest share price in about a month, Citadel had already started to unload shares and it controlled nearly half of the company at the peak of its holdings. Investors should consider this a win-win. Griffin’s Citadel gets to take some money off the table here and E*TRADE gets to be one more step closer to being less dominated by an outsider. The most recent monthly trading data from last night showed a 2% increase in trading from last month and the loan losses look better as well: total special mention delinquencies of 30 to 89 days delinquent fell by 6% from December 31, 2010 to January 31, 2011 and total at-risk delinquencies of 30 to 179 days delinquent were down 4% during the same period. With shares down over 5% at $15.80, just because this is good dilution does not mean that the shares will instantly recover. Shares were above $18.00 as recently as February 16 before the Libya and Bahrain market-hit from the Middle East and North Africa. This is the lowest level going back to January 27, 2011 and shares closed out 2010 at $16.00.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343752298000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343752504000-25</Id><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Msg>How many countries can he insult in one tour ?</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343752647000-26</Id><Topic><Title>etfc need to make news</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343745643000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:40:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>flood etfc with emails let thyem know the ceo goes or your money flows to another broker!!!most share holders are etfc investors and its time for change starting at the top!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343752647000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343753767000-27</Id><Topic><Title>Video Forecast</Title><Username>kelcismp990</Username><Timestamp>1343742781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting</Msg><Username>gerickjdt488</Username><Timestamp>1343753767000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343753787000-28</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FYI, the bill you cite was about a PUBLIC OPTION. the insurance cos made sure there would NOT be a public option, so there was no need for legislation that required those who voted for a PUBLIC OPTION to have use it, since there is no public option. Too bad there wasn't a bill to require members of congress to serve in the invasions and occupation they authorize the president to charge into.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343753787000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343753853000-29</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No sense waiting 'til the last minute.. Contribute to his 2016 re-election campaign now at slayer98@yahoo.com</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343753853000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343754506000-30</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was proposed at the time when HR3200 was introduced WITH public option. Current version of Obamacare was not in the picture yet. Very lame try to spin it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343754506000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343755327000-31</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, Evry Presidential candidate with weak international experience does this, yawn!!!!! Besides, you never had any support, no matter how small for this admin, so who are you kidding!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343755327000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343755655000-32</Id><Title>Despite tech sell off, Apple remains strong</Title><Msg>I hope this will spin off to other tech tomorroow.</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343755655000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343756253000-33</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obviously, the bill was meant to prevent a public option, and of course a public option had no chance at all. The insurance cos saw to that. Only an insurance co approved reform would ever pass, which the ACA is. The public gets more transparency, more benefit per premium dollar and and end to preexisting condition dumping in return for the mandate the ins cos demanded. You should know , after all , the ACA is based on gop ideas, Romneycare is the blueprint and the "responsible" way to go said Romney......... Romney the liar, huh?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343756253000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343756721000-34</Id><Title>When higher tax rates reduced the nation's debt</Title><Msg>higher tax rates and especially taxing the rich more is how the USA paid for its wars in the past, you know, the responsible, sane way to do it here are the facts: The cost of World War II was financed primarily by a highly progressive Income Tax, as well as other taxes on corporations to prevent excess profits being derived from government contracts. Even the Vietnam War was largely financed by a surtax on incomes, paid largely by wealthier citizens rather than by the transfer of a payroll tax-generated social security Surplus to cover U.S. budget deficits. and when did the trend of LOWER national debt each year after WW2 end?................. yep, Reagan turned that around! and he TRIPLED the nation's debts with his tax cuts and ENDED the entire post war history of a lower national debt each year.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343756721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:45:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343756731000-35</Id><Topic><Title>Despite tech sell off, Apple remains strong</Title><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343755655000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:27:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At this stage the only event that will increase the Price is the announcement of a company sale. There is simply no way this listless management team will do anything constructive for the shareholder. This management team will not come close to taking the bronze ever. Freiberg talked of a capital plan under review by regulators. I hope it never see the light of day and pray that it never gets public as nothing this group has done has ever served to benefit the shareholder. I shudder at the very idea that a plan wad submitted by etrade. It would be better to forgo any capital plan and simply move forward with a sale of the company. I doubt very much that freeberg, audette, and the board have any concept of what it means to be an advocate for shareholders. They have only been mid-level employes at best. Folks, the ship is being piloted by fools</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343756731000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 13:45:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343758067000-36</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bill was proposed by A. Davis, a Democrat from Alabama, not by GOP. But it was blocked by Democrats who controlled the House. The purpose was actually to show members of Congress should be in the same shoes as public which HR3200 would affect. Democrats didn't like that. HR3200 with public option, hundreds of pages long never had a chance to pass? So, Democrats who introduced it didn't know that! Please, don't re-write history. Everything is already documented. Have another spin?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343758067000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:07:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343758721000-37</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good grief, yes, the insurance industry has much influence on both sides. and nonetheless: obviously, the bill was meant to prevent a public option, and of course a public option had no chance at all. The insurance cos saw to that. Only an insurance co approved reform would ever pass, which the ACA is. The public gets more transparency, more benefit per premium dollar and and end to preexisting condition dumping in return for the mandate the ins cos demanded. You should know , after all , the ACA is based on gop ideas, Romneycare is the blueprint and the "responsible" way to go said Romney......... Romney the liar, huh?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343758721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343758968000-38</Id><Topic><Title>"Wimp" get spiegeled</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343745435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"W robbed Romney of any governing achievements, and all the moderates have been driven out of the party. Of course this has made them a bit grumpy! It's like the whole 8 years of GOP governance did not exist. But it did, and it was a failure like none other in American history. It also means the Presidency is out of reach of the modern GOP, as constructed. But Mitt's worst enemy by far are the words Mitt himself speaks."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343758968000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:22:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343759915000-39</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trying to change the subject from the four years of the community organizers failed policies...1.5% GDP, 8.2% unemployment, and the hits just keep on coming.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343759915000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343760645000-40</Id><Title>Freibergs new position to be announced soon</Title><Msg>Hopefully it will be "retired" But that is too hopeful. This carefree managemenr team will hold on to their position and salary until the bitter end. The company now had reduced revenues and is being relegated to cutting costs. The handwriting has been on the wall for some time. The board of directors of this etrade must be held personally responsible not only for the poor investment decisions of the past , but also in their derilection of fiduciary duties. Be very cautious of this ship piloted by fools. They actually have a 'capital' plan in the works. Shudder to think what harmful and dilutive conditions are in that plann. Fact of the matter is, management has a cushy job abd wants to keep it. The bumbling board demands no accountability or performance from its junior managers. A ghastly travesty has been perpetrated on the shareholders.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343760645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343761386000-41</Id><Title>New Topic: will this gasping machine be sold?</Title><Msg>It only makes sense. Kenneth Griffun wants to sell it because he's smarter than your average board member. Tough to call whether he will get all activist again - maybe he knows that a buyer has surfaced and a deal will get done maybe not. They tossed out one board member so lets see if that does the trick on getting this sold. Its obvious that the company is treading water on maintaining accounts. With 4.2 million accounts, spending $50-$60 million a year to pick up a few net accounts is an incredible waste of effort and shareholder funds. Now expense cuts are on the way. Face it folks, the show is all but over. Its time that the assets are sold to a company that will domsomething more constructive and earn a higher return.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343761386000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343761789000-42</Id><Title>Obama donates 5 grand!</Title><Msg>To whom, you axe? Why himself of course. His generosity to himself knows no limit. Pull his own brother out of poverty? That's a story wif a different result. You didn't think he was just gonna up and give his OWN money to someone else did you? ..Your money however, now that's a different story. http://www.politico.com/politico44/2012/07/obama-donates-to-himself-130613.html</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343761789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343762476000-43</Id><Title>Will Citadel be Inneffectual in Getting the Job Done?</Title><Msg>Hard to say, but Citadel and Kenneth Griffun must be pushing hard for a sale. Its ROI was reduced by another year on the holding period. Do you think he made a rational trade-0ff? Did he believe Freiberg and think another year hanging on to this would be compensated with a highet selling price? Only logic tells us that. But this here management team doesn't like to use logic. How does anyone hang on here with crazy people at the helm?</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343762476000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343762522000-44</Id><Topic><Title>Freibergs new position to be announced soon</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343760645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>low volume to me suggests a shelf offering coming to screw investors even more to buy springers. could this be why the pps is so low? Another lame idea costing the investors money. sell the company and let freiburg find a real job . something he is more qualified for!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1343762522000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343762802000-45</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Trying to change the subject from the four years of the community organizers failed policies...1.5% GDP, 8.2% unemployment, and the hits just keep on coming. &gt;&gt; bringing the country from the brink of collapse caused by Bush era policies, and putting it back on the growth track is hardly a failed policy. The hits keep on coming because the do-nothing GOP controlled house blocks every attempt to improve the status quot, and the GOP in Senate filibusters everything into a standstill. -------------------------------------------- when you have HALF THE GOVERNMENT focused on ensuring the country's failure purely for political gains - it is a small miracle we are not back in recession.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343762802000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>22</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343762893000-46</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It really proves he's not presidential. Running a business is nothing like running a country. Jimmy Carter was the last successful bizman to run a country. Mittens would be worse.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343762893000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:28:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343762927000-47</Id><Title>Kenneth Griffun: 28,000,000 shares cut by 50%</Title><Msg>What a disgrace. How long would you sit on that amount of shares with no divvy or no capital gain. What about a 50% loss in value? What about a 50% loss in value during a time when management begged not To force a sale.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343762927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343763416000-48</Id><Title>Goldman Sax in a Quandry.</Title><Msg>What to do. What to do. Last year they said the company was worth $18-$23 A share and the company should not sell Well. Times certainly changed. Now the price has fallen 50% almost to the year anniversary. Wonder what Goldman would recommend now? My guess is that Goldman was under The advisement of their own client, etrade. Now the table has turned with one solid year of pps degradation. What will goldman recommend now?</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343763416000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343763539000-49</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, You are a sorr loser, with excuses to fit your mantra!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1343763539000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343764039000-50</Id><Title>Charges baseless</Title><Msg>GOP REPORT FINDS NO CONNECTION BETWEEN WHITE HOUSE AND ‘FAST AND FURIOUS’ 2 hrs ago - GOP REPORT FINDS NO CONNECTION BETWEEN WHITE HOUSE AND ‘FAST AND FURIOUS’ | Despite insistence from GOP leadership that the White House was behind the so-called “Fast and Furious” gunwalking program, a report from House Republicans released Tuesday.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343764039000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343764239000-51</Id><Topic><Title>Shorted AXL @ 10.86</Title><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343743609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Covered @ 10.81. Tough to make a dollar in this market. tdc</Msg><Username>tradedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1343764239000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343764682000-52</Id><Topic><Title>Goldman Sachs recently commented on E*TRADE's "sum-of-the-parts" analysis</Title><Username>realtymole47</Username><Timestamp>1312939205000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-08-09 21:20:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now i like this discussion</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343764682000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343765204000-53</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;How many countries can he insult in one tour ?&gt;&gt; It's a simple formula &lt;Mitt insult total&gt; = &lt;# of countries visited&gt; + &lt;# of countries neighboring&gt; + &lt;# of countries sharing their religions&gt; Seems like in this 3 country hop the &lt;Mitt insult total&gt; stands at 50 or so..... he got lucky - Great Britain is an island...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343765204000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:06:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>23</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343765617000-54</Id><Topic><Title>GS says ETFC worth 23 dollars</Title><Username>ariaban</Username><Timestamp>1311857884000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-07-28 08:58:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mongo bump</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343765617000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:13:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343766016000-55</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the bill was meant to prevent a public option" A Democrat proposed a bill to undermine his own party major legislation? "of course a public option had no chance at all" Nanci Pelosi never promoted or put on the floor of the house a bill which had no chance to pass. She fought HR3200 tooth and nail until it became clear it lacks Senate votes. A. Davis, a Democrat, proposed a bill in good faith to make his party not look detached from other Americans which HR3200 would affect. And democrats spit on it. Rejecting this bill showed Democrats as true hypocrites. Public option was Obama's original idea. He promoted it in 2008 campaign. Apprently, he didn't mean it for himself nor his buddies in Congress. Only for OTHER Americans. Which makes him and democrats true aliens from another planet.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343766016000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:20:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343766687000-56</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A Democrat proposed a bill to undermine his own party major legislation?" as you previously stated there was no public plan proposed. and as i previously states the insurance cos have plenty of reps in their pocket on both sides of the aisle. and what about Romney who wrote the blueprint for Obamacare. Romney who said his mandate is the "responsible" thing to do. You must think Romney is either a liar or an idiot, based on your views expressed here.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343766687000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343766817000-57</Id><Title>Goldman said $2.5B in marks last year</Title><Msg>We are there - just about. and it makes sense. Since making that estimate, ETFC has charged off $1.6B and has a provision for .5B. Up to $2.1B in actual and provided for write-downs. The loan portfolio is beginning to be a no-brainer..</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343766817000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:33:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343767060000-58</Id><Title>Boehner working on healthcare in congress</Title><Msg>Representative John A. Boehner of Ohio, chairman of the House Republican Conference, decided to play Santa Claus. … In any event, Mr. Boehner took it upon himself to begin handing out money from tobacco lobbyists to certain of his colleagues on the House floor. Boehner stopped handing out the checks only “after being questioned about the practice by two freshmen who’d heard about the handoff on the House floor” [Charleston Gazette, Rep. Linda Smith (R-WA) said of Boehner’s actions, “[I]f it is not illegal, it should be.” Looks like Boehner may not be the best person to “build trust” in the House. (passing out big tobacco money on the floor of the congress says it ALL about John Boehner)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767060000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767186000-59</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;as you previously stated there was no public plan proposed.&gt; HR3200 was a plan proposed with public option. It was in intensive discussion for several months. It was supported by President Obama and it was his original core idea of nationalized care. Missed it? It makes you an alien too.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1343767186000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:39:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343767272000-60</Id><Title>Remember Precious?</Title><Msg>Apparently went down with the MF Global ship. Nothing posted after October 2011. http://messages.finance.yahoo.com/Business_%26_Finance/Investments/Stocks_%28A_to_Z%29/Stocks_M/threadview?bn=51579&amp;tid=16714&amp;mid=16728</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343767272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343767313000-61</Id><Title>GS buy rating at $18? Yup.</Title><Msg>Goldman Sachs Says E*TRADE (ETFC) Worth Up to $23 In a Takeover July 28, 2011 8:36 AM EDT Goldman Sachs commented on E*TRADE (NASDAQ: ETFC) in light of recent strategic review, promoted by its largest investor Citadel. The firm said their sum-of-the-parts analysis implies a theoretical M&amp;A valuation of $19-$23, and they see a 30-50% chance of a transaction. E*TRADE could be an attractive target for peers an non-peers. The biggest issue to a deal is the capital hole for the ETFC loan portfolio. Goldman's upper-end assumptions for loan loss reserve additions assume ETFC writes the carrying value of its loans down to 80% LTV (from an average of 108%) for an incremental $2.5 bn in credit marks, or 19% of the current carrying value. Goldman reiterated their Buy rating and $18 price target. For more ratings news on E*TRADE click here and for the rating history of E*TRADE click here. Shares of E*TRADE closed at $15.50 yesterday, with a 52 week range of $12.24-$18.13.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343767407000-62</Id><Title>Romney praises universal healthcare in Israel</Title><Msg>Romney Praises Israel’s Universal Health Care System, Which Includes Individual Mandate during his trip to Israel, Romney inadvertently praised the individual requirement and universal health care. “[F]or an American abroad, you can’t get much closer to the ideals and convictions of my own country than you do in Israel,” he said. And according to The New York Times, Romney spoke favorably about the fact that health care makes up a much smaller amount of Israel’s gross domestic product compared to the United States: “Do you realize what health care spending is as a percentage of the G.D.P. in Israel? Eight percent,” he said. “You spend eight percent of G.D.P. on health care. You’re a pretty healthy nation. We spend 18 percent of our G.D.P. on health care, 10 percentage points more. That gap, that 10 percent cost, compare that with the size of our military — our military which is 4 percent, 4 percent. Our gap with Israel is 10 points of G.D.P. We have to find ways — not just to provide health care to more people, but to find ways to fund and manage our health care costs.” Israel spends less on health care because of a universal health system that requires everyone to have insurance http://thinkprogress.org/health/2012/07/30/604111/romney-individual-mandate-israel/</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767437000-63</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;You must think Romney is either a liar or an idiot, based on your views expressed here.&gt;&gt; He is a Mormon - so, both....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343767437000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:43:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767562000-64</Id><Topic><Title>Remember Precious?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343767272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Precious worked for GS. She was selling calls, remember? GS was short before they advised etfc to hold.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767562000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767574000-65</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check this out - "Mitt the Twit" is flip-flopping again: http://news.yahoo.com/romney-denies-criticizing-palestinian-culture-133405905.html</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343767574000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>20</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767634000-66</Id><Topic><Title>GS buy rating at $18? Yup.</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That story is one year old.</Msg><Username>tmcg1367</Username><Timestamp>1343767634000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:47:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343767770000-67</Id><Title>ETFC Board Misled by Goldman Sax</Title><Msg>GS value last summer was $18-23.... They told the ETFC board to HOLD and 'build shareholder value'. hmmmmm,, guess what happened?</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767770000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:49:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767812000-68</Id><Topic><Title>GS buy rating at $18? Yup.</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you fail to see the point.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767812000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767824000-69</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fact IS, that Romneycare designed ACA IS the "responsible" way to go as per Romney...... and in Israel yesterday Romney praised THEIR universal healthcare. “[F]or an American abroad, you can’t get much closer to the ideals and convictions of my own country than you do in Israel,” he said. And according to The New York Times, Romney spoke favorably about the fact that health care makes up a much smaller amount of Israel’s gross domestic product compared to the United States" Romney said: "Our gap with Israel is 10 points of G.D.P. We have to find ways — not just to provide health care to more people, but to find ways to fund and manage our health care costs.” Israel spends less on health care because of a universal health system that requires everyone to have insurance. now you must really think Romney is a liar or a fool huh? he is talking about providing healthcare to MORE people....as in universal healhcare..... that was yesterday.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767824000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:50:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767828000-70</Id><Topic><Title>GS buy rating at $18? Yup.</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767313000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you fail to see the point.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343767828000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343767894000-71</Id><Topic><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fact IS, that Romneycare designed ACA IS the "responsible" way to go as per Romney...... and in Israel yesterday Romney praised THEIR universal healthcare. Romney said: "Our gap with Israel is 10 points of G.D.P. We have to find ways — not just to provide health care to more people, but to find ways to fund and manage our health care costs.” Israel spends less on health care because of a universal health system that requires everyone to have insurance. now you must really think Romney is a liar or a fool huh? he is talking about providing healthcare to MORE people....as in universal healhcare..... that was yesterday.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767894000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343768382000-72</Id><Title>Reid heard</Title><Msg>that the Wimp paid zero taxes for ten years. RELEASE THE RETURNS!!!!</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343768382000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343768850000-73</Id><Topic><Title>Reid heard</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343768382000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"His poor father must be so embarrassed about his son," Reid said, in reference to George Romney's standard-setting decision to turn over 12 years of tax returns when he ran for president in the late 1960s. Saying he had "no problem with somebody being really, really wealthy," Reid sat up in his chair a bit before stirring the pot further. A month or so ago, he said, a person who had invested with Bain Capital called his office. "Harry, he didn't pay any taxes for 10 years," Reid recounted the person as saying. "He didn't pay taxes for 10 years! Now, do I know that that's true? Well, I'm not certain," said Reid. "But obviously he can't release those tax returns. How would it look? That's a pretty extraordinary allegation for someone to make, and given that there's no reason to believe Bain investors have any greater access to Mitt Romney's tax returns than anybody else, this probably falls into the realm of conjecture. Nonetheless, as long as Romney keeps his returns secret, what he's hiding is anybody's guess. Over the weekend, Romney said that 'so far as [he] can recall,' he has paid "a very substantial amount" of taxes every year, but he's offered no proof of that. Given that Romney has consistently said he believes releasing his returns would be politically damaging, it's safe to say that even if the Bain investor is wrong, and Romney has paid taxes, there's a fair bit of material in there that Romney doesn't want voters to find out about before the election. And that's exactly why it's so important he come clean and release his returns. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1343768850000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343769426000-74</Id><Topic><Title>Romney praises universal healthcare in Israel</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney praised universal healthcare with a mandate here as well, obviously..... he designed the ACA, after all. Romney Strongly Endorses Mandate: ‘Personal Responsibility Was The Way To Go’ Romney said if other states adopted the individual mandate, it would be “a terrific idea…we’ll end up with a nation that’s taken a mandate approach,” and endorsed the Wyden-Bennett health care proposal, which also included a national individual mandate.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343769426000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343769705000-75</Id><Topic><Title>Romney's "let's insult the world" trip continues</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1343656360000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-07-30 09:52:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;bringing the country from the brink of collapse caused by Bush era policies, and putting it back on the growth track is hardly a failed policy&gt;&gt; Spoken like a true bureaucrat. It was the Wall Street money changers that brought this nation to its kness...where were all the government public sector union banking regulators during this Ponzi scheme. Under the Obama administration not one of these WS crooks were prosecuted, not one. Oh, didn't Obama recieved the biggest contributions to his campaign from Goldman Sachs.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343769705000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:21:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343769958000-76</Id><Topic><Title>"Wimp" get spiegeled</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1343745435000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 10:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Der Spiegel &amp; Newsweek are the same left wing papers!!! Read "Der Stern" of course you need to be fluent in German! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1343769958000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:25:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343770325000-77</Id><Title>Mitten's banks in countries with universal healthcare</Title><Msg>Mitten's banks in countries with universal healthcare (switzerland, bermuda, the caymans require employers to provide health insurance, that was a Nixon idea , btw) Mittens designed the ACA and mandate when he did his Romneycare, which he said was the " responsible " way to go. and yesterday, mittens praised how they do the mandate and universal healthcare elsewhere. I think mittens is all for the ACA and will leave it in place, he only says the other baloney to get the limbots to go for him, but the mandate and universal healthcare are in his genes, no getting it out.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343770325000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:32:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343771973000-78</Id><Topic><Title>I not a sunshine Pumper, you know that</Title><Username>precious0045</Username><Timestamp>1305535403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2011-05-16 04:43:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hold your horses, WCS Breeze</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343771973000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 17:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343772052000-79</Id><Topic><Title>Remember Precious?</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1343767272000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:41:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she was short the leap, selling. Made a killing.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343772052000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:00:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343772999000-80</Id><Topic><Title>Kenneth Griffun: 28,000,000 shares cut by 50%</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343762927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its got to hurt. Goldman says its worth $18-24 Company says "lets not sell, lets not even make an effort" Price goes to $7 Now what? Where's Goldman? Waiting for ???</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343772999000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343773201000-81</Id><Title>How can Citadel be the Smartest Guyz in da Rooom?</Title><Msg>They got conned big by etfc. Forgot all about the macros. Let Freiberg dupe him into backing down. Now moping in the shadows.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343773201000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:20:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343773724000-82</Id><Topic><Title>Kenneth Griffun: 28,000,000 shares cut by 50%</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343762927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The value was cut, not the number of shares</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343773724000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343774358000-83</Id><Topic><Title>Kenneth Griffun: 28,000,000 shares cut by 50%</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343762927000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:28:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats inferred. You should start pounding on griffun instead of reading too far into statements. Griffun has to be torqued. He got conned by a mid level bank employee and an accountant. And a board of directors that is mildly retarded. No ken be patient.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343774358000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343775020000-84</Id><Title>Etrade Financial: Case study in Negligence</Title><Msg>Board of Director negligence. What are they going to do for an encore? I hear they presented a capital plan to regulators. Horror of horrors. This management team has never come up with a shareholder friendly plan and is now more concerned with maintaining their positions and pay packages. And its all on the shareholders back.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343775020000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:50:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343778159000-85</Id><Title>One More Comment About ETFC....</Title><Msg>The management, board, and certain investors: Some individuals may be smarter than average bears, but together, think and act like mildly retarded zombies. Just think of this: The stock was $18 and you elected not to sell, with all the confidence it would go higher. One year later, the stock is a $7. Only ignorance gets you to this point.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343778159000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 19:42:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343780615000-86</Id><Title>Mittens Paid No Taxes for 10 Years !!!!!</Title><Msg>No wonder Mittens is hiding his taxes. WASHINGTON -- Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.) has what he says is an informed explanation for why Mitt Romney refuses to release additional tax returns. According a Bain investor, Reid charged, Romney didn't pay any taxes for 10 years. Romney is a huge joke !</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1343780615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>41</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343780769000-87</Id><Topic><Title>Freibergs new position to be announced soon</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343760645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spoken like a true short!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343780769000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:26:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343780956000-88</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens Paid No Taxes for 10 Years !!!!!</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1343780615000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Show us how the 1% live Romoney!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343780956000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 20:29:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>29</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343784641000-89</Id><Topic><Title>chart analysis</Title><Username>beauregardgsi187</Username><Timestamp>1343738013000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 08:33:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't Believe This WOW</Msg><Username>bonexqm278</Username><Timestamp>1343784641000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:30:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343784786000-90</Id><Topic><Title>Video Forecast</Title><Username>kelcismp990</Username><Timestamp>1343742781000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 09:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post of the day! Thanks</Msg><Username>bonexqm278</Username><Timestamp>1343784786000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:33:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343785443000-91</Id><Topic><Title>Obama donates 5 grand!</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343761789000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What greedy Brak apparently meant when he said, "I am my brother's keeper" was that he was gonna KEEP all the money for myself and not give any to his poverty striken bro, Geo'ge from Kenya. === Brak: "NO Moochelle! How many times I gotta tell ya.. Geo'ge aint getting a single penny from us, It's pointless. You know full well there's no vote to buy there." ===</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343785443000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343785462000-92</Id><Topic><Title>Romney praises universal healthcare in Israel</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343767407000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 16:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop is ALL about universal healthcare. Bush started universal healthcare in Iraq, 2004. and Romney wrote the blueprint for the ACA here and said the mandate is the "responsible" thing to do. and that was the real Romney.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343785462000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343785590000-93</Id><Title>Willard's handler loses his cool in Poland</Title><Msg>Romney aide loses cool with press July 31, 2012 8:09 AM Richard Gorka, traveling press secretary for the Mitt Romney campaign, lost his cool with reporters shouting questions at the candidate in Poland on Tuesday, telling the press to "show some respect," "shove it," and "kiss my a**." Mittens and his handlers know that his trip abroad was a total embarassment and failure from the very start.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1343785590000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:46:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343785909000-94</Id><Topic><Title>Freibergs new position to be announced soon</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343760645000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:50:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually a short would not be chanting for a sale of the company.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343785909000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:51:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343788155000-95</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>layer-honeybunch, Here is a news item for ya and your buddy bidder: Romney aide loses cool with press July 31, 2012 8:09 AM Richard Gorka, traveling press secretary for the Mitt Romney campaign, lost his cool with reporters shouting questions at the candidate in Poland on Tuesday, telling the press to "show some respect," "shove it," and "kiss my a**."</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1343788155000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:29:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343788771000-96</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and not only that - Mittens would love to release his tax returns to the American public, but his dressage horse ate them.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1343788771000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:39:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343789122000-97</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens 'Gaffe' Tour</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1343752504000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 12:35:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and also this, Uncle Mittens, the "Artful Dodger", dodged the draft during war-time, dodged his governorship, dodged Romney Care, dodged revealing his federal taxes and had to dodge the press in Poland yesterday! This guy is something else......and it's NOT Commander-in-Chief....</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1343789122000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:45:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343789743000-98</Id><Title>Kenneth Griffun of Citadel got Schmoked</Title><Msg>By a mid level banker from a failed bank and an accountant. Don't even begin to talk about the brain-dead, mildly retarded, board of directors. They collectively couldn't make a rational decision on behalf of shareholders. Collectively they make poor decisions and collectively they will be sued after refusing to sell the company at $18, under the embarassing assumption that they could make the company worth more by virtue of their inherent genious. The same genious that allowed massive investment into pools of subprime mortgages and uncollateralized helocs. Now the company is at $7 bucks and managent is debating the bonus pool for 2012. What great things management has done for its employes. Sad to say, they probably awarded PUTS to its employes Good job Freiberg.</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343789743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343790783000-99</Id><Topic><Title>Kenneth Griffun of Citadel got Schmoked</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343789743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:55:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sued for something from years ago ? It would have happened by now. Shorts bash the stock do they Fon't have to compete for shares on the way up . Psychology 101 is all that is needed with you guys!</Msg><Username>hermes4trading</Username><Timestamp>1343790783000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 23:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343791651000-100</Id><Topic><Title>Kenneth Griffun of Citadel got Schmoked</Title><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343789743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:55:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a simple minded twit. My sentiments are not short. I do want to see the management and board hang - it will happen, they have themselves in a corner at this point after such a foolhardy decision last summer. These idiots could not sell water in a desert. The ding-dong griffun really made a jack of himself last summer either in initiating his high powered missive or by getting schmoked by a middle manager from a failed bank and an accountant who diesn't have a grasp on ecinomics</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343791651000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 23:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>