<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347077088424-1</Id><Title>E#$%$ website is down</Title><Msg>A G A I N !!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 12:04 EST pos down</Msg><Username>tiglet2l</Username><Timestamp>1347077088424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347111465322-2</Id><Topic><Title>That's impressive</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347068979864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 21:49:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wish bill were running, but he ain't instead we have "know it all" BO - says I way more than We bill can't save him from himself</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1347111465322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117557223-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama got a bounce out of the DNC - Mittens did not get any bounce out of the RNC!!!</Title><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1347061502584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 19:45:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their big mistake was letting Mittens talk. Total teleprompter dependence.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1347117557223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347119223287-4</Id><Title>Another Bush legacy semi-officially FAILS. Something else for BO to fix.</Title><Msg>Texas No Child Left Behind Waiver Texas, the state that launched school accountability as an experiment, has applied to untangle itself from parts of the federal No Child Left Behind mandate, the same law that experiment eventually yielded. The deadline was Thursday for states to take President Barack Obama's administration up on its offer to waive parts of the law in exchange for implementing elements of the White House's education agenda. Texas announced that, like at least 40 other states, it wanted out, too. "NCLB’s reauthorization in a timely manner has created an obsolete system that does not adequately reflect the accomplishments of the state’s schools," the state's education chief Michael Williams wrote in an open letter Thursday. By the law's definition, in Texas 47.8 percent of schools -- and 27.6 percent of its school districts -- made "adequate yearly progress" this year. When campaigning in 2008, Obama promised to release states from the 2002 law, a signature initiative from President George W. Bush that requires standardized testing of students and a system of penalties for low test scores. The law expired in 2007. Despite a few attempts, Congress has failed to rewrite it, so the administration began offering states relief from its toughest parts. "People are making promises," said Sandy Kress, a Texan largely viewed as the grandfather of No Child Left Behind who now works as a lobbyist for companies like Pearson. "Will they fulfill them or not? He's [U.S. Secretary of Education Arne Duncan] done some incredible watering down of accountability, so here we are. Now we have Texas, believing that it ought to get some relief, wanting to just integrate its own accountability system. After a stint in the Jimmy Carter White House, Kress became interested in education and began looking at standardized test scores. For decades, the test scores of Dallas' minority students had increased, gains most experts attributed to civil rights. But starting in the late 80s, the scores began to stagnate. So in 1990, Kress proposed a plan called "accountability" to allow educators more say over school spending, in exchange for tying schools' performances on standardized tests to consequences. The idea spread and became law under then-Gov. Ann Richards. In 1995, Bush upheld it as law in Texas. By the time Bush became president, a bipartisan consensus had formed around school accountability, and negotiations with Democrats like Rep. George Miller (D-Calif.) turned Kress' homegrown idea into No Child Left Behind. While advocates credit the law for exposing test-score gaps among student groups, even the law's original cheerleaders acknowledge its mechanism for labeling schools that don't make progress is too broad, its mandated tutoring rarely boosts student achievement and the goal that 100 percent of U.S. students be "proficient" in science and math by 2014 is unrealistic. So in 2010, Obama announced that in exchange for the waivers, states could agree to a plan that included parts of the Obama education agenda, such as "college- and career-ready" standards and grading teachers using, in part, students' standardized test scores. Under the agenda, only 15 percent of each state's lowest-performing schools would be penalized. But instead of working with the administration's requirements, Texas wants the waiver without strings so it can create its own accountability system. California wants something similar and is still negotiating with the federal government, an official confirmed. Also seeking waivers right on Thursday's deadline: Alaska, Hawaii, Maine, New Hampshire and West Virginia, according to local news reports. In late August, Alabama, said it would apply, and reached by phone Friday, North Dakota's education chief Wayne Sanstead confirmed ND had sent out its request. So far, the Education Department has approved the requests of 33 states and Washington, D.C.; making the total 41 requests overall, including Texas and California.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347119223287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127922993-5</Id><Topic><Title>Gone for twelve years from Office...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346942464438</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:41:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u must be a magic underware follower...</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1347127922993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:12:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347130923444-6</Id><Title>Obama's recovery</Title><Msg>You go BHO, you go! Recovery? 96K New Jobs, 173K New Food Stamp Recipients **The moment a Republican enters the Oval Office, America's homeless are suddenly discovered, dragged before news cameras, and used as props to prove how heartless the current administration is. But as soon as a Democrat assumes office, the homeless suddenly disappear; presumably to a place with chocolate rivers and peppermint trees that only Democrat presidents are able to magically manifest as soon as the oath of office is complete. The media's been even worse with Barack Obama. Not only have the homeless vanished from news coverage, but so have America's poor. But as NBC's David Gregory made clear, if you even try to bring up the record number of food stamp recipients Barack Obama's failed policies have created, you'll be labeled a racist**</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347130923444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:02:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347131234499-7</Id><Topic><Title>More reasons the mortgage crisis is not the fault of GSE's or "poor people" as the droolers would like you to believe</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347062400605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:00:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a crook of #$%$ You lefties are always trying to rewrite history. Oh, that's right...for liberals history starts over everyday</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347131234499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:07:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347132964627-8</Id><Title>Mayor Villaraigosa on his bungling of the vote at the convention</Title><Msg>Spoken like a true Democrat, as he perpetrated voter fraud on his own delegates “That’s nice to know. I was the chairman and I did, and that was the prerogative of the chair.” Villaraigosa defends vote revising DNC platform on Jerusalem, God Such a change requires a two-thirds vote by delegates, and on Wednesday they were asked to approve language invoking God and affirming Jerusalem as the capital of Israel. Villaraigosa, the convention chairman, called for a voice vote three times before declaring the amendments approved. Some delegates and journalists on the convention floor at the Time Warner Cable Arena were adamant that one could not audibly be certain they heard two-thirds of the delegates present say “aye.” “It was a lot of ado about nothing,” the mayor said Friday. Villaraigosa said that when reporters told him after the vote that they did not clearly hear two-thirds support, he responded, “That’s nice to know. I was the chairman and I did, and that was the prerogative of the chair.”</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1347132964627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:36:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347140871881-9</Id><Title>Dipshidiot getting desperate!!!</Title><Msg>Romney Implies Obama Will Remove God From Coins, Obama Campaign Fires Back Last edited Sat Sep 8, 2012, 04:43 PM Mitt Romney suggested Saturday in Virginia Beach that President Obama wants to remove God from coins, provoking a fierce retort from the president's campaign. &amp;quot;I will not take God out of our platform,&amp;quot; the Republican nominee said after reciting the Pledge of Allegiance. &amp;quot;I will not take God off our coins, and I will not take God out of my heart.&amp;quot; In response, Obama spokeswoman Lis Smith called the insinsuation false and an act of desperation. &amp;quot;It’s disappointing to see Mitt Romney try to throw a Hail Mary by launching extreme and untrue attacks against the President and associating with some of the most strident and divisive voices in the Republican Party, including Rep. Steve King and Pat Robertson,&amp;quot; she said in a statement. &amp;quot;This isn’t a recipe for making America stronger, it’s a recipe for division and taking us backward.&amp;quot;</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347140871881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347141496422-10</Id><Title>Ms. Dipshidiot covers up</Title><Msg>Ann Romney Declines To Answer Questions On Gay Marriage, Contraception Source: Huffington Post "Here in Iowa, as you know, same-sex marriage is legal. Do you believe a lesbian mother should be allowed to marry her partner?" David Nelson, a KWQC anchor asked. "You know, I'm not going to talk about the specific issues," Romney responded, adding that "hot-button issues" distract from the economy. Nelson then asked whether employers should be required to provide health insurance that covers birth control. The Romney campaign has attacked the Obama administration for adopting a rule requiring most religiously affiliated employers to provide coverage for contraception in their health plans. She declined to answer. "Again, you're asking me questions that are not about what this election is going to be about. This election is going to be about the economy and jobs."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347141496422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:58:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347156697819-11</Id><Title>How can the GOP even claim to be christians?</Title><Msg>September 6, 2012 Clinton Paints GOP Threat to Medicaid by the Numbers Bill Clinton's address to the Democratic National Convention accomplished a good many things for his party. Among them was shining a spotlight on one of the least reported but potentially most far-reaching proposals Mitt Romney and his Republican Party have promised to pursue. While all eyes have been on the Romney-Ryan plan to voucherize Medicare, the Republican promise to slash Medicaid spending by a third over the next decade has largely gone unnoticed. But it shouldn't. The result would not only be the loss of health insurance for millions of lower-income Americans in the coming years, but devastating cuts to nursing home care for seniors and coverage for the disabled starting in 2013. Mitt Romney along with the 98 percent of Congressional Republicans who voted for the Ryan House GOP budget don't merely support the repeal of the Affordable Care Act and with it prevent over 30 million people from obtaining health insurance. As ThinkProgress explained, their cuts to Medicaid "start immediately and cut the program 35 percent by 2022 -- a loss of $810 billion over that time period." Last night, President Clinton did the arithmetic for the American people: They also want to block grant Medicaid and cut it by an third over the coming ten years. Of course that's gonna really hurt a lot of poor kids. But that's not all. Lot of folks don't know it, but nearly two-thirds of Medicaid is spent on nursing home care for Medicare seniors who are eligible for Medicaid... And a lot of that money is also spent to help people with disabilities. Including a lot of middle class families whose kids have down syndrome or autism or other severe conditions. And with that, David Frum acknowledged, "Clinton Socks GOP in its Glass Jaw." On stage Wednesday night, Frum fretted for his conservative allies, "former president Clinton detonated the H-bomb of the 2012 campaign": Republicans have promised to hold harmless from Medicare changes everyone under age 55, assuring high-voting senior citizens that they have nothing to fear from Republican budget plans. But while Medicare is left alone until 2023, Medicaid is immediately subject to very large cuts. Many of us may think of Medicaid as above all a program for the poor. It is also, however, increasingly the way in which America pays for nursing home care -- and indeed nursing care is the fastest-growing part of Medicaid. (Frum is actually wrong about Medicare being "left alone until 2023. By repealing the Affordable Care Act, Mitt Romney would roll back benefits already in place including the end of the prescription drug "donut hole" and free preventive care.) But the Big Dog's revelations are even bigger trouble for Republicans. In a nutshell, health care is worst where the GOP polls best. And it will be red states who will suffer most if President Romney succeeds in killing Obamacare and gutting Medicaid. Currently, the $350 billion Medicaid program serves roughly 63 million Americans. On average, the federal government picks up 57% of the tab, with poorer states like Mississippi and Alabama getting 75% of the funding from Washington. Medicaid not only pays for a third of nursing home care in the United States; it covers a third of all childbirths. (In Texas, the figure is one-half.) As with Medicare, Medicaid provides insurance for substantially less than private insurers (27% less for children, 20% for adults), while new studies from Oregon and Massachusetts show it dramatically improves the health of its recipients. (So much for the claims of Republicans like Tennessee Senator Lamar Alexander, who charged that Medicaid is "a medical ghetto" that "none of us, or any of our families, would ever want to be a part of for our health care.") But the worry for red state residents isn't just that South Carolina's Nikki Haley, Florida's Rick Scott and many of the same GOP governors who brought the suit against the Affordable Care Act have said they will reject the new dollars from Washington that could help cover 27 million uninsured in their states. With the no-strings attached block grants from a Romney administration, they would assuredly cut their dismal state programs further. As Jonathan Cohn explained: That's not to say plenty of governors wouldn't take advantage of block grant status to change their Medicaid programs in ways they cannot now. They surely would--by capping enrollment, thinning benefits, increasing co-payments, and so on. To understand how the Medicaid would work in the Romney-Ryan future, just look at Mississippi's present. New York's former Medicaid director Deborah Bachrach warned, "If Mississippi opted out of the 2014 expansion of Medicaid, poor childless adults wouldn't gain coverage in that state; at the same time, the state could roll back eligibility for parents with children who are currently enrolled, reducing the number of participants in the program." But as Glenn Kessler explained in the Washington Post last year, it is hard to believe that a state like Mississippi could make it current program any worse: Mississippi provides some of the lowest Medicaid benefits to working adults in the nation. A parent who isn't working can qualify only if annual family income is less than 24 percent of the poverty line. Working parents qualify only if they make no more than 44 percent of the federal poverty level. Seniors and people with disabilities are eligible with income at 80 percent of the poverty line... Translated from the federal poverty guidelines, that means a working Mississippi couple with one child could earn no more than $8,150 a year and still qualify for Medicaid, seniors and people with disabilities could earn no more than $8,700, and a pregnant woman could earn no more than $20,000 a year. None of what Bill Clinton highlighted in Charlotte is anything new. After all, Bloomberg News, the Washington Post and McClatchy have been reporting for months that the Romney-Ryan proposals would hurt the poor, the elderly and the disabled. But sometimes, you need a Big Dog to teach Americans about the Republicans' new tricks.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1347156697819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156789169-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ms. Dipshidiot covers up</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1347141496422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:58:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon they will be answering every question with: Look - I'm white - he's black - I'm not going to be getting into any other details...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1347156789169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:13:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>