<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354514462834-1</Id><Topic><Title>Da Fiscal Cliff = $7.01 E-Tub ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1353967592784</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-26 17:06:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Da Fiscal Cliff = Political Posturing, and everyone knows it. If the market really acted on based on the political landscape the election of Obama would have been the SECOND and worse wave of the 2nd Great Depression. Somehow his re-election was already priced into the market though (I guess the Wall Street types had confidence their horse would win) so there wasn't a significant effect. EFTC is waiting to get their provisioning right and to work off two bad quarters that bracket two good quarters, so the next quarters earnings will make a significant P/E difference (assuming positive earnings) as will the one three quarters later, at which point this company will be worth a great deal more than it is now, what with rising real estate prices. Lets face it, Obama is going to wear out the printing presses if he gets control of deficit expansion (as suggested in his latest budget) at which point stock prices will rise to trace the increased money supply, leaving inflation looming around the corner for his successor unless they manage to destroy most of the increased money supply by spending it on useless government programs that disperse wealth instead of creating it, an entirely likely situation under this President.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1354514462834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 01:01:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354539447508-2</Id><Title>Is the .20 income increase from refi in the .54 2013 analyst estimate</Title><Msg>I'm thinking no, they couldn't have been certain it would occur. I wonder when the estimate will be bumped to .74.</Msg><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1354539447508</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 07:57:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1354544329571-3</Id><Title>Le Fiscal Bunny Hill...very scary ... code alert orange</Title><Msg>sell everything hide under the bed.</Msg><Username>followthevolume</Username><Timestamp>1354544329571</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 09:18:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354560390412-4</Id><Topic><Title>"Aung San Suu Kyi" you hillbilly</Title><Username>alien_frikin_abduction</Username><Timestamp>1354140583068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:09:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our President apparently had an F in math at school, so did you. Give us the math. Real math. Would you you? All the president offer is rich has to pay more. Even with rudimentary arithmetic skills one can figure out with that we still end up with $1T deficit. And this president calls it a solution for "fiscal cliff"? It is a joke. He is throwing us right off the cliff with a smile.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1354560390412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 13:46:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1354562996923-5</Id><Topic><Title>"Aung San Suu Kyi" you hillbilly</Title><Username>alien_frikin_abduction</Username><Timestamp>1354140583068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-28 17:09:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know what was offered to Obama by GOP House. We are talking about entitlement reform in the first place. Obama has no guts to even look into this. Instead, he offers a fig leaf which resolves NOTHING, kecks a can down the road, and instead of addressing substance playing a blame game again. Easy! Once again, tax on the rich proposed by Obama is drop in the bucket. But that's the only "solution" Obama offers. Gutless and irresponsible.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1354562996923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-12-03 14:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>