<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-07-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343534406000-1</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens Compared to Sarah Palin ! LMAO !</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343489091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the morons can't debate the point, they insult. Gay Wingnutz are quite shallow.</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343534406000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 00:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343543295000-2</Id><Title>Roll out red carpet for ETFC!!!</Title><Msg>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/wall-street-week-ahead-rolling-213205408.html Equity prices tend to rise sharply in the hours before a Fed statement like the one expected on Wednesday as traders and investors jockey for position and a chance to make a profit. Next week's calendar has a double-whammy. The Fed's monetary policy statement will come one day before an ECB meeting packed with intrigue. ECB President Mario Draghi said earlier this week the bank was ready to do whatever was necessary, within its mandate, to save the euro. "People in this business like to get in front of big events, especially if (they) could be very, very positive for the market," said Brian Reynolds, chief market strategist at agency brokerage Rosenblatt Securities.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343543295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 02:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343566241000-3</Id><Topic><Title>Roll out red carpet for ETFC!!!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1343543295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 02:28:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only good that will come of ETFC is when the board of directors finally wakes up and recognizes the error of their ways and sells this company to the highest bidder. You know as well as all others, the time has come for this to go. Any attempt at long term revitalization is a fools mission given the economic outlook.</Msg><Username>hammerstein_klondike</Username><Timestamp>1343566241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343566242000-4</Id><Title>gop love Bushcare at the ER &amp; their tax to pay for it</Title><Msg>Bushcare at the ER is paid for by the middleclass... it adds about $1500 a year to a family premium: that's a 4% gop tax on the $40K a year family and a 0.003% tax on the Romney type family making $45 million A YEAR. Since the middleclass pay for it, it's easy to see why the gop don't care if an uninsured person racks up a $100K bill at the ER for a cancer surgery for example that may have been prevented by a $2K colonoscopy, if the person had insurance and could have gone to a doc.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1343566242000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 08:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>38</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343573444000-5</Id><Title>Due to the inordinate amount and high frequency</Title><Msg>wif which these gaffs are made. It seems easier to group them in subsets of 10 http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2012/07/28/Obama-Top-Ten-UK-Gaffes</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343573444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343575866000-6</Id><Title>Koch Bro Scientist Says Humans Cause Climate Change</Title><Msg>he was funded by the Koch Bros to deny climate change, now he reverses his opinion. Humans are almost entirely the cause" of climate change, according to a scientist who once doubted that global warming even existed. Last year, Richard Muller walked back years of climate change skepticism in light of new research. But Sunday's comments go one step further. Muller wrote in an NYT op-ed that after exhaustive research, he believes that an increase of greenhouse gases can be closely linked to the rise in the earth's temperature. He explains: Our results show that the average temperature of the earth’s land has risen by two and a half degrees Fahrenheit over the past 250 years, including an increase of one and a half degrees over the most recent 50 years. Moreover, it appears likely that essentially all of this increase results from the human emission of greenhouse gases However, Muller said that he did not believe that the recent heat waves or Hurricane Katrina were caused by global warming. Muller, a UCBerkeley professor, founded the Berkeley Earth Surface Temperature project, which receives substantial funding from GOP powerhouse donor Charles Koch.</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343575866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>28</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343577609000-7</Id><Topic><Title>Koch Bro Scientist Says Humans Cause Climate Change</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343575866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so drill baby...what are you committed to,..to make it better....the forte of your group is always whining, bit..chin...till someone solves it for you or throws you a bone...</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343577609000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 12:00:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343581919000-8</Id><Topic><Title>Koch Bro Scientist Says Humans Cause Climate Change</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343575866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm committed to the abolishment of ignorance. Which means you have to go.</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343581919000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 13:11:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>21</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343587577000-9</Id><Topic><Title>Koch Bro Scientist Says Humans Cause Climate Change</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343575866000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 11:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hahaha. That's no way for a commie pinko liberal socialist pacifist to act. You should be all about saving the world. But instead you're Quick to point out problems and short on solutions. Like your daddy brack</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343587577000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 14:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343590473000-10</Id><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Msg>&lt;&lt;The jacket cost more than the average American family makes in a month ($4,284)&gt;&gt; She Feels Your Pain... Michelle Obama Sports $6,800 Jacket to London Soiree. The liberal media was all upset that “elitist” Ann Romney wore a $990 top during a May interview on “This Morning.” Yet this same media cheered the fashion and style of Queen Michelle Obama whose taste in sweaters cost her over $2,000 a pop. But, yesterday Michelle Obama outdid herself. Michelle Obama wore silver-and-white J Mendel for the evening soiree at Buckingham Palace. The Embroidered Cap Sleeve Jacket costs $6,800. Just a drop in the bucket. The jacket cost more than the average American family makes in a month ($4,284). And, she does this as Americans continue to suffer through a deep recession and record unemployment.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>31</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343591581000-11</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps the only shovel-ready job ever created under this administration. http://thepeoplescube.com/images/Michelle_Obama_Shovels_Food.jpg</Msg><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343591581000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>30</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343592869000-12</Id><Topic><Title>Texting and stock investing don't mix</Title><Username>jarvismaggie250</Username><Timestamp>1343478861000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 08:34:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanx for the reports.</Msg><Username>trentonhenry120</Username><Timestamp>1343592869000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343593295000-13</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how much you want to bet that came out of bracks exspence allowance sponsored not so much by his constituents but you and me.....it would be fine by me...but since he wants to complain how taxes should be raised on upper incomes and believes the economy can be fixed with food stamps....again sponsored by you and me....he should be leading by example....quit pilaging those tax dollars on discretionary spending</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343593295000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>29</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343593681000-14</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems like a modest expense. Maybe after the millionaires start paying their fair share the burden won't fall so heavily on the likes of you.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593681000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:28:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>26</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343593944000-15</Id><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Msg>Pandering to the Israelis didn't work; he had to wimp off of that. Mitt will soon be a Polish joke.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343594063000-16</Id><Topic><Title>Screwed up in both England and Israel</Title><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343593944000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:32:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bet his backers are holding their collective breaths in hopes that he won't hurt himself even orse before he comes back to the US.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343594063000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:34:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>27</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343594294000-17</Id><Topic><Title>Due to the inordinate amount and high frequency</Title><Username>udinnitbewdat98_l</Username><Timestamp>1343573444000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 10:50:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Racist bigot, slayer, wif his whistling in the dark efforts to ignore Mitt's stupid mistakes in England, and now in Israel as well.</Msg><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1343594294000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:38:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343594531000-18</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens Compared to Sarah Palin ! LMAO !</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343489091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Comparing Mitt to Sarah is insulting--to Sarah. Well, that may be a bit of a hard sell, I suppose.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1343594531000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343594809000-19</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will never be a fair share no matter how much is paid..... Just more government spending more wah wah wah! and more gimme gimme take takers. The top 5% pays 60% of the government bill already. So what's fair.</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1343594809000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 16:46:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343596698000-20</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle Antoinette</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343590473000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 15:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>&lt;&lt;Seems like a modest expense&gt;&gt; I did know they sold J. Mendel jackets at Target. http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/reliable-source/post/hey-isnt-that-michelle-obama-at-target-jose-andres-and-ferran-adria/2011/09/29/gIQAplnF8K_blog.html</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1343596698000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 17:18:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>27</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343599157000-21</Id><Title>2009 All Over Again...</Title><Msg>BOHICA!... http://news.yahoo.com/earnings-perform-2009-boos-then-boos-now-231602882--finance.html</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1343599157000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 17:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343605721000-22</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens Compared to Sarah Palin ! LMAO !</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1343489091000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-07-28 11:24:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens is a shady Mormon, he'll never win</Msg><Username>serpa666</Username><Timestamp>1343605721000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 19:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>16</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343613147000-23</Id><Title>Monday Madness: the madness continues</Title><Msg>Eyes Wide Shut as the etrade board of directors continues onward in the wrong directions. Shakey plans call for continued pursuit in a shrinking market and an economy about to implode. Yet the mantra continues: lets spend lots of advertising dollars on a program that sees just a few less lost accounts than new accounts. Spending almost $80,000,000 a year on a paltry few new accounts. Kenneth Griffin of Citadel Investments has to be ready to pop with rage. After the company sang and danced for him last summer, Ken was stupidly looking forward to steady appreciation in stock price. But low, it went lower. So Ken is stuck trying to splain how an investment in 27,000,000 shares of etfc fell by more than 50 percent in a year. Tsk tsk tsk</Msg><Username>brandish_mow</Username><Timestamp>1343613147000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 21:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343616935000-24</Id><Title>Willard latest international incident</Title><Msg>Romney Says Jerusalem Is Capital, Would Move Embassy There Mitt Romney said that Jerusalem is the capital of Israel and that as president he would work to move the U.S. embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem in an interview with CNN’s Wolf Blitzer Sunday. “A nation has the capacity to choose its own capital city, and Jerusalem is Israel’s capital,” Romney said. “I think it’s long been the policy to ultimately have our embassy in the nation’s capital of Jerusalem.” Romney said the timing of the move would be worked out. “I would follow the same policy we have had in the past, our embassy would be in the capital, and the timing of that is something I would want to work out with the government,” Romney said. Earlier this week, the White House issued a statement in response to questions from the press, clarifying their position on the issue: “The status of Jerusalem is an issue that should be resolved in final status negotiations between Israelis and Palestinians. And we continue to work with both parties to resolve this issue and others in a way that is just and fair, and respects the rights and aspirations of both Israelis and Palestinians.” http://livewire.talkingpointsmemo.com/entries/romney-says-he-would-move-american-embassy-to Romney needs to be yanked off the international stage.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343616935000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 22:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>19</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343619184000-25</Id><Topic><Title>Willard latest international incident</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343616935000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 22:55:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Saturday's insults: http://www.dailykos.com/story/2012/07/28/1114277/-Israel-Romney-Insults-America-s-Mid-East-Allies?detail=hide</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1343619184000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-07-29 23:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>18</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>