<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355928849832-1</Id><Topic><Title>I am like the guy who was imprisoned on an asteroid - last ETFC guy here</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1355925961508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:06:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep! that tends to happen when the BOD destroys shareholder value with a 1 for 10 reverse split and long term stock holders are left holding the bag. This stock is still under a dollar even after profitable quarters.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1355928849832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 09:54:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355936425206-2</Id><Title>New Evidence Shows Fox Wrong on Benghazi</Title><Msg>Never let it be said that Fox reports the truth. The new report, by an independent Accountability Review Board established by the State Department, concluded that two bureaus at the department -- Near East Affairs and Diplomacy Security -- failed to properly recognize the rising dangers of Eastern Libya despite the lack of any specific threats, and neglected the growing concerns of security analysts on the ground about the capabilities of the local Libyan guard force. The result, the report said, was a "security posture that was inadequate for Benghazi and grossly inadequate to deal with the attack that took place." But while the unclassified version of the report, which was released Tuesday night, is undeniably harsh in its analysis of the State Department's management ahead of the attack, it also appears to undermine a number of the more outlandish charges made during the heat of the uproar this fall. For instance, while many figures -- led, in large part, by the news analysts at Fox News -- suggested that the administration had opted to watch the crisis unfold rather than send military reinforcements, the report found "no evidence of undue delays in decision making or denial of support from Washington."</Msg><Username>borderxingbeaner</Username><Timestamp>1355936425206</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355936575268-3</Id><Topic><Title>Moved more cash than I was expecting. $6 Billion</Title><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1355930290459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 10:18:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brig, I believe they will have to get to the ratio as quickly as possible and continue to maintain it - for their plans of moving capital end of 2013. IMO - Regulators wiill want to see their ability to hold the ratios for an extended period of time before letting them move any capital. I dont think the regulators will let them move capital end of next year if they only reach the 9.5 number end of 3rd quarter 2013. I think the amount of money they will ask and get to upstream will be equivalent to sum of their 1st three quarter earnings in 2013 (before tax - due to tax credit or after tax is the question) In 2014 (end of 2014) the number will be sum of prior four quarters plus any excess over 9 leverage ratio (and so on...).</Msg><Username>invlongtrm</Username><Timestamp>1355936575268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 12:02:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355941713434-4</Id><Title>Tax payers to take on the chin for the UAW</Title><Msg>I guess they didn't sell enough Chevy Volts....One hopes all those Union votes were well worth the now booked $40+ billion cost to all taxpayers. Uncle Sam Books 50% Loss As Government Motors Buys Back 200MM Shares From Tim Geithner A few days after divesting its stake in the firm that started it all, AIG, and at a profit at that (ignoring that the risk has merely been onboarded by the Fed whose DV01 is now $2+ billion as a result), the US Treasury continues to divest of all its bailout stake, this time proceeding to GM, where the channel stuffing firm just announced it would buyback 200MM shares from the US government at a price of $27.50. More importantly, the "Treasury said it intends to sell its other remaining 300.1 million shares through various means in an orderly fashion within the next 12-15 months, subject to market conditions. Treasury intends to begin its disposition of those 300.1 million common shares as soon as January 2013 pursuant to a pre-arranged written trading plan. The manner, amount, and timing of the sales under the plan are dependent upon a number of factors." Assuming a price in the $27.50 range, this implies a nearly 50% loss on the government's breakeven price of $54. So much for the "profit" spin. One wonders why the US government did not open up this particular buyback to a public tender: after all some taxpayers may still care about the financial mismanagement of Uncle Sam. Then again, perhaps not.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355941713434</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 13:28:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355943838818-5</Id><Title>The world as we know it will end on December 21</Title><Msg>Uh Oh! As Mayan 'Apocalypse' Nears, Doomsday Craze Grips The World The end is near. The world as we know it will end on December 21, when cataclysmic events will leave a trail of destruction and cause near-total human extinction on Earth. At any rate, that's the belief held by some people worldwide based on interpretations of the ancient Mayan calendar.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355943838818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:03:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355956952846-6</Id><Topic><Title>The world as we know it will end on December 21</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355943838818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:03:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you imagine how many suicides are going to happen on the 22nd when things don't work out for them!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1355956952846</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 17:42:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355965429593-7</Id><Topic><Title>The world as we know it will end on December 21</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355943838818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 14:03:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The world as we know it will ended on Nov 6th</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1355965429593</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 20:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355965928027-8</Id><Title>broke back brack</Title><Msg>word has it he got his tonsilectomy from the infamous johnny wadd holmes,...he's got 200 mph duct tape patching the hole behind his collar...is it twew is it twew............</Msg><Username>jimmee_crackcorn</Username><Timestamp>1355965928027</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-19 20:12:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>