<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356883743696-1</Id><Topic><Title>Only 49</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1356883219035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:00:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In keeping wif the laziness of the times.. It's 49 "mon's" You should get out more.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1356883743696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 11:09:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1356900520825-2</Id><Topic><Title>TP torpedoed the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1356900090536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:41:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>reactionsare results from your dear leader's actions.......dumbssa actions have dumbsaa results......or do you not believe odumbo is in charge........cant blame him if if he's not in charge......</Msg><Username>jimmee_crackcorn</Username><Timestamp>1356900520825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 15:48:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356902169609-3</Id><Title>The biggest awhole award in 2012</Title><Msg>Goes to....Justice Roberts for upholding the Affordable Care Act, and by doing so handed the election to the community agitator.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1356902169609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:16:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356903116523-4</Id><Title>OMG, there is gambling going on at Rick's cafe</Title><Msg>This why folks don't want their taxes raised, the government just throws it away to the 47%. **That’s a lot of bread for a store where the most expensive item is an $11.99** Food Stamp Fraud? Some Very Suspicious Transactions For Welfare Recipients Most people run to the corner bodega for a gallon of milk or a loaf of bread, but some welfare recipients are plunking down $500 at a time in suspicious transactions, The Post has found. Welfare users are only allowed to use their Electronic Benefit Transfer cards to buy food, yet they are rung up like fat cats in tiny stores in The Bronx and Brooklyn where the priciest item is usually an $8 pound of ham. Earlier this year, an owner and a cashier at Glenwood Food Corp. in Canarsie, Brooklyn, were arrested for ringing up bogus transactions. A federal sting found the bodega was recording phony purchases on EBT cards, handing customers about 70 percent of the amount in cash and pocketing the rest. Goods were rarely exchanged in the scam, which defrauded taxpayers out of $985,000. The Post found dozens of mysterious high-value “purchases” in low-end stores in a state database of 1 million EBT transactions. Sheridan Mini Mart in Morrisania, The Bronx, rang up single sales of $543.40 and $473.50 on June 4, 2012, alone. That’s a lot of bread for a store where the most expensive item is an $11.99 jug of cooking oil.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1356903116523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 16:31:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1356916487772-5</Id><Title>Hillary hospitalized with blood clot.</Title><Msg>Benghazi flu proponents embarrassed yet again.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1356916487772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-30 20:14:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>