<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350104654968-1</Id><Title>Magic underwear now available</Title><Msg>"For something that's always supposed to remain hidden, the Mormon Church's special undergarments are suddenly attracting a lot of attention. Sometimes referred to glibly as "Magic Mormon Underwear," replicas of the special white temple garments are now being sold online through a new website called MormonsSecret dotcom founded by a self-professed former Mormon. Mormon's Secret uses photoshopped images of Mitt and Ann Romney wearing the special undergarments, which come in a selection of styles. The website claims to be unique in its business model: For the first time in history, online shoppers can purchase these magical temple garments without first joining the Mormon church and giving up 10% of their income in tithes. Our goal is to make “magical” underwear available to the masses for use as costume wear, fetish wear, and all your kinky, dress-up needs. All the undergarments are assembled in China, but the authentic Mormon symbols, heirloom stitching techniques, and traditional Masonic symbols are hand-sewn on each garment in the United States, according to the website. Each item is priced between $32 and $46. According to Brigham Young University, these types of white garments, similar in pattern to plain T-shirts and long pajama bottoms, must be worn by members of the church who have received the ordinance of the temple endowment. They must be worn under their clothes (including bras for women) every day as an "outward expression of an inward covenant." As the Los Angeles Times notes, the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints has a handbook that devotes an entire section to the garments. The handbook states that the garments “provide protection against temptation and evil.” Mormon's Secret is the brainchild of "Ann Jackson," a woman who goes by an alias because of safety fears, the Los Angeles Times notes. Raised in the Mormon Church and married as a teen, Jackson claims on her site that she is familiar with the fabric-buying operations and construction of special LDS garments. She also says she is no longer married and no longer a Mormon. Jackson is capitalizing on the recent attention focused on Mormons, due to the Romney campaign as well as the smash Broadway hit, "Book of Mormon." . The latter has inspired a Halloween trend of sorts, with "Mormon missionary" making Time magazine's top 10 topical costume list last year, according to ABC4. The issue of Mormon undergarments has also become a hot topic after Ann Romney appeared on "The Tonight Show With Jay Leno" wearing a tight, leather skirt, causing some Mormon bloggers to question whether she was actually wearing her special garments.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350104654968</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350106036553-2</Id><Title>Rubio roommate in trouble</Title><Msg>" MIAMI | Fri Oct 12, 2012 9:13pm EDT (Reuters) - A campaign finance scandal involving a South Florida Republican could open the door to a surprise congressional victory for his Democratic party challenger, resulting in the election of Miami's first Cuban-American Democrat. The race for Florida's 26th district between two rival Cuban Americans is setting a new standard for dirty tricks, even for Miami's politically passionate Cuban exile community. The electoral shenanigans, which have dominated local news and prompted an FBI probe, went viral nationwide in a video when a local TV reporter knocked on the door of a candidate involved in the scandal and was doused with a jug of water. David Rivera, a one-term Cuban-American Republican and hardline crusader against Cuba's communist government, is seeking re-election in a rematch against Joe Garcia. Before being elected to Congress, Rivera served eight years in the Florida Legislature, sharing a house in Tallahassee with fellow Republican and rising political star Marco Rubio. Garcia, a former Department of Energy official, is also a tough critic of Cuba's government, though he supports the Obama administration's moderate policy of "people-to-people" exchanges, including cultural visits and unrestricted travel for Cuban exile families. Polls by both parties show Garcia now leading by at least 9 percentage points in what would be a surprise pickup for the Democrats. In a bizarre twist, Rivera is accused of interfering in the Democratic party's August primary by allegedly funneling at least $40,000 in cash to the campaign of a candidate running against Garcia, according to two sources who worked on the campaign. The money went to pay for campaign mailings backing another virtual unknown, Justin Sternad. An unemployed former hotel worker, Sternad was making his first bid for public office. Among the mailings, Sternad professed to be an Obama fan while raising questions about Garcia's recent divorce, suggesting he left his wife while she was battling cancer, an accusation the Garcia campaign strongly rejects. "This case has layer after layer of unreality," said Seth Gordon, 63, a former political consultant in Miami. "We have scruffy campaign practices here, but it's mostly low-grade stuff. This is pretty high-grade." Sternad's attorney declined to comment. Sternad's campaign team included Ana Alliegro, 42, a political consultant who is a friend of Rivera and calls herself a "Republican Political Guru and Conservative Bad Girl!" on her Facebook page. Alliegro went missing soon after the allegations about the payments surfaced. Her lawyer told Reuters that he doesn't know where she is. Rivera denies he had anything to do with Sternad's campaign. "Congressman Rivera has never met Mr. Sternad, has never spoken to Mr. Sternad, knows nothing about Mr. Sternad and has no connection whatsoever to Mr. Sternad or his campaign," he said in a statement. Garcia eventually won the primary easily with 53 percent of the vote, though Sternad still managed to come in third with 10 percent, beating out two other candidates. Despite the occasional whiff of scandal, no south Florida congressman has ever been indicted while in office. Democratic party Congressman and former judge Alcee Hastings was impeached by Congress in 1989 and removed from the bench but earned sweet revenge by getting himself elected to Congress in 1992. This is not the first time Rivera has faced allegations of campaign finance mischief. The Florida Department of Law Enforcement and the Miami-Dade State Attorney's Office recently closed an 18-month investigation into alleged misuse by Rivera of campaign contributions without filing any charges. The present accusations are potentially far more serious. Rivera provided tens of thousands of dollars in cash to finance Sternad's campaign, according to the companies that handled the mailing of flyers. Federal campaign finance law limits contributions to $2,500 per person in a primary, and only $100 in cash, according to the Federal Election Commission. When a veteran political reporter from the local ABC affiliate tried to interview the candidate at home, Sternad's wife gave him the water treatment. John Borrero, president of Rapid Mail Inc, told Reuters the mailings were paid for by Rivera in cash, totaling more than $40,000. "I never talked to. Everything was orchestrated by ... David Rivera," Borrero said. Borrero said he has worked for a lot of campaigns but usually is paid with checks from campaign accounts. "They paid in cash. It seemed odd, but I don't question who mails what, unless it's a bomb," he said. Borrero said he gave a statement to FBI agents who visited his office and also turned over purchase orders, Post Office receipts and bank deposit records. "It's federal now. I gave them everything," he said. The FBI office in Miami said it had no comment. Hugh Cochran, president of Campaign Data, told Reuters that his company compiled the mailing list data at Rivera's request. Cochran, a retired FBI agent, said he didn't realize the data was intended for Sternad's campaign until later when he spoke to Borrero. "I was baffled by that," he said.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1350106036553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 01:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350126804271-3</Id><Topic><Title>Rep. Jesse Jackson Jr. under federal investigation over alleged financial improprieties</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1350094674371</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 22:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who woulda ever guessed that ??</Msg><Username>browninme</Username><Timestamp>1350126804271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 07:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350135443134-4</Id><Topic><Title>healthcare for all is free at the hospital say mittens!</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350057425858</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:57:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who needs insurance, when you have free bushcare at the hospital.....again..... i told you mitt is a bush rerun. "you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital" Mittens 2012 “I mean, people have access to health care in America,” ... “After all, you just go to an emergency room.” W bush 2007</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350135443134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:37:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350136206496-5</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Socio-path says you will pay for Healthcare for Illegals (FAIR!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349992786308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:59:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Death panel to oversee your existance. High tech "Killing Fields'!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350136206496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350136295561-6</Id><Title>A little light reading</Title><Msg>11 October 2012 Reagannite Republican Clintons Look Set to Euthanize Obama's Dying Campaign as a Segue to Hillary 2016 Where's the smoke there's fire Of all the people that Barack Obama has compromised, pressured, controlled, manipulated, blackmailed, and otherwise kept a lid on over the last four years, hallelujah at long-last somebody has turned and refused to lie for him anymore- and that somebody is Hillary Clinton: the US State Dept. yesterday completely dis-avowed the White House's dubious account of events in Benghazi on 9/11, forcing Obama to retract his earlier, #$%$-laden version. Surprised? Can't imagine why- following a nasty 2008 primary, Bill Clinton and Obama have been what you might call 'frenemies', even as Hillary was co-opted/politically contained by bringing her into the Obama Administration. But it's doubtful she enjoys working for the guy, only the most fawning and subservient do for long. Bubba supposedly encouraged Hillary to stage a primary challenge against 'incompetent', 'amateur' Obama, yet she demurred: is it possible at that point they decided their best bet was 2016- perhaps regardless of who won 2012? If it sounds far-fetched, consider that both Bill's former aide and at least one Hillary staffer have remarked to the press they were 'voting for Romney', and specifically to 'propel Hillary to the WH'. Bill's convention speech in Charlotte provided cover for the Clintons now surreptitiously turning on Obama on the eve of his defeat, pending investigations, and ongoing disassembly of the factually-warped Obama myth... while Hillary's lack of attendance -the first DNC she's missed in 30 years- creates political space for things to come. Just look how the Benghazi debacle has gone down, the lies, the cover-up... WHY would Hillary take a fall for the WH? Obama wouldn't spit on her if her hair was on fire, and everybody -especially the Clintons- knows it. Small wonder Obama hustled her into the Oval Office yesterday for a little cawfee tawk. Neither Clinton has forgotten the way Obama screwed them over in the 2008 caucuses (+ other dirty tricks), and they're not what you'd call 'forgiving' types: what a perfect opening to stick it to Barry while setting up her run in 2016 as a 'truth-teller', all Hill's got to do is tell us that truth. This epic opportunity for revenge -one created by Obama's habitual dishonesty- has been laid before Hillary at the most inopportune moment for Dear Leader- and it looks to me like she's taking it..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350136295561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350136743014-7</Id><Title>ETFC Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can ETFC Last??</Title><Msg>If you ask me ETFC looks great right now. Its volume has been moving at an explosive rate all morning and word is that news about ETFC will be releasing soon... If you're playing ETFC like me play the dips or the average downs... Smart ETFC traders play like this all the time... For more Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- goo.gl/lZ6Rs</Msg><Username>fitzgeraldstokes197</Username><Timestamp>1350136743014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350137466771-8</Id><Topic><Title>business genius Mitt says you don't need health insurance. The hospital will pay for you</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349989299427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 17:01:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mittens the bush rerun touts "free" bushcare. "you go to the hospital, you get treated, you get care, and it's paid for, either by charity, the government or by the hospital" Mittens 2012 “I mean, people have access to health care in America,”. “After all, you just go to an emergency room.” w bush 2007</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350137466771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350137703335-9</Id><Title>dear repelicans please explian mitt's miracle cure for medicare</Title><Msg>explain how mitten's miraculous fix of medicare gets paid for: All 55 and older get the full, as is , no changes to, medicare....... and all under age 55 get the same , if they "choose" it over a mitten's voucher.............. so , medicare went from being near broke, to totally fixed , good to go AS IS for EVERYONE.. even those younger than 55 can choose traditional as is medicare as per mitt's promise at the debate......................wow!.......... do the tax cuts pay for it? I guess they will pay for staying in Afghanistan forever and building the romney 600 ship navy or whatever. details please?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350137703335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:15:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350137957344-10</Id><Title>Biden's Drug Problem..</Title><Msg>Was Biden using 'Adderal' during the debates.. The question is being asked becasue he was soooo over the top and in the last 20 minutes of the debate it was like he was 'Coming Down' off the high of druga and draged himself to the close. Very, very dramatic change inb behavior. Not to mention the pure insanity of the specticle that Biden displayed.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350137957344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350137957415-11</Id><Title>Biden's Drug Problem..</Title><Msg>Was Biden using 'Adderal' during the debates.. The question is being asked becasue he was soooo over the top and in the last 20 minutes of the debate it was like he was 'Coming Down' off the high of druga and draged himself to the close. Very, very dramatic change inb behavior. Not to mention the pure insanity of the specticle that Biden displayed.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350137957415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350139669779-12</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can ETFC Last??</Title><Username>fitzgeraldstokes197</Username><Timestamp>1350136743014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this to us.</Msg><Username>tristansnyder851</Username><Timestamp>1350139669779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:47:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350139789291-13</Id><Title>from Tweet Deck</Title><Msg>"Mitt Romney. For people who prefer unplanned wars to planned parenthood." "Mitt Romney hires Bush/Cheney foreign policy advisers and fires American workers. That's all you need to know. " "The only difference between Romney and Bush is Bush only wanted to take your Social Security away."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1350139789291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350143226243-14</Id><Title>GM lives</Title><Msg>Sat Oct 13, 2012 at 07:00 AM PDT Obama salutes success story of auto industry recovery in weekly address by Susan Gardner Just a few years ago, the auto industry wasn’t just struggling – it was flatlining. GM and Chrysler were on the verge of collapse. Suppliers and distributors were at risk of going under. More than a million jobs across the country were on the line – and not just auto jobs, but the jobs of teachers, small business owners, and everyone in communities that depend on this great American industry. But we refused to throw in the towel and do nothing. We refused to let Detroit go bankrupt. We bet on American workers and American ingenuity, and three years later, that bet is paying off in a big way. All hail the American auto industry, the focus of this week's success story in this morning's weekly address by President Obama. Not only was the huge sector saved, but all the ancillary businesses dependent upon and the communities built around it—and all the jobs saved in a cascading effect of rescuing the ailing industry. All this, the president pointed out, was achieved while also fuel standards were raised and trade agreements were put in place to keep American car technology cutting edge and competitive. So next time you see one of those brand new 2013 models on TV or on the lot, think about how far we’ve come together. Think about how – thanks to the hard work and can-do spirit of the American people – more of those cars and trucks are being manufactured by American workers at American companies in communities all across the country. And they’re going to save you more money at the pump. But there's more to it than just this one industry, the president claimed. The lesson learned through dealing with the industry's economic woes is larger than this one instance: That’s what America is all about. When we get knocked down, we get back up. We come back stronger. And as long as I’m President, that’s what we’ll keep doing. Sounds a heck of a lot more positive than the message of gloom and doom Team Romney is trying to sell on the stump. Sat Oct 13, 2012 at 07:00 AM PDT</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350144330689-15</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Accelerated Rate of Movement... How Long can ETFC Last??</Title><Username>fitzgeraldstokes197</Username><Timestamp>1350136743014</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Definitely going to give this post a bump. Great newsletter.</Msg><Username>carrollraymundo473</Username><Timestamp>1350144330689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146335067-16</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paul Ryan wasn't the one who decided to open new embassy in one of the most insecure places of the world with practically no security. Knowingly! There is no justified risk to put unarmed people in the place filled with Al Quaeda operatives without appropriate protection. The cut in funding to embassies over the world has no connection with pure negligence and clear dereliction of duties of people in State Department . Funding is a lame excuse for the people with an IQ even lower than our deranged Joe, the VP.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1350146335067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350148597707-17</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifica, It is you who is deranged. You cannot hold a candle to the VP. Joe Biden has an above average IQ. pacifica, You have been consistandly wrong about most topics in this board, yet you want to criticize the VP of the United States who has never lost an election since 1973.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350148597707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:16:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149613381-18</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden: "Well, we weren’t told they wanted more security again." Biden lied through his teeth about the fact that the administration--specifically, the State Department--had been told again and again that security on the ground in Libya, and in Benghazi in particular, was inadequate. The day before, in Congressional hearings on the Libya attacks, former regional security director Eric Nordstrom described his frustration with having those requests turned down by the government bureaucracy: "For me the Taliban is on the inside of the building." Deranged Joe and you can't handle the truth. Prove me wrong.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1350149613381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:33:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149710999-19</Id><Topic><Title>DUMBO! RESIGN NOW!! (cover up!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348936321730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:32:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 Dead Americans...Dumbo says: 'oh, just bumps in the road" SICK-O!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350149710999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:35:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149916213-20</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Video Lie is changing!! There is actual video from security cameras. Hillary. Rice and Dumbo REFUSE to release! Treason! Punishable by......</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350149916213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350150040636-21</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo (LOSING!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349878195905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 10:09:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden-palooza of SICK-O!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350150040636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153457819-22</Id><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Msg>Editorial: Protecting our diplomats isn't a political game Published: Saturday, Oct. 13, 2012 - 12:00 am | Page 14A In the past, the United States favored openness over fortress walls for its diplomatic facilities around the world. That shifted in a big way in the deadly 1980s, when a number of terrorist attacks occurred during the presidency of Ronald Reagan. And, now, with the attack on the U.S. consular outpost in Benghazi, Libya – killing the U.S. ambassador and three other Americans – Congress and the president should examine diplomatic security anew. The 1980s should provide some perspective for that task. In April 1983, terrorists attacked the U.S. embassy in Beirut, Lebanon, killing 63 people, including 17 Americans. Six months later, terrorists attacked peacekeepers' barracks in Beirut, killing 241 U.S. Marines and 58 French paratroopers. Then in September 1984, terrorists attacked the U.S. Embassy that had moved to East Beirut, killing 23 people, including two Americans. Congress appropriated more funds for diplomatic security and then-Secretary of State George Shultz formed the Inman Commission to make recommendations. The House passed HR 4151, the Omnibus Diplomatic Security and Antiterrorism Act of 1986, on a 389-7 vote, the Senate passed it on a voice vote and President Reagan signed it. Today, unfortunately, what should be a genuine bipartisan effort to #$%$ our needs in Libya and the security climate for our posts around the world has turned into a partisan witch hunt – led by U.S. Reps. Darrell Issa, R-Vista, and Jason Chaffetz, R-Utah. Yes, Regional Security Officer Eric Nordstrom, who testified before Issa's committee on Wednesday, had requested and was denied a 60-day extension through mid-September of temporarily assigned U.S. security professionals and a training team that was building a corps of local Libyan bodyguards. Ambassador Chris Stevens knew the security configuration in Benghazi and he understood the real dangers as well as anyone; other high-level diplomats had been recently attacked. Yet on the 9/11 anniversary, he chose to be in Benghazi, 400 miles from the U.S. Embassy in the capital of Tripoli. Would a handful more U.S. diplomatic security officers have been able to protect the consulate from the attack that killed Stevens and three other Americans? Not according to Nordstrom, who told Issa's committee that "having an extra foot of wall, or an extra-half dozen guards or agents would not have enabled us to respond to that kind of assault." Further, Nordstrom expressed the real issue: "I'm concerned that this attack will signal a new security reality, just as the 1984 Beirut attack did for the Marines; the 1998 East Africa bombings did for the State Department, and 9/11 for the whole country." That is what is being overshadowed in the Issa circus and what our political leaders must address. Our Diplomatic Security Service has been stretched thin providing security to U.S. diplomatic posts in Afghanistan, Pakistan and Iraq. Further, the same House Republicans who are criticizing diplomatic security in Libya, including Republican vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan, have aggressively slashed the budget – cutting the administration's request for embassy security by $128 million in 2011 and $331 million in 2012. House Republicans propose to cut the administration's request for 2013 by $216 million. We cannot assure our diplomats perfect security. As Nordstrom told Issa's committee: "It is critical that we balance the risk-mitigation with the needs of our diplomats to do their job, in dangerous and uncertain places. The answer cannot be to operate from a bunker." He's right. Retreat is not a solution. This is no time for the United States to abandon this fragile country emerging from the Gadhafi dictatorship, leaving a vacuum for extremists to fill.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160210096-23</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The text in "A read for our deranged pacifican" is good enough for me and millions of others.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160210096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160447880-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>read the text in A read for our deranged pacifican54. The security of our embassadors is not a po;itical game.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1350160447880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160654774-25</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bikeq4, your nanny wants you! Your bottle of nerve gas is ready!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160654774</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160654820-26</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bikeq4, your nanny wants you! Your bottle of nerve gas is ready!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160654820</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:37:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160767699-27</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repugnicans start two wars - Americans die!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160767699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:39:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160768435-28</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repugnicans start two wars - Americans die!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160768435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:39:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160829391-29</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your mama says, you're going besirk!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160829391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160829454-30</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your mama says, you're going besirk!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160829454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160829554-31</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your mama says, you're going besirk!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350160829554</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:40:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350161826027-32</Id><Topic><Title>GM lives</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets see, if you bought GM stock at the IPO price of $35, and it is selling today for $24, that would mean you have now lost 31% of your investment...another Obama success story. To boot in the furture GM will need another bailout, they build cars the folks don't want or need.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350161826027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350162407188-33</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bottomline, Obama, Biden and Hillary got those four Americans killed. They are the ones that choose where the security money is to be spend, not congress. You lefties won't ever admit that your beloved Obama screwed up, because that would be admitting that you were conned by the slick car salesman in chief. Just keep repeating to make yourself feel better..."it was the video stupid".</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350162407188</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350163335400-34</Id><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Msg>STOP YOUR LYING ABOUT BENGHAZI FUNDING!!!! Reductions were for requests of a HYPER BLOATED SUPER INCREASED funding!! Here are the numbers you A.I.D.S. infected #$%$: Funding shot up 50% Under Dumbo/Hillary/Rice Criminal gang: The Heritage Foundation pulls the numbers for “worldwide security protection,” the budget for which went from $1.18 billion in 2008 (out of about $35 billion for the State Department and “other international programs”) to $1.59 billion in 2010 (out of about $52) before dropping to just under $1.5 billion in 2011. The Heritage Foundation explains: Comparing FY 2011 actual funding versus the FY 2012 estimate, there appears to be a reduction in Worldwide Security Protection and Embassy Security, Construction and Maintenance. But that reduction does not account for additional funding in FY 2012 from Overseas Contingency Operations funds amounting to $236 million for Worldwide Security Protection (p. 63) and $33 million for Embassy Security, Construction and Maintenance (p. 467)... Together, there is a net increase.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350165075584-35</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegals need healfcare, welfare recipients need their ebt cards reloaded along with their obamaphones. Not unlike Leon --- Barry caint do it all--- After all how many votes can he buy protected a few US diplomats compared to the mileage he gets handing out free stuff to his idiot base.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350165075584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350165213521-36</Id><Topic><Title>Embassy Funding SUPER Lie!! (Typical Liberal #$%$!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350163335400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:22:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary needs to fund the extra vaseline needed for her Moosleem Sista'Hood pooosy licker: HUMA!!! Yeah, no breach of security there!! Yeah, SURE!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350165213521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350165492472-37</Id><Title>Sensata scandal to destroy Romney</Title><Msg>"This story is very damning to Mitt Romney and even worse, for the employees of Sensata Tech and every working class American if Romney wins. Romney's Bain Capital did what they do best. They bought out a company called Sensata Tech and are in the process of outsourcing it to China. They even brought in Chinese workers for the current employees to train. Yea, they were forced to train their own replacements. And Bain Capital forced the company to take down their American flag and put up a Chinese flag while they trained them. A Chinese flag was flying over a Bain-owned factory in Freeport, Illinois. This is our economy if Romney wins. Please don't take my word for it, read for yourself below. This story needs to get out for the sake of this election and for the workers camping out in protest of their jobs being outsourced. Oh.. and the company is set to to close on November 5th, one day before the election."</Msg><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350165492472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166036012-38</Id><Topic><Title>Sensata scandal to destroy Romney</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350165492472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:58:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Am I the only one who is detecting a note of desperation in your recent posts junglebob? It's crunch-time in the battleground states and mittens is going balls to the wall wif his television ads. He will outspend Brak -- hammer him when he's down-- 2 to 1 in these final weeks. Brak did the best he could, bought all the votes you could humanly expect. But it's time for him to face the music and quietly slink away.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1350166036012</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:07:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166252982-39</Id><Topic><Title>house gop admits they cut funding for embassy security since winning the majority in 2010.</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1350068696959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:04:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey pus times eight.....they didn't figure your type in the security circle.............ya friggin liberal benedict arnold lookin muter fusay</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350166252982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:10:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166667024-40</Id><Topic><Title>GM lives</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why waste your time trying to teach these odumbomites simple math...........they are creatures of convenience..........making things happen is incomprehensible to them..........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350166667024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350166994047-41</Id><Topic><Title>GM lives</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>omg.....let the propaganda reign.......gm has been jap slapped for years korea is even kicken their #$%$zz.............you know why????...because of you ...and the many aswipes like you....................</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350166994047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350168352499-42</Id><Title>jbeast...take a strong sook out of my pub aszzz......and enjoy it..........fakkot bwawny fwank lookin mfr</Title><Msg>heheheheheheh...bwaaaaaaaahahaahaheheehe...</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350168352499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:45:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350168376828-43</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Win, lose, or draw his behavior was borderline creepy, if not loney. If you think that kind of behavior is normal during a presidential debate you need to go back to the Elks Lodge for a couple more pops.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1350168376828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:46:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350168731392-44</Id><Title>this message board is....like</Title><Msg>fked up to the nth degree....run by a bunch of nymph rookies.......frigggin odumbomite types........romney will have this chit straightened out come january...put more of those idiot odumbomites in the soup line....we can afford to feed those idiots....just got to reign them in...........</Msg><Username>f4rest_gump</Username><Timestamp>1350168731392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:52:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350169375919-45</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>got ta be a mosse dik...........mammal member...head is stuck in the vaginal canal.</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350169375919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350170828599-46</Id><Title>Not a single comment on the short attack setup last week??</Title><Msg>I mean, it was textbook: Negative resuters article planted on cure, hit the bid at the open on Friday. Read the article; nothing but the same factors in place for the last 4 years or so.</Msg><Username>low_life_neutral</Username><Timestamp>1350170828599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350171937434-47</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidder needs to stop sniffing the chickencrap in his hood.</Msg><Username>hobojim4</Username><Timestamp>1350171937434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350171975204-48</Id><Title>Hey odumbomites</Title><Msg>Whatcha all think about your dear leader after the debate...is he not a clueless azzhatt...lolololol....</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350171975204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:46:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172411048-49</Id><Topic><Title>from Tweet Deck</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1350139789291</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:49:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your dear general wants to take the peoples choices away.....we eat ramen noodles and drink grape koolaid with you...friiggin azzhat</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350172411048</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:53:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172909281-50</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biden is the friggin taper on the end of a turd</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350172909281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:01:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172994482-51</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Disrepects Americans!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1350041990226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 07:39:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>his job is to keep the anal canal from slamming shut....other than that..he's useless.......</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350172994482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:03:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350173079686-52</Id><Topic><Title>Not a single comment on the short attack setup last week??</Title><Username>low_life_neutral</Username><Timestamp>1350170828599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JPM had great results and it sold off. In fact, all financials sold off Friday. I must admit I was surprised since it had held up so well on thurs when the market was tanking. Notice WFC added 200 mill back due to decreased write-offs. Our loan portfoilio hit bottom about a year ago so I expect ETFC to do very well in the future. Maybe enough for the regulators to lighten up.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1350173079686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350174742362-53</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Lies, Ambassadors DIE!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349876283628</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-10 09:38:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey bami...yer keys sperm locked or what you sick #$%$..</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350174742362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:32:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350175397265-54</Id><Title>is bammy not a derelict</Title><Msg>didn't the debate make that clear....lolololol</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350175397265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:43:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179078108-55</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike and his pubs are fearful of your post A read for our deranged pacifican54.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350179078108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179078120-56</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike and his pubs are fearful of your post A read for our deranged pacifican54.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350179078120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179078122-57</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>qbike and his pubs are fearful of your post A read for our deranged pacifican54.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350179078122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179325673-58</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is that bigmouth coward qbike4?</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350179325673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350179723646-59</Id><Topic><Title>GM lives</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biddermom, Why are there so many new GM cars and pickups on our roads and freeways???</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1350179723646</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 21:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180251403-60</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think slayer is q4bike.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350180251403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:04:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180252235-61</Id><Topic><Title>A read for our deranged pacifican54</Title><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1350153457819</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think slayer is q4bike.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1350180252235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350180597516-62</Id><Topic><Title>is bammy not a derelict</Title><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1350175397265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:43:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>retunusignoramus, There is always a sercond time.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1350180597516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350182959508-63</Id><Title>General Motors is Alive, and Osama is Dead</Title><Msg>Republicans hate both of those facts Anti American slime</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1350182959508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:49:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350183155922-64</Id><Topic><Title>GM lives</Title><Username>fritzinacrotchlesstutu</Username><Timestamp>1350143226243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:47:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey you old fart, the only reason yer still here is because you bought ET at $20. Your opinions are as useless as yer balls.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1350183155922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>