<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-15"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352994168785-1</Id><Topic><Title>Watch This</Title><Username>amelieboaz919</Username><Timestamp>1308194608000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2011-06-15 23:23:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great call!</Msg><Username>sarahsmithm268</Username><Timestamp>1352994168785</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 10:42:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353005889303-2</Id><Title>OMG, could this be true</Title><Msg>Folks in these states are dumb as dirt clods. **jobless claims were said to be declining, with the media proclaiming that they had reached the "lowest level in more than four years** Surprise! Jobless Claims Up 78,000 Week After Election; PA, OH Worst Hit The Department of Labor has announced that new jobless claims rose by a staggering 78,000 in the first week after the election, reaching a seasonally-adjusted total of 439,000. Over the past year, and in the weeks leading up to the election, jobless claims were said to be declining, dipping as low as 339,000, with the media proclaiming that they had reached the "lowest level in more than four years." Now, suddenly, the news seems far less rosy. From the Department of Labor press release this morning: In the week ending November 10, the advance figure for seasonally adjusted initial claims was 439,000, an increase of 78,000 from the previous week's revised figure of 361,000. The 4-week moving average was 383,750, an increase of 11,750 from the previous week's revised average of 372,000.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1353005889303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 13:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353031236773-3</Id><Title>Time to Put the Post Office Out of Our Misery!...</Title><Msg>It just reported a $16 BILLION LOSS! WASHINGTON -- The struggling U.S. Postal Service is reporting a record annual loss of $15.9 billion. The financial losses for the fiscal year ending Sept. 30 were nearly $11 billion more than the previous year. The numbers cap a tumultuous financial year in which the post office was forced for the first time to default on more than $11 billion in payments to avert bankruptcy. The mail agency for months has been urging Congress to pass an overhaul bill to let it trim letter delivery to five days a week and reduce annual payments for future retiree health care. Postmaster General Patrick Donahoe says the large losses cannot be sustained. The mail agency forecasts billions in additional losses next year as it awaits financial relief from Congress.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1353031236773</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-15 21:00:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>