<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349582647685-1</Id><Title>If America goes to War again, will Mitt Turn French again ???</Title><Msg>Mittens proved he had no balls when he escaped to France during Nam. No balls, and no patriotism for America. Hell, he's Mexican.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349582647685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349585066294-2</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney leading in Florida, Virginia</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349456523352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 13:02:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>vs. tax cuts for the rich... c'mon...</Msg><Username>prez_obama_4_more_yrs</Username><Timestamp>1349585066294</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:44:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349615137122-3</Id><Title>gop leader said slavery is a blessing...another gop leader said earth is 9000 years old &amp; Mitt said pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan.”</Title><Msg>why are republicans often such ignorant and stupid liars and bigots? ... Republicans tried to distance themselves Saturday from a Republican state representative’s assertion that slavery was a “blessing in disguise” and a Republican state House candidate who advocates deporting all Muslims. The claims were made in books written, respectively, by Rep. Jon Hubbard of Jonesboro and House candidate Charlie Fuqua of Batesville. The books received attention on Internet news sites Friday. Mitt Romney in Wednesday’s debate: “pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan.” .............No, they aren’t.........it's just a mittens lie. “I don’t believe that the Earth’s but about 9,000 years old" Rep. Paul Broun (R-GA):</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349615137122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349615527850-4</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens was "100% full of sh__t from the opening bell"</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349557048451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mittens lied by saying his healthcare plan covers preexisting conditions........it doesn't and Mittens promise that medicare stays the same for all over age 55..... and even all younger if they "choose" it over his voucher......... seems a bit of a stretch........ how can medicare go from being near broke to good to go, as is, the next day...... Mitt has no details how that works....... paid for by tax cuts? or more likely it is just a bll #$%$ lie , like the one about preexisting conditions.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349615527850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349616327285-5</Id><Title>gop leader compared women to farm livestock....</Title><Msg>if farmers have to “deliver calves, dead or alive,” then a woman carrying a dead fetus, or one not expected to survive, should have to carry it to term. Rep. Terry England (R-Auburn)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349616327285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:25:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349623498770-6</Id><Title>The terd starts it's final swirl around the rim</Title><Msg>The emperor will, once again, be shown to be donning no apparel ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Rumors Swirl: How Bad Will The Obama Foreign Donor Scandal Be? Katie Pavlich News Editor, Townhall Oct 07, 2012 08:00 AM EST Since last week, the news sphere has been buzzing about the possibility of an Obama campaign foreign donor scandal being the big October surprise of 2012. Since the Washington Examiner first reported the story last week, many are asking how the Obama campaign will handle foreign donation allegations expected to go public Monday in a major magazine and national website story. The Obama campaign has already tried to block the story from publication and although the details of the scandal are still under wraps, we do know taxes and unsecured credit card transactions are about to cause a major headache for the Obama campaign. Just yesterday, we received news the Obama campaign raised a whopping $181 million in September alone, pulling the question of foreign donations even closer to the surface and putting Obama closer than ever to reaching a $1 billion fundraising number. U.S. President Barack Obama's campaign and the Democratic Party have raised $181 million in September for his re-election effort - their highest monthly total yet of the 2012 presidential race. The president's campaign said Saturday that the money represents donations from more than 1.8 million people. Stay tuned.....the story could come as early as Sunday night, rather than Monday morning as originally planned.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349623498770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349623677114-7</Id><Topic><Title>7.8% ........... 7.8% ............. LOL !</Title><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1349450017379</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 11:13:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ask the President. He said it during debate, we didn't raise tax on millionaires and billionaires. He literally thinks that's going to help corporations to hire more. The answer for Americans with room temperature IQ.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349623677114</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:27:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349627065735-8</Id><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Msg>W's 1st budget ...$1.9 trillion W's last budget....$3.2 trillion obama's 1st....$3.2 trillion ...............2012..$3.6 trillion kinda obvious who did the bigger increase of spending, isn't it? the increase in federal spending under Obama is dwarfed by the colossal increase under President Bush. Don't believe it? Let's go to the chart. Here's Federal Expenditures from 2000-2011 (quarterly figures, annualized), from the St. Louis Fed: As you can see, from 2000 to 2008, under President Bush, Federal spending rose by $1.3 trillion, from $1.9 trillion a year to $3.2 trillion a year. From 2009 to 2011, meanwhile, under President Obama, federal spending has risen by $600 billion, from $3.2 trillion a year to $3.8 trillion a year. It has also now begun to decline. ($3.59 trillion for 2012) In other words, federal government spending under President Bush increased 2X as much as it has under President Obama.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349629278244-9</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Earnings (off topic)</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1349476364284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who peed in your cheerios? You can't argue that the RS was a bad thing; it had to be done. Pssssst: the provision this quarter will be $53 million, down $14 million from last quarter. With a few other cost reductions, EPS will be .17. take that to the bank.</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1349629278244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:01:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629436899-10</Id><Title>In 1936, FDR foreshadowed today's GOP and their subversive tactics</Title><Msg>"For nearly four years you have had an Administration which instead of twirling its thumbs has rolled up its sleeves. We will keep our sleeves rolled up. We had to struggle with the old enemies of peace: business and financial monopoly, speculation, reckless banking, class antagonism, sectionalism, war profiteering. They had begun to consider the Government of the United States as a mere appendage to their own affairs. We know now that Government by organized money is just as dangerous as Government by organized mob. Never before in all our history have these forces been so united against one candidate as they stand today. They are unanimous in their hate for me, and I welcome their hatred." It's like it could've been written for today, not 76 years ago. It's saddening that 80 years have gone by, and still the same dangers plague the nation, and the world.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349629436899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629746333-11</Id><Title>Newt confirms the Dipshidiot lies</Title><Msg>"Oct 7, 2012 at 9:51 am This morning on Meet The Press, Obama campaign adviser Robert Gibbs confronted Newt Gingrich on a fundamental inconsistency in Romney’s description of his tax plan. During the primary debates, Romney insisted that everyone in America would get a 20% tax cut, including the 1%. But last week’s during his debate with Obama, Romney insisted that his tax cut would not reduce taxes at all for wealthy Americans. Gingrich acknowledged the clear inconsistency, saying “I think it’s clear he changed.” He described the change as “good politics.”</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349629746333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349630492040-12</Id><Title>Romney Debate called "Fundamentally Dishonest"</Title><Msg>Everyone agrees. WASHINGTON -- Former White House spokesman Robert Gibbs on Sunday lit into Mitt Romney's recent debate performance, calling the Republican presidential nominee's claims "fundamentally dishonest" and "absolutely crazy." "The underpinnings and foundations of that performance were fundamentally dishonest," Gibbs said on ABC's "This Week with George Stephanopoulos." "He walked away from the central tenet of his economic theory by saying he had no idea what the president was talking about. Ten minutes after the debate, even his own staff is walking back his answers on health care and preexisting conditions." Pubs have to lie there way into office.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1349630492040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:21:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349631673749-13</Id><Title>22% of deficit is W's tax cuts. .so before the gop throws another debt ceiling tantrum consider that</Title><Msg>....The Congressional Budget Office has calculated that........expiration of the Bush tax cuts....would reduce the deficit by $221 billion. ...... the components of the fiscal cliff from smallest to largest. As you can see, the expiring Bush-era tax cuts are by far the biggest component, totaling $221 billion. By comparison, the sequester would save $65 billion.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349631673749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349633407910-14</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Earnings (off topic)</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1349476364284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, 14 mill and they estimate the cost to terminate Frieberg to be $13 mill. As the previous poster mentioned, not much to see here on the surface. However, never bet against Kenny. I think the loan elimination or refinance will give us the kick start we need. I also would not be surprised to see some of the loan balance sold off to quiet many of the critics.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1349633407910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349634328084-15</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Earnings (off topic)</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1349476364284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 18:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EPS this quarter will be pretty bad, i'm guessing .03 with Frieburg expense thrown in, .07 otherwise.. NIM still has a couple quarters left to drop and trading was just awful this quarter.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1349634328084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349637401426-16</Id><Title>Dipshidiot insults another U.S. ally!!</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- If Mitt Romney becomes president, he might need a crash course in Diplomacy 101. He irritated Britons and Palestinians during a summer tour abroad and has declared Russia to be America's No. 1 geopolitical foe. Just last week, the Republican candidate, who plans a foreign policy speech Monday, raised eyebrows in Spain by holding it up as a prime example of government spending run amok. That left Spaniards confused, and threatened to reinforce Romney's perceived handicap in international affairs, precisely at a time when lingering questions over the Sept. 11 attacks against the U.S. Consulate in Benghazi, Libya, has President Barack Obama on the defensive. "I don't want to go down the path of Spain," Romney said Wednesday night during the first presidential debate. He argued that government spending under Obama has reached 42 percent of the U.S. economy, a figure comparable with America's NATO ally. "I want to go down the path of growth that puts Americans to work." The remark was Romney's latest to cause international offense during a campaign that much of the world is closely monitoring. The sensitivity reflects a wide understanding that Romney could prevail over President Barack Obama and take over as leader of the world's top military, economic and diplomatic power. If Romney becomes commander in chief, he could face a testy beginning with Europe's economic laggards such as Greece, Italy and Spain, whom he has beaten up regularly throughout the campaign. No one contests that Spain's situation is dire, its economy in deep recession and unemployment hovering around 25 percent. But Spain's level of government spending is actually low by European standards, and significantly less than Germany and Scandinavian countries with far healthier economic prospects. Spain's woes were chiefly caused by the collapse of a property bubble that had fueled more than a decade of booming economic growth. Spanish reaction to Romney was swift. "What I see is ignorance of what is reality, but especially of the potential of the Spanish economy," said Deputy Prime Minister Soraya Saenz de Santamaria. Maria Dolores Cospedal, leader of Spanish Prime Minister Mariano Rajoy's Popular Party, noted that "Spain is not on fire from all sides like some on the outside have suggested." Foreign Minister Jose Manuel Garcia Margallo called it "very unfortunate that other countries should be put up as examples" when the facts are skewed. The criticism comes at an inopportune time for Romney. Obama has consistently outscored his challenger in polls asking about national security leadership, but the administration is struggling to deal with last month's attack on the consulate. Four Americans died, including the first ambassador killed in the line of duty in more than three decades. Romney will have a chance to fully articulate his vision of America's role in world affairs when gives his address Monday at the Virginia Military Institute. But the furor in Spain, however minor, instead serves as a reminder of Romney's record of diplomatic stumbles, such as calling Russia – not Iran or China, for example – America's primary global adversary in March. Russian President Vladimir Putin has since pointed to Romney's comment as justification for Russia's opposition to America's missile defense plans in Europe, saying the statement has "strengthened Russia's positions in talks on this important and sensitive subject." Then on a July trip to Europe and Israel meant to burnish Romney's foreign policy credentials, the candidate criticized Britain over its preparations for the London Olympic Games. The comment baffled America's closest ally, drawing withering retorts from the British press, the Conservative prime minister and London's right-wing mayor. He also cited a private meeting with Britain's spy service MI6, in a significant breach of protocol. In Israel, he followed up by declaring Jerusalem the capital of the Jewish state, which U.S. administrations have refused to accept for decades given Palestinian claims to the ancient city. At a gathering of mostly American Jewish donors, Romney implied that Israel was more advanced than the Palestinians because of cultural superiority. The comment drew a charge of racism from the Palestinians' chief peace negotiator, with whom the U.S. has been working to reach a two-state peace deal with Israel and counter the threat posed by Hamas, the Palestinian militant group that rejects Israel's existence.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349637401426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 15:16:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349643791604-17</Id><Title>Is this true?</Title><Msg>Troy Dem Officials' Home Used For Underage Sex Romp: Cops The FBI is reportedly investigating the existence of a child pornography operation in connection with the arrest of an official from the Troy Democrats who lives with a veteran Joliet reporter. By Joseph Hosey October 5, 2012 A Troy Township Democratic official was charged with setting up a sex date with a 15-year-old boy and federal agents searched her house on suspicion she has been producing child pornography videos, police said. Margarita Hernandez, 32, of 6901 Monmouth Drive on Joliet's far west side, was arrested about 3 p.m. Thursday and taken to the Will County jail on a warrant charging her with two counts of aggravated criminal sexual abuse. Hernandez had sex with a 15-year-old Chicago boy during a prearranged July meeting at her home, police said.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349643791604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:03:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349644014063-18</Id><Topic><Title>Study: Free Birth Control Access Dramatically Decreases Abortion Rates</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349546338044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 13:58:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't mind helping a woman out with birth control costs. I don't even mind paying for all of it. But not if I'm not having sex with her! Let her partner help her out.</Msg><Username>a.completeunknown</Username><Timestamp>1349644014063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:06:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349646657719-19</Id><Title>gop leader compares women to farm livestock</Title><Msg>if farmers have to “deliver calves, dead or alive,” then a woman carrying a dead fetus, or one not expected to survive, should have to carry it to term. Rep. Terry England (R-</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349646657719</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647110558-20</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George W Bush was in power for 8 years. Not 3. His budget for 2009 was $3.1T. He balooned budget $150B a year. Obama's 2012 budget request (3rd one)contained $3.729 trillion in expenditures. Republican budget request for 2012 contained $3.529T in expenditures. Stop distorting facts!!! In 3 years period budget increase was around $200B a year. 2013 proposed budget is $3.8T. In 4 years period budget increase is $175B a year. Now, Bush's budget deficit was never above $450. Obama's deficit is more than twice larger. So, while the revenue to the government decreased signifficantly, Obama continues to increase spending. Again, Bush added $5.5T in 8 years. Obama managed to beat this number in less than 4. Simpson-Bowles anyone? Oh, that's history trash.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349647110558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:58:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648535399-21</Id><Topic><Title>Within next 10 trading days, ETFC can collapse to $7s. Be prepare!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349577835827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 22:43:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With all the respect you are an idiot. The earnings will be good, because the expectations are very low with all that low trading activity. ETFC will NEVER trade below 8 if Israel will not attack Iran. If Israel go to kick Iran's #$%$ all stock will trade 20% down the first day and another 10% down the second day after the attack. I did not sell any ETFC shares last Thursday or Friday. ETFC will go to break the magic 10 bucks per share now. All my opinions.</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349648535399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:22:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648760672-22</Id><Topic><Title>10000 ETFC at 9.13 Long and Strong</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349526113473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr President lost big time. He was not pepared at all for the debate and for the presidency. He did not learn on the job unfortunately for all of us. My opinions</Msg><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349648760672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349650785775-23</Id><Topic><Title>Mittens was "100% full of sh__t from the opening bell"</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349557048451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:57:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sore loser!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349650785775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:59:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349650855897-24</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Debate called "Fundamentally Dishonest"</Title><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1349630492040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:21:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sore loser!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349650855897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:00:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349652283711-25</Id><Title>Dipshidiot, the living, breathing "liar loan"</Title><Msg>"What Mitt Romney and Liar Loans Have in Common (Be Very Afraid) Posted: 10/05/2012 5:32 pm As I watched Governor Romney in the Presidential debate Wednesday night I was reminded of a financial tactic the candidate's political supporters and financial backers on Wall Street used during the mortgage boom--the one that netted them billions of dollars while simultaneously pushing the American economy off a cliff. I'm talking about the liar loan, a line of credit based on smiling assertions without a shred of proof--the practice that helped flatten the mortgage market and gut the U.S. economy. This time around, though, the Governor was manipulating the truth not to score some jumbo re-fi deal (after all this is a man who could buy the White House outright), but to gain access to the U.S. Treasury and all the mechanisms of American fiscal and monetary policy. The loan he's looking for would be a four-to-eight-year instrument--one that would allow the nation's wealthiest Goldman Sachs-types to resume the looting of America that came to a screeching halt (or at least slowed dramatically) when President Obama took office. Governor Romney's performance at Wednesday night's debate was solid. The pundits (even the true believers at MSNBC) said he won. The polls were a mixed bag. But it doesn't matter, really. What does matter is the extreme makeover Romney pulled off in the blink of an eye. Gone was the right-wing rabble-rouser who dissed 47% of the country. Gone was the Wall Street darling who promised to gut consumer protections and give huge tax breaks to the wealthiest among us. The new, politically improved Mitt Romney leveled a condescending gaze at the president and morphed into a pro-business, anti-Muppet moderate. What are we to make of the fact that within 24 hours of the debate, the Governor told Fox News he had been "completely wrong" about that 47% comment in the video exposed by Mother Jones--you know, the one for which he refused to apologize two weeks ago? How should we read the fact that, in the time it takes for a hummingbird to flap its wings, Romney disowned his cronyistic $5 trillion tax cut for his friends and colleagues? The retooled Romney who showed up at the debate was suddenly passionate about regulating big business--and even claimed that a nouveau "Romneycare" would, lo and behold, cover pre-existing conditions. His campaign later said Romney had misspoken on this last point; still, it's amazing they didn't just shoot him with a tranquilizer gun as they watched him disavow the GOP platform, plank by plank, in the course of his supposed "big win." Governor Romney's debate appearance was a classic bait-and-switch. For a riveting ninety minutes, he dangled the bait of moderation--vague, smiling words about business-friendly regulation and blue-sky economic recovery, unburdened by any indication of how he would get it done. Not the worst way to divert attention from everything he's said over the past few years to clinch the Republican Party's nomination--a list that includes aggressive deregulation of Wall Street, tax cuts for the wealthiest few, and cuts and privatization for the programs upon which millions of Americans depend, such as Social Security and Medicare. And, of course, the deficit's linchpin: Sesame Street. Which brings us to the switch--the scam that could make this the biggest liar loan America has ever seen. Also referred to as no-document or stated-income loans, liar loans were mortgages in which borrowers promised to tell the truth about how much they earned and owed. It was virtually an invitation to lie, and people did--many of them eagerly and egregiously. They told the story everyone (banks, credit unions, home builders, even government bureaucrats) wanted to hear, and everyone quietly agreed not to call them on it--or at least not until it was too late. When the crisis came and people at the Texas Hold 'em were "called" to show their hands after the last deal, their losses slammed into the American economy like a tsunami. Now, when it comes to bluffing, it's clear we have a match. (Rolling Stone has provided the top five lies Romney told here.) The main difference is that while many people used liar loans to bootstrap their way into homes they couldn't afford, Governor Romney is trying to bootstrap his way into a job he is neither qualified nor trustworthy enough to do. But this time, Wall Street could be in line for a payout the likes of which the world has never seen--and, once again, the American people would be footing the bill. Much of the blame for the liar loan's failure has been placed on the shoulders of greedy homebuyers, and rightfully so. But what about the Wall Street bankers who created the moral hazard of those loans in the first place? They were also responsible for the bait-and-switch at the institutional level with their mortgage-backed securities--and they profited enormously. It was Wall Street insiders who ratcheted down their own banks' lending rules to make liar loans possible, Wall Street insiders who lent the money, Wall Street insiders who used captured regulators to prevent states from protecting their citizens. Using tricks like super-low "teaser" interest rates, balloon payments, and indecipherable exotic mortgages, the inside guys conned millions of Americans into buying homes they couldn't actually afford. And unlike many of those homebuyers, who lost everything to foreclosure and bankruptcy, the mortgage mavens on Wall Street made out like "The Hole in the Wall Gang." They and their colleagues in financial services reaped billions of dollars in fees from selling the loans, servicing the mortgages, and foreclosing (even when other alternatives would have better served the consumer and the economy) when the loans inevitably failed. The liar loan was the ultimate con, a gigantic bait-and-switch--one that left the entire nation on the hook for a painful period of unemployment and an excruciatingly difficult economic recovery. Mitt Romney's performance in the first debate was, in my view, a con structured on exactly the same lines--one where he works both sides of the deal and leaving the American people holding the bag. Romney, Adelson, the Koch boys, and others equally clever but less public don't just want to loot the Treasury. They want to empty the pockets of Americans like you and me. To do it effectively, Romney's got a no-doc approach: "I'll tell you later." That's his mantra. We can safely assume that his version of a balloon payment will involve cutting taxes for the rich, which will blow a $5 trillion hole in the federal budget. His deceptively low teaser rate is repealing "Obamacare," which will add another $109 billion to the federal budget deficit. His idea of an exotic mortgage: destroy Medicare, costing senior citizens $3.9 billion extra on prescription drugs alone. But the Governor's debate performance also showed that he understands how important it is to keep those facts hidden. The most deceptive thing about this latest Etch-a-Sketch version of Mitt Romney, and the scariest, is not that he avoided talking about the various impacts of his radical policy proposals. It's that he denied proposing them at all. "I don't have a $5 trillion tax cut," Romney said during the debate. "I don't have a tax cut of a scale that you're talking about." Or does he? Like all good financial instruments designed to dupe consumers (somewhat less common in the wake of Dodd-Frank and the advent of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau) the most important details are buried in the wee words; in this case Romney's own campaign's website, which says he will "make [a] permanent, across-the-board 20 percent cut in marginal rates," costing the government $456 billion a year, or $5 trillion over the next decade. The "contrast" here is more conventionally called "a lie." Romney's bait-and-switch is, of course, about money and power. But instead of the keys to your house (or in addition to them), he wants the keys to the White House. And he needs those keys because with them he can repeal the Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform Act, which regulates predatory practices heretofore either unregulated or under-regulated and requires lenders of all stripes to be transparent and open about the terms they're promising. If that happens, the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau will be roadkill on the conservative superhighway. There will be no more peering behind the smoke-and-mirrors of Wall Street to protect consumers from getting conned. It will be all con, all the time. Since the beginning, Romney has said one thing to his insider friends and another (and another and another) to the millions of American people who are his yellow brick road to the Presidency. To him, transparency is anathema. Snowing your marks with glittering platitudes of bipartisanship while stuffing anti-consumer plans into the fine print and stacking the deck with debunked conservative radicals is simply what he must do to make the sale. And it's all about the sale. America has been conned by liar loans once already. Now there's another financial wiz at the door, proposing to mortgage America's future for massive short-term gain. Let him knock. Let him lie. Let him huff and puff. Let's show him how hard it is to blow down the brick house--sturdier by the day--that the President and the American people have begun to rebuild." Follow Adam Levin</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349652283711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349653516160-26</Id><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Msg>Just look around..you can't miss them...Loser Lefties!! Throwing around; Romney lies.. Ah let me see... 1- Fox Lies 2- Bush Lies 3- Palin lies 4- Tea party lies 5- Ryan lies 6- Limbaugh lies 7- Koch Brothers lie PLEEEZ keep it up, because each time you say that ROMNEY's Poll numbers RISE OHHH this month is going to be great! President Romney will lead this us Back to Greratness!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349656697453-27</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT RETELLING THE BUSH LIES</Title><Msg>Does Romney’s Promise That His Tax Cuts Won’t Benefit The Rich Sound Familiar? George W. Bush Said The Same Thing By Travis Waldron on Oct 4, 2012 at 2:34 pm Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney’s tax plan would be a boon for the wealthiest Americans, a fact Romney himself admitted in GOP primary debates. Now, though, Romney has decided that cutting taxes for the rich isn’t what his plan will do, and he insists that he won’t support any tax plan — even his own, apparently — that provides the rich with a massive tax cut. “I will not reduce the taxes paid by high-income Americans,” Romney said in last night’s presidential debate. The last Republican president used a similar argument to sell his tax proposal when he was running for election. At a debate on October 3, 2000, George W. Bush made the exact same claim, telling debate moderator Jim Lehrer that once his tax plan became law, “the wealthiest of Americans” would “pay more taxes”: BUSH: Let me tell you what the facts are. The facts are, after my plan, the wealthiest of Americans pay more taxes on the percentage of the whole than they do today. Secondly, if you’re a family of four making $50,000 in Massachusetts, you get a 50% tax cut. Watch it: Bush’s tax cuts eventually became law, and as a result, the wealthy got a massive tax cut. In addition to rate cuts on income taxes, the Bush tax cuts included cuts to the capital gains rate and other investment taxes and an estate tax cut, all of which largely benefit the rich. The plan came at a cost of $2.5 trillion over its first decade. And while Bush was technically correct that the rich did “pay more taxes on the percentage of the whole,” that is “a useless measure of tax progressivity,” as Center for American Progress Director of Tax and Budget Policy Michael Linden has explained. The share of taxes paid by the wealthy grew by 25 percent under Bush, but their share of income grew by 30 percent, evidence that they actually got a massive tax cut. Bush’s promise, just like Romney’s, is a vague misdirection meant to distract from the overall tax cut he planned to provide. Romney’s plan, at a cost of nearly $5 trillion, is even bigger. And though Romney at least says he will cover some of the cost, the closure of loopholes wouldn’t offset the cuts for the rich, and to avoid adding to the deficit, he would have to raise taxes on the middle class. Romney relies on another similar argument Bush used, insisting that economic growth will offset the remaining costs. But the Bush tax cuts were followed by years of tepid job and economic growth that blew a massive hole in the federal budget and left Bush flailing when it came to his promise to pay off the national debt in a decade. A Republican National Committee spokesperson earlier this year said that Romney’s economic policies would be “Bush, just updated.” It turns out his arguments are too.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349656697453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349657222151-28</Id><Title>Welch weasels out</Title><Msg>Jack Welch Denies Referencing White House In Jobs Report Conspiracy Theory Claim The Huffington Post | By Bonnie Kavoussi Posted: 10/07/2012 7:05 pm EDT Former General Electric CEO Jack Welch denied on Sunday that he had accused the White House of manipulating the September jobs report to help President Barack Obama's reelection chances. "Have never commented on White House in any tweets I can recall," Welch tweeted on Sunday. Jack Welch @jack_welch Jack Welch Have never commented on White House in any tweets I can recall October 7, 2012 9:19 pm via web Reply Retweet Favorite Welch sparked a firestorm on Friday when he accused "Chicago guys" of manipulating the September jobs report. "Unbelievable jobs numbers..these Chicago guys will do anything..can't debate so change numbers," he tweeted Friday morning. Obama had debated Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney two days prior, in a performance that was widely panned. A number of prominent conservatives echoed Welch's conspiracy theory claims after the Bureau of Labor Statistics reported that the unemployment rate had fallen to 7.8 percent in September, the lowest level since Obama took office. In fact, it would be effectively impossible for anyone with political motives to manipulate the jobs report, since government analysts use long-established statistical methods to arrive at the jobs numbers each month.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349657222151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:47:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658760472-29</Id><Title>Nevada Gets It</Title><Msg>No state had a bigger stake in Wednesday's presidential debate than Nevada. No other state has suffered more economic hardship over the past five years. No state has a greater need for jobs than Nevada, which leads the nation with a real unemployment rate of at least 22 percent. No state will benefit more from a real economic recovery. Nevada is one of a handful of swing states that will decide which man wins the White House one month from now. But Nevadans' impressions of Democratic President Barack Obama and Republican nominee Mitt Romney have been driven largely by negative advertising and stump speeches. Wednesday's debate marked the first time voters saw the men present, defend and contrast their ideas for how to grow the American economy and manage the executive branch of the federal government. Which man's leadership is more likely to spur investment in businesses and encourage companies to hire? On Wednesday night, Nevadans watched Mr. Romney trounce the president. The evidence Mr. Romney systematically laid out exposed how the president's top-down interventions have virtually paralyzed our economy - and he presented a solution. Nevadans need a president with a vision and political philosophy capable of restoring ingenuity, competition and excellence to our education and health care systems, of paring back the budget deficit and the explosive growth of our debt, of keeping energy affordable, of bringing back jobs and prosperity not just here, but in every American city with residents who want enough economic security to be able to take a Las Vegas vacation. The answer is pro-growth tax and regulatory reform. The answer is tax and regulatory certainty for businesses. The answer is growing our way out of the budget deficit with a broader, simpler tax base and reduced rates and deductions for all - especially the risk-taker, the job creator and the entrepreneur. More jobs equals more taxpayers. Mr. Obama has a much different recipe for lifting the middle class: higher taxes on investors, job creators and small businesses; borrowing money to fund more public-sector jobs and government construction projects; borrowing money to fund more green energy enterprises and projects, which make electricity more expensive, while limiting the oil and coal industries; and pushing more young people to seek a debt-funded college education when they have little hope of landing a job upon graduation. The suggestion that tax increases and higher energy prices will lift the middle class defies logic. But it's not terribly surprising coming from an administration that's completely lacking in business experience and openly hostile to free-market capitalism. This summer, the president famously said "the private sector is doing fine," and to business owners: "You didn't build that." In a second Obama term, the national debt would soar past $20 trillion. And Mr. Obama has no plan to address the crushing future costs of Medicare and Social Security. Mr. Obama has never been the uniting agent of change he promised to be. His two biggest initiatives, the economic stimulus and his health care reform law, were rushed through a Democratic Congress without a single Republican vote, and the electorate responded in 2010 by giving Republicans control of the House. Instead of moving to the center, as President Bill Clinton did after the 1994 Republican Revolution, Mr. Obama has dug in his heels. He shares the blame for Washington's gridlock. If he won't change course, the country won't, either. Mr. Romney, however, is a Republican who was elected governor of heavily Democratic Massachusetts. He had to work with Democrats to get things done. His leadership and ability to bring people together saved the Salt Lake City Winter Olympics. As a businessman, his management skills turned failing companies into profitable ones. Mr. Romney vows to do that, again, in Washington. If we are to avoid a lost decade and a future calamity created by inaction on entitlements and government growth, this nation needs a team of turnaround experts. Mr. Romney has promised to create a Cabinet of private-sector leaders focused on strengthening the country's business climate and making it more competitive. He and his running mate, Wisconsin Rep. Paul Ryan, have dared to put forward ideas to preserve Medicare for current beneficiaries and reform it for future recipients, and they vow to work with Congress to prevent the program's collapse. Mr. Romney is a fine family man who donates millions of dollars to his church and charity every year. There is not a whiff of scandal about him. This is why his opponents have tried to turn his very successes against him. It's all they have. Early voting in Nevada begins Oct. 20. Election Day is Nov. 6. Over the last few weeks of this campaign, Nevadans must ask themselves which candidate will embrace policies that will put the people of this state back to work, creating the jobs that lift our incomes, our home values and our hope. The choice is clear. Only Mitt Romney has the principles and experience needed to put America back on the road to prosperity. The Review-Journal endorses Mitt Romney for president of the United States.</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1349658760472</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:12:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658939053-30</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT BASHFUL ABOUT HIS GUBERNATORIAL RECORD</Title><Msg>along with his taxes: Romney staff spent nearly $100,000 to hide records When is Team Obama going to make sure people know about this? ----- (Reuters) - Mitt Romney spent nearly $100,000 in state funds to replace computers in his office at the end of his term as governor of Massachusetts in 2007 as part of an unprecedented effort to keep his records secret, Reuters has learned. The move during the final weeks of Romney's administration was legal but unusual for a departing governor, Massachusetts officials say. SNIP When Romney left the governorship of Massachusetts, 11 of his aides bought the hard drives of their state-issued computers to keep for themselves. Also before he left office, the governor's staff had emails and other electronic communications by Romney's administration wiped from state servers, state officials say. Those actions erased much of the internal documentation of Romney's four-year tenure as governor, which ended in January 2007. Precisely what information was erased is unclear. Republican and Democratic opponents of Romney say the scrubbing of emails - and a claim by Romney that paper records of his governorship are not subject to public disclosure - hinder efforts to #$%$ his performance as a politician and elected official.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349658939053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349660123153-31</Id><Title>Our Feckless Leader</Title><Msg>During the same week when the American ambassador to Libya was murdered and his dead body dragged through the streets by celebrating mobs, the President of the United States found time to go on the David Letterman show to demonstrate his sense of humor and how cool he is. But Barack Obama did not have time to meet with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, the leader of a nation repeatedly threatened with annihilation by Iranian leaders, who are working feverishly toward the creation of nuclear bombs. This was an extraordinary thing in itself, something that probably no other President of the United States could have gotten away with, without raising a firestorm of criticisms and denunciations. But much of the media sees no evil, hears no evil and speaks no evil when it comes to Barack Obama -- especially during an election year. Nor was this public rebuff of a publicly requested meeting with Prime Minister Netanyahu unique in its expression of disrespect, if not contempt, for both the man and his country. Despite his glowing assertions of his commitment to Israel, especially in speeches to American Jewish groups, Barack Obama has been working against Israel's interests from his first day in the White House. As in many other contexts, Barack Obama 1 speaks but Barack Obama 2 acts -- often in the opposite direction. The vision in which Obama has been steeped is one in which white Western nations have oppressed and exploited non-white, non-Western nations, becoming rich and arrogant at other people's expense. It is a vision that calls out, not for justice, but for payback. When Jeremiah Wright said, "white folks' greed runs a world in need" -- and Obama, by his own account, was moved to tears -- this captured in a few melodramatic words what a whole series of Obama's mentors and allies had been saying for decades. No wonder it resonated with him. Despite hopes that Barack Obama's election as President of the United States would mark the beginning of a post-racial era in America, no hope was ever so completely doomed from the outset. Anyone who looks beyond Obama's soothing words about race to his record, from his joining self-segregated black students in college to his appointing Al Sharpton as a White House adviser, can see the contrast between rhetoric and reality. Barack Obama is not the first leader of a nation whose actions reflected some half-baked vision, enveloped in lofty rhetoric and spiced with a huge dose of ego. Nor would he be the first such leader to steer his nation into a historic catastrophe.</Msg><Username>hydronicoctopussy</Username><Timestamp>1349660123153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349660810560-32</Id><Title>Facts the GOP just hate</Title><Msg>Stocks Return More With Democrat in White House: By Bob Drummond - Feb 22, 2012 While Republicans promote themselves as the friendliest party for Wall Street, stock investors do better when Democrats occupy the White House. From a dollars- and-cents standpoint, it’s not even close. The BGOV Barometer shows that, over the five decades since John F. Kennedy was inaugurated, $1,000 invested in a hypothetical fund that tracks the Standard &amp; Poor’s 500 Index (SPX) only when Democrats are in the White House would have been worth $10,920 at the close of trading yesterday. That’s more than nine times the dollar return an investor would have realized from following a similar strategy during Republican administrations. A $1,000 stake invested in a fund that followed the S&amp;P 500 under Republican presidents, starting with Richard Nixon, would have grown to $2,087 on the day George W. Bush left office. “The market does tend to do better under Democrats than under Republicans,” Sam Stovall, chief investment strategist at S&amp;P Equity Research in New York, said in a telephone interview. “Is it because Republicans mishandled the economy, or inherited a weak economy? I’ll leave that to others.” Some of the difference may stem from the fact that every Republican president since at least the end of World War II has faced a recession during his first term in office, Stovall said. Nine of 11 recessions that began since 1945 -- and seven of eight since Kennedy ran for president in 1960 --started with Republicans in the Oval Office. Wall Street Republicans Democratic administrations also may be more likely to spend money on government programs that stimulate the economy, Stovall said. “I dare say that most people on Wall Street are Republicans,” Stovall said. “But it appears the bread is buttered on the Democratic side.” The S&amp;P 500 yesterday hit its highest intra-day level since June 2008 and closed at 1,362.21, the highest since last April 29. The benchmark index is up 8.3 percent so far in 2012, the biggest year-to-date gain at this point since 1991. Since Kennedy took office, the Democratic S&amp;P fund logged a 992 percent gain, versus 109 percent growth for the opposition party, even though Democrats occupied the White House for 23 years over the period, compared with 28 years of Republican presidential leadership. The annualized return for 23 years of Democratic administrations is 11 percent, or four times the 2.7 percent annualized return during 28 years of Republican presidencies. Democratic Edge Investing $1,000 in funds that mirror the Dow Jones Industrial Average under the same conditions, Democratic investors would have had $7,550, versus $2,716 under Republicans. The Democratic edge is so large that the party comes out ahead even without counting Bill Clinton (the Democrat with the biggest S&amp;P 500 gain) and George W. Bush (the Republican with the worst market record). A hypothetical $1,000 investment under Democrats excluding Clinton was worth $3,539 versus $3,296 invested under Republicans except Bush. Adding Dwight Eisenhower to the Republican column doesn’t overcome the Democratic advantage, either: $1,000 invested in the S&amp;P 500 in January 1953 would have been worth $4,796 after 36 years under Republican chief executives -- still less than half the $10,920 nest egg accumulated in 23 years under Democrats.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349660810560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:46:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349666091458-33</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In spite of Mitten's lie fest, Obama still leads 47% to 45%. Mittens has not yet defended his lies. DOA</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1349666091458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:14:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349666470418-34</Id><Title>Mitt's Chinese Buddies Threaten America's Security !</Title><Msg>Rep. Mike Rogers (R-Mich.), the Republican chairman of the panel, delivered that warning bluntly. "If I were an American company today -- and I'll tell you this as the chairman of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence -- and you are looking at Huawei, I would find another vendor if you care about your intellectual property, if you care about your consumers' privacy, and you care about the national security of the United States of America," Rogers told "60 Minutes." One U.S. company that could've benefited from Rogers' warning is Bain Capital, the private equity giant founded by Mitt Romney, which still pays the GOP presidential nominee millions each year. Romney has made his promise to "get tough" on China a central element of his economic message, though the company he started has made it easier for China to get tough on its own citizens........................................... Mitt has compromised America for his personal profits. He sucks Chinese dhck.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1349666470418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>