<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-14"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355494973410-1</Id><Title>The federal government screws up education</Title><Msg>the states build the schools and employ the teachers. the federal pigs exist only to burden and regulate an education system that used to work. When we shut down the Department of Education and off the federal bureaucrats, we can get rid of 90% of the bureaucrats at the state level who exist to shovel paperwork back and forth with the feds.</Msg><Username>amorano_123</Username><Timestamp>1355494973410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:22:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355496909377-2</Id><Topic><Title>The federal government screws up education</Title><Username>amorano_123</Username><Timestamp>1355494973410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is more than that, friend. At the district level, there are employees who exist to satisfy the state and federal bureaucrats. At every level, there are more who exist to hire and house and care for them. You coul dstart a virtuous cycle.</Msg><Username>tradingdirect1999</Username><Timestamp>1355496909377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:55:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355498308719-3</Id><Topic><Title>The federal government screws up education</Title><Username>amorano_123</Username><Timestamp>1355494973410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>8% of 8th-graders in the Detroit public schools are proficient in reading. That is right, READING. The percentage of public school teachers who are proficient in reading is unknown, but probably higher. And that comes at a price to the taxpayers of $40,000 per child per year. Had to correct myself. I almost called them students.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1355498308719</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 10:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355517147859-4</Id><Title>Eric Schmidt declines Obama cabinet post.</Title><Msg>Good for him? But wait! Obama’s Google Supporters Moved 80% of Pre-Tax Profits into Bermuda Shell Company. Obama invites to his cabinet tax dodgers? What else is new? Tax cheat Timmy is already there for almost 4 years. Mitt is tax dodger, but those in Google are just obedient existing law followers. Works well for "highly educated" Obama voters. Oh yeah, bring more of those who don't know where and how to obtain ID cards to voting booths. That will do it! Good grief. This country is sinking lower and lower day by day.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1355517147859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:32:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355518469577-5</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Schmidt declines Obama cabinet post.</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1355517147859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Patently wrong. But what difference does it make, genius? Obama brought him in, Obama keeps him for full term. Obama invites yet another "cheat" into his cabinet. That's perfectly acceptable. While Mitt is tax dodger? Right. This president has really high moral standards!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1355518469577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:54:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355520885844-6</Id><Topic><Title>The federal government screws up education</Title><Username>amorano_123</Username><Timestamp>1355494973410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 09:22:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's the public sector union paracites who are to blame and the corrupt politicians who pander to them....good luck with trying to change the system with the pander in chief in the Whitehouse.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355520885844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355521180137-7</Id><Topic><Title>40% of folks not working</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355337630149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no excuse for sitting on your duff collecting government money rather than working....none!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355521180137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355522346352-8</Id><Topic><Title>Eric Schmidt declines Obama cabinet post.</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1355517147859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 15:32:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's ok, it's Democrat tax cheating.... When Obama speaks 48% of the people can't believe what they are hearing, while the other 52% don't care what they are hearing.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355522346352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 16:59:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523001186-9</Id><Title>the gop lie of an anti-business atmosphere</Title><Msg>WSJ "Big U.S. companies have emerged from the deepest recession since World War II more productive, more profitable, flush with cash and less burdened by debt. An analysis by The Wall Street Journal of corporate financial reports finds that cumulative sales, profits and employment last year among members of the Standard &amp; Poor's 500-stock index exceeded the totals of 2007, before the recession and financial crisis. The chart above shows after-tax corporate profits for U.S. corporations as a whole, which set a new record high in 2011 of more than $1.5 trillion, and were 20.5% above the pre-recession peak of $1.26 trillion in 2006 (adjusted for inflation).</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1355523001186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:10:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355523250384-10</Id><Title>anti business?</Title><Msg>record corporate profits in 2011 that surpassed prerecession levels, were topped by the record profits of 2012. "Big U.S. companies have emerged from the deepest recession since World War II more productive, more profitable, flush with cash and less burdened by debt. An analysis by The Wall Street Journal found</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1355523250384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 17:14:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355526585918-11</Id><Title>Unprecendented decline in income for the american Middle Class in Last 4 Years</Title><Msg>Never in U.S. history have so many lost so much. Obama says he wants 10 million more on the Obamaphone program.</Msg><Username>donng_hung_lo</Username><Timestamp>1355526585918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-14 18:09:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>