<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355291844523-1</Id><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Msg>History: E-Tub was born in 1998. This used to be one of da most posted boards on Yahoo. Boohoohoohoo, now it's a shell of its former self. Nobody comes here anymore, all da King's men and all da Queen's horses are posting on other boards. See, I tole yaz. I tole Yinz back in 2007 that almost everyone here would be goners before I bought back into E-Tub-dumped it all in Aug 2005-and that y'all would lose money on this here stalk. Remember? Nah, Yinz newbies are probably ignorant of Da Hog's history. BTW, if y'all don't know who gave E-Tub da nickname Hog, ya shoulda bought Apple. BTW, it was Donk, a complete idiot, but, probably smarter that y'all Pilgrims. Oh, nobody's smarter than Da Bear-Mrs Bear thinks she is, but, shes wrong-at least on this here board. I do not currently have a single stock in this accident waiting to happen; but, I do intend to start a position as soon as we go over da GD Fiscal Cliff. Remember one thingy that will make y'all richer than yer neighbors, $7.01. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Only posters who have been here, done that, have da freaking t-shirt, are authorized to reply. Others will be shot. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355303481143-2</Id><Topic><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be adding again at $6.01. No holding currently.</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1355303481143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 04:11:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355304198066-3</Id><Topic><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're right Bear~ It was the worst of times.... it was the worst of times~ The old hog holders....Legends of the fall~ GAWD those were painful times. Shareholder took daily kicks to da nuts~ over and over again~ You tried and tried to warn the HOG Semper-fi. Merry xmas Bear!</Msg><Username>krisspcritter_da_1</Username><Timestamp>1355304198066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 04:23:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355320278136-4</Id><Title>now you can donate</Title><Msg>your worthless etfc stock through your etrade account. hooray!</Msg><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1355320278136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 08:51:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355326174673-5</Id><Topic><Title>now you can donate</Title><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1355320278136</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 08:51:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The PR department is on fire. Between that an the guy running the twitter account for etrade, things are really looking up. Why bother with another CEO or try to make money?</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1355326174673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 10:29:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355328392875-6</Id><Topic><Title>Help Is On Its Way...</Title><Username>lucierikard598</Username><Timestamp>1308671898000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2011-06-21 11:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>davidmary700</Username><Timestamp>1355328392875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 11:06:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355336651082-7</Id><Title>Bull Market for Etrade.....</Title><Msg>If you are a short seller.... Market goes way up- You make money Market stays flat- You make money Market goes down- You make lotsa money</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1355336651082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:24:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355337630149-8</Id><Title>40% of folks not working</Title><Msg>A fine kettle of fish this post "W" has got us into. Interesting and intriguing, is the continuing decline in the labor force. It came in at a sterling 63.6%, falling 0.2%. Can you fathom that in the United States almost 40% of those capable of working are NOT working? 350,000 more workers left the workforce. Fewer and fewer people are looking for work. Thus the unemployment rate fell to 7.7%. No job, no prospects, and most importantly, no income to tax to pay into the Treasury. Investor's Business Daily If you pay someone to do nothing, he will do nothing -- Jon Johnson Moreover, why even take a job if it is there and doesn't pay any more than you can get from the various government programs that you can stack one upon the other. I saw a story on CNBC today that highlights part of what I discussed a week ago about the effort to find a job and work versus simply collecting benefits. Phil Lebeau talked to machine shops making oil and gas production and exploration items that had the work but could not keep people at the starting level interested in doing the work. After a few days or even a day they throw in the towel because they can sit and do nothing and have as much disposable income as they made as an apprentice. A machine shop paying $13/hour for an apprentice translates into about $25K for the year. You can sit on your duff and collect benefits and then do a little cash only work on the side and live better than the poor schmuck who works 9 to 5. As I always say, if we want to pay people to do nothing, they will do nothing. That is what we are finding out but are not rectifying.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355337630149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:40:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355337967102-9</Id><Topic><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How about Washington Mutual, Downey Federal Savings...poof! At least E*Trade is still on the board...for now.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355337967102</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355338211706-10</Id><Topic><Title>40% of folks not working</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355337630149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:40:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People enabled by the obama doctrine just stay home and become lazy fat facedfucks. Not too dissimilar from those lazy fat faced unionfucks we all saw on TV yesterday.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1355338211706</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:50:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355344380975-11</Id><Title>Bernanke's at it again</Title><Msg>This #$%$ is now printing close to a trillion dollars a year and he says he will continue to do so until the unemolyment rate hits 6+%. Good luck with that, QE forever and zero interest rates. He continues on his path of punishing the responsible folks and reward the risk takers. He is forcing folks to get into the risky stock market to get any kind of return. The folks in retirement or are approching retirement are getting screwed. Of cource our public sector union brothers and sisters have to RISK NOTHING to get their bloated pensions and healthcare for life...Bernanke is truley a jew for all seasons.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1355344380975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 15:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355347047729-12</Id><Topic><Title>Bull Market for Etrade.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1355336651082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 13:24:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I rather liked today's little dip, I had a buy limit at 8.21 hoping it would bounce off the 8.2 first resistance line, and sure enough it touched it, briefly, and my order executed. The prices may go down alittle in the short term on eTrade, but as far as long term projections go we're pretty much looking at the bottom of the trench here. In the intermediate term, at least until next earnings, we're a fluctuating line with opportunities on both the short and long side, but here's the problem I have with playing the shortside on ETFC. Right now it has a tangible value to book of about .5, which means that buying the stock is like picking up dollar bills for 50 cents each AND getting a piece of a profitable business, so sooner or later the stock price is going to gap up in a SERIOUS way. I'd rather be caught long in that position than short. Being long you can trade around a permanent position, accreted to it, and still play the swings while allowing highside buys to gradually accumulate a larger core position with the resulting profits. I started the year with around a 1,000 share long term position, and now its 2,500 with 1,000 on the swing (including the 500 bought today). If I hadn't taken HORRIBLE losses abandoning an ill advised position in Radio Shack I'd be doing great this year. As it is I based my buy there on the CEO's promise that they'd NEVER cut their dividend . . . . . lying POS.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1355347047729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:17:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355347632056-13</Id><Topic><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ETrade was giving money away for awhile, it was all I could do to delete their "do you need a loan" eMails and Splash Screens from the late 90's until the bitter end. Still, now that's been smashed up a bit, it's quite an attractive property both because of the customers and their associated assets and the brand name, which has become one of the most recognizable brands in the field by most Americans. Never mind what's left of their mortgage portfolio and the losses that they're provisioning against there, that could end up being a net asset in the long run, particularly if real estate values pick up and repossessed properties can be disposed of at a profit. I frankly think that section has more potential than most give it credit. But remember that, aside from that provision, on a REAL basis, this is a profitable company making and accumulating assets while attempting to formulate a business plan to use those assets to get back into the game. There are going to be bumps on the road. Sure $7.01 is POSSIBLE, but I wasn't going to let this slide by on a possible P/tB of .5 or lower, so I started at about .67 If you manage to snag all in at under .5, then more power to you, you'll have called it far better than I have, but I'm not gonna sweat the extra $1.20 with this much long term potential.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1355347632056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:27:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355348175215-14</Id><Title>Today's Volume</Title><Msg>Today's volume was pretty massive. 11,000,000 shares and no news. What's up with that?</Msg><Username>ghost_of_ramat</Username><Timestamp>1355348175215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:36:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355349460959-15</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Volume</Title><Username>ghost_of_ramat</Username><Timestamp>1355348175215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:36:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one trade was for 9 million shares. Probably a tax loss sale.</Msg><Username>mtpocket</Username><Timestamp>1355349460959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 16:57:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355354083243-16</Id><Topic><Title>14 years and it finally happened ...learn what happened to E-Tub...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1355291844523</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 00:57:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah I almost didn't buy in until I was fairly sure they could bring it back with enough resources to avoid major dilution. As it was the shrinkage in share count and emergency measures to put out the fires just barely saved the company from being stripped to its component parts and sold as chitlins. Now they're provisioning, and indeed would have made money last quarter if not for a reticent mortgage servicer, since terminated, having hidden their losses, causing a large one time provisioning. We just have to hope there are no more such significant surprises hiding behind any more corners. Baring that annual income should start to steady out and grow in a year. I don't mind a year, or even three, if we gain back even a quarter of the companies pre-crash valuation. I'll hold on until after President Obama leaves office if I have to. I'm seriously doubting there'll be any takeover attempts either, since enough of the stock is held by people who probably won't take less than $24/share for the company as it is now. I know my standing sell order on this stock for my core position is $32 a share at this point.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1355354083243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-12-12 18:14:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>