<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346300211206-1</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC will go down tomorrow! Back to $8.40s!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346293028082</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 22:17:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No pumping today for once? Watch etfc go up tomorrow anyways.</Msg><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1346300211206</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 00:16:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346302569860-2</Id><Title>"We will not let the truth get in the way."</Title><Msg>At a campaign event on Wednesday, President Barack Obama latched onto remarks made by Neil Newhouse, a pollster for Mitt Romney, who said this week the Republican presidential candidate's campaign would not "be dictated by fact-checkers." Speaking to a crowd in Virginia, Obama brought up the Romney camp's sustained attacks on his welfare waiver policy. The ads have been widely panned for being factually inaccurate. "I mean, somebody was challenging one of their ads -- they made it up -- about work and welfare. And every outlet said, this is just not true. And they were asked about it and they said -- one of their campaign people said, we won't have the fact-checkers dictate our campaign," Obama said. "We will not let the truth get in the way." Obama was referencing comments Newhouse made at a panel organized by ABC News on Tuesday. Romney's campaign has said that its ads attacking Obama over welfare have been its most effective to date. Whether they are truthful is another matter. Romney insists they are. On Monday, Obama addressed Romney's claim that he had "gutted" work requirements for welfare recipients in a surprise appearance in the White House Briefing Room. "Everybody who's looked at this says what Gov. Romney's saying is absolutely wrong," Obama said. "They can run the campaign that they want, but the truth of the matter is you can't just make stuff up."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346302569860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 00:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346334313766-3</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Solyndrawas/ is an efficient, good product and I can only imagine that China will buy or steal the patents and be selling us the same product in a few years. Solyndra failed b/c the Chinese dumped large quantities of cheap panels on US markets, crippling US manufacturers. The Germans have heavily invested in solar electricity, as have others.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346334313766</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 09:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346336482991-4</Id><Topic><Title>"We will not let the truth get in the way."</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346302569860</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 00:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No surprise there. The GOP has long since bought into the big lie approach. Unfortunately, that has proven to be an effective propaganda technique. Swift Boating works, and is their only hope for November.</Msg><Username>joeleo70</Username><Timestamp>1346336482991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346336714000-5</Id><Topic><Title>How to be Really Stupid</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1346298758000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:52:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs would throw a convention in Alaska in January, and then complain about snow.</Msg><Username>mitt_da_szit</Username><Timestamp>1346336714000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346336726579-6</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeez shiny - appears to me it is the presidents role to make sure we protect our investments. so now BO can say "Hey I did everything right but those pesky Chinese dumped on our market. I do borrow alot from them so I don't want to get in their face too much." I mean really - you would give this man a pass no matter how bad things get. It is funny logic that everything is out of BO's control, while GW gets the exact opposite treatment.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1346336726579</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346336991367-7</Id><Title>acceptance speech tonigh</Title><Msg>by the nominee for assistant vice p.</Msg><Username>billietwinky</Username><Timestamp>1346336991367</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346338201782-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like to advocate for the future whenever possible. All energy comes from the sun anyway. I think it would be better to get it when it first arrives and not millions of years later when it is polluted with toxic chemicals such as mercury and heavy metals. Now is the time to jump on that bandwagon so if we had to pump more money into Solyndra, I feel like we should have done so. If we can physically lose 8 billion in Iraq, how much would it hurt if we lost a lot less on solar energy, if the US could ultimately become a leader in that field. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346338201782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 10:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346339054872-9</Id><Title>"Just the facts, ma'am."</Title><Msg>Condi Rice Can’t Name A Specific Obama Foreign Policy Failure By Ben Armbruster on Aug 29, 2012 at 10:40 am Condoleezza Rice Today on CBS’s morning show, former Bush administration Secretary of State and top Mitt Romney surrogate Condoleezza Rice could not offer any specific foreign policy failures made by President Obama. Romney’s allies, led by Rice and Sen. John McCain (R-AZ), are expected to attack Obama on national security grounds tonight in at the Republican National Convention in Tampa.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346339054872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346339072641-10</Id><Title>Jan Brewer endorses Obama saying...</Title><Msg>"I know that if President Obama is elected in November, which I hope that he is*, that he will be able to come together with all of us and come up with a solution and I believe he will secure our borders and therefore we can resolve all those other issues, it's a simple matter." *She meant to say "will be" LOL ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346339072641</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346339343874-11</Id><Topic><Title>"Just the facts, ma'am."</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346339054872</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:04:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FactCheckdotorg on "Ryan’s VP Spin" - "several false claims and misleading statements" TAMPA, Fla. — Paul Ryan’s acceptance speech at the Republican convention contained several false claims and misleading statements. Delegates cheered as the vice presidential nominee: - Accused President Obama’s health care law of funneling money away from Medicare “at the expense of the elderly.” In fact, Medicare’s chief actuary says the law “substantially improves” the system’s finances, and Ryan himself has embraced the same savings. - Accused Obama of doing “exactly nothing” about recommendations of a bipartisan deficit commission — which Ryan himself helped scuttle. - Claimed the American people were “cut out” of stimulus spending. Actually, more than a quarter of all stimulus dollars went for tax relief for workers. - Faulted Obama for failing to deliver a 2008 campaign promise to keep a Wisconsin plant open. It closed less than a month before Obama took office. - Blamed Obama for the loss of a AAA credit rating for the U.S. Actually, Standard &amp; Poor’s blamed the downgrade on the uncompromising stands of both Republicans and Democrats. And when he wasn’t attacking Obama, Ryan was puffing up the record of his running mate, Mitt Romney, on taxes and unemployment. Taking Money from Medicare? Ryan continued the campaign’s false line of attack that Obama had “funneled” money out of Medicare to pay for the federal health care law “at the expense of the elderly.” But that’s contradicted by Medicare’s chief actuary, in a statement at the end of the most recent report of the system’s trustees (our emphasis added):</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346339343874</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346340540271-12</Id><Topic><Title>BO perfect on foreign policy, says Condi</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346297598527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 23:33:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Condi couldn't mention a specific failure - because they are ALL failures! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1346340540271</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:29:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346340835932-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so now you want the president to micro manage everything while at the same time crying about big-government and too many regulations? contradictions seem to be the only constant for the GOP</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1346340835932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 11:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346343138756-14</Id><Title>Ailes suffers stroke!!</Title><Msg>The following is from Fox News. Yes, that Fox News: [T]o anyone paying the slightest bit of attention to facts, Ryan’s speech was an apparent attempt to set the world record for the greatest number of blatant lies and misrepresentations slipped into a single political speech. On this measure, while it was Romney who ran the Olympics, Ryan earned the gold. Apparently Fox News has started paying attention to facts and goes on to name some that Ryan blurred the edges of during his speech — with supporting links and everything: Fact: While Ryan tried to pin the downgrade of the United States’ credit rating on spending under President Obama, the credit rating was actually downgraded because Republicans threatened not to raise the debt ceiling. Fact: While Ryan blamed President Obama for the shut down of a GM plant in Janesville, Wisconsin, the plant was actually closed under President George W. Bush. Ryan actually asked for federal spending to save the plant, while Romney has criticized the auto industry bailout that President Obama ultimately enacted to prevent other plants from closing. Fact: Though Ryan insisted that President Obama wants to give all the credit for private sector success to government, that isn’t what the president said. Period. Fact: Though Paul Ryan accused President Obama of taking $716 billion out of Medicare, the fact is that that amount was savings in Medicare reimbursement rates (which, incidentally, save Medicare recipients out-of-pocket costs, too) and Ryan himself embraced these savings in his budget plan. To Fox News‘ (dis)credit, they also called Ryan’s speech “dazzling,” patting the prospective VP on the back for helping to humanize the Automatic Teller Machine with whom he shares a ticket. Then Fox News zagged instead of zigging once again, calling the speech “distracting” by failing to mention a few things that may not sit so well with voters — again, with supporting links!: Ryan didn’t mention his extremist stance on banning all abortions with no exception for rape or incest, a stance that is out of touch with 75% of American voters. Ryan didn’t mention his previous plan to hand over Social Security to Wall Street. Ryan didn’t mention his numerous votes to raise spending and balloon the deficit when George W. Bush was president. Ryan didn’t mention how his budget would eviscerate programs that help the poor and raise taxes on 95% of Americans in order to cut taxes for millionaires and billionaires even further and increase — yes, increase —the deficit. We don’t know if the Fox News site has been a victim of cyberterrorism, or someone had an extra bowl of bipartisan Wheaties this morning, but blatantly calling #$%$ on a Republican candidate when that number is almost strictly reserved for the opposition is…weird. Fair and balanced. But weird.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346343138756</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:12:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344005103-15</Id><Title>Local chapters of "Polygamists for Romney" are confused by Hatch position.</Title><Msg>Is Orrin angling to make polygamy state specific? Concerned polygamists want to know!! Utah Sen. Orrin Hatch breaks with Romney, GOP over federal ban on same-sex marriage Source: LGBTQnation TAMPA, Fla. — Utah’s senior U.S. Senator and an influential voice in the Republican party broke ranks Tuesday with GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney and the party’s platform, differing on support for a constitutional amendment banning same-sex marriage. Sen. Orrin Hatch, speaking on the convention floor to Sirius Q XM radio, said, “I’m a believer that the states should be able to make their own determination. There are about, what, six states that have done it? They’ve chosen to do that. I don’t agree with that, because I believe in the sanctity of the marriage covenant and the traditional definition, but the states have a right to do it.” Hatch, who is running for reelection this year, said that he felt it should be a state’s rights issue. “Well, my personal belief is that we should not discriminate against anybody, but I do draw the line at the definition of marriage,’ he said. “I think that it’s a very important thing for men, women and children. But I don’t want to see anybody showing prejudice against anybody.”</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346344005103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344551895-16</Id><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Msg>The doctor who delivered Barry in Kenya.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346344836382-17</Id><Title>Why the GOP is polling at zero percent</Title><Msg>"Poor Michael Steele. He still does not see that the team he's trying so hard to belong to sees no difference between him and Barack Obama. They do not have enough respect for him to give him one invitation out of 50,000. He had to get there as a journalist. I just heard on the radio Steele is wandering around the venue, no one wants to talk to him. When will you learn, Michael?"</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346344836382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346345648388-18</Id><Title>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+!! Very Soon!!!</Title><Msg>With a New CEO announcement, ETFC will jump 10%+!! Very Soon!!! Expecting $10+ within a month!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346345648388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:54:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346346140982-19</Id><Title>If market turns to green this afternoon or tomorrow, ETFC will be skyrocketing to $8.70s~8.80s!</Title><Msg>If market turns to green this afternoon or tomorrow, ETFC will be skyrocketing to $8.70s~8.80s!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346346140982</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:02:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346346947715-20</Id><Topic><Title>GOP can't repress their racism</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346290240209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Republican convention emphasizes diversity, racial incidents intrude Source: Washington Post TAMPA — From the convention stage here, the Republican Party has tried to highlight its diversity, giving prime speaking slots to Latinos and blacks who have emphasized their party’s economic appeal to all Americans. But they have delivered those speeches to a convention hall filled overwhelmingly with white faces, an awkward contrast that has been made more uncomfortable this week by a series of racial headaches that have intruded on the party’s efforts to project a new level of inclusiveness. The tensions come amid a debate within the GOP on how best to lure new voters. The nation’s shifting demographics have caused some Republican leaders to worry not only about the party’s future but about winning in November, particularly in key swing states such as Virginia and Nevada. “The demographics race we’re losing badly,” said Sen. Lindsey O. Graham (S.C.). “We’re not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term.” That followed an on-air shouting match between MSNBC host Chris Matthews and Republican National Committee Chairman Reince Priebus over whether presidential nominee Mitt Romney was injecting race into the campaign by joking about President Obama’s birth certificate and attacking his record on welfare reform. “There’s no doubt he did,” Matthews declared.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346346947715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346347801954-21</Id><Title>BOOMERS &amp; ELDERLY: do not trust Romney, he is a LIAR who will sell you out first chance</Title><Msg>Romney has no intention of keeping his promise of full, as is, medicare and social security for all on them now and for most all boomers, too. Romney tax cuts and increased military spending will rack up the largest ever USA deficits for many years.......the tax cuts are definate and soon.... the spending cuts are vague and in the future .........</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346347801954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 13:30:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346349747973-22</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry who? ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346349747973</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346349923779-23</Id><Topic><Title>Local chapters of "Polygamists for Romney" are confused by Hatch position.</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1346344005103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:26:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want to ban "same-old-sex" in marriage. Actually, not really. The worst sex I ever had was wonderful. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346349923779</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346350530039-24</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be Barry Soetoro.. Lolo Soetoro, also known as Lolo Soetoro Mangunharjo, Lolo Sutoro. January 2, 1935- March 2, 1987 was the Indonesian stepfather of Barack Obama, the 44th President of the United States of America.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346350530039</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:15:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346352666991-25</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lenona will tell how only the "little people have to pay taxes"...and MORE!!! all via a ouija board, reagan will mumble some alzheimers things about the after life.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346352666991</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 14:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346353371000-26</Id><Title>E*TRADE Financial Corporation is showing historic technical movement</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial Corporation looks really unstable right now. Check out this site for the latest updates in E*TRADE Financial Corporation http://TRADINGINSTOCK.INFO</Msg><Username>jacklynkissling</Username><Timestamp>1346353371000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346354048003-27</Id><Topic><Title>GOP can't repress their racism</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346290240209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP to NEO-Nazis - "we will fight for no restriction on gun magazine capacity. We don't want you to have to change the clip when you are mowing down a shopping mall or a movie theater."</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1346354048003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:14:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346356522650-28</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**reagan will mumble some alzheimers things about the after life**... You are a class act hydrop</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346356522650</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346356721183-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOP can't repress their racism</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346290240209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I have a very strict gun control policy: if there's a gun around, I want to be in control of it."....Clint Eastwood</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346356721183</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 15:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346357755898-30</Id><Title>Democrats are 'Racists"!!!!</Title><Msg>Democrats/Progressives/Marxists/Liberals/Racist or whatever you freaky gays call yourself, Do you even know what the word 'Racism" means??? Or do you continuously act like a Parrott with Tourette's Syndrome?? Squacking out with a twitch: Racism, Racism!! Well, look how the Freakazoid Left treats: Herman Cain, Condeleeza Rice, Clarence Thomas, Thomas Sowell, Col. Allen West....That's friggin' RACIST you #$%$! Not to mention your WAR ON WOMEN!!! But your Loser #$%$ and your Messiah, the Composite Girlfriend serial dater is about to be Ex-president. Even No President, an empty chair, os better than this piece of moo-slim crap!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346357755898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346359947463-31</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are 'Racists"!!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346357755898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow - so much anger........ I bet you are one of the guys waiting for GOP to lift restriction on ammo clip sizes.... and by the way - congrats on listing by name ALL minority members withing GOP rank :) I hear are worried they'll be pelted by peanuts and racial slurs. Seems to be the 'theme' at the GOP convention.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1346359947463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360094053-32</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's a simple question: Since the Mittens types will be paying close to zero income taxes, who will pay for the gop promised increase in military spending and the promised full, as is, medicare and social security for most all of the aging boomers? .......your answer will involve snake oil and voodoo , but sure pretend you bums know what you a doing, just like with the Trillions of $$ you committed to decades of mideast murder, meddling and occupations, paid for with several trillions of $$ in tax cuts to the rich for the last decade, that sure added up in those empty gop brains and keep repeating your magic words "blind faith", "blind faith".</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1346360094053</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346360853484-33</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clint Eastwood</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346360853484</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346361695088-34</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are 'Racists"!!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346357755898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have the biggest smile on my face! Thanks to President Romney!!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346361695088</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346362313786-35</Id><Topic><Title>On 'Lection day, get out there and vote for a good Christian!</Title><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346101435665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-27 17:03:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are all kinds of Christians but Obama is not a Catholic. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346362313786</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346362693545-36</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney!!! (Done!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1345413053000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like I could care less: Let 'em elect Romney, I loves me a good train wreck. When Romney can't tame the economy, the pubes will blame it on Obama and they will elect him for 4 more years. Then in 2020, the truth will be too obvious and the voters will be _real_ ready for some Democrats. Pubes don't know how to create jobs, they know how to make a few people rich and a lot of people very poor. ~S</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1346362693545</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346363309715-37</Id><Topic><Title>Democrats are 'Racists"!!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1346357755898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 16:15:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Minorities for you. Great Americans for normal people.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1346363309715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346363719000-38</Id><Title>Standard &amp; Poors Rating headin up</Title><Msg>Last rating action March 2011 (upgrade). Etfc springer refinance in december taking out 12 1/2% notes. Expect another major transaction, even could be sale of the company Along with springer refinance. Bank sale will not take place.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346363719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:55:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346364022054-39</Id><Topic><Title>Take Your Angry Campaign and Go Back To Chicago</Title><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1345214428000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-17 10:40:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever seen a more depressed crowd.. The only group smiling and laughing are the millionaires... Top 1% having a ball in this. The Mormon recruiting missionaries are having a field day also, recruiting heaven.. The pubs have recognized and given credibility to Mormonism as a real religion in America.. Mormons no longer a cult, Catholics no longer allowed to believe Mormon teachings are a false God. Mormonism a true made in America Religion.. Amazing!</Msg><Username>migrationisahumanright</Username><Timestamp>1346364022054</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:00:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346364524315-40</Id><Title>$8.80+ Tomorrow!! Possibly $8.90 with a Good Fed News!!!</Title><Msg>$8.80+ Tomorrow!! Possibly $8.90 with a Good Fed News!!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1346364524315</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346365648000-41</Id><Title>Loans paying down at record pace. By $2B a year</Title><Msg>Morgasm Stanley said one year ago that the loan book required $2.5billion in marks. Is this still wif credence.</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346365648000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 18:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346369429855-42</Id><Title>enough cryin odumbomites</Title><Msg>yer about to take a dam out in new orleans..........</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346369429855</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346370240118-43</Id><Topic><Title>GOP surprise speaker</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346344551895</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 12:35:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if the mittens types pay 0 taxes...sammy would be collecting 0 taxes......that $3 box you checked on your 1040ez to give to your odaddy is not a tax.....</Msg><Username>returnusmaximus</Username><Timestamp>1346370240118</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 19:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346375260169-44</Id><Topic><Title>GOP can't repress their racism</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346290240209</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 21:30:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Election Black CNN Camerawoman Speaks Out About Peanut-Throwing Incident By Annie-Rose Strasser posted from ThinkProgress Election on Aug 30, 2012 at 1:35 pm A black camerawoman for CNN is speaking out after she was assaulted at the Republican National Convention when two attendees began throwing nuts at her, saying “This is what we feed animals.” Carroll, 34, said that as an Alabama native, she was not surprised. “This is Florida, and I’m from the Deep South,” she said. “You come to places like this, you can count the black people on your hand. They see us doing things they don’t think I should do.” Carroll noted of the Republican convention, “There are not that many black women there.”[...] “I can’t change these people’s hearts and minds,” Carroll added. “No, it doesn’t feel good. But I know who I am. I’m a proud black woman. A lot of black people are upset. This should be a wake-up call to black people. . . . People were living in euphoria for a while. People think we’re gone further than we have.” Caroll’s assessment that “you can count the black people on your hand” isn’t far off; only 2 percent of delegates at the RNC are African-American. When the Democratic Convention begins, an estimated 26 percent of the delegates will be black.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346375260169</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:07:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346375739468-45</Id><Title>Mttlies dotcom</Title><Msg>There you can find nice selections of his lies on virtually every topic conveniently in one place. Like this: Romney on Wall Street “Look, no one is talking about deregulating Wall Street.” [ThinkProgress, 8/15/2012] REALITY: Romney has called for the full repeal of the Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform Act, the first major overhaul of the nation’s financial regulatory system since the Great Depression, and while he has supported a “streamlined regulatory framework,” the only specific regulations he mentions in his plan are already in Dodd-Frank. His own running mate is certainly talking about deregulating Wall Street: the House GOP budget authored by Ryan dismantles key parts of the law. [ThinkProgress, 8/25/2011, 8/13/2012, 8/15/2012] “The rate of regulatory burden has increased four-fold since Obama has become president. Four times the amount of regulation coming out per year as in the past. And so businesses say, ‘gosh, I’m not sure I want to invest in America.’” [ThinkProgress, 12/12/2011] REALITY: Obama approved 613 new rules during his first 33 months, 4.7 percent fewer than Bush did in the same timespan. The campaign initially claimed that “the governor misspoke” in levying the charge, but Romney keeps using it. [NPR, 9/9/2011, Bloomberg, 10/25/2011]</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346375739468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:15:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346375819000-46</Id><Title>Xhoo xhoo here come da pain train</Title><Msg>All aboard</Msg><Username>busser_hyman</Username><Timestamp>1346375819000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346375870910-47</Id><Topic><Title>Mttlies dotcom</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346375739468</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:15:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct spelling is "Mittlies"</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1346375870910</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346375954000-48</Id><Topic><Title>Standard &amp; Poors Rating headin up</Title><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346363719000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 17:55:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Out here in big sky country, this is a larkSpur</Msg><Username>orland_kravitz</Username><Timestamp>1346375954000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346376542049-49</Id><Topic><Title>Obama is clueless</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1346278287265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-29 18:11:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you would spend all the king's gold on a perpetual motion machine you appear easily duped</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1346376542049</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 21:29:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346382472900-50</Id><Title>Dirty Harry doesn't due fact checking.....</Title><Msg>Clint Eastwood: Mitt Romney Should Not Be President Source: sunshine state news Hollywood actor and director Clint Eastwood may not have meant to, but in his surprise speech at the RNC this evening, he effectively said the GOP nominee should not be elected President. "I never thought it was a good idea for attorneys to be president." {Source} Of course, he meant this as a humorous swipe against Democratic incumbent Barack Obama, who graduated from Harvard Law School and was admitted to the Illinois Bar in 1991.. But someone at the RNC should have vetted the remarks ahead of time. Here's why: Romney received his Juris Doctorate from Harvard in 1975, and was admitted to the Michigan Bar later that same year. "I never thought it was a good idea for attorneys to be president." Ouch.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346382472900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346382535646-51</Id><Title>Scammers</Title><Msg>Scammers</Msg><Username>longs_galore</Username><Timestamp>1346382535646</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346383679812-52</Id><Topic><Title>Dirty Harry doesn't due fact checking.....</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346382472900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ouch!!! Attorney is job position, not a degree. Never heard Romney worked a single day as an attorney.</Msg><Username>formykidsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1346383679812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346383725137-53</Id><Title>Romney blew it!!!</Title><Msg>He didn't tell the American people how he will turn the economy around, how to handle immigration, how to fix Medicare and Social Security. He was very deliberate about getting this country into another war. Even Mitch McConnell said, there was alot missing in Mittens speech. I doubt very much that Willard swayed any Independents. Mittens really blew it!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1346383725137</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:28:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346383795066-54</Id><Topic><Title>Dirty Harry doesn't due fact checking.....</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346382472900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeezus xrhist - this is the #$%$ dumbest group of words ever put together. did a monkey type it?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1346383795066</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346384519234-55</Id><Topic><Title>Dirty Harry doesn't due fact checking.....</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1346382472900</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:07:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JB, are y'all dumb ore just stupid, huh? Don't cha know da difference between a dummy law degree and an attorney, huh? C Yaz Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( JB, where did ya get yer degree, huh? )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1346384519234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-30 23:41:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>