<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349670143207-1</Id><Topic><Title>Facts the GOP just hate</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349660810560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:46:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So dismal GDP growth, high unemployment, ever increasing cost of living, individual income dropping are not important? It is Wall Street performance we should vote for in November? Obama worshippers, you sound desperate.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349670143207</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 00:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349681303511-2</Id><Topic><Title>10000 ETFC at 9.13 Long and Strong</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349526113473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should've sold at $9.30s on Friday. ETFC will be beaten down this week! Low $8 is coming!!</Msg><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1349681303511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 03:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349693033682-3</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOOOHH!! EXCELLENT!!!! PLEEEZ keep living in your fantasy land of believing YOUR polls!! John Kerry annonced as New President at 4pm Election Day 2004!! Sleep well!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349693033682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 06:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349693213150-4</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WINNING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349693213150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 06:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349693474110-5</Id><Topic><Title>I Hope the Right Wingnutz Watch the Debate</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349308114036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:48:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOHHH!!! WE WATCHED!!!! Along with 70 Million others...SUCKAS!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349693474110</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 06:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349698887224-6</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our Supreme and Victorious Angry Communist Leader has a pole and he will show it to everyone unless they allow a TELEPROMPTER in to the debates !</Msg><Username>communist_rubbish</Username><Timestamp>1349698887224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 08:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349699578977-7</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EEEWWWW!!! The 'MOOOOO-shell' pole??? YUCK!! Yeah, givem the TOTALITARIAN teleprompter!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349699578977</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 08:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349699831415-8</Id><Topic><Title>10000 ETFC at 9.13 Long and Strong</Title><Username>bid100k</Username><Timestamp>1349526113473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 08:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I also started adding to my position. Housing is recovering and that is not baked into the price. Once they can start using their cash this stock will fly towards $20.</Msg><Username>tobypharma</Username><Timestamp>1349699831415</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 08:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349701139323-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no matter that W was in for 8 years, his last budget was still twice that of his first. the last budget year obama did was about the SAME as HIS FIRST... get it , numskull? (and if Romney does a taxcut,plus increased military spending ,his first deficit will be LARGER than obama's last and you bums are going to throw another tantrum over his first debt ceiling increase right?) the no spin fact of the mess w and the gop did: W's 1st budget ...$1.9 trillion W's last budget....$3.2 trillion obama's 1st....$3.2 trillion ...............2012..$3.6 trillion kinda obvious who did the bigger increase of spending, isn't it?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349701139323</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 08:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349701497010-10</Id><Topic><Title>gop leader said slavery is a blessing...another gop leader said earth is 9000 years old &amp; Mitt said pre-existing conditions are covered under my plan.”</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349615137122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:05:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It seems to me that many in the gop have about the same caliber of thinking on economics as the guy with the 9000 yr old earth............the idiot laffer curve is held up as if it is a miracle, but it's just a childish myth like Noah's ark. (a texas school board leader once had a discussion about how it was possible to get all the dinosaurs on the ark......)</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349701497010</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349703196352-11</Id><Title>BO cleaning up the GOP mess</Title><Msg>Score For Obama! The 2012 Deficit Down By $207 Billion And Heading Lower The Congressional Budget Office has released its estimate for the fiscal year 2012, just ended on September 30 and the news is good. The federal deficit was just under $1.1 trillion, compared to just under $1.3 trillion at the end of fiscal year 2011, a reduction of $207 billion. As a percentage of the GDP, the 2012 deficit dropped to 7.0 per cent, down from 8.7 percent in 2011 and 9.0 percent in 2010. The actual deficit numbers will be released later this month by the Treasury Department The September 2012 numbers show an increase in receipts of about $23 billion, or 9% higher than the same period a year ago and a decrease of $115 billion in spending.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703196352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349703493048-12</Id><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Msg>Austerity continues to work wonders in Greece: Greece's far-right Golden Dawn party is increasingly assuming the role of law enforcement officers on the streets of the bankrupt country, with mounting evidence that Athenians are being openly directed by police to seek help from the neo-Nazi group, analysts, activists and lawyers say. In return, a growing number of Greek crime victims have come to see the party, whose symbol bears an uncanny resemblance to the swastika, as a "protector".... Far from being tamed, parliamentary legitimacy appears only to have emboldened the extremists. In recent weeks racially-motivated attacks have proliferated. Immigrants have spoken of their fear of roaming the streets at night following a spate of attacks by black-clad men on motorbikes. Street vendors from Africa and Asia have also been targeted.... One survey last week showed a near doubling in the number of people voicing "positive opinions" about Golden Dawn, up from 12% in May to 22%. The popularity of Nikos Michaloliakos, the party's rabble-rousing leader had shot up by 8 points, much more than any other party leader.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349704306946-13</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very interesting - funny how nazi's gain traction with a people that has been crushed by debt. it is the circle of life simba......</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1349704306946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349704751128-14</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NAZI defintion: National SOCIALIST WORKER'S party. Read the LEFTY Hilter's political stance!! Nice try with the NAZI propaganda of 'Far Right Wing"! Its only 'right wing' to Communists!!! Please read your History.. Being STUPID is no way to go through Life!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349704751128</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:59:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349707134167-15</Id><Title>Dipshisiot, Bain and China</Title><Msg>Huawei Bain Capital WASHINGTON -- The House intelligence committee on Monday will release a damning investigation into the Chinese telecom firm Huawei Technologies, according to a "60 Minutes" investigation that aired Sunday night. A principal aim of the two-track media and political onslaught is to warn U.S. companies not to do business with Huawei, arguing that its close relationship with the Chinese government creates unacceptable security risks. Rep. Mike Rogers (R-Mich.), the Republican chairman of the panel, delivered that warning bluntly. "If I were an American company today -- and I'll tell you this as the chairman of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence -- and you are looking at Huawei, I would find another vendor if you care about your intellectual property, if you care about your consumers' privacy, and you care about the national security of the United States of America," Rogers told "60 Minutes." One U.S. company that could've benefited from Rogers' warning is Bain Capital, the private equity giant founded by Mitt Romney, which still pays the GOP presidential nominee millions each year. Romney has made his promise to "get tough" on China a central element of his economic message, though the company he started has made it easier for China to get tough on its own citizens. In 2007 and 2008, Bain Capital partnered with Huawei -- pronounced Wa-way -- to take electronics manufacturer 3Com private in a $2.2 billion deal. The Bush administration raised national security concerns and refused to approve the deal. Huawei is closely tied to the Chinese military, and was founded by a former army major. Two years earlier, Bain had tried to buy its way into a joint partnership between 3Com and Huawei, but 3Com fended it off. Bain didn't give up. Later in 2008, it made a bid for Huawei's mobile handset unit, but the company decided not to sell. In December 2011, Bain finally got its piece of China's telecom world, buying the surveillance company Uniview from the joint venture it had failed to join. Uniview uses advance technology to enable the Chinese government to track dissidents in and out of their homes, at demonstrations, or wherever else they may travel. The New York Times highlighted the Bain-Uniview relationship earlier this year: The Bain-owned company, Uniview Technologies, produces what it calls “infrared antiriot” cameras and software that enable police officials in different jurisdictions to share images in real time through the Internet. Previous projects have included an emergency command center in Tibet that “provides a solid foundation for the maintenance of social stability and the protection of people’s peaceful life,” according to Uniview’s Web site. [snip] Li Tiantian, 45, a human rights lawyer in Shanghai, said the police used footage recorded outside a hotel in an effort to manipulate her during the three months she was illegally detained last year. The video, she said, showed her entering the hotel in the company of men other than her boyfriend. During interrogations, Ms. Li said, the police taunted her about her sex life and threatened to show the video to her boyfriend. The boyfriend, however, refused to watch, she said. “The scale of intrusion into people's private lives is unprecedented,” she said in a phone interview. “Now when I walk on the street, I feel so vulnerable, like the police are watching me all the time.” The House intelligence committee argues that if Huawei gains a foothold in the U.S., as it is attempting to do, it would be able to exploit its access to the U.S. grid in any number of ways on behalf of the Chinese government. "It's a strategic industry in the sense that an opponent can gain serious advantage ... from being able to exploit the telecommunications network," Jim Lewis, a foreign technology analyst, told "60 Minutes." "The state tells them what to do and they do it.” Neither Bain nor the Romney campaign immediately responded to requests for comment. On his website, however, Romney stands strong for human rights in China. "Any serious U.S. policy toward China must confront the fact that China's regime continues to deny its people basic political freedoms and human rights," the website reads. "The United States has an important role to play in encouraging the evolution of China toward a more politically open and democratic order."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349707134167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349707516759-16</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3.1 = 3.7 ? Your math logic is on par with our Commander in Chief. Incoherent.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349707516759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349707779966-17</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Equating Nazis with socialism is just IGNORANT!! " National Socialists, aka Nazis, were "Socialists" in roughly the same way that the "Union of Soviet Socialist Republics" was run by Republicans. It was a marketing term that reflected more the fascists' real roots in the radical ferment around socialism, but there is little question that fascism generically and Nazism specifically were right-wing phenomena. The citations available on this subject are numerous, but probably the clearest explanation comes from Robert O. Paxton in The Anatomy of Fascism, who explains that fascism for all its rhetoric was in practice closely aligned with and allied with capitalists and conservatives -- some of whom, years down the road, came to regret the association, but the vast majority of whom approved enthusiastically up through the war years. (Think Krupp.) They were also decidedly -- violently, murderously -- anti-socialist."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349707779966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349708003377-18</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try! TOTALIARIANISM is a fully owned, created EVIL product of you crapola 'Hope and Changer' Left loser #$%$!! Enjoy the next debates and LOSING in LANDSLIDE the election to President Romney. Facism IS what Dumbo has been slowly implementing into our Country!! Evil is for LOSERS, like yourself!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349708003377</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 10:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349708401941-19</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Society require order and if you defund the courts and cops, the people will turn to alternate groups be they neo-nazis or as was the case in Italy and on the streets of early New york, the mafia. "Protection rackets" flourish in such environments.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349708401941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349709612709-20</Id><Title>The Obama Years Have Forced Austerity On Millions of Americans</Title><Msg>No cutbacks for illegals and the welfare dependent, but a reduced standard of living for hard-working Americans. Or as Obama calls them, The Greedy Oppressors</Msg><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1349709612709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349709940674-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Obama Years Have Forced Austerity On Millions of Americans</Title><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1349709612709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:20:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo's EVIL plan is working. In Dumbo's World, things are moving along Great! 1- Reduction of America's Wealth and Power 2- Taxes about to go through the roof 3- Obamacare Facist takeover of healthcare 4- Next is to end that pesky "Freedom of Speech'</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349709940674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:25:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711356743-22</Id><Topic><Title>BO cleaning up the GOP mess</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703196352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GM to add 2,000 jobs in Michigan Source: Detroit News October 8, 2012 at 1:00 am GM to add 2,000 jobs in Michigan IT center to open in Warren tech campus; other projects in works General Motors Co. and the state are expected to announce today that GM will create 2,000 new jobs in Michigan, beginning with up to 1,500 at a new information technology innovation center in Warren. The automaker and the Governor's Office are expected to make formal announcements later today. It's unclear where GM would add the other 500 jobs, but the state says the innovation center is the first of three projects the company will announce. GM will invest $300 million combined for the three. The state said GM plans no major investment spending on the information technology center; it will be housed in an existing building undergoing renovation on the Warren Tech Center campus.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349711356743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349711403544-23</Id><Topic><Title>Austerity has its costs</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703493048</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:38:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So we have low crime in Palo Alto because they have enough policemen? That's Joe Biden! Stupid.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349711403544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715599522-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot, the living, breathing "liar loan"</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349652283711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sore loser!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349715599522</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 12:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715814493-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fact...Under your boy the price of gas has risen 100% and the deficit increased by 50%, how bout them apples.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349715814493</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715923580-26</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Quit now Dumbo!! Your STUPID LIE that its Romney who lies is FAILING. But Dumbo is Lying failure with a dead 'Hope and Change' crapola!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349715923580</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349715997406-27</Id><Topic><Title>I Hope the Right Wingnutz Watch the Debate</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1349308114036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-03 19:48:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan-Biden debate! Oh..Biden should 'Tap-Out' now!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349715997406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349716086887-28</Id><Topic><Title>The Obama Years Have Forced Austerity On Millions of Americans</Title><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1349709612709</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 11:20:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Next is to end that pesky "Freedom of Speech'** Done, where is the fellow who made the infamous Mulslim video...in jail.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349716086887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349716981680-29</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are so dishonest . the fact is W's last budget was about 1.68 times his first compared to 1.16 for obama So, who , you dishonest person increased federal spending by more and by what percent? It is Obvious W increased federal spending far more than the obama , but you bums only whine about obama.... who is doing a far better job than w did..... and don't forget that EVERYONE knows W had the first trillion dollar deficit in US history , and he left office whining "unless money is loosened up the sucker could go down" and most can figure out that Romney will balloon the deficit ...... he is just a rerun of bush.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349716981680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349717283221-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last Bush Budget included $700 million "TARP". That is the glitch in your 'Dumbo is Losing so I need to make pu more LIES!!"</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349717283221</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349717417411-31</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo is STUPID!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349356960487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-04 09:22:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo is a 'Harvard-Ho'!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349717417411</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718227988-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dipshidiot, the living, breathing "liar loan"</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349652283711</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:24:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"What are we to make of the fact that within 24 hours of the debate, the Governor told Fox News he had been "completely wrong" about that 47% comment in the video exposed by Mother Jones--you know, the one for which he refused to apologize two weeks ago? How should we read the fact that, in the time it takes for a hummingbird to flap its wings, Romney disowned his cronyistic $5 trillion tax cut for his friends and colleagues" My take is that Mitt is a #$%$ and a liar. and a plutocrat who meant it when he said it's not his job to represent half of all Americans......</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349718227988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:43:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718603471-33</Id><Topic><Title>President Romney WINS in Landslide!!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1348835996084</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 08:39:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Loser Liberals posting 'War and Peace' length crapola! Advice: If you got to explain in a thesis your point...YOUR LOSING! See ya at next debates and Then Election crushola of Liberal/Progressvie/Facist non-movement (more like a bowel movement)</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349718603471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349718690038-34</Id><Title>Albert Einstein dismissed the idea of God as a product of human weakness</Title><Msg>LONDON (AP) — A letter in which Albert Einstein dismissed the idea of God as a product of human weakness is being sold on eBay for a starting price of $3 million (others uses that weakness and sell people mormon underwear, papal dispensations, tickets to the "afterlife" of eternal "lifeafterdeath", or to rule over them in "god's" name)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1349718690038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349718906988-35</Id><Topic><Title>Albert Einstein dismissed the idea of God as a product of human weakness</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1349718690038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you will definitely going to HELL!! Enjoy the heat, you devil worshiper!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349718906988</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349719273893-36</Id><Topic><Title>Albert Einstein dismissed the idea of God as a product of human weakness</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1349718690038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 13:51:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you must know the devil. Do you talk to him? Have you paid for special protection from your holy moly man to keep you from going to hell? You just sinned by lying . So you might want to pay a little more for that protection.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1349719273893</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:01:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349721882422-37</Id><Topic><Title>Profit by examinging these guys right now.</Title><Username>brianwix12</Username><Timestamp>1348153109275</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 10:58:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fundamentally strong Im buying</Msg><Username>charlesblackburn97</Username><Timestamp>1349721882422</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349722515626-38</Id><Topic><Title>What You May Not Know About ETFC...</Title><Username>brucelang826</Username><Timestamp>1349703226425</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:33:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pretty much this stock will double in the next 6 months</Msg><Username>donnywest523</Username><Timestamp>1349722515626</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:55:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349722531015-39</Id><Title>Wendell Potter, American hero!!</Title><Msg>Wendell Potter: Romney's Phony Answers to Tough Health Care Questions During last week’s debate, GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney once again pledged to repeal Obamacare, but he was light on details about what he would replace it with, other than to suggest that his administration would encourage states to come up with reform plans of their own. “What we did in Massachusetts is a model for the nation, state by state,” he said. “And I said that at that time. The federal government taking over health care for the entire nation and whisking aside the 10th Amendment, which gives states the rights for these kinds of things, is not the course for America to have a stronger, more vibrant economy.” But considering that the Massachusetts law was the model for Obamacare, what, other than replicating what Massachusetts did, are the states to do? High on the list of recommendations in Romney’s health care platform is an idea frequently touted as a silver bullet by conservatives: allow insurance companies to sell policies across state lines. Doing so, they say, will increase competition and, consequently, bring down the cost of coverage. The problem is that no one had done a study to determine definitively whether the across-state-lines idea would work—until now. And the conclusion of that study, conducted by the Georgetown University Health Policy Institute, is that allowing coverage to be purchased across state lines is much more of a blank than a bullet.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349722531015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349723054998-40</Id><Topic><Title>Wendell Potter, American hero!!</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349722531015</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 14:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!! Another Liberal University study done by Tenure-Protected Liberal Professors that are at least paritally Goverment-Taxpayer funded that is against Consumer based capitalism!! WOW!! That's a Shocker!! I admit, you Liberals really HATE the Free-market.. HATE is a big theme with you.</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349723054998</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:04:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349723075354-41</Id><Topic><Title>BO cleaning up the GOP mess</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349703196352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 09:33:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Former Republican Senator, Vietnam Veteran Endorses President Obama 10/08/2012 Larry Pressler Former U.S. Senator from South Dakota As a combat veteran of two tours in Vietnam with twenty-two years of service as a Republican member of the U.S. House and Senate, I endorse President Barack Obama for a second term as our Commander-in-Chief. Candidates publicly praise our service members, veterans and their families, but President Obama supports them in word and deed, anywhere and every time. As a Vietnam vet, one of the reasons I support President Obama is because he has consistently shown he understands that our commitment to our servicemen and women may begin when they put on their uniform, but that it must never end. This decision is not easy for any lifelong Republican. In 2008 I voted for Barack Obama, the first time I ever voted for a Democrat, because the Republican Party was drifting toward a dangerous path that put extreme party ideology above national interest. Mitt Romney heads a party remaining on that dangerous path, proving the emptiness of their praise as they abandon our service members, veterans and military families along the way. What really set me off was Romney's reference to 47% of Americans to be written off -- including any veteran collecting disability .</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349723075354</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:04:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349723207387-42</Id><Title>BO is a SMELLY MESS!!</Title><Msg>The whole campaign of 'Romney Lies' is soo funny as President Romney's poll numbers keep going up! 'Hope and Change' is just CRAP!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349723207387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349724920990-43</Id><Topic><Title>BO is a SMELLY MESS!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349723207387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This board is populated wif sick individuals who voted for the leaderless one back in '08 and who cannot bring themselves to admit they made a mistake despite all the evidence to the contrary. It's a clear disconnect wif reality, masking serious psychological issues for which help is urgently needed.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349724920990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349725007052-44</Id><Topic><Title>BO is a SMELLY MESS!!</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349723207387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:06:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Hope and Changers' still clinging to their Koran and 'Che' t-shirts!!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349725007052</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349725272657-45</Id><Topic><Title>Bush increased federal government spending 2X as much as Obama</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349627065735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:24:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush - 1.2x in first 3 years. . Obama - 1.19x in 3. Never under George W Bush federal budget exceeded $450B. Federal revenue under Obama is not even close to $2.7T riched in 2007 under George W Bush. And this is the reason for sky rocketed debt and deficit since spending didn't slow down.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349725272657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 15:41:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349728033537-46</Id><Title>a typican quote from pacifican showing he is 100% wrong</Title><Msg>"Never under George W Bush federal budget exceeded $450B" pacifican here are the facts: W's 1st budget ...$1.9 trillion W's last budget....$3.2 trillion obama's 1st....$3.2 trillion ...............2012..$3.6 trillion do note that W's last budget was about 1.7 times his first........ WOW huge increase in spending, nearly twice what his first............. compared to obama's increase of 1.15 times his first.......... Bush OBVIOUSLY increased federal government spending MORE than has obama.... it is just a fact. Naturally dishonest pacifican can't deal with it and has to spin, obfuscate and lie or what every you can call his quote above. Maybe he means deficit and not budget? in which case he is STILL wrong because 2009 was a GEORGE W BUSH budget and it was for $3.2 trillion and it was also the first every $1 trillion deficit in US history.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349728033537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349728972827-47</Id><Title>first $1 trillion deficit in USA history was the George W bush budget for 2009</Title><Msg>2009 United States federal budget From Wikipedia, The United States federal budget for fiscal year 2009 began as a spending request by President George W. Bush to fund government operations for October 2008 – September 2009. $3.107 trillion (requested) Deficit $1.413 trillion</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349728972827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:42:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349729490850-48</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh PLEEZ!!! Someone post some really, really long post again and again about Bush budget!!! Don't forget to re-post the same crapola again!!</Msg><Username>profit_swine</Username><Timestamp>1349729490850</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:51:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349729964574-49</Id><Title>Pew! Brak skunk it up worse than anyone had expected.</Title><Msg>Pew: Romney Leads By 4 In Post-Debate Survey By Tom Kludt | Romney Leads By 4 In Post-Debate … In the first national poll to be conducted entirely after the opening presidential debate, former Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney now leads President Barack Obama by 4 points. The poll, conducted by Pew Research Center from Thursday through Sunday and released on Monday, shows Romney leading Obama among likely voters nationwide, 49 percent to 45 percent. That's a stark contrast from Pew's mid-September poll after both parties' conventions, which showed Obama up 8 points among likely voters. The dramatic 12-point swing in Pew's poll from Obama to Romney is perhaps the strongest piece of evidence to date that the president has paid a political price for his listless performance in the Denver debate. But the complete suite of post-debate surveys from national pollsters is only beginning to emerge, and the early indications are of a less dramatic shift than Pew is showing.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349729964574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:59:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349736168609-50</Id><Title>Etrade.</Title><Msg>Test message.</Msg><Username>brandish_now</Username><Timestamp>1349736168609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349736753115-51</Id><Topic><Title>Pew! Brak skunk it up worse than anyone had expected.</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349729964574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:59:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brak unwittingly becomes best player on Rumney's team. Oh what a kick in the teeth that's gotta be for the libtart lemming faithful.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349736753115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 18:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349737591061-52</Id><Topic><Title>a typican quote from pacifican showing he is 100% wrong</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349728033537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant budget deficit. Thought you are smart enough to catch that. $1T is complete fabrication.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1349737591061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:06:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349738634573-53</Id><Title>Another Obama achievement</Title><Msg>Kinda makes you wonder about the big drop in the uneployment number... Chicago style. Number Of Americans On Food Stamps Hits Another Record High About 46.68 million Americans received food stamps in July, the government said in a report released late on Friday afternoon before a holiday weekend, a traditional time for dumping bad news. The report for July, the most recent month that data was available, showed participation up by 11,532 from June and 2.9 percent higher than a year earlier. “When the president took office, 32 million people on food stamps — 47 million on food stamps today,” Republican Mitt Romney said in last week’s presidential debate. “Going forward with the status quo is not going to cut it for the American people who are struggling.”</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349738634573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349739277205-54</Id><Title>47% of food stamp recipients are children</Title><Msg>Another 15% are elderly poor. The Bush recession is by far the greatest single cause of the rise of food stamp recipients. Just the facts. Phoenix Mayor Attempts To Live On A Food Stamp Budget: ‘I’m Tired, And It’s Hard To Focus’ By Travis Waldron When local activist groups challenged Phoenix Mayor Greg Stanton to live on a food stamp budget for a week to mark Hunger Awareness Month, he took them up on the offer and found out just how hard it was. Stanton kept a diary on the challenge, which allotted him roughly $29 a week, the same amount 1.1 million Arizonans receive from the Supplemental Assistance Nutrition Program (SNAP) each week. By day four, Stanton noted that he was “tired” and “it’s hard to focus” after leaving the house for work without time to scramble eggs or eat a decent breakfast: OK- ran out the door today with no time to scramble eggs or even make a sandwich. So I’m surviving on an apple and handful of peanuts, and the coffee I took to the office until dinner. I’m tired, and it’s hard to focus. I can’t go buy a sandwich because that would be cheating- even the dollar menu at Taco Bell is cheating. You can’t use SNAP benefits at any restaurants, fast food or otherwise. I’m facing a long, hungry day and an even longer night getting dinner on the table, which requires making EVERYTHING from scratch on this budget. It’s only for a week, so I’ve got a decent attitude. If I were doing this with no end in sight, I probably wouldn’t be so pleasant. Watch a local news report about Stanton’s challenge, via Huffington Post’s Bonnie Kavoussi: According to Stanton’s Facebook page, the city he governs ranks 34th-worst among America’s 100 largest metro areas in terms of hunger, and one-in-four Arizona children are food insecure. Across the nation, there are more than 46 million people receiving SNAP benefits. Despite the challenges presented by poverty and hunger, Republicans have proposed cuts to the programs that help struggling families afford food. The House GOP budget could kick millions out of SNAP and hundreds of thousands of children out of school lunch programs, exacerbating the high rates of food insecurity America’s families are already facing.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349739277205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:34:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349739361630-55</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama achievement</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349738634573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You maroons never stop to think that there is also a RECORD number of Americans ! Every day the population grows. So it's easy for the intellectually dishonest to manipulate the headlines. BTW; how about those gas prices in Riverside ??? Free market at work !</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1349739361630</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349739616184-56</Id><Title>Republican Endorses Death Penalty for Children</Title><Msg>This is Pro Life ? Charlie Fuqua, the Republican candidate for the Arkansas House of Representatives who called for expelling Muslims from the United States in his book, also wrote in support for instituting the death penalty for "rebellious children." In "God's Law," Fuqua's 2012 book, the candidate wrote that while parents love their children, a process could be set up to allow for the institution of the death penalty for "rebellious children," according to the Arkansas Times. Fuqua, who is anti-abortion, points out that the course of action involved in sentencing a child to death is described in the Bible and would involve judicial approval. While it is unlikely that many parents would seek to have their children killed by the government, Fuqua wrote, such power would serve as a way to stop rebellious children. UnFrickkingBelievable</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1349739616184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349739679072-57</Id><Title>GOP voter fraud is oddly ignored by their media flacks</Title><Msg>FL GOP FIRES ROMNEY CONSULTANT'S VOTER REGISTRATION FIRM AFTER FRAUDULENT FORMS REPORTED IN PALM BEACH COUNTY Firm owned by notorious GOP operative Nathan Sproul, accused of destroying Democratic registration forms in years past, hired 'at request of RNC', still operating in several key swing states... By Brad The Republican Party of Florida's top recipient of 2012 expenditures, a firm by the name of Strategic Allied Consulting, was just fired on Tuesday night, after more than 100 apparently fraudulent voter registration forms were discovered to have been turned in by the group to the Palm Beach County, FL Supervisor of Elections. The firm appears to be another shell company of Nathan Sproul, a longtime, notorious Republican operative, hired year after year by GOP Presidential campaigns, despite being accused of shredding Democratic voter registration forms in a number of states over several past elections. According to the Center for Responsive Politics, Strategic Allied Consulting has been paid some $667,000 this year by the FL GOP, presumably to run its voter registration campaigns in the state. That number, however, does not account for another identical payment made in August. The Palm Beach Post is reporting tonight that the firm received "more than $1.3 million" from the Republican Party of Florida "to register new voters." The firm is not only tied to the FL GOP, but also to the Mitt Romney Campaign, which hired Sproul as a political consultant late last year, despite years of fraud allegations against his organizations in multiple states. Moreover, the firm is also reportedly operating similar voter registration operations on behalf of the Republican Party, to the tune of hundreds of thousands of dollars, in a number of key battleground states this year, including North Carolina, Virginia and Colorado. Strategic Allied has recently taken steps to hide their ownership by Sproul's notorious firm, Sproul &amp; Associates. Palm Beach County Supervisor of Election Susan Bucher confirmed to The BRAD BLOG late this evening that she turned over 106 suspicious voter registration applications to the Florida State Attorney during a meeting yesterday afternoon in Palm Beach, after the "questionable" applications were submitted to her office by a worker for Strategic Allied. The forms were said to all have similar signatures, changed addresses and party affiliations, and other defects which appear to have all been done by the same hand. The case emerging in Florida tonight mirrors a similar incident reported earlier this year when more than a thousand fraudulent voter registration forms were discovered to have been turned in to the Sacramento County, CA Registrar of Voters by a group hired by that state's Republican Party. But that's not the only similar case, as a massive GOP voter registration scheme, which appears to involve the upper-echelons of the national party, begins to emerge... 'Questionable' registrations in Palm Beach The Palm Beach Post reports tonight that Bucher turned the "questionable" applications over to FL State Attorney Peter Antonacci and Chief Assistant State Attorney Paul Zacks during a meeting on Monday in "an abundance of caution" after her staff "had questions about similar-looking signatures, missing information and wrong addresses on the forms." The paper reports that "some of the applications she questioned were for new voter registrations while others were for address or party affiliation changes or requests for new voter cards." According to the FL Election Code, the alteration of a "voter registration application...without the other person's knowledge and consent" is a third degree felony, punishable by a $5,000 fine and up to five years in jail. Similarly, the willful submission of "any false voter registration information" is also a third degree felony. (Though don't tell fading GOP superstar Ann Coulter that, since she submitted fraudulent information on her own voter registration form --- in Palm Beach County, FL, coincidentally --- back in 2005, before knowingly voting at the wrong precinct illegally, as we have covered in great detail here over the years. The Post reports that "The 106 applications flagged by Bucher were part of a batch of 304 turned in Sept. 5 by the contractor, using the Republican Party of Florida’s identification number." As of tonight, the Republican Party of Florida (RPOF) says they have fired the firm, which they claim they had hired at the request of the Republican National Party. "When we learned today about the instances of potential voter registration fraud that occurred in Palm Beach County," RPOF Director Mike Grissom said, "we immediately informed the Republican National Committee that we were terminating the contract with the voter registration vendor we hired at their request because there is no place for voter registration fraud in Florida." Palm Beach Post reports that Strategic Allied Consulting was given "identical payments of $667,598 in July and August" by the RPOF. Strategic Allied Consulting Strategic Allied Consulting, which has only a single-page, generic website (including typos, as seen above) has been advertising for paid registration workers on "Craigslist, Monster Jobs, Jobs Indeed, Conservative Jobs, etc.," according to a source who has been researching them over the past several days. Late last month, Greg Flynn at the North Carolina blog BlueNC reported on some of their job listings seeking workers in that swing-state, which Obama narrowly won in 2008, offering to pay anywhere from $11 to $13 per hour. "WANT TO HELP REPUBLICANS WIN IN NC?," reads one ad, "We are currently hiring self-motivated people to contact voters for the election. No experience needed! We are paying $13/per hour for this program." "Are you interested in helping Mitt Romney win North Carolina?," reads another, "I am with the North Carolina Republican Party working with Voter Registration Projects and am looking for team members to help expand Republican voter registration." "Republican Voter Registration Captains Needed," begins another, requesting applicants submit resumes to John Bria of Strategic Allied Consulting. "Help GOP candidates win in November and become an integral part a [sic] presidential campaign." "Employees will go to high traffic areas, identify conservative voters, ensure that their voter registration is up to date, and then report back at night with their data and the voter registration forms that they collected." Curiously, that's exactly what is seen in a rather breathtaking viral video we reported on this morning revealing a young voter registration worker in Colorado Springs, CO (El Paso County), asking a potential registrant, "Would you vote for Romney or Obama?" before she would offer a voter registration form. While the worker, when pressed, reluctantly admitted, "we're out here in support of Romney," she then claimed to be working for the El Paso County Clerk's office. In fact, as we reported, the El Paso County Republican Party Chairman has since admitted the young lady was working for the party. Following publication of our story, we were informed by a tipster that the young lady was actually hired by a third-party contractor, though we have not yet been able to either confirm that point, or identify the name of the contractor. BlueNC reports, however, that, in addition to FEC campaign filings showing the NC Republican Party paid some $333,000 to Strategic Allied Consulting for services in that state in July, "There is evidence that similar operations are being conducted in Colorado, Florida and Virginia on behalf of the Republican Party." Was the young worker in Colorado Springs hired by Strategic Allied Consulting for her work with the local GOP? The techniques described in the NC help wanted ads sound very familiar to what was seen on video tape in CO. At BlueNC, Flynn reports "The company was set up in Virginia in June 2012 and filings with the Virginia Secretary of State reveal no identifying information other than that of a corporate filing service." He adds: "There is no evidence of business registration in either North Carolina, Colorado, or Florida (or Arizona)," where Sproul's Sproul &amp; Associates is based. At the time of BlueNC's report, the domain StrategicAlliedConsulting dotcom was registered to Sproul &amp; Associates in Tempe, Arizona. The day after they published their report, the domain name registration was quickly changed to "private", but not before Flynn was able to grab a screen shot confirming the ownership of the domain: The notorious Nathan Sproul We've reported on Sproul many times over the years, as the GOP operative, and former chair of the Arizona GOP and the state's Christian Coalition, pops up again and again in each Presidential Election year. He is hired over and over by the Republican Party, despite years of fraud allegations in multiple states against his organizations, which are said to have routinely changed or entirely destroyed Democratic voter registrations. He operates as Sproul &amp; Associates as well as Lincoln Strategy Group, among other names, including now, apparently, Strategic Allied Consulting. And this year, after being hired by the Bush/Cheney campaign in '04 and the McCain/Palin campaign in '08, Sproul was "quietly" hired by the Romney campaign as a political consultant late last year, according to a June report from Lee Fang at the non-partisan Republic Report: Late last year, Mitt Romney’s presidential campaign began paying Nathan Sproul, a political consultant with a long history of destroying Democratic voter registration forms and manipulating ballot initiatives. Sproul, who changed his firm’s name from Sproul and Associates to Lincoln Strategies, has received over $70,000 from Romney’s campaign ... Republic Report reviewed disclosures from the Federal Elections Commission. Sproul’s Lincoln Strategy Group has received about $71,391 in payments for “field consulting” and “rent &amp; utilities” by the Romney for President Inc. committee from November 30th through March 2nd of this year. Fang then goes on to highlight what he describes as some of Sproul's "greatest hits" as detailed by ThinkProgress while reporting on Sproul's Lincoln Strategies astroturf work for a so-called "Clean Coal" industry campaign in 2009 [emphasis in original]: - In Oregon and Nevada, Lincoln Strategies - then known as Sproul and Associates - was investigated for destroying Democratic voter registration forms. The Bush-Cheney 2004 presidential campaign paid Sproul $7.4 million for campaign work. [CNN, 10/14/04; KGW News, 10/13/04; East Valley Tribune, 09/07/06] - In Nevada, people who registered as Democrats with Lincoln Strategies - then known as Sproul and Associates - found their names absent from the voter registration rolls. [Reno Gazette-Journal, 10/29/04] - During the 2006 midterm elections, Wal-Mart banned Lincoln Strategies for partisan voter registration efforts in Tennessee. The Republican National Committee had hired the firm. [Associated Press, 08/24/06] - In Arizona, Lincoln Strategies employed a variety of deceptive tactics - including systematically lying about the bill - to push a ballot initiative to eviscerate the state's clean elections law. [Salon, 10/21/04] - Lincoln Strategies, then employed by the Republican Party, was behind efforts to place Ralph Nader on the ballot in states such as Arizona. [American Prospect, 06/25/04] Despite all of those years of allegations, the McCain campaign went on to hire Sproul in 2008, according to Sam Stein at Huffington Post, who reported at the time: John McCain's campaign has directed $175,000 to the firm of a Republican operative accused of massive voter registration fraud in several states. According to campaign finance records, a joint committee of the McCain-Palin campaign, the RNC and the California Republican Party, made a $175,000 payment to the group Lincoln Strategy in June for purposes of "registering voters." The managing partner of that firm is Nathan Sproul, a renowned GOP operative who has been investigated on multiple occasions for suppressing Democratic voter turnout, throwing away registration forms and even spearheading efforts to get Ralph Nader on ballots to hinder the Democratic ticket. ... That Sproul would come under the employment umbrella of the McCain campaign --- the Republican National Committee has also separately paid Lincoln Strategy at least $37,000 for voter registration efforts this cycle --- is not terribly surprising. Sproul, who has donated nearly $30,000 to McCain's campaign, has been in the good graces of GOP officials for the past decade despite charges of ethical and potentially legal wrongdoing. In Fang's report, he goes on to note that "Even former Rep. Chris Cannon (R-UT), during a hearing on voter fraud, admitted that 'the difference between ACORN and Sproul is that ACORN doesn't throw away or change registration documents after they have been filled out.'" GOP voter registration fraud epidemic continues As we described earlier today, in our story on the disturbing Colorado GOP voter registration worker video, while Republicans had long been critical of fraudulent voter registration efforts they inaccurately attributed to ACORN, the non-partisan, four-decade old community organizing group (which has since been forced into bankruptcy as a result of the years-long GOP effort to mischaracterize them and their work) there is no evidence, to our knowledge, that any of its tens of thousands of registration workers ever screened out potential registrants from one party or another before allowing them to register, as seen in CO. Neither is there evidence that any of their workers ever changed party affiliations on registration forms, as is being alleged tonight in Palm Beach County, or destroyed Democratic forms, as has been alleged over the years, as noted by Republican Rep. Cannon. Moreover, it should be noted that of the handful of ACORN registration workers who submitted fraudulent applications over the years, almost all of those workers were turned into officials by ACORN themselves. The group checked all applications for validity before turning them in, flagged those which appeared to be fraudulent, and then turned them in to officials, along with the names of the workers who had defrauded them. Contrast that with the disturbing activities of Sproul &amp; Associates, Lincoln Strategies and now Sproul's Strategic Allied Consulting, along with what was admitted to by the Republican Party today in Colorado, and revealed by a number of recent cases of massive registration fraud by the Republican Party in California. (For the record, ACORN was never hired to do registration work by the Democratic Party, despite inaccurate Republican claims to the contrary.) In 2006, GOP voter registration firms in California were reported by the LA Times to have turned in thousands of invalid registration forms, as well as fraudulent signatures on petitions in San Bernardino County. In once instance, "About 4,800 of more than 5,600 signatures submitted [by John Burkett Petition Management] were found to be invalid and were tossed out by election officials," the paper reported. In 2008, at the height of that year's GOP/Fox "News" ACORN "voter fraud" scam, a group calling itself Young Political Majors (YPM) was hired by the CA Republican Party to do voter registration. The firm was reportedly paid $7 to $12 for every Californian it registered as a member of the GOP. YPM was subsequently found to have been changing thousands of voter registration forms from Democratic to Republican. The group's CEO, Mark Anthony Jacoby, was eventually arrested (see video of my appearance announcing the news on Fox in a live "Fox News Alert" that year) before he later pleaded guilty to voter registration fraud. And, earlier this year, in 2012, the Sacramento Republican Party was found to have hired Momentum Political Services, a firm headed up by a woman described as a "professional con-artist". The group allegedly turned in thousands of fraudulent voter registrations as part of a $50,000 bounty scheme seeking Republican registrations, as paid for by the GOP in the district of Republican Congressman Dan Lungren. All the while, Republicans were loudly accusing Democrats of committing "voter fraud" requiring polling place Photo ID restrictions to stop it, even though there are just 10 known cases of in-person impersonation --- the only type of voter fraud that can possibly be deterred by Photo ID --- out of hundreds of millions of votes cast in all 50 states since 2000, according to a recent exhaustive report by the non-partisan investigative news consortium, News21. Perhaps it's a case of projection. Perhaps the GOP knows about the fraud that they are carrying out, so they presume that Democrats must be doing something similar. Nonetheless, when it comes to voter registration fraud, Republicans are the champs, hands down. And it remains to be seen how wide and how high this story will go. This one may have legs. As to actual voter fraud, it's Republicans --- and very high profile ones at that, including Mitt Romney himself --- who are winning that contest as well. See our recent report detailing 10+ recent cases of voter fraud and other related election fraud crimes by very high profile Republicans right here.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349739679072</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349739997663-58</Id><Title>Tax math simplified for short attention span GOP droolers</Title><Msg>President Obama's traveling press secretary Runs Through $5 Trillion Tax Math With Reporters Jen Psaki, traveling press secretary for the Obama campaign, started the press gaggle aboard Air Force One Sunday by running through the math of Mitt Romney's tax plan, according to a readout of the gaggle. "I just wanted to go through some simple 'back of the notecard' math on how we get to the $5 trillion ," Psaki said. So lowering the rates, as Mitt Romney has said he would do, to 20 percent -- $2.7 trillion over 10 years; eliminating the AMT -- $700 billion; repealing high-income payroll tax -- $300 billion; ending estate tax -- $150 billion; lowering the corporate rate from 35 to 25 -- $1.1 trillion. That adds up to $4.8 trillion. If you factor in interest for additional borrowing, you get to $5 trillion.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349739997663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349740023962-59</Id><Title>Husseini Obomba getting donations from China ?</Title><Msg>Chinese returning favor for outsourcing Solyndra jobs to China an paying for it with our tax money ? Major questions being raised “about the legality of tens of millions of small donor donations” to Obama – including major links to a bundler in Shanghai, China. - Washington Examiner</Msg><Username>leftie_weezner</Username><Timestamp>1349740023962</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349740442475-60</Id><Title>Romney explains his sudden revival</Title><Msg>Romney Proudly Explains How He's Turned Campaign Around--"I'm Lying More," He Says BOSTON—For weeks many Beltway insiders had written off the Romney campaign as dead, saying the candidate had dug himself into too deep a hole with too little time to recover. However, with a month to go before ballots are cast, Romney has pulled even with President Obama, and the former Massachusetts governor credits his rejuvenated campaign to one, singular tactic: lying a lot. “I’m lying a lot more, and my lies are far more egregious than they’ve ever been,” a smiling Romney told reporters while sitting in the back of his campaign bus, adding that when faced with a choice to either lie or tell the truth, he will more than likely lie. “It’s a strategy that works because when I lie, I’m essentially telling people what they want to hear, and people really like hearing things they want to hear. Even if they sort of know that nothing I’m saying is true.” “It’s a freeing strategy, really, because I don’t have to worry about facts or being accurate or having any concrete positions of any kind,” Romney added. Romney said he is telling at least 80 percent more lies now than he was two months ago. Buoyed by his strong debate performance, which by his own admission included 40 or 50 instances of lying in one 90-minute period, the candidate said he will continue to “just openly lie his butt off” until the Nov. 6 election. Once again, The Onion is the most accurate source of news.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349740442475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349741063732-61</Id><Title>Investors need to think about this</Title><Msg>Stocks Return More With Democrat in White House: By Bob Drummond - Feb 22, 2012 While Republicans promote themselves as the friendliest party for Wall Street, stock investors do better when Democrats occupy the White House. From a dollars- and-cents standpoint, it’s not even close. The BGOV Barometer shows that, over the five decades since John F. Kennedy was inaugurated, $1,000 invested in a hypothetical fund that tracks the Standard &amp; Poor’s 500 Index (SPX) only when Democrats are in the White House would have been worth $10,920 at the close of trading yesterday. That’s more than nine times the dollar return an investor would have realized from following a similar strategy during Republican administrations. A $1,000 stake invested in a fund that followed the S&amp;P 500 under Republican presidents, starting with Richard Nixon, would have grown to $2,087 on the day George W. Bush left office. “The market does tend to do better under Democrats than under Republicans,” Sam Stovall, chief investment strategist at S&amp;P Equity Research in New York, said in a telephone interview. “Is it because Republicans mishandled the economy, or inherited a weak economy? I’ll leave that to others.” Some of the difference may stem from the fact that every Republican president since at least the end of World War II has faced a recession during his first term in office, Stovall said. Nine of 11 recessions that began since 1945 -- and seven of eight since Kennedy ran for president in 1960 --started with Republicans in the Oval Office. Wall Street Republicans Democratic administrations also may be more likely to spend money on government programs that stimulate the economy, Stovall said. “I dare say that most people on Wall Street are Republicans,” Stovall said. “But it appears the bread is buttered on the Democratic side.” The S&amp;P 500 yesterday hit its highest intra-day level since June 2008 and closed at 1,362.21, the highest since last April 29. The benchmark index is up 8.3 percent so far in 2012, the biggest year-to-date gain at this point since 1991. Since Kennedy took office, the Democratic S&amp;P fund logged a 992 percent gain, versus 109 percent growth for the opposition party, even though Democrats occupied the White House for 23 years over the period, compared with 28 years of Republican presidential leadership. The annualized return for 23 years of Democratic administrations is 11 percent, or four times the 2.7 percent annualized return during 28 years of Republican presidencies. Democratic Edge Investing $1,000 in funds that mirror the Dow Jones Industrial Average under the same conditions, Democratic investors would have had $7,550, versus $2,716 under Republicans. The Democratic edge is so large that the party comes out ahead even without counting Bill Clinton (the Democrat with the biggest S&amp;P 500 gain) and George W. Bush (the Republican with the worst market record). A hypothetical $1,000 investment under Democrats excluding Clinton was worth $3,539 versus $3,296 invested under Republicans except Bush. Adding Dwight Eisenhower to the Republican column doesn’t overcome the Democratic advantage, either: $1,000 invested in the S&amp;P 500 in January 1953 would have been worth $4,796 after 36 years under Republican chief executives -- still less than half the $10,920 nest egg accumulated in 23 years under Democrats.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349741063732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349741450551-62</Id><Topic><Title>Presidne Romney (Winning!!!)</Title><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349653516160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:45:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes! Dumbo is D.O.A.!! Over, BABY!!</Msg><Username>q4bike</Username><Timestamp>1349741450551</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349742592514-63</Id><Topic><Title>Romney explains his sudden revival</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1349740442475</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:54:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey JB... You know Pew has Romney out in Front now...and it must be Scaring the Hell out of You! You are going to have to find a new job after the elections...and I have a feeling you will just flip sides and start bashing the Left!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1349742592514</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349744092702-64</Id><Title>Dipshidiot tied to Chinese spy firm</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- The House intelligence committee on Monday will release a damning investigation into the Chinese telecom firm Huawei Technologies, according to a "60 Minutes" investigation that aired Sunday night. A principal aim of the two-track media and political onslaught is to warn U.S. companies not to do business with Huawei, arguing that its close relationship with the Chinese government creates unacceptable security risks. Rep. Mike Rogers (R-Mich.), the Republican chairman of the panel, delivered that warning bluntly. "If I were an American company today -- and I'll tell you this as the chairman of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence -- and you are looking at Huawei, I would find another vendor if you care about your intellectual property, if you care about your consumers' privacy, and you care about the national security of the United States of America," Rogers told "60 Minutes." One U.S. company that could've benefited from Rogers' warning is Bain Capital, the private equity giant founded by Mitt Romney, which still pays the GOP presidential nominee millions each year. Romney has made his promise to "get tough" on China a central element of his economic message, though the company he started has made it easier for China to get tough on its own citizens. In 2007 and 2008, Bain Capital partnered with Huawei -- pronounced Wa-way -- to take electronics manufacturer 3Com private in a $2.2 billion deal. The Bush administration raised national security concerns and refused to approve the deal. Huawei is closely tied to the Chinese military, and was founded by a former army major. Two years earlier, Bain had tried to buy its way into a joint partnership between 3Com and Huawei, but 3Com fended it off. Bain didn't give up. Later in 2008, it made a bid for Huawei's mobile handset unit, but the company decided not to sell. In December 2011, Bain finally got its piece of China's telecom world, buying the surveillance company Uniview from the joint venture it had failed to join. Uniview uses advance technology to enable the Chinese government to track dissidents in and out of their homes, at demonstrations, or wherever else they may travel. The New York Times highlighted the Bain-Uniview relationship earlier this year: The Bain-owned company, Uniview Technologies, produces what it calls “infrared antiriot” cameras and software that enable police officials in different jurisdictions to share images in real time through the Internet. Previous projects have included an emergency command center in Tibet that “provides a solid foundation for the maintenance of social stability and the protection of people’s peaceful life,” according to Uniview’s Web site. [snip] Li Tiantian, 45, a human rights lawyer in Shanghai, said the police used footage recorded outside a hotel in an effort to manipulate her during the three months she was illegally detained last year. The video, she said, showed her entering the hotel in the company of men other than her boyfriend. During interrogations, Ms. Li said, the police taunted her about her sex life and threatened to show the video to her boyfriend. The boyfriend, however, refused to watch, she said. “The scale of intrusion into people's private lives is unprecedented,” she said in a phone interview. “Now when I walk on the street, I feel so vulnerable, like the police are watching me all the time.” The House intelligence committee argues that if Huawei gains a foothold in the U.S., as it is attempting to do, it would be able to exploit its access to the U.S. grid in any number of ways on behalf of the Chinese government. "It's a strategic industry in the sense that an opponent can gain serious advantage ... from being able to exploit the telecommunications network," Jim Lewis, a foreign technology analyst, told "60 Minutes." "The state tells them what to do and they do it.” Neither Bain nor the Romney campaign immediately responded to requests for comment. On his website, however, Romney stands strong for human rights in China. "Any serious U.S. policy toward China must confront the fact that China's regime continues to deny its people basic political freedoms and human rights," the website reads. "The United States has an important role to play in encouraging the evolution of China toward a more politically open and democratic order."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349744092702</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 20:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349745710996-65</Id><Title>DIPSHIDIOT'S DIARY</Title><Msg>Mon Oct 08, 2012 at 06:00 PM PDT The Chronicles of Mitt: Oct 8, 2012 by Hunter pen on paper: 'Dear diary' Hello, human diary. It is I again, Mitt Romney, your better. Today I gave a major speech on what my foreign policy would be, if I had one. I do not know what was in it; all I was required to do was read the statement prepared for me by my foreign policy advisers. I do not like meeting with that group—they are odd individuals, and tend towards whispered discussions and inappropriate humors—so I had a lower member of the staff obtain the speech from them. The papers smell strongly of cigar smoke and beef jerky. My staff had to cut much of their proposed language out, mostly a large number of paragraphs explaining which nations can go to hell and what efforts I would undertake as president in order to send them there. Eric F. said that commoner units do not like sending more than one or two other nations to hell at once, as the implementation of such poses considerable burdens on the commoner class, and that we should therefore pare the list considerably for now. (There was also a full three pages of language about how Russia and China could perform a specific bodily function on themselves, all of which needed to be cut due to broadcast decency rulings.) The foreign policy team was apparently quite chagrined, but I had word sent to them that we could add the other language back in once I was safely elected. Fallout from the Big Bird incident continues. On advice of staff, I have declined to participate further in something called the Nickelodeon "Kids Pick The President" special. Apparently I had been expected to answer questions posed to me by small children, but after promising to fire the large television bird my staff judged that too many of the questions from that demographic would likely be hostile. Apparently all other presidential candidates have participated in this event over the years, but all other presidential candidates have also released multiple years of tax returns as well—I do not think our campaign needs to be unduly burdened by such traditions. It is a shame, because the network is named after money, or after a machine in which people deposit money, and so I had felt an immediate kinship. (I also am constantly surrounded by child units, although my versions are of more appropriate wealth). I am not, however, willing to risk taking questions from young children in public. There are too many dangers involved. My experiment in forgoing all sleep has been terminated. Over the weekend my staff explained to me that I had indeed been sleeping each night, but that I was simply not aware of it because I was not conscious at the time.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1349745710996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 21:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349748363515-66</Id><Topic><Title>a typican quote from pacifican showing he is 100% wrong</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349728033537</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 16:27:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican the liar. the fact is, Pacifican, the budget george w bush submitted for fy 2009 requested $3.1 trillion and resulted in a deficit of well over $1 trillion, and who could forget what the classy W said : "unless money is loosend up, the sucker could go down" 2009 United States federal budget From Wikipedia, The United States federal budget for fiscal year 2009 began as a spending request by President George W. Bush to fund government operations for October 2008 – September 2009. $3.107 trillion (requested) Deficit $1.413 trillion</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1349748363515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 22:06:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349748375065-67</Id><Title>An Ode to junglebob</Title><Msg>Brak destroys his reelection chances. I've seen where they show Rumney debating an empty chair. The only way it could be made more realistic would have been to dump a fresh steaming pile onto the seat. I hate these long stories but I be making an exception for this one. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Did Obama Just Throw The Entire Election Away? The Pew poll is devastating, just devastating. Before the debate, Obama had a 51 - 43 lead; now, Romney has a 49 - 45 lead. That's a simply unprecedented reversal for a candidate in October. Before Obama had leads on every policy issue and personal characteristic; now Romney leads in almost all of them. Obama's performance gave Romney a 12 point swing! I repeat: a 12 point swing. Romney's favorables are above Obama's now. Yes, you read that right. Romney's favorables are higher than Obama's right now. That gender gap that was Obama's firewall? Over in one night: Currently, women are evenly divided (47% Obama, 47% Romney). Last month, Obama led Romney by 18 points (56% to 38%) among women likely voters. Seriously: has that kind of swing ever happened this late in a campaign? Has any candidate lost 18 points among women voters in one night ever? And we are told that when Obama left the stage that night, he was feeling good. That's terrifying. On every single issue, Obama has instantly plummeted into near-oblivion. He still has some personal advantages over Romney - even though they are all much diminished. Obama still has an edge on Medicare, scores much higher on relating to ordinary people, is ahead on foreign policy, and on being moderate, consistent and honest (only 14 percent of swing voters believe Romney is honest). But on the core issues of the economy and the deficit, Romney is now kicking the president's #$%$: By a 37% to 24% margin, more swing voters say Romney would improve the job situation. Swing voters favor Romney on the deficit by a two-to-one (41% vs. 20%) margin.... Romney has gained ground on several of these measures since earlier in the campaign. Most notably, Obama and Romney now run even (44% each) in terms of which candidate is the stronger leader. Obama held a 13-point advantage on this a month ago. And Obama’s 14-point edge as the more honest and truthful candidate has narrowed to just five points. In June, Obama held a 17-point lead as the candidate voters thought was more willing to work with leaders from the other party. Today, the candidates run about even on this (45% say Obama, 42% Romney). Lies work when they are unrebutted live on stage. And momentum counts at this point in the election. Now look at Pew's question as to who would help the middle cl#$%$ the most: Look: I'm trying to rally some morale, but I've never seen a candidate this late in the game, so far ahead, just throw in the towel in the way Obama did last week - throw away almost every single advantage he had with voters and manage to enable his opponent to seem as if he cares about the middle cl#$%$ as much as Obama does. How do you erase that imprinted first image from public consciousness: a president incapable of making a single argument or even a halfway decent closing statement? And after Romney's convincing Etch-A-Sketch, convincing because Obama was incapable of exposing it, Romney is now the centrist candidate, even as he is running to head up the most radical party in the modern era. How can Obama come back? By ensuring people know that Romney was and is a shameless liar and opportunist? That doesn't work for a sitting president. He always needed a clear positive proposal - tax reform, a Grand Bargain on S-B lines - as well as a sterling defense of his admirable record. Bill Clinton did the former for him. Everyone imaginable did what they could for him. And his response? Well, let's look back a bit: With President Obama holed up in a Nevada resort for debate practice, things can get pretty boring on the White House beat right now. Pretty boring for Obama too, apparently. "Basically they're keeping me indoors all the time," Obama told a supporter on the phone during a visit to a Las Vegas area field office. "It's a drag," he added. "They're making me do my homework." Too arrogant to take a core campaign responsibility seriously. Too arrogant to give his supporters what they deserve. If he now came out and said he supports Simpson-Bowles in its entirety, it would look desperate, but now that Romney has junked every proposal he ever told his base, and we're in mid-October, it's Obama's only chance on the economy. Or maybe, just maybe, Obama can regain our trust and confidence somehow in the next debate. Maybe he can begin to give us a positive vision of what he wants to do (amazing that it's October and some of us are still trying to help him, but he cannot). Maybe if Romney can turn this whole campaign around in 90 minutes, Obama can now do the same. But I doubt it. A sitting president does not recover from being obliterated on substance, style and likability in the first debate and get much of a chance to come back. He has, at a critical moment, deeply depressed his base and his supporters and independents are flocking to Romney in droves. I've never seen a candidate self-destruct for no external reason this late in a campaign before. Gore was better in his first debate - and he threw a solid lead into the trash that night. Even Bush was better in 2004 than Obama last week. Even Reagan's meandering mess in 1984 was better - and he had approaching Alzheimer's to blame. I'm trying to see a silver lining. But when a president self-immolates on live TV, and his opponent shines with lies and smiles, and a record number of people watch, it's hard to see how a president and his party recover. I'm not giving up. If the lies and propaganda of the last four years work even after Obama had managed to fight back solidly against them to get a clear and solid lead in critical states, then reality-based government is over in this country again. We're back to Bush-Cheney, but more extreme. We have to find a way to avoid that. Much, much more than Obama's vanity is at stake. (Photo: Obama as he imploded, by Andrew Harrer/Bloomberg via Getty Images.)</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349748375065</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 22:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349751445794-68</Id><Title>Truth About Jobs By PAUL KRUGMAN, 10/8/12</Title><Msg>If anyone had doubts about the madness that has spread through a large part of the American political spectrum, the reaction to Friday’s better-than expected report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics should have settled the issue. For the immediate response of many on the right — and we’re not just talking fringe figures — was to cry conspiracy....................It was nonsense, of course. Job numbers are prepared by professional civil servants, at an agency that currently has no political appointees................ Is the U.S. employment picture getting better? Yes, it is.................................... ......................On the employer side, the current numbers say that over the past year the economy added 150,000 jobs a month, and revisions will probably push that number up significantly. That’s well above the 90,000 or so added jobs per month that we need to keep up with population. (This number used to be higher, but underlying work force growth has dropped off sharply now that many baby boomers are reaching retirement age.) But remember those aging baby boomers: the fraction of American adults who are in their prime working years is falling fast. Once you take the effects of an aging population into account, the numbers show a substantial improvement in the employment picture since the summer of 2011.......... ............ we should be doing better — a shortfall largely due to the scorched-earth tactics of Republicans, who have blocked any and all efforts to accelerate the pace of recovery. (If the American Jobs Act, proposed by the Obama administration last year, had been passed, the unemployment rate would probably be below 7 percent.) ....................... The furor over Friday’s report revealed a political movement that is rooting for American failure, so obsessed with taking down Mr. Obama that good news for the nation’s long-suffering workers drives its members into a blind rage. It also revealed a movement that lives in an intellectual bubble, dealing with uncomfortable reality — whether that reality involves polls or economic data — not just by denying the facts, but by spinning wild conspiracy theories. It is, quite simply, frightening to think that a movement this deranged wields so much political power.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349751445794</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 22:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349751767288-69</Id><Title>Holy Ship!</Title><Msg>Brak, you really stepped in it this time. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Business Cruise Liner Exec Writes Scathing Letter to Obama Over New Regulations Posted on October 8, 2012 at 9:50pm by Erica Ritz A Royal Caribbean cruise ship is seen near Falmouth, Jamaica in March, 2012. (AP File Photo) The most common complaints by business-owners against the current administration tend to revolve around the economic uncertainty and increased regulation that have made it next to impossible to plan for the future. Stephanie Gallagher, the president of World City America Inc., is lending her voice to the fray after the Obama administration reportedly moved to prevent American cruise liners from being eligible to get the long-term financing under Title XI that make building something as massive as a cruise ship possible. As Royal Caribbean acquires its third Oasis-class ship from Finland, Gallagher writes that World City America has invested over a decade and $60 million in designing a “superior product” that would be built in America, by Americans, and paying taxes to the U.S. government. “Having demonstrated that our plan would be economically sound, would not cost the taxpayers anything, would not increase the debt but would improve the deficit, the only way to push us off the cliff was to enact policy that preempted the nation’s ship financing program from being used to build cruise ships. That’s what the Obama Administration did,” Gallagher claims. (AP File Photo) Gallagher’s main point of contention is that the cruise industry is overwhelmingly funded by American dollars, but the companies typically build the vessels out of the country, hire international employees, and pay far fewer taxes than a wholly American company would. Gallagher thinks the change is the result of politics and special interests, and while she notes that both parties are susceptible to such incentives, Gallagher ultimately holds the current administration responsible. Gallagher’s letter continues: “…we do blame the Obama Administration for throwing down the gauntlet…for precluding America’s long-delayed entry into this booming US-driven market; for shutting the door on what we have proven is possible and viable if the government applied the Title XI regulations as intended – not as a subsidy for special interests, but as a job-creating, economy-boosting and tax revenue-generating program and policy.” “Why, Mr. Obama, would you choose this, of all times, to lock out American shipbuilders, hotel construction companies, hundreds of US suppliers in all fifty states, and thousands of long-term self-sustaining new jobs for our dwindling Merchant Marine and US hospitality workers?” “Why…when there are twenty-three million Americans out of work, would you decide to announce a policy that America and Americans can’t participate in this booming US-driven market that has grown steadily at 7% or more every year, recession or no recession, for decades?” “All is fair in love and war,” Gallagher accepts in conclusion, adding: “but don’t tell the American people that you wake up every day thinking of ways to give the American workers a fair shot in the global economy. Don‘t claim to ’walk the walk.’”</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1349751767288</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:02:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349752765652-70</Id><Title>TAGGED WITH A PONZI SCHEME</Title><Msg>Covering Their Tracks: Firm Linked To Ponzi Scheme Erases Tagg Romney From Website Yesterday, ThinkProgress released our investigation of the Romney family’s investment firms, including Solamere Advisors and its parent company, Solamere Capital, which is run by Mitt Romney’s son Tagg. The report found that Tagg founded his firm using $10 million of Mitt’s money, and later partnered with a group of brokers who allegedly helped perpetrate one of the largest Ponzi schemes in modern history, the $8.5 billion Stanford Financial Group. After our report, the Romney campaign released a statement to ABC News and the National Journal simply attacking ThinkProgress as a “a left-wing blog with a highly partisan agenda.” Despite calling our story “false material,” the Romney spokesperson did not directly dispute any of our assertions. The Romney campaign has not explained why, for instance, Tagg Romney falsely claimed that his Solamere Advisors partners were “cleared” of wrongdoing in connection to the Stanford Financial Group Ponzi scheme. Now, it appears that one of the firms is trying to cover up its tracks. Sometime last night, Solamere Advisors, the firm run by brokers who allegedly took part in the Stanford Ponzi Scheme, deleted the section of their website that lists Tagg Romney and Spencer Zwick, the Romney for President lead fundraiser. View a screen shot of the current web address, which shows a “404 File or directory not found” error message. ortunately, ThinkProgress captured screen shots of the Romney family investment firm websites before we published our story. View a screen shot of the Solamere Advisors directors page before the deletion. In an interview last month, Tagg Romney told ThinkProgress that his partners were “cleared” from the Stanford Ponzi scheme lawsuit to retrieve what prosecutors believe are the fraudulent gains made by his partners, Tim Bambauer, Deems May, and Brandon Phillips. He also suggested that his former Stanford employee partners were the true victims since they had been promised bonuses that they had never received. In fact, in court documents obtained by ThinkProgress, none of the men have been cleared, and a court-appointed audit found that they made about $1.6 million in participating in the Stanford Ponzi scheme.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1349752765652</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:19:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349753394204-71</Id><Title>Dipshidiot defends BO's job record</Title><Msg>Mon Oct 08, 2012 at 04:30 PM PDT Romney 2006 calls Romney 2012's jobs attacks 'silly' by Laura Clawson Way back in 2006, Mitt Romney unintentionally and presciently defended Barack Obama against Romney's own attacks on Obama's jobs record: "I came in and the jobs had been just falling off a cliff. And I came in and they kept falling for 11 months. And then we turned around and we're coming back. And that's progress. "And if you're going to suggest to me that somehow the day I got elected, somehow jobs should immediately turn around, well that would be silly. It takes a while to get things turned around. We were in a recession; we were losing jobs every month, we've turned around, and since the turn around we've added 50,000 jobs. That's progress. "There will be some people who try to say, 'Well governor, net-net you've only added a few thousand jobs since you've been in.' Yeah, but ... we were in free-fall for three years and the last year of that I happened to be here and then we've turned it around as a state, private sector, government sector turned it around and now we're adding jobs.... I'm very pleased that over the last two, two-and-a-half years we've seen pretty consistent job growth." The video, which Steve Benen reminds us of now that unemployment has fallen below eight percent and Obama has presided over net positive job creation, was found by American Bridge. Remember too that Romney made these big turn-around claims despite Massachusetts having been 47th in job creation during his tenure as governor. Not only was the state not, in early 2003, in the kind of free fall that the United States was in when Barack Obama took office, but under Romney Massachusetts' recovery lagged behind almost every other state. So much of Romney's defense of himself, back in 2006, is better suited to President Obama now. Romney said then that "if you're going to suggest to me that somehow the day I got elected, somehow jobs should immediately turn around, well that would be silly." That is exactly what Romney has said about Obama's presidency—but it's actually something worse than just "silly."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1349753394204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349753614782-72</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Endorses Death Penalty for Children</Title><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1349739616184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:40:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs only care about the fetus. They think children should be digging in the mines........... Until they die. Except for their kids.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1349753614782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:33:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349754269530-73</Id><Topic><Title>Another Obama achievement</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1349738634573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 19:23:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've noticed that poor old biddermon never has a reply to posts that clarify his hypocrisy. He's a coward.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1349754269530</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-10-08 23:44:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>