<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-22"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366605028184-1</Id><Topic><Title>One man surrounded. By an army!</Title><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1366380076846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:01:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ ant little coward. You can do all your little thumbs down, but you'll never be a man. Shiver in your paranoia. Load up on guns and hide behind your door. While we liberals walk in the sun. Unafraid.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1366605028184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 00:30:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366618419399-2</Id><Title>City of Boston #$%$ Its Collective Pants</Title><Msg>Fro three days, the liberal city shut down and all the bedwetters stayed inside because they were afraid of a wounded teenager. After the cops captured the perp, they all came out to congratulate themselves.</Msg><Username>fat_french_freak</Username><Timestamp>1366618419399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 04:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366636163541-3</Id><Topic><Title>City of Boston #$%$ Its Collective Pants</Title><Username>fat_french_freak</Username><Timestamp>1366618419399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 04:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't forget the "hero" of the story - a guy that called the cops because somebody was in his boat.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1366636163541</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 09:09:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366640923072-4</Id><Topic><Title>City of Boston #$%$ Its Collective Pants</Title><Username>fat_french_freak</Username><Timestamp>1366618419399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 04:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All I got to say is #$%$.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1366640923072</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:28:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366641008281-5</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are ignorant of history. Every culture had drugs that could abort a baby. The view is quite limited from the back of your cave.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366641008281</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366642032244-6</Id><Title>"Murricans confound the Brits</Title><Msg>Why does America lose its head over 'terror' but ignore its daily gun deaths? The marathon bombs triggered a reaction that is at odds with last week's inertia over arms control Michael Cohen Michael Cohen in the US The Observer, Saturday 20 April 2013 The thriving metropolis of Boston was turned into a ghost town on Friday. Nearly a million Bostonians were asked to stay in their homes – and willingly complied. Schools were closed; business shuttered; trains, subways and roads were empty; usually busy streets eerily resembled a post-apocalyptic movie set; even baseball games and cultural events were cancelled – all in response to a 19-year-old fugitive, who was on foot and clearly identified by the news media. The actions allegedly committed by the Boston marathon bomber, Dzhokhar Tsarnaev and his brother, Tamerlan, were heinous. Four people dead and more than 100 wounded, some with shredded and amputated limbs. But Londoners, who endured IRA terror for years, might be forgiven for thinking that America over-reacted just a tad to the goings-on in Boston. They're right – and then some. What we saw was a collective freak-out like few that we've seen previously in the United States. It was yet another depressing reminder that more than 11 years after 9/11 Americans still allow themselves to be easily and willingly cowed by the "threat" of terrorism.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366642032244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366642572227-7</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not ignorant of history, that very phrase doesn't even work right. It's just that ancient history and the uses of herbs have little to nothing to do with abortion via modern medical techniques. You're bringing in a straw man so old that it's gone moldy. Almost every ancient culture had some form of slavery as well, does my unwillingness to apply slavery to a modern conundrum also mean the view is limited from the back of my cave? We're not living in history, we're living in now, it might be a GREAT idea to get used to it.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366642572227</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:56:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366643230423-8</Id><Topic><Title>City of Boston #$%$ Its Collective Pants</Title><Username>fat_french_freak</Username><Timestamp>1366618419399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 04:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A blood hound and a good tracker would have caught the punk. After all he was close to where he ditched the car he ran his brother over in-- and he was bleeding. Cops must not have had a dog they were willing to sacrifice in the event the punk kid was strapped with explosives.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1366643230423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:07:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366645099346-9</Id><Title>Criminalizing abortion</Title><Msg>is untenable. It enslaves women, denies them equal rights and creates societal economic havoc.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1366645099346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366645291187-10</Id><Topic><Title>Criminalizing abortion</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1366645099346</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:38:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed 100%</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1366645291187</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366645440054-11</Id><Title>Breaking!!!</Title><Msg>BO to be POTUS for another 196 weeks. GOP whining to continue until Hillary inaugurated. LMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1366645440054</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366645644471-12</Id><Topic><Title>"Murricans confound the Brits</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366642032244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At the same time that investigators were in the midst of a high-profile manhunt for the marathon bombers that ended on Friday evening, 38 more Americans – with little fanfare – died from gun violence. One was a 22-year old resident of Boston. They are a tiny percentage of the 3,531 Americans killed by guns in the past four months – a total that surpasses the number of Americans who died on 9/11 and is one fewer than the number of US soldiers who lost their lives in combat operations in Iraq. Yet, none of this daily violence was considered urgent enough to motivate Congress to impose a mild, commonsense restriction on gun purchasers. It's not just firearms that produce such legislative inaction. Last week, a fertiliser plant in West, Texas, which hasn't been inspected by federal regulators since 1985, exploded, killing 14 people and injuring countless others. Yet many Republicans want to cut further the funding for the agency (OSHA) that is responsible for such reviews. The vast majority of Americans die from one of four ailments – cardiovascular disease, cancer, diabetes and chronic lung disease – and yet Republicans have held three dozen votes to repeal Obamacare, which expands healthcare coverage to 30 million Americans."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366645644471</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 11:47:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366647328510-13</Id><Topic><Title>"Murricans confound the Brits</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366642032244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 10:47:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OSHA doesn't like to inspect businesses they don't understand, which is why their investigators spend most of their time investigating fast food joints. Fertilizer plants smell too much for their white collar rears. And when anti-gun zealots start doing alittle work and removing the suicides and self defense homicides from their "daily death toll" recitals, then maybe I might listen to them. Until then their bias is too obvious to attempt to employ logic as their emotional investment is higher than those who want to keep our Constitutional freedoms even though they may be despised by those they inconvenience or that are incapable of understanding them. How many fell to each type of weapon, how many suicide, how many self defense, how many home intrusions, domestic violence, black on black inner city crime, etc, etc, and how many of those incidents involved firearms illegally possessed? You can't answer the questions because all you care about are your foregone conclusions rather than the raw data used to arrive at them.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366647328510</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:15:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366649622284-14</Id><Topic><Title>City of Boston #$%$ Its Collective Pants</Title><Username>fat_french_freak</Username><Timestamp>1366618419399</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 04:13:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he smelled like a gerbil, you would have found him.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366649622284</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 12:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366655046032-15</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Learn the facts, dear. Outside of Kosovo: 489-528 civilian deaths caused by NATO bombing 3 Chinese journalists killed in NATO bombing Inside Kosovo: 2,238 Serb civilians killed or missing 230,000 Kosovo Serb, Roma and other non-Albanian civilians expelled Between 3,000 - 6,000 Kosovo Albanian civilians killed 848,000 Kosovo Albanians displaced</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366655046032</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 14:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366657581056-16</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Most)Media is wise not to wantonly apply labels where they can do more harm than good. Are you sure this was "Islamist terrorism"? Maybe they converted to Christianity the day before the bombing? So far no data came forth as to reasons these two had. Maybe they were not happy with Bostonians for some reason? Maybe they truly hated marathons? Or maybe they got an audit from Uncle Sam or owed in back taxes? That they came here from Russia is a fact. Everything else is speculation.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366657581056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366657791002-17</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For every person "saved" by religion - you can find 100 killed by it. "GOD" - the best excuse to do the inexcusable!</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366657791002</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 15:09:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366663981484-18</Id><Title>Obama the conqueror X 10</Title><Msg>Well, well, well....another sterling accomplish by the Al Green impersonator. Food Stamp Use Increased 10 Times Rate Of Job Creation Under Obama South Dakota Republican Sen. John Thune and Indiana Republican Rep. Marlin Stutzman introduced legislation Thursday aimed at saving $30 billion in the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program over a decade. Thune and Stutzman said their “Streamlining the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program Act” would eliminate waste, fraud, and abuse and close loopholes in a program that, under President Obama, has seen participation increase from 32 million to 47.8 million people and spending double to $80 billion in fiscal year 2012.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366663981484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 16:53:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366664856008-19</Id><Topic><Title>30,000 deaths in USA per year, no big deal to gop. (but they charged off to iraq)</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366426530804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those deaths are just culling the herd to the NRA and Republicans!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366664856008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366665416324-20</Id><Topic><Title>"Guns Save Lives" ?!</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366310901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The deaths from the civil war were approx. 620K which include death from diseases. Counting only battlefield deaths you are probably accurate.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366665416324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366667481798-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Children of Newtown are Ashamed of Republicans</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366256949714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excuse please, if 90% of Americans supported that BS it would have passed, the frank and honest truth is that not even 90% of liberals supported those ludicrous bills.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366667481798</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 17:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366668819736-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is an arrogant #$%$, fraud, lazy, self-centered, treacherous, vain, jealous, ignorant, cowardly liar.</Msg><Username>goodadvicedotcom</Username><Timestamp>1366668819736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 18:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366671680710-23</Id><Topic><Title>The Children of Newtown are Ashamed of Republicans</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366256949714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Excuse please, if 90% of Americans supported that BS it would have passed" Americans didn't get to vote on that. Elected Representatives did. Against the will of their constituents. You might want to bone up on the system.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366671680710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 19:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366676057812-24</Id><Topic><Title>"Guns Save Lives" ?!</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366310901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crown... I have a Gun...Several in fact. Come on by and visit me....And we will make it Six! LMAO!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1366676057812</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 20:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366688194450-25</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did I even give a hint that some kind abortion were not accessible at any time of human civilization? Or point I was making is too hard to see from your cave?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366688194450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-22 23:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>