<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-03"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370237227206-1</Id><Title>The Geezers Are All Right - by Paul Krugman</Title><Msg>The Geezers Are All Right So what are we looking at here? The latest projections show the combined cost of Social Security and Medicare rising by a bit more than 3 percent of G.D.P. between now and 2035, and that number could easily come down with more effort on the health care front. Now, 3 percent of G.D.P. is a big number, but it’s not an economy-crushing number. The United States could, for example, close that gap entirely through tax increases, with no reduction in benefits at all, and still have one of the lowest overall tax rates in the advanced world. But haven’t all the great and the good been telling us that Social Security and Medicare as we know them are unsustainable, that they must be totally revamped — and made much less generous? Why yes, they have; they’ve also been telling us that we must slash spending right away or we’ll face a Greek-style fiscal crisis. They were wrong about that, and they’re wrong about the longer run, too. The truth is that the long-term outlook for Social Security and Medicare, while not great, actually isn’t all that bad. It’s time to stop obsessing about how we’ll pay benefits to retirees in 2035 and focus instead on how we’re going to provide jobs to unemployed Americans in the here and now.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370237227206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:27:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370263080753-2</Id><Title>Dumbo poll numbers drop (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Msg>What new Hillary-Dumbo lie will be revealed this week?? Remember when it was just 2 rogue I.R.S. agents in Cincinatti? Now it's 90 in places all over the country. Remember Benghazi when it was just the 'Video'? Dumbo's fake fiction Autobiographies have 'Composite Girlfriends'. This is Socio-Pathic behavior. And Hillary-Dumbo are Criminals.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370263080753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370264369703-3</Id><Title>Dumbo's Mistress is a MAN (Liberlals blame Bush!)</Title><Msg>There is sooo many rumors about Dumbo's mistress. Moooscheeel is already gone and in hiding. The Crapola is about to hit the fan.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370264369703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:59:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370264783785-4</Id><Topic><Title>Social welfare nonprofits are supposed to have social welfare, and not politics, as their “primary” purpose.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370206994570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more pacifican BS, the question was . does Karl Rove's "social welfare" group really devote more than half of its efforts and money to NON-political activites as the law requires.......Pacifican 'answers' with blather about media matters..... which as far as I know doesnt spend money on political ads like Karl roves group..... see the difference...... more pacifican lies... he says none of the tea party groups got its tax exempt status.... which is just not true.... the fact is...... nearly ALL applications are approved, period.... AND while they are delayed they can ACT the very same as if they ARE approved......jeez........... here is the real issue: "Of the more than $256 million spent by social welfare nonprofits on ads in the 2012 elections, at least 80 percent came from conservative groups, according to FEC figures tallied by the Center for Responsive Politics. None came from the Tea Party groups with applications flagged by the IRS. Instead, a few big conservative groups were largely responsible. (in other words the flagged teabaggers were trivial and it doesn't fit with conspiracy bs to let the big fish go.... more like just plain bureaucratic bumbling) Crossroads GPS, which this week said it believes it is among the conservative groups "targeted" by the IRS, spent more than $70 million in federal races in 2012. Americans for Prosperity, the social welfare nonprofit launched by the conservative billionaire brothers Charles and David Koch, spent more than $36 million. American Future Fund spent more than $25 million. Americans for Tax Reform spent almost $16 million. American Action Network spent almost $12 million."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370264783785</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:06:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370265589189-5</Id><Topic><Title>The Geezers Are All Right - by Paul Krugman</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370237227206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzzz zz z z zzz zz zzz yawn zzzz z z z z zzzz</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1370265589189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370266762435-6</Id><Title>Dumbo's Poll licked by Paul Krugman (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Msg>Hillary has the 'Video' of this Dumbo-Krugman feeehg-ut 'Benghazi'</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370266762435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370267691369-7</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Incompetence? You're really into something here! After 157( !!! ) total visits to the White House, Obama couldn't figure out his IRS commissioner is not up to task? Or president's trust in Bush's choice was that unshakable? Oh yeah. Believable... So, what does it say about White House current owner? Gullible? But I'd rather say it's reminiscent to KGB tactics. And Obama owns this deal 100%.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370267691369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370268564096-8</Id><Title>GOP pups maul elders</Title><Msg>How GOP lost young voters Source: Politico A new postmortem on the November elections from the nation’s leading voice for college Republicans offers a searing indictment of the GOP “brand” and the major challenges the party faces in wooing young voters, according to a copy given exclusively to POLITICO. The College Republican National Committee on Monday will make public a detailed report — the result of extensive polling and focus groups — dissecting what went wrong for Republicans with young voters in the 2012 elections and how the party can improve its showing with that key demographic in the future. Titled the “Grand Old Party for a Brand New Generation,” the report is sharply critical of the GOP on several fronts. The study slams some Republicans’ almost singular focus on downsizing Big Government and cutting taxes; candidates’ use of offensive, polarizing rhetoric; and the party’s belly-flop efforts at messaging and outreach, even as the report presents a way forward and, at times, strikes an optimistic tone.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370268564096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370270248125-9</Id><Topic><Title>The Geezers Are All Right - by Paul Krugman</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370237227206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 01:27:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most all of those "projected numbers going forward" call for using the basically the same assumptions about national population growth they've been using for 20 years. Unfortunately those assumptions, both about population and revenue growth, are sadly flawed. More and more people who get work are staying in the cash economy, and fewer new workers are being sufficiently educated to replace the older ones (particularly in fields related to hard sciences including engineering and materials science). But despite the differences in estimated time to insolvency (which is actually NOW since we've loaned the entire trust fund to an unreliable borrow, that is, us) the solution remains the same. We need to make the new generation gainfully employable and internationally competitive. How to do that has become so complicated it'd take a committee just 3 years and a diet of nothing but honesty pills to determine how it got screwed up to begin with.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370270248125</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:37:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370270466694-10</Id><Topic><Title>Social welfare nonprofits are supposed to have social welfare, and not politics, as their “primary” purpose.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370206994570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the NAACP ?? The organization who spent more on get out the vote efforts during the Clinton administration because with a Black Man running they didn't NEED to tell people to vote. Any group of single issue voters who vote en bloc on certain issues based purely on information having NOTHING to do with the relative merits of the situation under the gavel is NOT a "social welfare" group, unless by that the NAACP is defining it as "welfare for all". In which case yes, the NAACP is a social welfare group.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370270466694</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370271985774-11</Id><Topic><Title>Social welfare nonprofits are supposed to have social welfare, and not politics, as their “primary” purpose.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370206994570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One minute you are saying it was IRS incompetence. The other minute IRS did nothing wrong. Make up your mind, you're making no sense. Or you're just barking? Woof, woof...</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370271985774</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:06:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370272567342-12</Id><Title>Issa mugged</Title><Msg>Raw Story “Darrell Issa should call Jay Carney and apologize this morning,” Gibbs told MSNBC host Joe Scarborough on Monday. “He’s laying out the charge and then saying it might be true. And then he’s saying, ‘As the investigator, I know where I want to get, now I’m just getting around to proving it.’” “I mean, it’s a stunning thing. It’s why five people in this town take Darrell Issa seriously. And it’s the surest bet that the Republicans are very much on the verge of overplaying their hand publicly and that the American people will lose interest in their side of this,” he added. “To throw around the words liar and perjury as easily as he did is shameful. And if he’s got information that these people lied, he should put it out there today.” Co-host Mika Brzezinski pointed out that “Darrell Issa just kind of took it down to a level that makes us all just want to walk away and ignore it.” “It shows how unserious he is about investigating anything,” Gibbs agreed. “The notion that he’s in charge of — quote — Government Oversight might now be the biggest joke in all of Washington.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370272567342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:16:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370273066661-13</Id><Title>gerbil, IT IS NOW MONSAY AND AG HOLDER IS STILL IN OFFICE</Title><Msg>GERBIL AND RODENT - EAT YOUR HEARTS OUT!!!</Msg><Username>returnuspompus</Username><Timestamp>1370273066661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370273301946-14</Id><Title>You know youre a Teabagger when...</Title><Msg>"You didn't get mad when the Supreme Court stopped a legal recount and appointed a President. You didn't get mad when Cheney allowed Energy company officials to dictate energy policy. You didn't get mad when a covert CIA operative got outed. You didn't get mad when the Patriot Act got passed. You didn't get mad when we illegally invaded a country that posed no threat to us. You didn't get mad when we spent over 600 billion(and counting) on on illegal war. You didn't get mad when over 10 billion dollars just disappeared in Iraq. You didn't get mad when you saw the Abu Grahib photos. You didn't get mad when you found out we were torturing people. You didn't get mad when the national debt doubled under the previous President from $5.674 trillion to $10.024 trillion. You didn't get mad when the government was illegally wiretapping Americans and the President lied about it. You didn't get mad when we didn't catch Bin Laden in Tora Bora. You didn't get mad when you saw the horrible conditions at Walter Reed. You didn't get mad when we let a major US city drown! You didn't get mad when the deficit hit the trillion dollar mark. You finally got mad when the government decided that people in America deserved the right to see a doctor if they are sick. Yes! Illegal wars, lies, corruption, torture, stealing your tax dollars to make the rich richer, are all ok with you, but helping other Americans... well that makes you mad! "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370273301946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370274940663-15</Id><Topic><Title>Social welfare nonprofits are supposed to have social welfare, and not politics, as their “primary” purpose.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370206994570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:03:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gee, you just can't show that Karl Rove's crosswords gps devotes more than 50% of its effort to NON- political.....'social welfare'...... they got approved......there is the scandal and the incompetence.......in fact... not a single teaparty group has been denied.... and being delay does not hinder them from do business AS IF THEY ARE APPROVED....... now, what is the scandal you accuse Obama of perpetrating at the IRS and do show the evidence......</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370274940663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:55:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370275322413-16</Id><Title>Closed-minded, racist, rigid, old-fashioned ..............</Title><Msg>That's what young Republicans are saying about the GOP. The same GOP that alienated Women, Hispanics, Blacks, Gays, and everyone else except angry, old white maroons who listen to Rush.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370275322413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:02:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370275552368-17</Id><Topic><Title>You know youre a Teabagger when...</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1370273301946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:28:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They didn't get mad when Bush ignored multiple warnings while golfing.......... and 3000 Americans died on American soil. But they got reeeeeeeeeel mad when 4 Americans died in enemy territory.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370275552368</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:05:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370276526600-18</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't know much about the LOAC. The war was quite legal because no peace treaty has been arrived at following the 1991 war. Legally what we did in Iraq was a de jury and de facto extension of the previous policies, but we'd decided we no longer wanted our patrol planes fired on, our inspectors hassled (though if Saddam had let us in on the gag we might have gone along with him, as long as he was otherwise complying), or any more cross border "incidents" between US units on the Kuwait side of the line and lost Iraqi units (most of which stayed lost after running into US Cavalry units). So, totally ignoring all the #$%$ reasons they came up with that didn't matter, and some that mattered alittle, ONE reason mattered SO much the others were moot. Saddam wasn't keeping up his side of the ceasefire agreement, and that meant the war was still on.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370276526600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370277253148-19</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dear dishonest and immoral person...... most of the visits were at the Eisenhower building on 17th street and , I don't know, there is a lot of new congressional requirements for tax policy and so forth....... so your false allegations are just nonsense.......... but hey if you are into making something out of visits to the whitehouse the 200 visits of a male prostitute to the WH house on Bush's watch must have really gotten you into a tizzie... it proves bush and cheney and the entire WH staff at the time used the male prostitute, right?... not that there is any evidence......... you do have evidence that Obama told the Bush appointee to NOT deny a single teaparty 'social welfare' applications , right?... that is what happened..... none were denied.... jeez you are an imbecile and a totally dishonest.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370277253148</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370279209292-20</Id><Title>Holder, the Criminal, still in Office?? (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Msg>Liberal Losers keep going a little lower in 'Loser-ville'. I miscalculated on Liberals ability to realize a Loser and cut their losses. Holder is still in office. I thought last Friday was the expiration date. To show how funny and Stupid the 'Loser Liberals' are, they actually think this is a 'Win' for them. Oh, when your digging a deep hole for yourself, stop digging. Well, lets see how long Holder stays. Again, the longer he stays, Liberals actually think its a 'Win' for them! This is soo classically Funny!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370279209292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370280246446-21</Id><Topic><Title>GOP pups maul elders</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370268564096</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 10:09:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About time, the GOP has been long overdue for a sanity dialysis on some of its positions, many of which are so archaic I have to go to my late 19th Century Encyclopedia to figure out what they're talking about. Most of the GOP party leadership thinks "The Web" is something an Obama aide named Charlotte came up with.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370280246446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:24:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370281659987-22</Id><Topic><Title>Closed-minded, racist, rigid, old-fashioned ..............</Title><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370275322413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:02:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2016 will be another huge embarrassment for Pubes.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1370281659987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370281843178-23</Id><Title>latest teabag scandal in a teapot: Teaparty leader reveals that Grover Norquist is a Muslim!!!</Title><Msg>heck, they proved Obama was born in Kenya....... and now Grover is proven a Muslim......WOW!!!! you see, since Norquist has beard he must be muslim........ so says the president of the Texas Eagle Forum..............ha ha ha</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370281843178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370281950157-24</Id><Topic><Title>It's a rout!!!</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370211441795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 18:17:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**My boy is POTUS and heading for Mt. Rushmore** Why, there is no golf course there.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370281950157</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370283147385-25</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Mistress is a MAN (Liberlals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370264369703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Rapist Bill Clinton is into geeeh too!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370283147385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 14:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370283207337-26</Id><Title>Holder is a Maladroit</Title><Msg>For are friends on the left, you may want to look up the word "maladroit"....pretty well sums it up. **The New York Times reported Sunday that even some West Wing aides in President Barack Obama’s White House now want Holder gone** West Wing Ready to Dump 'Politically Maladroit' Holder? Republicans have long been calling for Attorney General Eric Holder to resign. But citing new controversies at the Justice Department, The New York Times reported Sunday that even some West Wing aides in President Barack Obama’s White House now want Holder gone. “Over the course of four and a half years, no other member of President Obama’s cabinet has been at the center of so many polarizing episodes or the target of so much criticism,” the paper reported. “While the White House publicly backed Mr. Holder as he tried to smooth over the latest uproar amid new speculation about his future, some in the West Wing privately tell associates they wish he would step down, viewing him as politically maladroit.”</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370283207337</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 14:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370284381426-27</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are LOSING (it)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370018303887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:38:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 'Liberal Loser' venom is extra vile today! A clear sign these Liberals are really, really 'Losing It'!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370284381426</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 14:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370286139839-28</Id><Topic><Title>Holder is a Maladroit</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370283207337</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 14:13:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder - Holder is a calculated MALFUNCTION, that's why OBIMBO surrounded himself with "Yes Sir Zcars" - which he can fire and they still say "Thank You" because he will keep them on the Tax Payer's payroll or moves them to another top job! This whole "White House" is becoming a "Black House" and should be illuminated with "Black Lites" maybe then it would show up white again, at least at night!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370286139839</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370286413610-29</Id><Topic><Title>Closed-minded, racist, rigid, old-fashioned ..............</Title><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370275322413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:02:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget 2014 comes before 2016!!! Till then the "Firing Squad" will continue - another REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN is going to replace CONGRESS WOMAN BACHMAN in MN - it's in the bag!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370286413610</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370286531296-30</Id><Title>A good day . . .</Title><Msg>A million shares or so went from weak panicky hands to buy and hold hands . . . something I'm always happy to see is the pre-summer shakedown. Hold those shares ya'll hear now? :-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370286531296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370286864715-31</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Top IRS officials are not invited to WH meetings without specific agenda. Douglas Schulman's predecessor didn't have that much privilege, in fact almost none of that. Reporters (dozens every day) in the WH are much like stenographers. They are not invited to make or discuss policies. But to make sure executive branch is opened for the press. Your bringing up this comparison of a reporter with IRS commissioner officially invited 157 times is just barking not for real argument. But that's what you are here for.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370286864715</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370287343913-32</Id><Title>Frum scolds his own GOP</Title><Msg>"All Good Things... by David Frum Jun 3, 2013 11:05 AM EDT ....................... Conservative reformers are understandably allergic to arguments about income inequality…one of the lessons I think conservatives should take from the 2012 Romney defeat is that the increasing concentration of wealth in America has dangerous political and intellectual consequences. Conservative reformers must not absent themselves from the environmental debate. Humanity’s impact on the climate — and how to address that impact — is our world’s largest long-term challenge. If conservatives refuse to acknowledge that challenge, they only guarantee that the challenge will be addressed in ways that ignore conservative insights and values. Conservative reformers should make their peace with universal health coverage. It’s the law, and it won’t be repealed. Other countries have managed to control costs while covering everyone, and the US can too. A message of “protect Medicare, scrap Obamacare” reinforces the image of conservatism as nothing more than the class interest of the elderly. I appreciate that conservative reformers must pay lip-service to shibboleths about Barack Obama being the worst president of all time, who won’t rest until he has snuffed out the remains of constitutional liberty, etc. etc. Dissent too much from party orthodoxy, and you find yourself outside the party altogether. Still … conservative reformers should admit, if only to themselves, the harm that has been done by the politics of total war over the past five years. Now Republicans are working themselves into a frenzy that will paralyze Congress for the next 18 months at least, and could well lead to an impeachment crisis. As it becomes clear that the IRS story is an agency scandal, not a White House scandal, conservative reformers need to be ready to do their part to apply the brakes and turn the steering wheel. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370287343913</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370287678846-33</Id><Topic><Title>Closed-minded, racist, rigid, old-fashioned ..............</Title><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370275322413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 12:02:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One thing NOT in the old bag is her fay geet husband Marcus ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370287678846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:27:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370287981420-34</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Poll licked by Paul Krugman (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370266762435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:39:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Benghazi' is like when 'The Rapist Bill Clinton' murdered by burning to death all those Black women and children in Waco, Texas.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370287981420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370288435222-35</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets KISS, so what is more likely that a top IRS officail was invited 157 times to discuss the effects of a massive new responsibility for the IRS, OR, what could be accomplished in a single 15 minute meeting ("WE WANT YOU TO TARGET TEA PARTY GROUPS" So, which is more likely, Oops, I forget, logic is not part of pubs thought process."</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1370288435222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370288756195-36</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo poll numbers drop (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370263080753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo's 'She-male' 6 ft. 3in. mistress named 'MANica' is about to come out of the Closet.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370288756195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289265942-37</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Poll licked by Paul Krugman (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370266762435</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 09:39:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When it comes to pole licking, the Log Cabin girls are # 1 !</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370289265942</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:54:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289448033-38</Id><Topic><Title>latest teabag scandal in a teapot: Teaparty leader reveals that Grover Norquist is a Muslim!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370281843178</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:50:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waltzer, I really enjoyed your post and I'm still laughing. Keep up the good work.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1370289448033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:57:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289608279-39</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Mistress is a MAN (Liberlals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370264369703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'MANica' is Dumbo's cross dressing love toy. Watch for cat fight with Hillary's Huma!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370289608279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289633919-40</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo poll numbers drop (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370263080753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gerbil, you just can't win and that makes you a loser</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1370289633919</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370289666458-41</Id><Title>RePubs Call Issa a Liar !</Title><Msg>Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) on Monday became the latest Republican to reject Darrell Issa's comments that White House press secretary Jay Carney is a "paid liar" in relation to the IRS controversy. But Graham went further than his Republican colleagues, saying there's no evidence that the White House ordered the tax agency to target conservative groups. If you have an "R" in front of your name, it's true.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370289666458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289808160-42</Id><Topic><Title>Holder, the Criminal, still in Office?? (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370279209292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder is Dumbo's Secret Lover??</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370289808160</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370289978271-43</Id><Topic><Title>THEE place for pup tents</Title><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1369963759257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 21:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W/hat's a burner ID sheena?</Msg><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1370289978271</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:06:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370290049350-44</Id><Topic><Title>THEE place for pup tents</Title><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1369963759257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 21:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyway, had some nice Cheetos, pringles and pop chips.</Msg><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1370290049350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370290052392-45</Id><Title>Clinton, Carter, Obama, Reagan ALL more Popular than Bush !</Title><Msg>Apparently Americans are none too eager to see a Bush each time they reach into their wallets for who knows what. According to a new poll published by Vanity Fair, only 6 percent of Americans would prefer former presidents George H.W. Bush or George W. Bush “to be the face of a new bill.” Bill Clinton, Jimmy Carter, Barack Obama and Ronald Reagan were all more popular choices for the hypothetical honor. For those interested, Reagan took top honors scoring a whopping 38 percent of the vote. So now we KNOW that Bush was the worst ever !</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370290052392</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370290087973-46</Id><Topic><Title>THEE place for pup tents</Title><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1369963759257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-30 21:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a bit concerned about some things happening in the house.</Msg><Username>e.dilutionn</Username><Timestamp>1370290087973</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370290131489-47</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Mistress is a MAN (Liberlals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370264369703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:59:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gerbil, why do you keep posting to yourself? maybe, you like to read your own crapola! you're getting nuttier by the day!</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1370290131489</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:08:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370290492575-48</Id><Title>A moment of silence for Lautenberg</Title><Msg>He lived by the sword and died by the sword...a shinning example of term limits. NEW JERSEY SEN. FRANK LAUTENBERG DIES AT 89 Democratic New Jersey Sen. Frank Lautenberg has died. Lautenberg, who was the oldest member of the Senate, died at age 89 after battling health problems.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370290492575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370290814198-49</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We do know IRS assigned new task to make sure all US citizens buying health insurance coverage. We know it's not an easy task to make sure no one escapes "responsibility" and pay his/her "fair share". But what we also know is last Tea Party application "sneaked" in and approved in early 2010 was at the time those lovely meetings with IRS commissioner started and process took only 90 days. "Coincidentally", no other group was processed for minimum next 27 months. We also know the number of 2010 501(c)(4)applications was less than previous year. So the number of applicants wasn't that overwhelming at all to make an excuse for "overworked" IRS employees. It is really unimaginable that never in the course of those 118 WH meetings special treatment of tea party groups took place.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370290814198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:20:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370290931576-50</Id><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Msg>the fact that NO tea party group was denied anything? is the scandal that if delayed a tea party group can do business AS a tax exempt? is the scandal that in the last 4 years only 60 out of over 8200 applications have been turned down!? or is it a scandal that the IRS approves nearly ALL "social welfare" applications!?????/!</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370291232800-51</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals are LOSING (it)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370018303887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 12:38:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid questions are some of the Postings from Liberal Losers. Oh, what is next? So much corruptocracy and everyday, it's something new!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370291232800</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370291376250-52</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh geez, now your scandal is something else....something about the ACA...jeez.... well yes, some people will get a subsidy based on income so the IRS is involved...... same as it would have been if McCain had done his plan to subsidize or ryan or anyother gop plan that also was doing income based changes......and liar as stated........... but of course you don't want the IRS to verify anything so people can say whatever they want, right..... why even pay taxes... let the "free market" pay for defense and the courts and the schools and hiways and etc etc... why even have taxes everyone hates them and you people hate the taxman so much you just never shut up....... but hey did you hear that your tax cut grover norquist is a muslim? as per a teaparty leader, so you tax cutting dupes are wrecking the usa as per sharia I guess....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370291376250</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:29:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370291536814-53</Id><Topic><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when do we get a gop and fox news revelation that Obama is responsible for both taxes AND death? It's a conspiracy!!</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370291536814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370294422910-54</Id><Topic><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the IRS scandal is about? It's for brainwashed liberals, leftwingers like YOU, who don't get it! Would you like to go "line dancing" in the tune of the tax payers? Glad that CNN is reporting all those "wonderful investments" by the IRS and I am sure that you are more than happy to pay for it! Glad that the media is finally getting it right - not just FOX! OBIMBORAMA coming unglued on every seem - one scandal after the other!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370294422910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 17:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370297686320-55</Id><Topic><Title>A good day . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370286531296</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 15:08:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no idea where shares went to today. No one does. With the S&amp;P sitting at 1640, this stock should be much higher than $1.15 pre split. Back when the S&amp;P was trading at 1100 this stock was north of $15 per share. You should be worried that the performance has been so lousy on a very high beta stock during the magical BB QE to infinity rally. If things correct...just a little.......this dog will get punched in the face like so many times before. Single digits is not out of the question in a throw everything out the window rout. You seem a tad cocky with a stock that is under performing peers......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370297686320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 18:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370301102754-56</Id><Topic><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was cloudy and damp today. That DARN OBAMA!</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1370301102754</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370301280038-57</Id><Topic><Title>lame logic of pacifican &amp; others when confronted with the fact that a Bush appointee was running the IRS</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370208561810</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-02 17:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why I put pacifican54 on IGNORE. It's refreshing not to be subjected to his blather.</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1370301280038</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370302147244-58</Id><Topic><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose if you were singled out by the IRS because they didn't like your name for a tax audit where you would have to hire lawyers to prepare answers to 100 personal and irrelevant questions, that wouldn't bother you. But you would cry, "why are they picking on me? What did I do to deserve this?" And when other people with different names or backgrounds didn't get singled out for IRS reports, interviews, delays, and expenses, you wouldn't complain? But then you, of course, you would understand what discrimination is. Obviously you do not have a clue! But if they threw your grandparents into a gas chamber, or hung your grandfather by the neck from a tree, maybe then you would have a better idea of discrimination by the government, the worst type of discrimination! Maybe now you understand what the IRS scandal is all about!</Msg><Username>glennman100</Username><Timestamp>1370302147244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:29:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370303454199-59</Id><Title>AG ERIC HOLDER IS NOT RESIGNING BEFORE FRIDAY</Title><Msg>gerbil, All of your posts in regard to AG Eric Holder date back to the end of May! Who do you think your fooling??? gerbil, get real!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! And in the meantime the AG is still in office.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370303454199</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370303758006-60</Id><Title>Reminder: what the IRS scandal is about!</Title><Msg>It's when democrat apparatchiks suppressing one group of people and favor another all at our taxpayer's expense. We don't like double standards when applied by individuals. On government level it's a crime against 1st amendment. Some deranged individuals on this MB clearly loosing it. They think freedom of speech doesn't apply to those who disagree. In China, Cuba and former USSR they would be carrying Communist party memberships. EOM</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370303758006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370304409923-61</Id><Topic><Title>Reminder: what the IRS scandal is about!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370303758006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 19:55:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent! Perfectly worded!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370304409923</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370304464607-62</Id><Topic><Title>remind me what the IRS scandal is about</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370290931576</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 16:22:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, What the IRS scandal is about? It is about investigating, investigating, investigating, investigating and more investigating. rodent, who do you think is paying for all of this never ending investigating - we taxpatyers pay for it. The majority of Americans are fed up with this scandal crapola. If anyone is brainwashed it is you rodent. Du spinnst mal wieder!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1370304464607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370304646406-63</Id><Topic><Title>Holder, the Criminal, still in Office?? (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370279209292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 13:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only constant going forward is that we will learn more about the enormous crimes that Hillary-Dumbo-Holder-Lerner (and unknown crimes) have committed against us.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370304646406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370304777057-64</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo poll numbers drop (Liberals blame Bush!)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370263080753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 08:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Lie to be revealed is???</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370304777057</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370304974915-65</Id><Topic><Title>gerbil, IT IS NOW MONSAY AND AG HOLDER IS STILL IN OFFICE</Title><Username>returnuspompus</Username><Timestamp>1370273066661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 11:24:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he'll serve out his term</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1370304974915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 20:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370308803312-66</Id><Title>CONDI IS NOW A CONTRIBITOR TO CBS</Title><Msg>Condi is a big phony, always has been, a neocon and neocon enabler pretending to diplomatic objectivity. Recall it was Condi who was responsible for fielding info on foreign threats here in the U.S. so it was to her that the al Qaeda threats were being reported. She's more responsible for what happened on 9/11 than anyone else in or connected with the U.S. government (And no, I'm not a "truther"; read what I've written; obviously the terrorists themselves are most responsible by far, and I've not implied or suggested any 'conspiracy'. Condi, like Sonny and #$%$ and the rest, where blinded by their preconceived view of the world to stay willfully ignorant of whatever the actual diplomatic and professional security agencies were telling them were the actual facts and actually serious threats.) If Condi went to FOX, then she'd be owning up to being the neocon artist she is, of a piece with John Bolthead. Going to CBSNews means the same thing for her as it means for Frank Luntz: to "normalize" and "socialize" their neconartistry and outright mendaciousness with an msm org. CBSNews has gone really deep into the cesspool of corruption here.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370308803312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 21:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370310032332-67</Id><Topic><Title>CONDI IS NOW A CONTRIBITOR TO CBS</Title><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370308803312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 21:20:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes she is a War Criminal along with the good General Powell, Mr Wolfowitz, Rumsfeld, Tenent, Vice President #$%$ "Darth vadar" Cheney and President George W Bush. If we had real justice they'd all be settled in prison tried and found guilty at The Hague.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1370310032332</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 21:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370311819123-68</Id><Topic><Title>CONDI IS NOW A CONTRIBITOR TO CBS</Title><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370308803312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 21:20:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>member, - truth , Houston, United States, 21/1/2013 12:27 I really like Face the Nation but now it has slipped to a low, low, place. Rice is not a hero nor remotely close to one, in fact she should hang her head in shame. She had a chance to get Osama Bin doo-da more than once. One time he was shown on the news standing with villagers but she would not okay the shoot as innocent people would have died, Well Ms Rice, that kind of thing happens in war, covert or not, innocent people die just ask the relatives from 9/11. You are well educated, a very smart person but you do not have a backbone and as for PM McNeely from Birmingham who thinks she "WILL SPEAK THE TRUTH TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE", Ms or Mr McNeely, she is no different to our other political people or your political people, they only tell the truth when it suits there own ends, most of the time they skate around the truth, normally for one of two reasons, 1. there is an election coming up or 2. they have no back-bone and you can take that to the bank.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1370311819123</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-03 22:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>