<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-27"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361955623043-1</Id><Title>ETFC Could Be Added To The NASDAQ-100 Soon:</Title><Msg>My posts are my opinions. Happy investing to ALL!</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1361955623043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 04:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361967792528-2</Id><Title>Don't tell junglebop</Title><Msg>or any other Gore spoogesiphons. But it just got done winter storming like heck out in the mid-west.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361967792528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:23:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361976440927-3</Id><Title>Excessive Government Spending Did Not Make America Great</Title><Msg>We got where we are by hard work, innovation, capital investment and risk-taking. Obama's government-owned economy steals our mojo. Now we are about victimhood, corruption and lies. We gotta get our mojo back. Put Obama in a straitjacket and lock him in the basement. HI-iii-iii diklik!</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1361976440927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 09:47:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988802963-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity trashed</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1361981872748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:17:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ellison's right, how could Obama be responsible for our massive debt when you consider that only 6 billion of the 16 billion dollars of the nation's indebtedness was incurred on his watch. That other 10 trillion was #$%$ away by previous President on frivolities like World War II, the Cold War, the Space Program, the War on Poverty, Drugs, Terrorism, the national interstate highway system, the Tennessee Valley Authority . . . Instead of on important things like bailouts for the FOB's and FOO's in the money industry and buying up the UAW's votes. And he has 4 more years left, no telling what he might need to spend an extra 6 trillion on in his second term. Give the guy a break, there are still checks in his checkbook, so he's not broke yet . . . . Oh, wait, Congress cut off his NELOC (National Equity Line of Credit), now how's he doing to pay the bills . . .</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361988802963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:13:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361988942289-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hannity trashed</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1361981872748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:17:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why did I swap "billions" for "trillions" in my first sentence? Because it didn't seem POSSIBLE that any one Presidential term could increase our total national debt by over 60% in ONE term. It just boggles the freaking mind. I have alot of big project's I'd LOVE to do, including interstellar seed ships, and I could do it ALL for under 6 trillion dollars. At least without the helpful hand of government to provide "oversight".</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361988942289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:15:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361989146524-6</Id><Title>I'll drive This To Over $15 All By Myself!</Title><Msg>Just you watch me! Bye-bye shorty... LMAO. You are about to become "toast".</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1361989146524</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:19:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361989905849-7</Id><Topic><Title>Federal Appeals Court: There Is No Second Amendment Right To A Concealed Firearm</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1361981057399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 11:04:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't see much ambiguity in "the right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed". None at all. It is the Constitutional equivalent of banning the anonymous posting of messages because while speech is protected anonymous speech was NOT specifically listed in the 1st Amendment. That ruling will be overturned. Now state laws requiring you get TRAINING before you're allowed to carry a concealed firearm ARE Constitutional providing the burden isn't any greater than that shouldered by the police and military (e.g. qualification once a year or less, reasonable storage accommodations for the weapons, and demonstration of positive control, e.g. you have the weapons locked away so someone can't just find one laying about unless you're present at the time. Remember the FULL clause begins "A well regulated militia". Back then "well regulated" meant trained and disciplined to the limit expected of a civil militia, which frankly wasn't much, basically a familiarity with your weapon and keeping enough powder and shot to provide a reasonable number of reloads before needing resupply. I almost bought an M2 60mm Mortar yesterday to rub into the face of an idiot who said "why should people have "assault" rifles when they're not allowed to own machine guns and tanks". I could have bought the armored vehicle, or the anti-tank gun, but they were too expensive. The mortar was cheap but ammo for it is expensive, so I'll have to be satisfied with showing him my machine gun collection. REAL assault rifles, not semi-automatic only clones. Anyone otherwise qualifieid to own a firearm can own a Class 3 Firearm, all you have to do is have it legal in your state, go through an extensive background check similar to what the gun control idiots are suggesting for ALL weapons, and keep the ATF notified of where the weapon is kept permanently stored at all times, and further warn them any time you intend to take it out of the state. By the way, I REALLY want that anti-tank gun. The guy wants $70k though, and that puts it alittle out of my price range, so, for those that want to prove that the assault weapons ban is stupid, contribute to my "buy Caligula an anti-tank gun fund" so I have a great public demonstrator for how seriously ignorant it is. That ATG is living proof that when you ban something all you do is make it more desirable. That and the 6 ounces or so registered HK conversion part I have that are worth something like 17k on the open (civilian) market right now . . . normal price (if I was a federal agency) for the ENTIRE weapon is $2,500, for that one component it's less than $200 normally. In other words, if the same restrictions are put on AR's that are put on NFA's items the same thing will happen, only wealthy people will be able to own them. Now who does that benefit, the government, or the wealthy?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361989905849</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:31:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991469223-8</Id><Topic><Title>government spending saved capitalism and defeated hitler</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1361977301804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:01:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Government that joined a war to liberate Poland from Germany only to turn it over to Russia and decades of suffering at the end? That war? Do you even remember how it started and why? Do you realize that it was supported by a REPUBLICAN legislature? Do you realize that everything else Roosevelt did during his time in office actually made the situation WORSE in the long run? Roosevelt at Potsdam was almost as generous to our enemies as Neville Chamberlain was to the enemies of Britain, if not more so.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361991469223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 13:57:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361991820657-9</Id><Topic><Title>government spending saved capitalism and defeated hitler</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1361977301804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:01:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should clarify that . . . the Republicans were AGAINST getting involved in the war in Europe UNTIL Japan attacked Pearl Harbor and Germany foolishly declared war on the US despite their treaty with Japan not requiring them to as Japan was the aggressor (EVERYONE supported that war). Otherwise we largely participated by Lend-Lease, a neat little way of supporting our nominal allies while depriving Germany of the ability to cry foul as they also liked to "pretend play" that hostilities between the US and Germany were almost all but a fact by the time of Pearl Harbor anyway. And don't give me that "the German were evil because they killed the Jews" nonsense as that has nothing to do with the political situation at the time these decisions were made. In point of fact Germany had made every effort to EXPEL the Jews from Europe but . . . . No one would take them. Not Britain, not France, not the United States. The British wouldn't even allow them into the British Mandate of Palestine, which was originally formed to provide a homeland for a new Jewish state after the breakup of the Ottoman Empire. In a purely moral sense the allied powers share in the collective guilt for the Holocaust just as those who walk past a woman being raped and pretend not to see it are complicit in the rape itself.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361991820657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:03:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361993143021-10</Id><Title>Ellison</Title><Msg>Well, the MOST liberal spender of MN tax money and defender of Obimbo is so far to the left, that he doesn't have a "right turn signal" on his car, maybe that's why he likes to drive at Obimpolosi's area streets - left turns only! This Bast..... has the gut's to represent the black, Somali, Muslim community, which want's to build a "Somali-Muslim City" with their own court and mosque system in Minneapolis, MN, funded by the MN tax payers??? Last I checked - we were still living in America! Another community organizer just like Obimbo! I hope that our neighbors in MN wake up and send that POS packing and his bunch back to where they came from!!! They need a governor like our Walker and NOT a Dayton Millionaire Clown like he has become to set those reps in Washington straight - then they have Al Franken - at least he was and still is a REAL Comedian! Ellison is the worst Rep. ever MN had/has!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1361993143021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:25:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361994246626-11</Id><Topic><Title>government spending saved capitalism and defeated hitler</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1361977301804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:01:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>take it up with pacifican and others like Hannity who say debt is "immoral" or that governments should never borrow and such nonsense..... the USA could not have defeated the axis without borrowing huge sums of money......and no doubt had the grover norquists and paul ryans been around they would have said no dice to incurring debt to create jobs during the depression and would have played ball with the axis since opposing them would cost money.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361994246626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 14:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361997556079-12</Id><Topic><Title>Don't tell junglebop</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361967792528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 07:23:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't remind those libtarts who the prez was when America's debt got downgraded for the first time. Or who history will remember as the first prez to offer petstew at a WH luncheon..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361997556079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:39:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361999796113-13</Id><Topic><Title>pacifican repeats his old lie</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361995364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Weekly Standard: 2009 - $940B CBO estimate by Pelosi's request to pass Obamacare bill. 2010 - $1.4T 2011 - $1.7T 2012 - $2T 2013 - $2.3T 2014 - $2.6T All CBO estimates. "The latest estimate, as the chart details, is that Obamacare will cost $2.6 trillion dollars in its first real decade. The bill does not fully go into effect until 2014, therefore the estimate begins with that year. "President Obama promised a joint session of Congress in 2009 to spend $900 billion over ten years on his health care law: 'Now, add it all up, and the plan that I’m proposing will cost around $900 billion over 10 years.' Adding up all the different spending provisions in the health care law, however, (including closing the Medicare 'donut hole,' implementation costs, and other spending) total gross spending over the FY 2010–19 period is about $1.4 trillion, based on CBO estimates," the Senate Budget Committee Republican staff explains. "And most of the major spending provisions in the law do not even take effect until 2014. Congressional Democrats delayed these provisions in order to show only six years of spending under the plan in the original 10-year budget window (from FY2010-19) used by CBO at the time the law was enacted. Therefore, the original estimate concealed the fact that most of the law’s spending only doesn’t even begin until four years into the 10-year window. A Senate Budget Committee analysis (based on CBO estimates and growth rates) finds that that total spending under the law will amount to at least $2.6 trillion over a true 10-year period (from FY2014–23)—not $900 billion, as President Obama originally promised." The actual Obamacare spending won't begin before 2014. That's where the cost should start. CBO though starts estimate in thecurrent year when not a dime was spent on the program. So darn honest! How come original $940B estimate became $1.2T just a year later?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361999796113</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 16:16:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362005587719-14</Id><Topic><Title>pacifican repeats his old lie</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361995364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you might also note that the CBO has consistently stated the fact that the ACA will LOWER USA deficits: Letter to the Honorable John Boehner providing an estimate for H.R. 6079, the Repeal of Obamacare Act July 24, 2012 What Is the Impact of Repealing the ACA on the Federal Budget? Assuming that H.R. 6079 is enacted near the beginning of fiscal year 2013, CBO and JCT estimate that, on balance, the direct spending and revenue effects of enacting that legislation would cause a net increase in federal budget deficits of $109 billion over the 2013–2022 period. Specifically, we estimate that H.R. 6079 would reduce direct spending by $890 billion and reduce revenues by $1 trillion between 2013 and 2022, thus adding $109 billion to federal budget deficits over that period.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362005587719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:53:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362005776698-15</Id><Topic><Title>government spending saved capitalism and defeated hitler</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1361977301804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:01:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You missed 8 years of Great Depression when government was pouring money left and right for no results to show. It is only when government got busy with what was required by Constitution(protecting the country from ennemies) the economy started to grow at unprecedented pace. Yes, debt to GDP ratio after WWII was far greater than now, but ... The debt was held by American citizens. Further economic growth helped to pay the debt back. We have neither of that today. The debt is held by chineese, there is no economic growth to catch up with debt, and prospects for the future of the economy are bleak. So, sing your song about your beloved government until we all will be forced to speak chineese.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362005776698</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 17:56:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362006060231-16</Id><Title>Furlough the whole government</Title><Msg>Most of them were doing next to nothing anyway.</Msg><Username>the_whizinator</Username><Timestamp>1362006060231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 18:01:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362010894452-17</Id><Topic><Title>government spending saved capitalism and defeated hitler</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1361977301804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 10:01:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can only imagine Obama bowing down to another dictator and US being a spectator on WWII arena. In WWII US government only executed the role for which it was designed. We do want the government executing its primary reponsibilities. Welfare for poor and middleclass may be well defined in Communist Manifesto, but nowhere in this country's main document.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362010894452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:21:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362012084681-18</Id><Topic><Title>pacifican repeats his old lie</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361995364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pay attention. You didn't read the word I say. Since 2009 of original estimate, CBO keeps changing numbers every year. And misleading public by not applying estimates to years Obamacare actually takes effect.. In other words it feeds us with pack of lies. It does the same today with estimates for the sequestration effect on GDP growth. Projected GDP growth in 2013 is at least $500B. Sequestration size which will cut $80B is nowhere near to be half of projected GDP growth as CBO claims.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362012084681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 19:41:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362014998328-19</Id><Title>Boy, wasn't that expected from this WH?</Title><Msg>White House Threatens Bob Woodward: Mr. Woodward, how does this compare to Watergate? You have a lot to answer for. You and the rest of the enemedia have been at war with the American people for decades. You destroyed the right, the rational and the reasoned - the rights of the individual. Did you think they wouldn't come for you? BOB WOODWARD: A 'Very Senior' White House Person Warned Me I'd 'Regret' What I'm Doing Business Insider Bob Woodward said this evening on CNN that a "very senior person" at the White House warned him in an email that he would "regret doing this," the same day he has continued to slam President Barack Obama over the looming forced cuts known as the sequester. CNN host Wolf Blitzer said that the network invited a White House official to debate Woodward on-air, but the White House declined. "I think they're confused," Woodward said of the White House's pushback on his reporting. Earlier today on MSNBC's "Morning Joe," Woodward ripped into Obama in what has become an ongoing feud between the veteran Washington Post journalist and the White House. Woodward said Obama was showing a "kind of madness I haven't seen in a long time" for a decision not to deploy an aircraft carrier to the Persian Gulf because of budget concerns. The Defense Department said in early February that it would not deploy the U.S.S. Harry Truman to the Persian Gulf, citing budget concerns relating to the looming cuts known as the sequester. "Can you imagine Ronald Reagan sitting there and saying, 'Oh, by the way, I can't do this because of some budget document?'" Woodward said on MSNBC. "Or George W. Bush saying, 'You know, I'm not going to invade Iraq because I can't get the aircraft carriers I need?'" Or even Bill Clinton saying, 'You know, I'm not going to attack Saddam Hussein's intelligence headquarters,' ... because of some budget document?" Woodward began stirring controversy last weekend, when he called out Obama for what he said was "moving the goal posts" on the sequester by requesting that revenue be part of a deal to avert it. Good thing, we still have sime real old time journalists. Not all of them are Obama puppets.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362014998328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:29:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362024620763-20</Id><Topic><Title>pacifican repeats his old lie</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361995364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you pay "Pay attention" there was no ACA in 2009.....Nor have you cited ANY actual report from the cbo, but only rightwing blather ...... and the fact remains that the cbo has not changed its view that the ACA will LOWER USA deficits compared to do nothing or compared to the gop repealing it.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362024620763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 23:10:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>