<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373775477234-1</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!....Wassa Matter?....</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373773695630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 23:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you .......... You exactly describe Zimmer's mindset when he attacked a kid going home.</Msg><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775477234</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:17:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373775736650-2</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!....Wassa Matter?....</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373773695630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 23:48:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JB!.... Is THAT All you Got? Well....it's Really No Surprise!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373775736650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:22:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373775992478-3</Id><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Msg>And the little black kid had the nerve to fight back. I won because I had a gun. And he didn't know it.</Msg><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373777663713-4</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well... You got the Second part Right! And it's No Surprise that you are crying about it...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373777663713</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:54:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373789646174-5</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're making assumptions about facts not in evidence. And which are, in fact, contradicted by ALL the evidence.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373789646174</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 04:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373821558057-6</Id><Title>Oakland</Title><Msg>Well, as usual CA is leading the nation with the losers in Oakland! We should put them in a WORKFARE NOT WELFARE program - they got too much time on their hands to riot - about anything!!! If their Oakland football team losers loses - they riot, if their basket ball team wins they riot - if a thug on the side walk gets shot they riot - if they can't run around nude - they riot and on and on! With clearing Zimmerman - they riot - triple losers: California - Oakland - Liberal RACISTS!!! ROWDY (Next riot - liberal Hollywood)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373821558057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373826554924-7</Id><Title>aryan brothers to make make Zimmerman an honorary member?</Title><Msg>starting him at the rank of Stabsgefreiter.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373826554924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:29:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373826567402-8</Id><Topic><Title>Oakland</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373821558057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 13:05:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like whitey acquitted brownie of blackie's murder. No big deal. The interesting part is the blacks have to be told not to riot. Only a barbarian would have to be told not to riot --- all non-barbarians would act civilly wifout having to be tolt.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1373826567402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373831445863-9</Id><Topic><Title>aryan brothers to make make Zimmerman an honorary member?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373826554924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 14:29:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hamas, Fidel Castro endorsed Obama, Hugo Chavez praised him. That's without a question mark. What does it tell you? Prosecution in Zimmerman's case discarded racial profiling charge. Is that what must be the main charge against Zimmerman in your view? Darn!!! Do they deserve to be honorary members of Aryan brothers too for doing that? Electing black president, having Congressional black caucus, black representation in all branches of government is not nearly enough to pay for some 70 years history of slavery in this country, which ended more than 150 years ago. We have to apologize, apologize, apologize even if my ancestry was thousands of miles apart from here when blacks were slaves. When will this end? Never. Because to you this country has wrong foundation and you won't stop until it's completely abolished.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1373831445863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 15:50:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373835081082-10</Id><Title>a drunk racist white man knocked out by black standing his ground</Title><Msg>A Drunk, Racist Former Goldman Sachs Employee Got Knocked Out A Drunk, Racist Former Goldman Sachs Employee Got Knocked Out There was an altercation between a drunk, racist, well-dressed white man and a black couple in New York's Greenwich Village on Friday. It did not end well for the white man, who is now in critical condition after he was knocked out and his head hit the pavement. A black couple was sitting outside the Mexican joint when an intoxicated white man stumbled into their table. Douglas Reddish, 25, who was eating with his girlfriend, tried to help him regain his balance, cops said, and the wait staff came over to shoo the table crasher away. And here's the Daily News: Witnesses on Greenwich Ave. near W. 12th St. said the white man — who cops said is in his 30s — was belting back beers outside Benny’s Burritos about 5:30 p.m. when he began mouthing off to a black customer in the outdoor seating area. What happened next isn't really up for debate, though. The drunken white man hurled racial slurs at the couple who were, up until this point, privately enjoying some Mexican food. "You n-----s are why I lost my job," the unidentified drunk said, witnesses told the Daily News. "This n----r wants to fight me!" he yelled, police told the Post.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835081082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373840654946-11</Id><Title>What white liberals would have you believe</Title><Msg>That Zimmerman profiled and stalked Martin to shoot a black kid for just being black. Murders don’t call the police before killing their victims In light of all the evidence that night before Zimmerman fired, Martin was beating the day lights out of him, not the other way around. The prosecution over charged Zimmerman and turned the incident into a racial one for political purposes. These same phony's don't give a damn about the carnage black crime on blacks causes. And for the white African President to insert himself into the white Hispanic trial was pure politics. A good way to change the subject from black on black crime, and the high unemployment among blacks under his Presidency. Is Zimmerman's hands clean, no....but to ignore the facts because you don't like the verdicts outcome says volumes about the white liberal establishments hypocrisy.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373840654946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 18:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373846869675-12</Id><Title>Nuclear option approaches</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- When Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid (D-Nev.) declared Thursday that he intended to push ahead with a "nuclear option" rules change in order to confirm a handful of President Barack Obama's stalled nominees, Republicans declared that he was destroying the world's greatest deliberative body -- and that he would pay for it. Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) went so far as to declare that Reid would be remembered as the "worst leader of the Senate ever" if he changed procedural rules with just a 51-vote majority -- instead of the usual super-majority -- to help nominees evade threats of filibuster. Democrats responded that Republicans had already destroyed the chamber by using blocking tactics to turn every nomination (and much legislation) into a drawn-out, time-consuming fight that eats time from the rest of the country's business and hamstrings the executive branch's ability to function. The heated rhetoric requires some context. The Senate has changed its rules in mid-session before, and the reform Reid is talking about is relatively narrow, applying only to administrative nominees in the executive branch. But it's still a bombshell because it targets the core advice-and-consent duty of the Senate, and because use of the nuclear option has been threatened before, but the historically judicious body has not actually used it. Proponents dub the maneuver the constitutional option. Most recently, the majority threatened to go nuclear in 2005, when Republicans were in control of the upper chamber. The arguments on Thursday sounded remarkably like those of eight years ago -- just reverse the parties -- when the minority Democrats mounted a concerted effort to stall some of President George W. Bush's more conservative judicial nominees.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373846869675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:07:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373846970322-13</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear option approaches</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373846869675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But there are key differences. Republicans back then were forced to seek cloture on nominations -- that is, to end debate with 60 votes, usually because of a filibuster -- 18 times. Overall, there were 68 motions for cloture in the Senate legislative and appointment battles of that two-year session of Congress, the 109th. In frustration, Republicans very nearly crafted a nuclear-option rules change that Democrats at the time said would destroy the Senate. The showdown was averted when a bipartisan "Gang of 14" senators declared they would unite to break filibusters unless there were "extraordinary" circumstances. That deal mostly held on nominations until the last Congress, the 112th, when procedural battles escalated over nearly everything. Cloture had to be sought on 33 nominations, almost twice as many as the 18 that so bothered the GOP in 2005. More broadly, ever since the Democrats regained control of the Senate in 2007, the incidence of cloture fights in which the minority party had to be overridden has spiked dramatically. While there were 68 cloture motions when the GOP-led Senate nearly went nuclear in the 109th Congress, there were 139 cloture motions after the Democrats took over with the 110th Congress. Democrats reacted at the start of the 113th Congress, in January, by threatening rules changes that included reinstating the old-fashioned "Mr. Smith Goes to Washington" talking filibuster -- in which a lawmaker must hold forth on the floor, not just phone in an objection, to block action. The Democrats settled for a more modest change, however, with Reid agreeing he would not try to change the rules again in this session, while McConnell pledged that Republicans would conduct themselves more in accord with the norms of the Senate.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373846970322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847253593-14</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear option approaches</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373846869675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP has become somewhat more cooperative (there have been 22 cloture motions one quarter of the way through this session of Congress). But House Republicans have also engaged in some spectacular stalling, forcing a cloture vote for the first time ever on the nomination of a secretary of defense, for instance, and steadfastly refusing to ease the way for nominees to agencies they do not like, particularly the National Labor Relations Board and the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau. Such entrenched positions are raising the temperature in the arcane rules battle. Democrats see the labor board as vital, and Obama dealt with the blockade by going around the Senate, appointing NLRB nominees (and a CFPB director) during a technical recess of the Senate in 2011. Republicans were infuriated. An appeals court has since ruled the labor appointments unconstitutional, although the case is being appealed to the Supreme Court. Because of expiring terms, the labor board is about to become nonfunctional. McConnell offered Thursday to solve the problem by putting two Republican nominees on the board, which Reid summarily rejected. The CFPB, which was not part of the court case, continues to operate.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373847253593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373847297060-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear option approaches</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373846869675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:07:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perhaps an even bigger concern for Democrats is finally filling vacancies on the influential U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit, often considered the second-highest court in the land and the court that ruled against Obama's NLRB appointments. Democrats have not yet included judges in the rules fight that is expected to play out Monday and Tuesday, but there are three open seats on the D.C. Circuit. Three nominees are working their way through the Senate process, and Republicans have signaled they will fight bitterly to prevent the empty seats from being filled, claiming the attempt to do so amounts to "packing" the court. Democrats feel equally strongly that a president who has won reelection and the voters who chose him deserve to see his policy and judicial philosophy reflected in federal agencies and judges. The only way Reid can find to make that happen is by forcing a concession from the GOP with the nuclear threat, or actually carrying out that threat. The importance the GOP attaches to preserving a set of Senate rules that allow its senators to debilitate the NLRB and prevent a key court from tilting to the left can be gathered from senators' impassioned statements Thursday, after Reid announced he was ready to change the rules. Indeed, they pledged that Reid would "rue the day" and that eventually the "shoe would be on the other foot."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373847297060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 20:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373852417032-16</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like CNN's picture of Trevon when he was 12 years got yah "hook line and sinker". Actually he was 17 yr's old and about 6 ft tall. Dont feel too bad most of the country got punked also.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1373852417032</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 21:40:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373854754092-17</Id><Topic><Title>a drunk racist white man knocked out by black standing his ground</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1373835081082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 16:51:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 Black Americans were murdered in Chicago over the 4th of July weekend..., by SOBER BLACK gangsta's...</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1373854754092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 22:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>