<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374380020482-1</Id><Title>Tres amusant</Title><Msg>"July 19, 2013 09:31 PM Maher Bemoans the Resurgence of the Smart Stupid Person Bill Maher bemoaned the resurgence of the "smart stupid person" during his New Rules segment on Real Time this Friday evening. After explaining that this is nothing new, Maher ran down the recent list which includes the like of Dr. Ben Carson, who is a brilliant surgeon, but also believes the earth is 6000 years old, likened homosexuality to #$%$ and said the Bible calls for a flat tax. And then there's Antonin Scalia, Ted Cruz and Bobby Jindal, who are all, as Maher described them, accomplished scholars on the outside, and a creamy layer of Michele Bachmann on the inside. Maher wrapped things up by going after the "know-nothing" doctors like Scott DesJarlais, Paul Broun and Tom Coburn, who as Maher noted, are OBGYN's but "know nothing about reproduction." He wasn't through with the list of wingnut OBGYN's yet though. He went on to go after Ron Paul, Michael Burgess, and last but not least, Phil Gingrey. MAHER: Let's ask the more important question. Why are we electing so many gynecologists to Congress? If having your head between a woman's legs is a qualification for public office, then why not Congressman Michael Douglas? I don't think the problem with those clowns is having their heads between women's legs. It's having it up their own posteriors.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374380020482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 00:13:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374412902798-2</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope, you are wrong. here is what I found using your advice and "realitycheck/3" "Linda Douglass of the White House Office of Health Reform debunks the myth that reform will force you out of your current insurance plan or force you to change doctors. To the contrary, reform will expand your choices, not eliminate them." ...........whitehouse..............gov/realitycheck/3 you should read my previous post about how insurance network providers work to see what BS this idea is. and ntm you should also figure out when you have been had by foz news spreading lies.. It should be simple for you to show the HHS quote and a real source which should be from HHS. I found the original Fox news report of this and as I said before they cited a right wing BLOG.....jeez...... with a dead link.....jeez......and also as everyone knows insurance provider have ALWAYS had networks of providers.......jees</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374412902798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374414131827-3</Id><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Msg>fox and righties are spreading the lie that "hhs admits you may not be able to keep your doctor under the ACA" typical rightwing fricking BS that is. fyi , LIARS, the very same thing can be said of health insurance now and ALWAYS WAS that WAY....jeez.... it ALWAYS depended on your insurance's network of providers and you ALWAYS had to pay more to go out of net work.......... so THAT is the bottom line of this FOX and righty BS....... Doctor Choice &amp; Emergency Room Access You have the right to choose the doctor you want from your health plan’s provider network. You also can use an out-of-network emergency room without penalty. You pick your doctor: You can choose any available primary care provider in your insurance plan’s network. You can choose any available network pediatrician as your child’s primary care doctor. healthcare dot gov if you buy your own insurance, as always, you have to look for a plan that has your doc in the network or pay more to see that doc.... SAME AS ALWAYS.... and it is the same for employer health insurance as ALWAYS....see what a bunch or weasels you fox and friends are?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374415143883-4</Id><Title>gop is afraid that the ACA will be a huge success and even lower healthcare costs</Title><Msg>hence their costly campaign of lies and misinformation and bs. heck, if they are so sure it will collapse they don't have to spend a dime on misinformation , or waste so much effort to repeal it, it will simply end all by itself. as it turns out it does seem like the ACA will offer good plans at reasonable prices , this of course, will be a disaster for the gop, but good for the nation.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374415143883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374415939228-5</Id><Topic><Title>gop is afraid that the ACA will be a huge success and even lower healthcare costs</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374415143883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did faux report that "New York State regulators have approved health insurance rates for individual policies for 2014 that are at least half the cost of current policies on average."...... it doesn't fit in with what the gop says, does it? of how about in Oregon once "....comparison of proposed 2014 health premiums became public online, causing two insurers to request do-overs to lower their rates even before the state determines whether they're justified. The unusual development was sparked by a comparison that used to be impossible because plan benefits varied so widely. But under the federal reforms that take effect Jan. 1, health insurance is mandated and every insurer must offer certain standard plans. ....Providence Health Plan on Wednesday asked to lower its requested rates by 15 percent. Gary Walker, a Providence spokesman, says the "primary driver" was a realization that the plan's cost projections were incorrect. But he conceded a desire to be competitive was part of it. A Family Care Health Plans official on Thursday said the insurer will ask the state for even greater decrease in requested rates. CEO Jeff Heatherington says the company realized its analysts were too pessimistic after seeing online that its proposed premiums were the highest."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374415939228</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 10:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374419830399-6</Id><Title>Where's the 'Benghazi' Idiot ?</Title><Msg>You know, the moronic slope head who posted 50 times a day that Obama would be impeached ? Hillary would be fired and go to jail ? Holder would be fired and go to jail ? maybe it's best that the idiot stays quiet.</Msg><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1374419830399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:17:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374420932855-7</Id><Topic><Title>GOP admits assault on democracy</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354117352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:01:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wished that every state has the voter ID LAW, then the FRAUD wouldn't have elected OBIMBO! Now they sorry they did, starting right now with the UNIONS! Wait for the FREELOADERS to squeal when OBIMBOCARE kicks in!!! They can't pay for it and nobody is going to take them - then make them pay a fine on top of it - love it!!!! The fat, black Detroit City Council woman (as seen on TV) with her $150000 salary is going to scream more "WHERE IS THE BACON"???? Maybe $50000/year would have been good enough! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374420932855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374421125702-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOP bloodsuckers</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374334224926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:30:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for Bain Capital! We need more private investments and get away from the incompetent Government and it's regulations! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374421125702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:38:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374421517438-9</Id><Topic><Title>For the next 184 weeks</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374375988643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:06:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like the freeloaders and the left wing unions???? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374421517438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374422177416-10</Id><Topic><Title>For the next 184 weeks</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374375988643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:06:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is essential that there should be organizations of labor. This is an era of organization. Capital organizes and therefore labor must organize. Theodore Roosevelt *"Workers have a right to organize into unions and to bargain collectively with their employers. And a strong, free labor movement is an invigorating and necessary part of our industrial society." *"Only a fool would try to deprive working men and women of their right to join the union of their choice." Republican President Dwight Eisenhower People like Rowdy hate the USA and democracy. The above show how far this ilk has strayed from even the best of republican thought. This ilk are are often the supporters of the pauls. rand and ron. a Rand aide recently expressed his hatred of Lincoln and praised john wilkes booth. These types of republicans hate Teddy Roosevelt, Ike and even Lincoln, which is to say they hate the USA and democracy itself.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374422177416</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374424920370-11</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try reading the WHOLE page. The quote you claimed wasn't a quote was right in there.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374424920370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:42:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374425133818-12</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't really bother me since I've NEVER been "allowed to keep my own doctor", just fire ones (e.g. sever them from my care and files) who I find totally incompetent, and the VA doesn't even like it when I do that, particularly since every doctor I've done this with so far save one they've had to later fire for incompetence. Being a doctor fired from the VA for incompetence is QUITE an achievement, almost like an actor winning a razzie, only they're rarer.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374425133818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374425261593-13</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just copy and paste the quote, is that so hard. and btw . if the ACA is repealed you could say the same thing, that "You May Not Be Able To Keep Your Doctor ".... because, mr dishonest person, that is the way private insurance has ALWAYS been. get it? Why do you make a big deal about the fact that private insurance always has required the use of NETWORK providers and that to use a doc out of the network you just pay more. see what weasels you people are?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374425261593</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:47:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374425825193-14</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the point being that fox and the rightie blog that originated the "story" are just liars, basically. and then the liars here and in rightwing blogoshere repeat the lie endlessly. Any honest person than has had health insurance knows that insurers have ALWAYS required the use of doctors within their network, else you pay more. I have never had a problem finding docs within the networks of several providers. Fox news could have just as easily reported that the "repeal of Obamacare means you won't be able to keep your doctor"..... jeez...and to spin it that Obama care is the cause of that is pure propaganda, but that is what fox news is known for isn't it?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374425825193</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 12:57:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374430013771-15</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on lucky...we didn't need to change insurance providers - the corporations just DUMPED us! If you got Aetna, United Health and other try to find an IN NETWORK PROVIDER - (hospital/ Dr./Specialist) especially if you are in CA and some other states! My company at least pays for my Medica "Prime Enhanced" plan which has in network providers everywhere and even over seas! (As a bub for MEDICARE) He ex company (IPG) flat dropped and switched their employees and put them on COBRA, when they "down sized" as long as they could and then it was off to Medica also, but out of her own pocket! (As a sub for MEDICARE) What when NOT IF MEDICARE becomes insolvent??? MEDICAID &amp; Badger Care - where will they get service??? The devil lays in the details and that's where OBIMBOCARE will blow up! Don't just skew - what fits your view - OH GREAT ONE! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374430013771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374430641343-16</Id><Topic><Title>For the next 184 weeks</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374375988643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:06:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The UNIONS just SH## in OBIMBOS basket! ;o) Last I checked, the USA is a REPUBLIC NOT A MONARCHY what OBIMBO wants it to be - him the KING!!! The Roosevelt day are over and so is the time for Unions, which were productive and protected the worker when it was needed to be! FYI, I was a supporter of JFK who didn't SH## on us, the Military - like this clown OBIMBO - and also liked the leadership of MLK who NON violently got things done - NOT like an AL Sharpton! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374430641343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374431032157-17</Id><Topic><Title>gop is afraid that the ACA will be a huge success and even lower healthcare costs</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374415143883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:59:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be one of those who goes to every SALE - after the price has been marked up by 100% and then cut by 50% - what a deal!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374431032157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 14:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374433566926-18</Id><Topic><Title>Even low paid workers can afford health insurance with the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374356414769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CLGL - you are right about transportation! I drove myself to the Hudson Medical Emergency Center (4 miles) with a dislocated jaw. They had nobody on duty that eve who could set it - so the fire department ambulance/paramedics had to to take me to Regions Hospital Emergency in St. Paul, MN. (I then had MEDICARE &amp; MN-BCBS from my ex employer - which got dropped with OBIMBOCARE now in 2013) The ambulance was $580 for the 18 mile trip! How could a "POOR working class" afford this - as you wrote? When OBIMOCARE is supposed to be ready by OCT. (far away from it here, while the state is trying to get the money for "NAVIGATORS" to be trained yet)) to help with the paper work - as you wrote, how will they get to the State Medical centers selected by the EXCHANGE PLAN??? The closest one will be a 2 hour one way drive to the Indian Reservation South of La Cross! When you pull up the state map - the state it has NONE in the western half of WI -all private Medical Centers, were not only MEDICADE &amp; Badger Care is NOT excepted - I even had to go to MN to see a specialist because I have MEDICARE, in Washington County, MN because RAMSEY &amp; HENNEPIN will NO LONGER except out of state/county patients - That's what all this is coming too! That screwed up "junkie" has no clue out of his little world and when the unions don't like iot -you know there is something terrible wrong with this legislation!!! You as a - I take it a Vet. - would have to drive to Madison or Milwaukee to get decent service at a VA Clinic - better book a over nite stay for a 2-day trip! Those are facts! Good luck with your health! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374433566926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374434045982-19</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clgl - don't even reply to those left wing spin drs. junkie or lucky, they are disconnected from real life, have too much time on their hands and can only see OBIMBORAMA, they must be on food stamps and assistance! When I watched CNN last eve - even they now "all the sudden" don't approve of some of the escapades of OBIMBORAMA - maybe they are worried about their union jobs/pay??? ROWDY (Time to watch NASCAR from Chicagoland, first Nationwide and then ARCA!)!</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374434045982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:14:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374434188620-20</Id><Title>Take enough money from other people and give it to me. I can 'afford a Ferrari</Title><Msg>#$%$ does that prove? Let's try it and see.</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1374434188620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:16:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374434372224-21</Id><Topic><Title>Take enough money from other people and give it to me. I can 'afford a Ferrari</Title><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1374434188620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and after you give me other people's money, I will not say thank you. I will rob and loot and spray paint. I will call you a greedy, ignorant bloodsucker. You had better give me money to 'afford' gas and 20" rims or the place will burn.</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1374434372224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374438968179-22</Id><Topic><Title>Take enough money from other people and give it to me. I can 'afford a Ferrari</Title><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1374434188620</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 15:16:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now where did I hear this last - OHHHH in the rundown Downtown MPLS HOOD - and they all bought Viking gear and $100+++ tickets for "MN CROAKINS" seats! Losers - just like their team! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374438968179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 16:36:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374440756396-23</Id><Topic><Title>Even low paid workers can afford health insurance with the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374356414769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>** A pizza cook in Canada has health insurance but the one in the USA does not. now a young min wage person in LA will be able to buy the silver plan for $34 a month. Two points you conveniently left out. First, Canada has a population of 33 million, the US has a population of 310 million, apples and orange. Second, who do you think is going to subsidize the rest of the cost for this low wage worker insurance if he even choose to pay it....dopes like you. The cost of koolaid will be going up my friend.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374440756396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374443839144-24</Id><Topic><Title>Even low paid workers can afford health insurance with the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374356414769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you add up the population of Europe, the UK, Canada, Australia, japan, Taiwan, Israel and so forth.... and all the other nations that get the cook and the waitress covered.? and ntm, that Canada and all the others get everyone covered and spend less per capita than we do, so your point is silly.... and btw.... McCain's plan was to subsidize the poor by taxing your employer health benefits as income, so there you go.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374443839144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 17:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374445273154-25</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they'd have simply gone back to the days when national insurance companies competed for health care plans we'd be alot better off than we are with Obamacare. As it is an Insurance company here in the US can only do business at the state level, not the national level, without create a subdivision specifically for that state. So you have high load states like Mississippi with a HUGE population still living in pseudo 3rd world conditions, versus lower load states like Washington with a younger, healthier, and more literate population. Naturally average heath care in Mississippi is going to STINK compared to most other states. Opening policies to nationwide distribution again would have done a great deal to close the gap in and of itself.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374445273154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:21:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374445498942-26</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think a brokerage account would sort of preclude public assistance, unless it had zip for assets in it. I'm prepared to assume most of the folks here at least have a brokerage account and a few loose bucks to play with, even if they might be on a fixed income (e.g retired) outside their brokerage activities. It's the only way I've found to stretch disability pay that extra little bit.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374445498942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 18:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374450613477-27</Id><Topic><Title>THIS JUST IN...................</Title><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1374343125152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fubar, Just like most Pubs, you love to beat around the bush to avoid a straight anwser. ***Nawww...it's legal, but Eric Holder would have a freaking stroke.*** fubar, Are you any kind of a lawyer? I don''t think so! Therefore, you don't know what's legal in the state of Michigan and the city of Detroit in regard to bankruptcy. The Constitution of the State of Michigan declares that the State or City may not unfertake any actions that endanger pensions. This matter is now before the Appellate Court of Michigan fubar, You will have a stroke and not AG Eric Holder. Sometimes, you make sense but more often, you do not.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1374450613477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 19:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374451226674-28</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what in some way what Obamacare is about - it promotes competitions betwixt Obamacare and private insurers and also competitions between private insurers.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1374451226674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374451311311-29</Id><Topic><Title>liars here caught spreading another lie about the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374414131827</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 09:42:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, GO BACK UNDER YOUR ROCK!!!</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1374451311311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374453977777-30</Id><Title>Obamascare is for Gerbil Stuffing Liberals</Title><Msg>Ant that ain't no Lie, you A.I.D.s carrying Feeehg-uts!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374453977777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374457005843-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obamascare is for Gerbil Stuffing Liberals</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374453977777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 20:46:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Martin would be alive today if it wasn't for a doctor shortage cause by Obamascare.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1374457005843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 21:36:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374458712438-32</Id><Topic><Title>Where's the 'Benghazi' Idiot ?</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1374419830399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 11:17:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that was gerbil who got slapped on the wrist by Yahoo and guess who'll be next if he doesn't slow down with his OBIMBO BS? None other than ROWDY-RODENT, better known as "rodent."</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1374458712438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:05:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374460266508-33</Id><Title>Zim to host "Stand your ground" on Fox</Title><Msg>EXCLUSIVE: Fox News Signs George Zimmerman As Host: “Stand Your Ground” Premieres This Fall Posted by: Mark @ 10:56 am Now that the jury has delivered a “not guilty” verdict for teen stalker/killer George Zimmerman, Fox News has taken a bold move to extend the ratings bonanza of the trial into the fall television season. Sources inside Fox News have confirmed that Zimmerman has agreed to host a nightly crime and social affairs program on the network that is set to premiere in October 2013. The controversial signing is consistent with Fox’s programming philosophy of exploiting the transient publicity of media spectacles by drafting the beneficiaries of inordinate press attention, despite a lack of experience or qualifications – e.g. Sarah Palin. The preliminary format for the Zimmerman program is said to consist of segments analyzing breaking crime dramas such as murderous spouses, kidnapped sorority girls, celebrity arrests, high-speed police chases, and any stray rumors involving presidential sex scandals. Fox News contributor, and noted racist ex-cop, Mark Fuhrman, will have a regular spot on the panel segment to offer his expertise in undermining criminal prosecutions with racial epithets. In that respect Fuhrman, who famously extolled the virtues of the “N” word, shares common ground with Zimmerman who regards innocent black teenagers walking through his neighborhood as “f*&amp;^ing punks.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374460266508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:31:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374460340583-34</Id><Topic><Title>Zim to host "Stand your ground" on Fox</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374460266508</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:31:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox News CEO Roger Ailes welcomed Zimmerman to the network saying “We could not be more excited by having such a strong advocate of law enforcement on our team. George’s unique insight and commitment to safe neighborhoods and the preservation of the Second Amendment will connect with our audience and inspire Americans to stand their ground.” Ailes also said that Zimmerman will have a role on the Fox Nation web site where they specialize in flagrant lies, a skill Zimmerman has already demonstrated a knack for. Zimmerman’s new colleagues at Fox are also anxious to work with him. Sean Hannity, who gave Zimmerman his first platform on cable TV, praised his keen instincts and predicted that his hair-trigger analysis and spin on reality will surprise many. Bill O’Reilly is looking forward to lunching with Zimmerman at Sylvia’s. And Geraldo Rivera lauded Zimmerman’s critical eye on fashion that he hopes will put an end to the trendy adoption of thug-wear that has resulted in so much unnecessary bloodshed. The addition of George Zimmerman to the Fox lineup is a good fit to shore up both their editorial mission and their audience appeal. They are already receiving rave reviews from the NRA and the Tea Party. Throughout the trial Fox demonstrated an overt favoritism for Zimmerman and the prospects of his acquittal. Now, with his new assignment, he will make Fox the first and only network to feature a host who has actually snuffed out the life of an innocent American. And the icing on the cake is that the victim was black and almost certainly not a Fox viewer."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374460340583</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 22:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374464574315-35</Id><Title>Liz &amp; Sarah</Title><Msg>says she's considered entering Alaska's 2014 Senate race, and Liz Cheney has announced she'll try to unseat GOP Sen. Mike Enzi in Wyoming Cheney will run against a well liked Pub and the GOP leadership is furious, Palin may run against a Dem. These two and Ted Cruz should make for spicy entertainment.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1374464574315</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-21 23:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>