<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373429068746-1</Id><Title>What a REAL Scandal Loks Like ...........</Title><Msg>A prominent political donor gave $70,000 to a corporation owned by Virginia Gov. Robert F. McDonnell and his sister last year, and the governor did not disclose the money as a gift or loan, according to people with knowledge of the payments. Republicans will ignore such things as is convenient.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1373429068746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 00:04:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373429357975-2</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ole bidder needs ta post less and edjeekate hissef more</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1373429357975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 00:09:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373432404700-3</Id><Topic><Title>ETard, $1.34, big whoop</Title><Username>thirboa</Username><Timestamp>1373331250347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aye, MUCH more room to grow.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373432404700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373433385777-4</Id><Topic><Title>ETard, $1.34, big whoop</Title><Username>thirboa</Username><Timestamp>1373331250347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With Kenny gone there is a ton of room to grow....</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373433385777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373433576778-5</Id><Title>Lord Farquaad Gone so shortie is FRIED</Title><Msg>I love the smell of shortie sizzling in the morning. dalordie cares.</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373433576778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373433750585-6</Id><Title>ETFC Green Lights</Title><Msg>* Loans below 10 billion * Kenny gone * Real estate continues to rise * Interest rates soon to rise * Buyout on the table...company cleaned up * Reserves are too high * Moon went short</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373433750585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373464249053-7</Id><Title>Probing "transvaginal Bob"</Title><Msg>"Tuesday, July 9, 8:22 PM RICHMOND — A prominent political donor gave $70,000 to a corporation owned by Virginia Gov. Robert F. McDonnell and his sister last year, and the governor did not disclose the money as a gift or loan, according to people with knowledge of the payments. The donor, wealthy businessman Jonnie R. Williams Sr., also gave a previously unknown $50,000 check to the governor’s wife, Maureen, in 2011, the people said. The money to the corporation and Maureen McDonnell brings to $145,000 the amount Williams gave to assist the McDonnell family in 2011 and 2012 — funds that are now at the center of federal and state investigations. Williams, the chief executive of dietary supplement manufacturer Star Scientific Inc., also provided a $10,000 check in December as a present to McDonnell’s eldest daughter, Jeanine, intended to help defray costs at her May 2013 wedding, the people said."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1373464249053</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 09:50:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373464930529-8</Id><Title>Professor Palin on Global Warming</Title><Msg>Palin interview on Fox ...... The overwhelming majority of scientists believe that the Earth's climate is warming due to emissions of CO2 and other greenhouse gases created by industrial activity. If left unchecked, this process could increase temperatures significantly by the end of the century and lead to increased drought, severe weather and mass extinctions across the globe. According to Palin, however, these negative effects are outweighed by the positive, which apparently includes the dubious idea that restoring a Pliocene climate will bring Cretaceous species back to life. "Just to be clear," Carlson interrupted, "you're saying that if some animals go extinct because it's too hot, they'll be replaced by heat-loving animals that went extinct millions of years ago?" "Well, yes exactly," Palin responded. "That's what I call logic, Gretchen. Something the Looney Left in this country doesn't understand. They're so Debbie Downer about this whole thing, they can't see the bright side." "I don't think you can actually bring back the dinosaurs," interjected co-host Steve Doocy. "Once something is extinct it's gone forever. Also, dinosaurs went extinct 65 million years ago, so your dates are a bit off as well. " "Really?" a surprised Palin inquired. "But they did it in Jurassic Park. Are you telling me that movie wasn't based on a true story?"</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1373464930529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373466085118-9</Id><Title>Professor Palin on Global Warming</Title><Msg>shorty just starting to sweat</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373466085118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373466200009-10</Id><Topic><Title>What a REAL Scandal Loks Like ...........</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1373429068746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 00:04:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not a scandal if a Pubbie does it.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1373466200009</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:23:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373466320885-11</Id><Title>What a REAL Scandal Loks Like ..........</Title><Msg>being short in this stock is scandalous</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373466320885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373467680021-12</Id><Topic><Title>Professor Palin on Global Warming</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1373464930529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:02:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But they did it in Jurassic Park. Are you telling me that movie wasn't based on a true story?" She really said that?? The GOP tried to put this tool a heartbeat away from the POTUS.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373467680021</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373469734163-13</Id><Topic><Title>Professor Palin on Global Warming</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373466085118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ain't nobody got time for that</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373469734163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373470285741-14</Id><Title>GOP terrorizing NC</Title><Msg>"July 9, 2013 The Decline of North Carolina By THE EDITORIAL BOARD Every Monday since April, thousands of North Carolina residents have gathered at the State Capitol to protest the grotesque damage that a new Republican majority has been doing to a tradition of caring for the least fortunate. Nearly 700 people have been arrested in the “Moral Monday” demonstrations, as they are known. But the bad news keeps on coming from the Legislature, and pretty soon a single day of the week may not be enough to contain the outrage. In January, after the election of Pat McCrory as governor, Republicans took control of both the executive and legislative branches for the first time since Reconstruction. Since then, state government has become a demolition derby, tearing down years of progress in public education, tax policy, racial equality in the courtroom and access to the ballot. The cruelest decision by lawmakers went into effect last week: ending federal unemployment benefits for 70,000 residents. Another 100,000 will lose their checks in a few months. Those still receiving benefits will find that they have been cut by a third, to a maximum of $350 weekly from $535, and the length of time they can receive benefits has been slashed from 26 weeks to as few as 12 weeks. The state has the fifth-highest unemployment rate in the country, and many Republicans insulted workers by blaming their joblessness on generous benefits. In fact, though, North Carolina is the only state that has lost long-term federal benefits, because it did not want to pay back $2.5 billion it owed to Washington for the program. The State Chamber of Commerce argued that cutting weekly benefits would be better than forcing businesses to pay more in taxes to pay off the debt, and lawmakers blindly went along, dropping out of the federal program.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373470285741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:31:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373470461439-15</Id><Topic><Title>GOP terrorizing NC</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373470285741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:31:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At the same time, the state is also making it harder for future generations of workers to get jobs, cutting back sharply on spending for public schools. Though North Carolina has been growing rapidly, it is spending less on schools now than it did in 2007, ranking 46th in the nation in per-capita education dollars. Teacher pay is falling, 10,000 prekindergarten slots are scheduled to be removed, and even services to disabled children are being chopped. “We are losing ground,” Superintendent June Atkinson said recently, warning of a teacher exodus after lawmakers proposed ending extra pay for teachers with master’s degrees, cutting teacher assistants and removing limits on class sizes. Republicans repealed the Racial Justice Act, a 2009 law that was the first in the country to give death-row inmates a chance to prove they were victims of discrimination. They have refused to expand Medicaid and want to cut income taxes for the rich while raising sales taxes on everyone else. The Senate passed a bill that would close most of the state’s abortion clinics. And, naturally, the Legislature is rushing to impose voter ID requirements and cut back on early voting and Sunday voting, which have been popular among Democratic voters. One particularly transparent move would end a tax deduction for dependents if students vote at college instead of their hometowns, a blatant effort to reduce Democratic voting strength in college towns like Chapel Hill and Durham. North Carolina was once considered a beacon of farsightedness in the South, an exception in a region of poor education, intolerance and tightfistedness. In a few short months, Republicans have begun to dismantle a reputation that took years to build."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373470461439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:34:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373471399721-16</Id><Title>GOP terrorizing NC</Title><Msg>and shorty screams</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373471399721</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 11:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373485418330-17</Id><Title>Hey Shorty: Aloha ‘oe</Title><Msg>it's a glorious day in Hawaii</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373485418330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 15:43:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373485523608-18</Id><Title>Hey Shorty: E Komo Mai</Title><Msg>the water is fine</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373485523608</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 15:45:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373485703535-19</Id><Title>Hey Shorty: LLF Is A Real Kahuna</Title><Msg>hind site is 20/20</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373485703535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 15:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373486388504-20</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course you would not comment on the substance of the post, you chose to continue to show you are a type "A" personality which comes from being over mothered. Must have been tough growing up in such a household, being in constant trouble for dirtying your diapers. These kind of experiences do have a lasting effect on young children development later in life....just saying</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373486388504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 15:59:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373486913946-21</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Green Lights</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373433750585</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 01:22:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was a caution on the play when I first starting buying (at like $1.80 aka $18 today) but I knew the company had what it would take to recover, and everything under a buck/$10 was a freaking gift. I already took profits on those positions, all through last year and part of this year. It was free money. I have my long term position and my LEAPS left, but that's good enough, it let me power my account up nicely over the last years to where I have just about as much eTrade, but am diversified into two other similarly sized holdings as well. On the down side I end up paying short term gains on most of this years haul so far.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373486913946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:08:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373487111079-22</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It'd hide the profits or hide the kids when the Priest comes around . . . Don't want any of those asset destroying lawsuits the Catholic Church seemed to have no problems paying off? Some think their coffers still have gold coins dating from the reign of Emperor Constans, though I'd think they'd have probably melted them down by now . . . Maybe.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373487111079</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373487386229-23</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the bit where its better to teach a man to fish than to just give him a fish? I've always liked that part. Most liberals seemed to have skipped it though, forgoing mandatory job training and placement programs and instead embracing handouts, making the poor utterly dependent on the continued power of the Democratic party. No wonder Barrack can't implement ObamaCare, he'd drained the treasury giving away bread and hosting circuses.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373487386229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373487500626-24</Id><Title>Arab Spring going the way of the employer mandate</Title><Msg>Look as though the Golfer in Chief is turning the Arab Spring into a nuclear winter. But hey, President out golfing, and Secretary of State Kerry boating as the whole bloody affair blows up in their collective faces....how's $106 a barrel of oil feel at the pump coming to a town near you... And you dopes talk about Sara Palin being out of touch, what a canard.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373487500626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373487695506-25</Id><Title>Arab Spring going the way of the employer mandate</Title><Msg>and shorty has a tender brown eye</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373487695506</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373488675417-26</Id><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Msg>By Aviva Shen on Jul 8, 2013 at 10:00 am In the wake of the Newtown massacre, several states passed laws to allow school officials to carry firearms on campus, arguing that more guns would keep students safe. Insurance companies apparently disagree now that these laws are beginning to take effect. In Kansas, where the law kicked in July 1, major insurers have deemed the new policy too risky and are refusing to cover schools that arm their employees. Des Moines-based EMC Insurance, which covers 85 to 90 percent of Kansas school districts, has a longstanding policy of denying coverage to schools that arm employees, and they seem unlikely to change it to accommodate Kansas’ new law. Two smaller insurance firms that cover the remaining 10 percent of Kansas schools are also adopting the same policy. Insurers say the risk of giving guns to anyone but law enforcement in a building full of children would make a school’s coverage much more expensive. “We’ve been writing school business for almost 40 years, and one of the underwriting guidelines we follow for schools is that any on-site armed security should be provided by uniformed, qualified law enforcement officers,” EMC executive Mick Lovell told USA Today. While no Kansas schools have thus far taken advantage of the new law, districts all over the country started encouraging and even requiring teachers to carry weapons after the Newtown shooting. Over the weekend, a school district in Newcomerstown, Ohio, announced that they would allow employees to carry guns starting in the 2013 school year. The selected employees will undergo tactical training and get certified by the Sheriff’s department.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373488752126-27</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A week after the Newtown shooting in December, the National Rifle Association pushed for more guns in schools, arguing that “gun-free zones” attract killers. However, as the insurers recognize, arming teachers and custodians poses a far greater danger. Nor do more weapons do much to stop gunmen from doing harm; Columbine High School, the site of one of the most deadly shootings in U.S. history, had an armed guard. Most gunmen wreak havoc in just a few minutes, which would require an armed staffer to have a lightning-fast response time to disarm the shooter. Indeed, even gun shows require aficionados to check their weapons at the door for safety reasons."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488752126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:39:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373488807104-28</Id><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Msg>and shorty puckers</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373488807104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373489597549-29</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why did we arm airline pilots? Why do we put armed marshals on both random flights and some flights where suspicious activity among passengers was noted in the boarding area? I mean, guns can't really HELP can they?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373489597549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373489706237-30</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373488807104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe LLF will give shorty a reach around</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373489706237</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373490822933-31</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373488807104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:40:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unlikely, and if they do it'll only because they've figured out a way to pry some more of shorty's money away.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373490822933</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 17:13:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373494280147-32</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to ask the insurers why they trashed the NRA "plan". As for planes, most of the 9/11 concerns were met by reinforcing cockpit doors. Arming pilots is very controversial and actually fairly rare. Air marshals also rare and extremely expensive not to mention incredibly unproductive (estimated 4.2 arrests /year). APSA stats: # Airline Flts per day: 28,000 Airborne Right Now: 4988 Flights Protected by 2 Armed Pilots:</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373494280147</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373494522944-33</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg># Airline Flts per day: 28,000 Airborne Right Now: 4988 Flights Protected by 2 Armed Pilots:</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373494522944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 18:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373497267215-34</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flights Protected by 2 Armed Pilots:</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373497267215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373497472283-35</Id><Topic><Title>Free market rejects NRA lunatics</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373488675417</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 16:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yapoo acting up! Flights Protected by 2 Armed Pilots , under 3% Flights Protected by Air Marshals: (est.) 2% At Risk Flights: 95% Taxes Spent on Airline Security: $12B Pilot Volunteers Refusing to Fly Armed Due to Program Problems: 50,000 Cost to Protect 2% of flights with Air Marshals: $700M/year</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373497472283</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 19:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373504177379-36</Id><Title>Congress to stuff the individual mandate where they stuck gun control</Title><Msg>Up Obama's #$%$! tears the donkster</Msg><Username>robert_carr_donk</Username><Timestamp>1373504177379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 20:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373505075197-37</Id><Title>Palin on Global Warming</Title><Msg>junglebob is a dumb #$%$. The Daily Currant is a goof site for jr. high girls.</Msg><Username>contempt_4_conservative_idtios</Username><Timestamp>1373505075197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 21:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373506881709-38</Id><Title>Palin on Global Warming</Title><Msg>shorty getting hot too</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373506881709</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-10 21:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>