<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-04"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359992985450-1</Id><Title>DARTS for Jan</Title><Msg>When will ETFC announce DARTS for Jan? I have options that expire Feb 15th and was wondering if I should wait for this news. They said on the earnings call that were encouraged by Jan volume.</Msg><Username>gentlegiantromeo</Username><Timestamp>1359992985450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359995891795-2</Id><Title>Obama says buy a Volt</Title><Msg>After the first 70 miles, you start putting gas in your $40,000 volt for $4 per gallon. That is if it did not catch fire already. #$%$ him. The poor overtaxed man can't afford a Volt but he knows what tar and feathers are for. LOLOL!</Msg><Username>obama_2012_bankrupt_2013</Username><Timestamp>1359995891795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:38:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359997294994-3</Id><Topic><Title>-= =- Major ETFC Pre Promotion Report (LEAKED!!!!) -= =-</Title><Username>fosterjoseph487</Username><Timestamp>1359407914135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:18:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great report</Msg><Username>johnmorrill470</Username><Timestamp>1359997294994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 12:01:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360001830264-4</Id><Topic><Title>Understanding the Second Amendment</Title><Username>billtimmee</Username><Timestamp>1359996324485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:45:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Move back to England, they gave up their right to bear arms (previously assured by the Great Charter, which you probably know as the Magna Carta), and now they're being mugged by thieves with straight razors AND guns (more rarely because of sentencing enhancements). Often in their own homes were the mugging won't be seen by a bystander and reported.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1360001830264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:17:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360001929241-5</Id><Topic><Title>Understanding the Second Amendment</Title><Username>billtimmee</Username><Timestamp>1359996324485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:45:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jefferson once said that the greatest irony about the Second Amendment is that it really won't be pertinent until they try to take it away.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1360001929241</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:18:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360002475226-6</Id><Topic><Title>Understanding the Second Amendment</Title><Username>billtimmee</Username><Timestamp>1359996324485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:45:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funniest part of this is Barry is just grandstanding. When all is said and done Brak won't risk his political power on gun control, at least not right now. He's looking squarely at 2014 and taking back the house. This is just the latest shiny object meant to take the country's focus off a dismal economy, high debt and a poor record on job creation..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1360002475226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:27:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360002759070-7</Id><Title>On TV - MPLS-ST. PAUL!</Title><Msg>Air Force ONE is landing!!! Oh goodie! Another $40000 tax payer money down the drain for a 15 min. visit to the 4th precinct (that's where our property is located) to talk about his OBIMBO gun control and greet another tear jerker family who lost relatives by the shooting from a "proven mentally ill" employee, who obtained a gun legally and killed when got fired! (The family knew - the hospital knew - but the MN PRIVACY did NOT allow the data to be entered into the data base for gun applications) Picture - show's the idiot jogging like 12 year old from the car (hope he falls on his a$% on the ice - another PHOTO OP and WCCO just said - it's another CAMPAIGN STYLE approach (and they are the most left wing station!) More to follow as OBIMBO will speak! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360002759070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360002962940-8</Id><Topic><Title>On TV - MPLS-ST. PAUL!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360002759070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:32:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The coward of Benghazi.</Msg><Username>getyer_mittens_off_my_buns</Username><Timestamp>1360002962940</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:36:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360003175662-9</Id><Topic><Title>On TV - MPLS-ST. PAUL!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360002759070</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:32:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you like your police dog, hide it 'til after dinner.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1360003175662</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 13:39:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360004400246-10</Id><Topic><Title>DARTS for Jan</Title><Username>gentlegiantromeo</Username><Timestamp>1359992985450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 10:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On this leg up, I had sold about 7000-8000 shares, bough to close about 60 contracts of Jan13 $10 puts, bought about 100 contracts of Feb $11 calls, about 80 contracts of March $11 calls, some March $12 calls, and about 30 contracts of April $11 calls. I closed the Feb $10 calls and April $11 calls. My sense is to collect as high a gain as possible, while leaving the cheap calls there to rot over the time, just in case another spike is to occur. Or else, one month from now, or half a month from now, extend to buy the March and April calls at a lower time premium.</Msg><Username>etfc2013</Username><Timestamp>1360004400246</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:00:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360004785340-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says buy a Volt</Title><Username>obama_2012_bankrupt_2013</Username><Timestamp>1359995891795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:38:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Any trader worth his or her salt knows being too early is just as bad as being too late. Green technology is decades away from being substainable without massive subsidies. Don't write the epitaph on the combustion engine just yet.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360004785340</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:06:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360005967986-12</Id><Title>The CLOWN CLUB is in session!</Title><Msg>1.Escorted by the new MPLS Chief of police (a now outspoken lesbian - the old chief was a great officer who started on the beat and he is NOT there) and liberal civilians, families of which their kids who got shot in houses by pistols because of gang retaliations! 2. Senator Chief CLOWN Al Franken - comedian! 3. All OBIMBOCRATS at large! I think that the nation will see his "Campaign Speech" on world news - here it is life on the local stations! - NO, they started and then switched to reg. programming, how can this be in liberal MN with their beloved OBIMBO???? Guess, have to wait till tonite's news??? But then it was just a 15 Min./$40000+ event (Not to count all the money spent locally for security and to inconvenience the citizen to take icy side roads)! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360005967986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:26:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360005991453-13</Id><Title>Jessie Jackson, come home Mr. President</Title><Msg>Right on brother! Obama needs to send in Big Sis to clean up these thugs and murders in these inter cities. I have even a better plan, send in the ACLU, Feinstein, Schumer, Bloomberg, Axlerod, and the Hollwood elities to patrol the streets with bull horns asking the criminals to surrender their weapons. Put it on "Pay For View" to help pay down the deficit. ...heck I would pony up the asking price in a New York minute. Chicago marchers urge Obama to come home to address gun violence CHICAGO (Reuters) - Civil rights leader Jesse Jackson and relatives of victims of fatal shootings in Chicago urged President Barack Obama on Saturday to come back to his hometown and address the gun violence plaguing the city. Before a march on the city's South Side, Jackson, a former Democratic presidential candidate, said America's third most populous city needed more help than Mayor Rahm Emanuel and police superintendent Garry McCarthy could offer. "When the president shows up, it shows ultimate national seriousness," said Jackson, a Chicago resident. He also called for the U.S. Department of Homeland Security to help patrol the streets of Chicago. Gun violence in Chicago has been in the national spotlight over the past year, with 506 murders in 2012, an increase of 17 percent from the previous year. As of Thursday, there were 42 homicides and 157 shootings so far this year, according to Chicago police. The issue received new urgency with the killing this week of 15-year-old Hadiya Pendleton, an honors student who performed with her high school band at Obama's inauguration on January 21.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360005991453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:26:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360006606279-14</Id><Topic><Title>Jessie Jackson, come home Mr. President</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360005991453</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:26:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad that the gang members didn't open fire on OBIMBO on the north side, because they "wonnaah keeep ther gunnnnns"! But then on the other hand if he can take the guns away from the legal owners then its easier for the gangs to rob people/stores and break in! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360006606279</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:36:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360007618198-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says buy a Volt</Title><Username>obama_2012_bankrupt_2013</Username><Timestamp>1359995891795</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 11:38:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Some how you always seem to miss the point. First, stop putting yourself out as some oracle of self righteousness, it's not becoming. Second, you can't compare other developed nations in regards to gas prices, the US has millions of miles of roads and is 10+ the size. Thirdly, what happened to the federal road taxes per gallon we already pay..#$%$ away on social justice programs. Lastly, if you feel so strongly that government has the answers to our energy problems tax time is right around the corner...there is a line on the tax form where you can send in additional money. Call up that hypocrite Al Gore, he could direct you on how to do it.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360007618198</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:53:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360007828364-16</Id><Title>ROY BEAN!</Title><Msg>We need some more of his kind and the death penalty!!! Here in St. Croix county it's already going in the right direction! You might have heard about the case, where a estranged husband (with RESTRAINING ORDER) came to River Falls and slit the throat of his 3 girls and then called his ex at work that she can come home now! Well our judge her in Hudson (County Seat) did deny "Change of Venue", denied "Insanity Plea" till proven other wise and one way or another he will go away forever! Synopsis: Ban AL knifes, (easy - not under the second amendment) Law Change: Violation of a restraining order - life in prison! MN judges finally coming around too! 17 year old shoots thru a hose with pistol and kills 7 year old - gang retaliation! 1. Judge waves him into adult court! - GOOD! 2. Judge gives him 28 years and PLUS two years being a gang member! GOOD (for MN) Synopsis: No death penalty - ROY BEAN would have handled it different! Law change: STOP &amp; FRISK (You you arrest 50% of the gang bangers carrying - 99% black Of course they would scream DISCRIMINATION right away! Results: NOTHING will change! Matter of fact the MPLS/ST. Paul "Gang Strike Force" got disbanded!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360007828364</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:57:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360007838417-17</Id><Title>positive price action!!</Title><Msg>I have been a long term holder of etfc and of course, have gone through some tumultuous times. Since the earnings release, the price action has just seemed different. Days, like today, in which you would have had more weakness than the rest of the market and other financials over the past 4or 5 years, now appears to have some strong support and postitive price action. I am guessing, but I don't think this is coming from the retail investor. I feel this has to be driven by institutional buying, which will be a great sign. Hope this continues. It has been a long time coming.</Msg><Username>kwhitey16</Username><Timestamp>1360007838417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:57:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360008772690-18</Id><Title>Yep - Campain Speech!</Title><Msg>OBIMBO IDIOT, concentrate on MN and what got Gabi Gifford to do with it! You'll hear his rant on TV tonite! "Don't count on Washington to get things done - nothing get's done, till it is done" - Finally the truth! Mentioned: Assault weapons and magazines! Not mentioned: How to control of gang violence and weapon possession! How to fix the mental health and institutional released reporting programs! How to enforce applications by felons, who lied and got denied, they walk??? The law states..........under oath - no consequences and then they get a weapon on the street! (Gun running is already alive and well) Congratulations OBIMBO for wasting $40000+ for nothing but a PHOTO-OP!!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360008772690</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:12:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360010553548-19</Id><Title>Best Super bowl ad</Title><Msg>The baby rides again ....besides Buyonce super spectacular body movements, the ETFC was the greastest</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1360010553548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:42:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360012769468-20</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$- IN DEPTH ETFC Analyst Report #$%$-</Title><Username>paulward735</Username><Timestamp>1360008343521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:05:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Important report</Msg><Username>albertlee911</Username><Timestamp>1360012769468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360013359622-21</Id><Topic><Title>Best Super bowl ad</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1360010553548</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:42:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buyonce sucked! Couldn't even understand a word she screamed and then like a broken record screamed the same SH** over and over, like a stuck record! Maybe next Superbowl we could have a "White or Spanish girl" (NOT Madonna) and the under wear show?? Even SMOOTCHELLE in a bikini swinging a Skeet Gun! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360013359622</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 16:29:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360016385066-22</Id><Topic><Title>The CLOWN CLUB is in session!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360005967986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 14:26:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on CLOWN_11111! You were missing at the clown meeting, he could have at least sent VP-Clown "Little Joe", so he could have worked on the 4th budget to pass, he missed in a row now! But that would have been real work, plus - NO PHOTO-OP!!! "The CLOWN CLUB is in session!" Another GOP summit - NOT? VERY SCARY! Did you get your new bumper sticker yet? Support your local (O) #$%$??? And O#$%$ is sitting on top of the Capitol fiddling (like Caesar Nero) while the USA is going down in flames - keep it up left winger! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1360016385066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:19:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360017960878-23</Id><Title>Obama's pay back to Gays and trail lawyers</Title><Msg>I quess Obama wants to do to the Scouts what the gays did to the Catholic Church...Once they got in to the church they do what they always do...unfortunately for the church it cost them billions in settlements for child molestation charges which the trial lawyers benefited handsomely from. It ooks like the lawyers are looking for another host to bleed dry with the community organizer help. Obama Calls on Boy Scouts to Welcome Homosexuals President Obama called on the Boy Scouts to open their ranks to homosexuals. His response came during an interview ahead of Super Bowl XLVII. CBS News’ Scott Pelley asked the president if scouting should be open to gays. “Yes,” the president replied. “Gays and lesbians should have access and opportunity the same way everyone else does.” BSA national leaders are meeting this week in Dallas to discuss lifting a ‘no-gay’ ban on both members and leaders. On Monday a group of 42 religious groups will publish a half-page ad in USA Today calling on the Scouts to resist political and economic pressures to lift the ban. The group is taking out a major advertising buy tomorrow denouncing the Scouts’ decision to consider changing their longstanding policy prohibiting openly gay Scout leaders or Scouts.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360017960878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:46:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360018971255-24</Id><Title>Bank ny mellon bought 6% of etfc</Title><Msg>Just annonced today</Msg><Username>headtoo</Username><Timestamp>1360018971255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360019463686-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's pay back to Gays and trail lawyers</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360017960878</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 17:46:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the BSA decides to invite gay men into the program, I'm pulling out my 15 year old son!</Msg><Username>acuna_matada</Username><Timestamp>1360019463686</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:11:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360020427163-26</Id><Topic><Title>Bank ny mellon bought 6% of etfc</Title><Username>headtoo</Username><Timestamp>1360018971255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's interesting, the Bank of New York is not your typical bank, they tend to invest in fee driven businesses rather than focusing on standard banking. They also own Pershing which is one of the largest clearing firms on Wall Street and has a software platform for broker dealers for clearing trades, executing orders, etc, many brokers use them as their back office. Pershing used to be owned by Credit Suisse but was sold to BNY when CS had a meltdown and needed to raise capital. Pershing's tech is not that great while E*Trade's is as we know amazing. While not on my suitor radar I could see BNY make a play for E*Trade as BNY/Pershing does not have nearly the financial advisory (buy side) business as TD Ameritrade or Schwab so perhaps an E*Trade and BNY/Pershing merger could have a lot of synergy and put the combined company into that category. Very interesting scenario. Stay long and strong, this company is worth more than $10. I was in the securities business for nearly 20 years, I've been to Pershing's office in Floram Park, I know the sell and buy side well. I do not belive E*Trade will be bought by TDA or Schwab rather a suitor like BNY or one of the top tier banks.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1360020427163</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:27:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360021484366-27</Id><Topic><Title>Bank ny mellon bought 6% of etfc</Title><Username>headtoo</Username><Timestamp>1360018971255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:02:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good news...although I still believe one of the big money center banks like BofA, WF, or Citi will eventually own ETFC.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1360021484366</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 18:44:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360036956634-28</Id><Title>ETFC is position 8 on a top 10 Over Valued listing in the website Extreme Value Stocks Pretty cool.</Title><Msg>ETFC is position 8 on a top 10 Over Valued listing in the website Extreme Value Stocks Pretty cool.</Msg><Username>norberto859</Username><Timestamp>1360036956634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 23:02:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>