<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371190354656-1</Id><Topic><Title>The Real Problem with this Country</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371178947444</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 23:02:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real problem are douche bags that spam our etrade forum with political drivel. Why do this here?</Msg><Username>driveby881100</Username><Timestamp>1371190354656</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 02:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371214070962-2</Id><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Msg>(prism 2007 was to protect Americans they said, but prism in 2009 is unconstitutional well why didn't they say so in 2001 or 2005 or 2007?) Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance How does Sean Hannity feel about the federal government collecting information on millions of Americans? Well, that depends. According to clips compiled by Media Matters, the Fox News host’s position regarding government surveillance is evidently based entirely on who happens to be occupying the Oval Office at the time. For example, Hannity called the recent revelation about the extent of National Security Agency surveillance programs under Democratic President Barack Obama a “very clear violation of the Fourth Amendment.” But when President George W. Bush was in power, the conservative commentator seemed to have no problem with the NSA gathering data on Americans. In fact, he was a staunch defender of the practice during the Dubya years.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371216825511-3</Id><Topic><Title>United STASI of Amerika</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370890040156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Question Authority' use to be a popular Liberal Bumper Sticker. Now, the Liberals are 'THE MAN'!! Now it's 'Trust Us' and SHUT UP!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1371216825511</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 09:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371219206844-4</Id><Topic><Title>NEARLY HALF OF ALL AMERICANS SAY SURVEILLANCE ARE ACCEPTABLE WITHIN LIMITS</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1371015094463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is good it is getting exposure sooner or later. I guess with Bush the "Patriot Act" was the least of America's problems, as that bunch was hell-bend on destroying the country any way they could, so in that respect, just by the fact it is getting exposure now - it indicates America is much better off under Obama than it was under Bush. I just find it interesting that the conservatives are up in arms about the second amendment being sacred, but don't care about the 4th at all... Seems to me amendments are all about ensuring individual "rights and freedoms"..... so why 1 and 2 are "oh so important" and nobody can even name 3 and 4? OK - so 3rd is kinda lame if you look at it, but still..... 5th is well exposed as all the wall-street crooks, politicians, criminals and Hollywood use it all the time, but seriously, second and fourth should come hand in hand.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371219206844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:13:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371219902238-5</Id><Topic><Title>NEARLY HALF OF ALL AMERICANS SAY SURVEILLANCE ARE ACCEPTABLE WITHIN LIMITS</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1371015094463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so far.... you meant to say "I have not seen or heard of any illegal use so far"..... And frankly - since the Patriot act makes practically ANY surveillance activity "LEGAL", so yeah- you may not ever hear of "illegal use" .... The point of the issue is not if it IS misused - it's if it the government CAN misuse it... and in this one, it's a loud and strong "YES, WE CAN" No checks or balances usually lead to abuse. Be it in corporate , criminal, or political world....... (hell - these 3 go hand in hand anyway...)</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371219902238</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:25:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371220313190-6</Id><Topic><Title>Im thinking $14 + after they report in July</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371150983032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:16:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Hell freezes over.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1371220313190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371220359244-7</Id><Topic><Title>Im thinking $14 + after they report in July</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371150983032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:16:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Rand Paul becomes POTUS.</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1371220359244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:32:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371220452412-8</Id><Topic><Title>Im thinking $14 + after they report in July</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371150983032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:16:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When wimmen look at John Holmes and say "whyzit so short".</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1371220452412</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371221462712-9</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heard something about FISA court? What happened to Obama's position on Patriot Act since 2008? Not "Breathtaking Hypocrisy"?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1371221462712</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:51:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371221593950-10</Id><Topic><Title>Im thinking $14 + after they report in July</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371150983032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-13 15:16:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rocked for 2% on a half million shares today. That is the turd everyone knows and loves. Dead money for years and will be for years to come......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1371221593950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 10:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371225561280-11</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's on Fox. They're either hypocrites, or wear really short skirts. Or both.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371225561280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 11:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371228006037-12</Id><Title>Ain't this the truth???</Title><Msg>Perhaps the Intelligentsia of the Radical Right might pay attention to Christie. After all, he does seem to put the Public first, rather than" winning at any cost" , which has been the GOP approach for the past 4 years. Block and stall, "Keep America struggling, and we will win in 2012(nope) 2014 (dream on) 2016 ( only if the GOP chooses to move towards the middle) Until the GOP decides to put all Americans first, not just the non performing job creators, it will remain a "Failed Party" with a Failed Agenda.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1371228006037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371234482272-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ain't this the truth???</Title><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1371228006037</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 12:40:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Frankly - I think they should double down on their policies - I think they are not "conservative" enough.!!! They should double down on "pro birth/anti life", double down on he xeno and #$%$ phobias (and frankly any and all phobias they currently experience .... like science-phobia, knowledge-phobia, reason-phobia, civility-phobia, social-phobia, progress-phobia, compassion-phobia etc etc etc ..........I'm sure they all these phobias have very important sounding names, but I'm not a psychologist...) I think this would truly serve the country and its future the best. Who knows - maybe one day they will develop voting-phobia and the problem will be solved just like that... !!!</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371234482272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 14:28:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371239226335-14</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have come to the conclusion that "Lucky" is falling further and further into the intellectual abyss. In fact he is beginning to make the baby in the E*Trade commercials look smart... Now you know how the Fuhrer came to power.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1371239226335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 15:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371241483078-15</Id><Title>Etrade keeps hiring ppl from Blackrock/GS, etc.</Title><Msg>only because these firms have investments in Etrade. Etrade is only a stepping stone for these people before moving out to another firm. Yet these CEOs collect vastly amount of salary while in Etrade. There is a reason ETFC is not going anywhere.</Msg><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371241483078</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371241892887-16</Id><Topic><Title>time to heed Ike's warning of the military industrial complex? Mitt just ran on increasing the defense budget</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371057195067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is head of NSA. What do you want him to say? Similarly Lois Lerner testified before Congress. She also said IRS did nothing wrong and than took the 5th.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1371241892887</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371243514839-17</Id><Topic><Title>time to heed Ike's warning of the military industrial complex? Mitt just ran on increasing the defense budget</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371057195067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jeez, that is all you have? and btw.... just about the entire US congress..... and the people YOU voted for McCain and mitttens are telling you that you are not being spied on....... which if you understood how prism works... you might have a clue..... NOBODY is reading you emails or listening to your phone calls....... but if al Qaeda linked people in other countries call your NUMBER.... that would pop up...... get it?......and THEN.... since THAT would be a flag....... a warrant would be obtained .............. how about if you want to prove how YOU are harmed..... just show it... the harm to you..... . or ANYONE.... NOBODY has claimed any harm from this program..... ....where are they? Snowden and others are saying what if,,,, or it could be........</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371243514839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 16:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371243964182-18</Id><Topic><Title>time to heed Ike's warning of the military industrial complex? Mitt just ran on increasing the defense budget</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371057195067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everybody loved the Fuhrer, he was just looking for the good German people...cut him some slack.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1371243964182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371244438113-19</Id><Topic><Title>time to heed Ike's warning of the military industrial complex? Mitt just ran on increasing the defense budget</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371057195067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as usual you don't make much sense.... except that Mitten's, like the fuhrer, you mention, was big on increasing military spending, and mittens was a strong advocate of domestic surveillance. Is that your point? and your ilk ARE the "might is right" types who hate democracy, also like the fuhrer.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371244438113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371244819941-20</Id><Title>57% fear the obvious</Title><Msg>That is a pretty big majority of folks that don't trust the government...can't blame them after the IRS behavior. 57% Fear Government Will Use NSA Data to Harass Political Opponents Friday, June 14, 2013 There is little public support for the sweeping and unaccountable nature of the National Security Agency surveillance program along with concerns about how the data will be used. Fifty-seven percent (57%) of voters nationwide believe it is likely the NSA data will be used by other government agencies to harass political opponents. A new Rasmussen Reports national telephone survey shows that just 30% consider it unlikely and 14% are not sure.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1371244819941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371244917001-21</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dear stupid dishonest person.... did congress send Obama a bill ending the patriot act? and what a hypocrite you are, faulting Obama for not undoing the bush policies that you supported. Everyone here knows that you are such a dishonest hypocrite that if Obama and the dems HAD undone the patriot act somehow ( the gop house could obstruct THAT effort) that you would then be denouncing him for NOT protecting the nation and being negligent for ending Bush's Prism program which has the support of the nearly the entire republican party ....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371244917001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371245473369-22</Id><Title>Ariz Gov Wins BIG for Obama !</Title><Msg>Arizona will expand Medicaid to cover nearly 300,000 poor residents next year after a bipartisan coalition passed a measure backed by Gov. Jan Brewer (R) through the state legislature on Thursday. Brewer, a conservative and avowed foe of President Barack Obama's health care reform law, announced her support for the Medicaid expansion in January, but faced stiff resistance from fellow Republicans in Arizona's House and Senate. During a marathon session that began Wednesday afternoon and stretched into the wee hours of Thursday morning before culminating in a final vote late Thursday afternoon, a handful of Republicans joined Democrats in the House and Senate to pass the Medicaid expansion. Although Obama's health care law continues to divide elected officials and the public along starkly partisan lines, Brewer is one of nine Republican governors who have bucked their party and embraced the Medicaid expansion.................... Pubs are falling in line to kiss Obama's bottom.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371245473369</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371245847409-23</Id><Title>this boards rightys would whine about their rights being violated in a slow supermarket lane, no doubt</Title><Msg>the jackass honking in slow traffic is one of these guys too, honking because the traffic is a violation of his constitutional rights.............. that's about the gist of the law suits against the IRS..... the fact is being delayed is not a violation of anyone's rights at all.....jeez.....especially as these groups could have just done business as tax exempts while delayed and anyway none were denied the tax exempt status they applied for......</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371245847409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:37:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371246293393-24</Id><Title>2007 Prism good, pubs not wadding panties: 2009 Prism bad &amp; some pubs throw their skirts up &amp; wad their panties</Title><Msg>Prism good, pubs not wadding panties: 2009 Prism bad and some pubs throw their skirts up and wad their panties........ what a spectacle! Bush 2007 prism is about protecting America they said..but now some of the same ones say Prism 2009 is a totalitarian monster..... wow what happened between 2007 and 2009....... to make them do their pantie wad dance.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371246293393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:44:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371248209680-25</Id><Topic><Title>2007 Prism good, pubs not wadding panties: 2009 Prism bad &amp; some pubs throw their skirts up &amp; wad their panties</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371246293393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 17:44:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have to agree. If the Republican party is anything like the posters on this board, not one of them wears pants. Never seen so much hormonal hysteria.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371248209680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 18:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371251251543-26</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I supported Patriot Act the way it was originally designed. With strict approval of FISA court. Obama though didn't like it as Senator, as well as many in democrat camp. Patriot Act was bad for Senator Obama. For president Obama it didn't do enough! As president Obama had another "change of heart". He not only got along with the program he harshly criticized, he largely expanded it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1371251251543</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 19:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371258581735-27</Id><Topic><Title>NEARLY HALF OF ALL AMERICANS SAY SURVEILLANCE ARE ACCEPTABLE WITHIN LIMITS</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1371015094463</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 01:31:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crown, Freedom? Unless your chin deep in porn or selling dope, who do you imagine wants to hear any details about your small and meaningless life mr/ms paranoia? This is a ridiculous issue blown up by village idiot libertarians like the Pauls and Glen Beck. No one even cares if you pumped the town floozies or have been exercising your right hand to the sight of bearded women. Go back to sleep Gomer.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1371258581735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 21:09:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371264251491-28</Id><Topic><Title>Sean Hannity’s Breathtaking Hypocrisy on NSA Surveillance ( same as with many on this board)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371214070962</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 08:47:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are breathtakingly ignorant and dishonest from 2001 until 2007 Bush was doing Warrantless wiretapping .............Warrantless wire tapping done............"by the BUSH National Security Agency (NSA) was revealed publicly in late 2005 by the New York Times and then discontinued in January 2007." ..............................get it?.......................... .that is why the patriot act was bad and why it was IMPROVED... I guess you were too busy mindlessly cheerleading bush to notice that he was the one subverting the constitution................... you are such a fox toady.......</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371264251491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-14 22:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>