<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364621592053-1</Id><Topic><Title>Guns saves lives and property</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364480388387</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 10:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you're missing the forest for the trees. Your loss, unless you think liberties that have been important to free societies for over 3,000 years suddenly don't apply because "we're different".</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364621592053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 01:33:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364623254625-2</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Voter ID push found racist</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364245743675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We demanded the American Indian tribes learn English to treat with us on THEIR land, and convert to Christianity to boot . . . and people are now upset that citizens are becoming aware that we have a serious free rider issue and want to do something about that. Answer, deflect the question, instead call into question the character of the person who's become aware that the emperor has no clothes. Obviously, if he cannot SEE the clothes, it must be because he works for a competing clothier . . . If only the Emperors tailors had been as clever as the DNC.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364623254625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 02:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364623816748-3</Id><Topic><Title>The 28th Amendment</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364604325150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The VA also exempted themselves, requiring veterans to receive care at THEIR facilities rather than giving them vouchers for the equivalent insurance they would need to get the kind of care they need WITHOUT getting it from the government and supporting a corrupt and inefficient system that dissolves the bulk of its food and excretes it in the form of paperwork. Unending reams of paperwork. The few tasks that have automated don't leave paper around, so as a result the directions, prescriptions, and referrals on those electronic documents need never be read by anyone else once they are filed. Though they CAN be recalled later if the patient manages to remember that they HAD an appointment and when it was the VA moved and/or cancelled it the LAST time. I'm waiting on oh so many things at the Dallas VA, some from 10 years ago, that by the time it all comes rolling in I'll likely be in the hospital a week being poked, prodded, cut, measured, and generally made miserable by freaking titanium through me bones.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364623816748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 02:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364624199380-4</Id><Topic><Title>CA home prices: Back to 2008!</Title><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1364413302730</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:41:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually my area in incredibly popular in the Dallas Metroplex; Grapevine in a nice residential district built during the late 60's off Rt 114 right between Dallas and Tarrant counties on the Tarrant county line side (important as Dallas Country is a dry county, and restaurant row starts on the first highway exit about 300 meters from my house. Directly at the intersection at the end of the road is a major Hospital (which the VA has decreed I can't use), and down the road a bit on the other is a large church, going north up the road near the hospital a bit is an elementary school, and then the police department. I'll be putting my house here on the market soon at a rather steep market, and according to the Real Estate agent, I may well get it before I'm actually ready to move, which sill complicate things a bit, but still . . . Real estate prices ARE looking up in some areas. Though admittedly here they never fell, they just failed to grow at the previous rate.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364624199380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 02:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364648194891-5</Id><Title>Profit Share Hits Post-War High and the Post Doesn't Notice</Title><Msg>Profit Share Hits Post-War High and the Post Doesn't Notice by Dean Baker The revised GDP data for the fourth quarter released yesterday showed the profit share of corporate income hitting 25.6 percent. This is the highest since it stood at 25.8 percent in 1951. However if we look at the after-tax share of 19.2 percent, we would have to go back to 20.8 percent share in 1930 to find a higher number, excepting of course the 19.3 percent number hit last year. To put this in context, the after-tax profit share was just 14.5 percent in Reagan's Morning in America days. The difference would have come to roughly $330 billion last year. To put this in the 10-year budgetary window that is the standard framework in Washington these days, the rise in after-tax corporate profits since the Reagan era can be seen as equivalent to a $5.0 trillion tax on the nation's workers</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364648194891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 08:56:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364655979313-6</Id><Title>If we recalibrate the model. increasing CO2 cools the atmosphere</Title><Msg>"The global temperature standstill shows that climate models are diverging from observations," says David Whitehouse of the Global Warming Policy Foundation. ( I predict it's the Heimholtz variable) "If we have not passed it already, we are on the threshold of global observations becoming incompatible with the consensus theory of climate change," he says. (Hello. Your model is wrong.) Whitehouse argues that whatever has happened to make temperatures remain constant requires an explanation because the pause in temperature rise has occurred despite a sharp increase in global carbon emissions. (Anybody seen Al Gore?)</Msg><Username>call_your_mommee</Username><Timestamp>1364655979313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364657457964-7</Id><Title>Home prices market vs replacement price</Title><Msg>home prices in most areas, exclude SFO &amp; SJC haven`t gotten close to their replacement values, until that happens moving to new homes will continue to fade.. some areas roof replacement exceeds the actual current market price.</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1364657457964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:30:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364659794694-8</Id><Title>BO defends democracy</Title><Msg>President Barack Obama issued an Executive Order today, March 28, which will set up the Presidential Commission of Election Administration. The Commission will consist of 9 members appointed by the President and have two co-chairs. Those appointed will have experience and or knowledge of “Federal, State or local elections”. “The Commission shall be composed of not more than nine members appointed by the President. The members shall be drawn from among distinguished individuals with knowledge about or experience in the administration of State or local elections, as well as representatives of successful customer service-oriented businesses, and any other individuals with knowledge or experience determined by the President to be of value to the Commission.” The Commission will be making recommendations that will “promote the efficient administration of elections in order to ensure that all eligible voters have the opportunity to cast their ballots without undue delay” “The Commission shall identify best practices and otherwise make recommendations to promote the efficient administration of elections in order to ensure that all eligible voters have the opportunity to cast their ballots without undue delay, and to improve the experience of voters facing other obstacles in casting their ballots, such as members of the military, overseas voters, voters with disabilities, and voters with limited English proficiency.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364659794694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364660234953-9</Id><Topic><Title>If we recalibrate the model. increasing CO2 cools the atmosphere</Title><Username>call_your_mommee</Username><Timestamp>1364655979313</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:06:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bombshell IMF Study: United States Is World’s Number One Fossil Fuel Subsidizer By Jeff Spross on Mar 29, 2013 at 12:24 pm Between directly lowered prices, tax breaks, and the failure to properly price carbon, the world subsidized fossil fuel use by over $1.9 trillion in 2011 — or eight percent of global government revenues — according to a study released this week by the International Monetary Fund. The biggest offender was by far the United States, clocking in at $502 billion. China came in second at $279 billion, and Russia was third at $116 billion. In fact, the problem is so significant in the U.S. that the IMF figures correcting it will require new fees, levies, or taxes totaling over $500 billion a year, or more than 3 percent of the economy. The most significant finding is that most of the problem — a little over $1 trillion worth — is the failure to properly price carbon pollution. Global warming is the ultimate example of a “negative externality” — a market failure in which one market actor enjoys the benefits of an exchange while another actor pays the costs.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364660234953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 12:17:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364677777694-10</Id><Title>MN REJECTS Fed. Exchang!</Title><Msg>Of all LIBERAL, left wing strong hold states, MN rejected the FEDERAL (OBIMBO-OBIMPOLOSI) health insurance exchange program! They will have their OWN system instead, so the Feds. can't dictate MN what to do about health care and where/how their money is applied (Just passed and signed by Governor Dayton)! Here in WI, we already have a system to choose from insurance and supplements if you are retired/Medicare (including plan D), problem is that you have to have the money to purchase the insurance!!! Medicaide and "Badger Care" no longer qualify for supplemental Insurance and are no longer taken by the Medical Centers and Clinics! WI will never adapt the FEDERAL system - the governor already made that clear! ROWDY (Watch for my next topic)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364677777694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:09:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364698869608-11</Id><Title>Armed in the South</Title><Msg>Three killed after dispute between neighbors Posted: Mar 29, 2013 3:58 PM CDT Updated: Mar 30, 2013 8:35 AM CDT By Chris Dyches HARRISBURG, NC (WBTV) - According to police it is determined that 50-year old, Anthony Charles Hardy was the double shooting suspect that fatally shot and killed a neighbor after an argument. Deputies were called to a home off Coachman Court in Harrisburg around 4 p.m. Friday afternoon where reported shots were fired. The Cabarrus County Sheriff's Office arrived on the scene, along with Harrisburg Fire First Responders and Cabarrus County EMS. Shortly after their arrival, 42-year old Daniel Thomas Kirchner and another neighbor, 64-year old Gary Wade Stocks both of Coachman Ct., were the deceased victims found in the backyard behind Kirchner's residence.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364698869608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364700329879-12</Id><Topic><Title>MN REJECTS Fed. Exchang!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364677777694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And that's why Walker is well hated by the left. Wonder what took Dayton to reject exchange? By all means, he is no Walker. Did he bump his head? There must be some political calculation here.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364700329879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364700891787-13</Id><Title>Arkansas residents evacuate as Exxon-Mobil tar sands pipeline ruptures</Title><Msg>By David Ferguson Saturday, March 30, 2013 12:38 EDT An Exxon-Mobil oil pipeline ruptured Friday afternoon in the town of Mayflower, Arkansas, forcing the evacuation of 20 homes and shutting down sections of interstate highway. According to Little Rock’s KATV, a hazardous materials team from the Office of Emergency Management has contained the spill and is currently attempting a cleanup. The burst pipe is part of the Pegasus pipeline network, which connects tar sands along the Gulf coast to refineries in Houston. Thousands of gallons of crude oil erupted from the breach around 3:00 p.m. on Friday, spilling through a housing subdivision and into the town’s storm drainage system, fouling drainage ditches and shutting down Highway 365 and Interstate 40. Residents were evacuated to avoid health hazards from crude oil fumes and to keep stray sparks from igniting the standing oil. Emergency workers contained the spill by hastily constructing earthen dams. Exxon-Mobil reportedly has a crew investigating the accident. The company released a statement Friday that read, in part, “We are working with emergency responders and local authorities to respond to the incident and are establishing an information line for community support. We regret that this incident has occurred and we apologize for any disruption or inconvenience this has caused.” The Arkansas Oil and Gas Commission told Channel 7 News that, as an interstate pipeline, Pegasus has no local control, oversight or inspection. Only federal officials from the Pipeline and Hazard Material Safety Administration are authorized to inspect and maintain the pipeline..</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364700891787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>