<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-28"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367154987317-1</Id><Title>Al Gore: Douchenozzle</Title><Msg>Hey, fatso, it's April and it's freezing cold.</Msg><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1367154987317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367157790100-2</Id><Topic><Title>I have communists under by bed, and probably in the closet too</Title><Username>investorpelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367079886739</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 12:24:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i have an impersonator that is infatuated with me. while flattering, i hope their adoration doesn't overwhelm.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367157790100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 10:03:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367169059595-3</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore: Douchenozzle</Title><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1367154987317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it depemds where you are in our nice country. Hereabouts temps are in the upper 90 degrees. Why are you so dumb???</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1367169059595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367169447681-4</Id><Topic><Title>What's in your wallet</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366920354218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, all you ever do is make predictions that never come tthrough</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1367169447681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 13:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367174690050-5</Id><Title>IMO Company Needs To Issue Shares-At Least $300 million</Title><Msg>Rarely does issuing shares increase earnings per share but in this case I believe it does. They are hamstrung by the leverage ratio, both at the bank and the holding company, so much so that they had to move 8 billion in potential interest earning assets off the balance sheet. Increasing equity by 300 million should allow them to move approximately 3 billion of that cash back to the company. If it just earns 2% it would create approximately 60 million of additional interest income before taxes, approximately 40 million after taxes and if my math is correct this move would be earnings per share accretive. It also would give them flexibility to make some other moves that may have been prevented by their leverage ratio situation, like taking a loss on paying back the fed borrowings of over 6 billion on which they are incurring 200 million in annual interest expense. I wonder if maybe they were floating this possibility and Ken G. wanted to get out before it happened.</Msg><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1367174690050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:44:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367176584452-6</Id><Topic><Title>IMO Company Needs To Issue Shares-At Least $300 million</Title><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1367174690050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:44:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Screw that, we've had all the dilution we need considering the cost of money today. Yes, if Interest rates were higher I'd accept the dilution, but for now they're not and we've already taken all the dilution we can in the short term (last few years)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367176584452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367178976978-7</Id><Topic><Title>IMO Company Needs To Issue Shares-At Least $300 million</Title><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1367174690050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:44:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you do the math and see just how hamstrung they are because of the leverage ratio issue. It will get worse if they can't use the TRUPS in their equity calculation. They won't be able to do much of anything capital wise for a decent amount of time if the CFO was correct when he said provisions will stay in the 50 million per quarter range for the balance of the year. This move should add $50 million a year to their equity number due to the increased earnings and the ability to use more of their DTA. Also, my math may be incorrect as I said but this isn't dilutive to earnings per share, it's accretive.</Msg><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1367178976978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 15:56:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367180357380-8</Id><Topic><Title>What's in your wallet</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366920354218</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-25 16:05:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**all you ever do is make predictions that never come through** Lets be honest, did your health premiums rise after the President said they would not?.... It's a simple yes or no question.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367180357380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367180812548-9</Id><Topic><Title>Get used to it GOP cave dwellers !</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366732196845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but rodent - would you riot against your own Republican senators. like those in Rhode Island who propose gay marriage???</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367180812548</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 16:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367185858601-10</Id><Title>al gore is fat proves global warming false</Title><Msg>and who needs science when the bible says everything is under control as designed? If global warming is true, which it isn't but if it is, then it is part of the grand design like malaria ,the tsetse fly, tape worms and leukemia all working for the best in this the best of all possible worlds even if we can't see the big picture.</Msg><Username>investorpelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367185858601</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 17:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367187859969-11</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's the IDIOT Now?... Jac_k#$%$!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1367187859969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:24:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367188335537-12</Id><Topic><Title>Get used to it GOP cave dwellers !</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1366732196845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-23 11:49:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WRONG we voted those liberals out already and got Ryan and others into federal and state government!!! (Yep, riot agaionst them, just like with the unions as was shown on TV! Sen. Harsdorf and Gov. Walker WON the recall election, imposed by the liberals and unions by a LANDSLIDE! (Was just a waste of money!) Gun control lawe was a given and the next gun show is held in our High School and as the schedule showes in many other school troughout WI!! In WI "Domestic Partner" is NOT legal, like across the border in MN!!! (We threw a bunch of that UNION #$%$ out too, including "Poodle Wasserman" - now we have surplusses and our school/property taxes and saletaxe didn't/wont go up since Walker became governor!) If they would move to WI, their marriage is NOT recognizedand they won't get spousal support, shared insurance coverage and all the FREE STUFF that goes with it! MN is pushing for gay marriage rights too because of their democRATS including the governor, but of course he is running for reelection! I just got a e-mail from the governor Walker, he is in China with a big deligation, pushing WI products and sent a picture of the grand opening of a Harley-Davidson Dealership! Now the Keystone pipeline will be the next program that flies into OBIMBOS face! More Obimborama failures to come! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367188335537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367188876194-13</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sadam had them moved to Syria before the UN DEBATING CLUB had a clue and that's why we couldn't find them! Sadam was as clever as Stalin and by the looks, they could have been brothers! Now they are DEBATING again on SYRIA and are still clueless! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367188876194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367189538065-14</Id><Title>,,,,,Pig Tales,,,</Title><Msg>Whatttzzzzzzup?????? Lemmee start by giving a shout out to Warren,,,,, Heyyyyyy Warren,,,, :-) ,,,, I hope you all are enjoying one of my new commercials,,, I'm driving along and a cop pulls me over and asks, "Do you know why I pulled you over???",,,, and I reply,,, "Cause I'm a pig in a convertible???",,,, Hahahahahaha,,,, gotta luv it. Warren, U rock. Hmmmmm, what else,,, Oh, I'm still driving da semi's. Thanks George. Oh, to duh young girl who cut me off and then hit be brakes in front of me 2 nites ago, then waved at me thru her sun roof as I blew the horn at her,,, Sweetie, imagine your car flipping over about 10 times as your head is smashed against the pavement. Just the front axle on my truck weighs more than two Escalades, never mind the rest of the truck and trailer. Hmmmm, what else,,,,, think U have problems????,,, a half a tank of fuel costs $400,,, glad someone else is paying duh tab,,,,, Ok, lemmmeee conclude by aXing,,,, is duh turd at 35.50 yet??? Yer friend, p ,</Msg><Username>z_pigster</Username><Timestamp>1367189538065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 18:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367192579450-15</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lackofinfo, Look at the date of your post, idiot!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! On March 19. 2013 there was no evidence of chemicals flowing in Syria, idiot!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1367192579450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 19:42:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367193739460-16</Id><Topic><Title>Al Gore: Douchenozzle</Title><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1367154987317</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 09:16:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More nonsense from the back of the cave. Are all republicans #$%$ ? Or do all the #$%$ ones post here ?</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367193739460</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:02:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367194594684-17</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Reagan aided saddam and the Ayatolloh, and both were on the terrorist list. And neither were a threat to the USA." How can they be on terrorist list and not being a threat? Can you make some coherent point? Or just farting white noise to let everyone know ducky didn't go away from this MB? Soviet Union was US ally during the WWII. Yet, Soviet Union remained major threat to this country for many decades after. Does that mean FDR should never make deals with Soviets to defeat #$%$ Germany? Help to Saddam was limited by weaponry and intelligence needed to fight Iranians. US didn't help Saddam building his nuclear reactor. France did. And if it wouldn't be for Israels' "meddling" in 1981 Saddam would be sitting on nukes today. Would that be wonderful! US military aid to Saddam was strategic move to fight a bigger threat at the time. We acted accordingly to our best interests. Now, what's meddling? Afghanistan was meddling. I guess, 3000 Americans murdered on our soil is not an act of war? Obama didn't want to meddle with Iran in early 2009 when mullahs were doing carnage on the streets after elections. But helping Libyan rebels to overthrow Qaddafi wasn't meddling? Last year he said that using chemical weapons in Syria would be a "game change". If he will take action(big IF), will that be meddling? Look, I am getting confused with this word. Can we even loudly condemn actions of foreign governments or it's going to be interpreted as meddling? Would you be kind to give a proper definition for the word that wouldn't make you a hypocrite?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367194594684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367196296338-18</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dates mean Nothing when you are talking about people being tortured by a rogue Dictator. You want to Quibble...while you try and Bury the Topic! Your exclamation point usage just indicates how Stupid you are...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1367196296338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 20:44:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367207274916-19</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Saddam never moved anything to Syria. Syria has always had iits own chemical-bio weapons.</Msg><Username>hollywood_liberal</Username><Timestamp>1367207274916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 23:47:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367207458860-20</Id><Topic><Title>HEY JB!...Chemicals are Flowing in SYRIA!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363743004938</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 21:30:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1367207458860</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 23:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>