<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367300475469-1</Id><Title>Did deluded liberals follow Al Gore into Stupidland because he is fat?</Title><Msg>No! Deluded liberals followed Al Gore into Stupidland because they are every bit as stupid as he is. It is cold. Throw another liberal on the fire.</Msg><Username>contempt_4_conservative_idtios</Username><Timestamp>1367300475469</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 01:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367301764176-2</Id><Topic><Title>Here's our idiots list . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367260579387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 14:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hedging is expensive, I tend to do it ONLY when there is a pivotal event coming up that could cause issues for my long term strategy if the stock took a temporary dive. Or I try to do it only then, sometimes you just can't help but got for an options play that you think might work out even though it's a long shot.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367301764176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 02:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367326744027-3</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist move over!</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367292866351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 23:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grover can do the gop tantrum and hissie fit two step all he wants but it seems to have lost its effect. Maybe he can try getting boozed up and swallow a bottle of valium to let everyone know he is really really serious.</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1367326744027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 08:59:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367327958176-4</Id><Title>Republican-Heavy Counties Eat Up Most Food-Stamp Growth</Title><Msg>Seventy percent of counties with the fastest-growth in food-stamp aid during the last four years voted for the Republican presidential candidate in 2008, according to U.S. Department of Agriculture data compiled by Bloomberg. They include Republican strongholds like King County, Texas, which in 2008 backed Republican John McCain by 92.6 percent, his largest share in the nation; and fast-growing Douglas County, Colorado. The number of food-stamp recipients in Pitkin County, which includes the Aspen Ski Resort, has increased faster than any other reported county in the nation during the last four years. It climbed to 270 households, a 463 percent increase over the 48 that received food stamps in 2008. The increase in food-stamp recipients also was pronounced in Republican bastions such as Collin County, Texas, which registered a 128 percent increase to 47,102 households in 2011, and Gwinnett County, Georgia, where usage climbed 117 percent to 101,815 households. Collin County, a Dallas suburb, gave McCain 62 percent of its 2008 vote. Gwinnett, part of the Atlanta metro area, supported the Republican with 55 percent of its ballots. The increase in food stamps in those strongholds doesn’t mean Romney will lose votes, said Michael Franc, vice president for governmental studies at the Heritage Foundation, a Republican-leaning research organization in Washington. “We’re talking about people who got pretty hammered by the economic meltdown,” he said. “It’s a temporary hand-up, not a permanent condition of life. They’ve gotten help, but it’s been something they’ve requested very reluctantly.”</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1367327958176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 09:19:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367331479077-5</Id><Topic><Title>Republican-Heavy Counties Eat Up Most Food-Stamp Growth</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1367327958176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 09:19:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's 2014 - IDIOT!!! St. Croix County, WI 78% Republican - almost ZERO Food stamps- voted for/elected Romney and NOW Gov. Walker, Ryan, Harsdorf, Johnson ............in 2012 by LANDSLIDE - will elect REPUBLICAN by those numbers or better again!!! (White Population 96%, Lationo 1%, Asian 3%, Black 0%) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367331479077</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367332739383-6</Id><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Msg>can't log on</Msg><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367332842839-7</Id><Topic><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Me too!</Msg><Username>dctrig</Username><Timestamp>1367332842839</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367332970446-8</Id><Topic><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same here. Think they are getting DOS attacks, like SCHW?</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367332970446</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333073604-9</Id><Topic><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, same. seems like a DOS attack.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1367333073604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333245581-10</Id><Topic><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ditto</Msg><Username>a_girl_in_black</Username><Timestamp>1367333245581</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:47:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333280512-11</Id><Topic><Title>Web site down,again</Title><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367332739383</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:38:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>make sure you're not responding to the board with the email you sign into at etrade. ask for lots of free trades</Msg><Username>triathlete_investor</Username><Timestamp>1367333280512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:48:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367333422003-12</Id><Title>Site down</Title><Msg>getting ready for the merger.....lol</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367333422003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333788348-13</Id><Topic><Title>Site down</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367333422003</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:50:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Site is back up</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1367333788348</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:56:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333802268-14</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist move over!</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367292866351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 23:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing wrong with taxing internet purchases or from out of state - good for local business! People go and "window shop" at stores and then ordering on the net - the local store loses that business and wastes time on demos! I had to pay WI sales tax last year for my parts for my BMW from sales tax free NH - it's only 5.5%! In MN, merchants/customers paying a sales tax for the Viking Stadium and now a sales tax on clothing - and don't even talk about theit now cigarrett and alkohol taxes - no wonder our liquer stores which are open 365 (even on election day) are doing a brisk business - by the Van loads! I saw one MN loading 20 cases of Leinenkugels, 10 carton of cigarretts, shopping carts of Wine and Booze!!! (MN - Discout liquer, 12pack of Coorse $14.99 - Hudson, WI - 24pack $16.99 -10% Senior discount!) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367333802268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367333842044-15</Id><Topic><Title>Republican-Heavy Counties Eat Up Most Food-Stamp Growth</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1367327958176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 09:19:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh sure, you can cherry pick a couple exceptions, and think the whole world looks like the view from your cave. But the truth is, Pubs are HUGE consumers of social services. And they always elbow their way to the front of the line for cheese.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367333842044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 10:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367334309317-16</Id><Title>Site back up</Title><Msg>Good deal!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367334309317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367335832971-17</Id><Title>Obama hates capitalism and that's what made America great!!!</Title><Msg>Obama: Favors progressive taxes on the rich to redistribute income and wealth from winners to losers and to ensure that all pay their fair share. (As he has said: “When you spread the wealth around, it’s good for everybody.”) PES: Collective responsibility makes society stronger when people work together, and all people are enabled to live a dignified life, free of poverty and protected from social risks in life. Obama: Favors collective responsibility (as defined by the federal government) to protect all from social risks through food stamps, welfare programs, extended unemployment benefits, guaranteed health care, the bailing out of big companies, forcing renegotiation of mortgages, class action law suits, and other measures. (Instead of opportunity and incentive to succeed, no one is allowed to fail).</Msg><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367335832971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367335910772-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates capitalism and that's what made America great!!!</Title><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367335832971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now take a look at RCON it's got earnings due out maybe it will break $5... Looks good for a huge move RCON</Msg><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367335910772</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367337733335-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates capitalism and that's what made America great!!!</Title><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367335832971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really have no clue how wealth is distributed in america today.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1367337733335</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367338340539-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama hates capitalism and that's what made America great!!!</Title><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367335832971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:30:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sec_fordummies</Msg><Username>steammaker</Username><Timestamp>1367338340539</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 12:12:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367341239084-21</Id><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Msg>all time since WW2 record corporate profits.....due to Obama! pub logic....if they blame him for the bad things they should praise for the good........ceos know, they too are making record money and their taxes are lower than the avg rate of the Reagan 80s. American business has never had it so good. U.S. corporations’ after-tax profits have grown by 171 percent under Obama, more than under any president since World War II, and are now at their highest level relative to the size of the economy since the government began keeping records in 1947, according to data compiled by Bloomberg. Profits are more than twice as high as their peak during President Ronald Reagan’s administration and more than 50 percent greater than during the late-1990s Internet boom, measured by the size of the economy. US jobless aid applications fall to 5-year low the deficit has been lower nearly every year of obama, it rose nearly every year for bush. UE is lower than where bush left it, Bin laden is dead, more people have health insurance,stocks are making money, the record corporate profits of 2011 were topped by all time record corporate profits of 2012, usa oil production is higher now than bush era, there is less illegal immigration; and lol Mittens went back to the cayman islands after losing big. UE rose 2.8% in w's last year and it never rose that much again. and had Mccain won, UE would have gone to 17% and would still be there ala hoover taking UE to 25%.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367342567398-22</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you know, the companies are not making anything, consumers are not purchasing anything, the fed is simply handing out money...sheesh.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1367342567398</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367342807101-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear that, but no one will tell me where to go get my pile of fed money. Do I have to listen to tush limbbalz or glenn beck to find out where people are going to get a pile of fed money, or what? I will buy some more stocks as soon as I get my pile of that money.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367342807101</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367343307950-24</Id><Topic><Title>Grover Norquist move over!</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367292866351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 23:34:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, This is probably one of these rare occasion when I give your post a thumbs up. It is indeed refreshing to see your post without your childish and ugly "Obimbo stuff."</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367343307950</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:35:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367344564850-25</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you ever seen a Muslim hospital? Have you heard a Muslim orchestra? Have you seen a Muslim band march in a parade? Have you witnessed a Muslim charity? Have you seen Muslims, shaken hands with a Muslim Girl Scouts? Have you seen a Muslim Candy Striper? Have your seen a Muslim do anything that contributes positively to the American way of life ???? The answer is no, you did not. Just ask yourself WHY ??? Barack Obama, during his Cairo speech, said: "I know, too, that Islam has always been a part of America's history." AN AMERICAN CITIZEN'S RESPONSE Dear Mr. Obama: Were those Muslims that were in America when the Pilgrims first landed? Funny, I thought they were Native American Indians. Were those Muslims that celebrated the first Thanksgiving day? Sorry again, those were Pilgrims and Native American Indians. Can you show me one Muslim signature on the: United States Constitution? Declaration of Independence ? Bill of Rights? Didn't think so. Did Muslims fight for this country's freedom from England? No. Did Muslims fight during the Civil War to free the slaves in America ? No, they did not. In fact, Muslims to this day are still the largest traffickers in human slavery. Your own half-brother, a devout Muslim, still advocates slavery himself, even though Muslims of Arabic descent refer to black Muslims as "pug nosed slaves." Says a lot of what the Muslim world really thinks of your family's "rich Islamic heritage," doesn't it Mr. Obama? Where were Muslims during the Civil Rights era of this country? Not present. There are no pictures or media accounts of Muslims walking side by side with Martin Luther King, Jr. or helping to advance the cause of Civil Rights. Where were</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1367344564850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:56:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367348501437-26</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"G-d only knows in how many evil hands weapons sold by Obama's "Fast and Furious", to Libyan or Syrian rebels ended up in." Funny you didn't mention the greatest source of weapons getting into criminal's hands............ Gun shows and private sales. Your Obama hate confuses you to the point of total confusion.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367348501437</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367348796206-27</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has done all the things Bush couldn't. End the war in Iraq. Killing Osama. Increasing captures on the border. A highly successful drone war. Greatly reducing military casualties as a result. It seems you were much happier when our military were coming home in body bags. Bush is responsible for 9/11 Obama has Benghazi. You Pubs think Benghazi was far worse.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367348796206</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367349347651-28</Id><Topic><Title>Site back up</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367334309317</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 11:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's pathetic is based on the behavior I know exactly what the problem is and exactly how to fix it. Meanwhile, if I know this then the company's CTO should also know this, and he should be beating his database management crew with a large wooden stick.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367349347651</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367349587771-29</Id><Title>New economic outlook, am in a bidding was for 16 acres of prime riverfront property.</Title><Msg>price has been jacked twice now, Figuring that the economy will float merrily along for another two years. zrip and such. If there was anything better to "invest" in, would be reluctant to tie up so much cash. Wish me luck?</Msg><Username>hard_on_eraser</Username><Timestamp>1367349587771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367351510722-30</Id><Topic><Title>New economic outlook, am in a bidding was for 16 acres of prime riverfront property.</Title><Username>hard_on_eraser</Username><Timestamp>1367349587771</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:19:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good luck. I did the same in 2007 when I exited the market, investing in 43 acres of wooded land near Texarkana on the Texas side. Was one of the best investments I've made. Not only is God not making additional land in any significant quantity, but to hear the pundits the results of man's actions are taking it away. Just don't build on any land less than 8 meters above sea level. Mine is 29 meters above sea level, so it'll be a swamp someday (in fact there is already a swamp nearby) BUT, I built on a local high point, so eventually mine will be a vaguely dry area in a swampy area built into the ground in a lined concrete amalgamate shell. I'm building a more conventional 2,400 foot structure on it first, later for use an an incentive for employment for ranch hands, but the eventual structure will be earth sheltered concrete and if I have no other use for it I'll rent the smaller building I'm working on now out by the week during deer season, at least until the area is consumed by swamp probably long after I'm dead. That alone should earn me enough for the payments. Always keep at least 25% of your assets in carefully chosen real estate, land on habitable planets is at a premium. DON'T invest in overpriced structures in cities where the value of your land is dictated by the policies of local "enlightened" people who might, unless you live in a REALLY upscale neighborhood, just seize your land for an "economic development project" (though thank God and Texans that practice has been made significantly harder here now).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367351510722</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367351770628-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come up with a totally impractical idea that sounds like if it'll work it'll solve a big hunk of their political problems but pump it like you're just THIS close to a solution for the impossible part (like Newtons laws of motion and other trivial physical laws) but you just need a few paltry (tens, hundreds, thousands) of millions of dollars and you'll have the solutions in (fill out a span of years either BEFORE or AFTER the next election cycle depending on if the current administration needs a quick successful looking company or an "eventual success" to point to, or just wants to quietly crater the money).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367351770628</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 15:56:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367352847919-32</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't make funny statements. Weapons sold on gun shows do require background checks just like being sold from gun store. Criminals always find their illegal ways to obtain ammo. In 2009 and 2010 gun store owners made numerous calls to ATF authorities about suspicious buyers, and they were forced to sell those illegal arms. Lots of people in Mexico died from AK47s sold in Arizona. There is at least one border agent fallen victim from those arms too. No one in AG department is held responsible. We have government allowing to buy arms illegal way. Yes, it is funny. Government sets an example. But you blame gun shows? Pathetic.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367352847919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 16:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367355408624-33</Id><Title>New President Hired at Etrade....</Title><Msg>$250k signing bonus upfront. They love handing out the money over there...... The Company entered into an employment agreement with Mr. Nandra, pursuant to which he will receive an annual base salary of $750,000. He will be eligible for an annual cash performance bonus with an annual target of $1,650,000 and for an equity incentive with an annual target initial value of $1,650,000, subject to vesting over four years following the grant. For 2013 only, he will be guaranteed his target cash bonus and his target equity bonus, each to be paid in early 2014. Mr. Nandra will also receive a one-time cash sign-on bonus of $250,000. If Mr. Nandra is terminated without cause or resigns due to adverse actions by the Company, and he signs a release of claims, he would receive severance benefits of one times his annual cash compensation (salary and annual cash target bonus) and his equity would be accelerated, in addition to a pro rata payment of his cash bonus for the year of termination. If the termination occurs in anticipation of, or following, a change of control, his severance would be increased to two times his annual cash compensation.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1367355408624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 16:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367357528733-34</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gun shows are highly unregulated. Why do you think they are trying to strengthen regulations ? Aside from private sales, gun shows lead in unregulated sales. But you are too bothered by Fast &amp; Furious to see through your clouded vision.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367357528733</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 17:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367359615953-35</Id><Topic><Title>Republican Backlash Claims 5 More Senators !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1367282324728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 20:38:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Horse feathers...dream on!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367359615953</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:06:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367360436986-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think the unemployment rate is really around 13%, these companies fired just about all they could, and have no plans to hire anyone new. Corporate profits are up because productivity is up. No jobs allows these corporations to squeeze the folks left with a job....wise up! To credit the community organizer is laughable...there is no top line growth, and WS has lowered the bar on earnings so low even E*Trade could beat.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367360436986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:20:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367360713268-37</Id><Title>!00K in benifits went to the bombersand their parents</Title><Msg>The verdict is in...liberalism is a mental disorder. Tsarnaev family received $100G in benefits The Tsarnaev family, including the suspected terrorists and their parents, benefited from more than $100,000 in taxpayer-funded assistance — a bonanza ranging from cash and food stamps to Section 8 housing from 2002 to 2012, the Herald has learned. “The breadth of the benefits the family was receiving was stunning,” said a person with knowledge of documents handed over to a legislative committee today.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367360713268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:25:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367362300061-38</Id><Topic><Title>!00K in benifits went to the bombersand their parents</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367360713268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They had a blast with the money. The ungrateful b'tarts blasted the very taxpayers who was footin the bill.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1367362300061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367362350919-39</Id><Title>Where O' where is the volume..</Title><Msg>Not the volume of hot air from the politicalretards who think their opinions really matter on a financial board.. You'd think theselosers would make a move out of mom's basement and get a life.. Such wasted volume..</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367362350919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:52:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367364567023-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush and beck tell you to buy gold ! LOL !!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367364567023</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 19:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367364753552-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical logic from the back of the cave. Technology and robotics have made too many jobs obsolete. Workers will have to retrain to keep up with a rapidly changing world. I forgot. You wingnutz hate change. You're still bitter cause there's no need for buggy whips anymore.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367364753552</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 19:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367364985246-42</Id><Topic><Title>!00K in benifits went to the bombersand their parents</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367360713268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, they had a blast with the mula they received from the very conservative Cheney/Bush administration. Look out conservatism is a disease!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1367364985246</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 19:36:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367366512697-43</Id><Topic><Title>!00K in benifits went to the bombersand their parents</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367360713268</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 18:25:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You gotta admit that the targeting was spot on!...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1367366512697</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367366565489-44</Id><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Msg>My bet is that within 36 months there will be 10's of millions paid out in Severance...again!!.....when will it ever stop?</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367367171873-45</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All authorized gun retailers are doing background check in store or at the show. Theoretically you can bring your toilet sink to gun show for sale. Or you can bring AR- 15 to flea market. You sell your private ammunition at the place or event of your convenience. Where do you think a criminal rather go to buy ammunition? Gun show where you deal mostly with professionals, or flea market where anyone can sell anything? I bothered by Fast &amp; Furious because our beloved govt authorized arm sales into the hands of known criminals. People are still dying from those arms. But those gun shows are the problem?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367367171873</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:12:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367373077931-46</Id><Title>Idzik costing shareholders lots of money</Title><Msg>I seldom find replacing everyone in every position very helpful. It just makes the current people loyal to you no matter how crazy you are. Do we have a leader with a vision or another crazy #$%$ CEO ? His previous reputation points to the latter. God help us if his bonuses just pay for his lithium! The good guys and bad guys are jumping ship. Lets see what we have in about 3 quarters.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367373077931</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:51:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367373514058-47</Id><Topic><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree 100 % . They replace everyone as if it is their fault that interest rates are so low. Maybe they should fire the chief of the Federal Reserve and keep some of the managers. Idzik is buying loyalty not talent. These newbies probably no better or worse than the others.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367373514058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 21:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367379023285-48</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big news. Robotics started affecting the job market only after Obama occupied Oval Office.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367379023285</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 23:30:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>