<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-28"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362059619386-1</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Could Be Added To The NASDAQ-100 Soon:</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1361955623043</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 04:00:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1st... let's see some consistent profits</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1362059619386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 08:53:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362062111309-2</Id><Title>The thoughts of budget cuts regardless of how they happen may improve market sentiment</Title><Msg>If we rally instead of crashing then maybe Congress will get the hint. However, our Markets are as dramatic as a reality show, so probably expect a sell-off.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1362062111309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 09:35:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362069986036-3</Id><Topic><Title>pacifican repeats his old lie</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361995364611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 15:02:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You make it more difficult, dear. "there was no ACA in 2009....." HR 3590 (ACA) was introduced in the summer of 2009. It was voted in the House in late December 2009. CBO report was requested by Pelosi to set the vote. Preliminary acceptable condition for the vote to take place was the cost for ACA not exceeding $1T, which Douglas W. Elmendorf successfully "delivered". Anyone can google this report and see what's in it. Although, when Senate vote took place in March 2010, the CBO estimate was already changed upward to be around $1.2T. I gave you quotes from articles from Weekly Standard, you on the other hand do not refer to direct source either. Actual report is more for professionals to digest, so good luck with it. Fact is, CBO itself released numbers, they were cited in the media and the cost was revised upward but magically "balanced" by other parts of the program. "rightwing blather" disageed. But GAO claming Obama care will add $6T to US debt in the future decade. You can hardly call GAO a "rightwing blather". In my eyes CBO lost its credibility.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362069986036</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 11:46:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362079292697-4</Id><Topic><Title>Boy, wasn't that expected from this WH?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362014998328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:29:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a. I don't see the law Obama would brake in this particular case. Are you making this staff up? b. Obama breakes the law many at will. He makes recess appoinments when Congress is not in recess. He makes executuve orders overwriting existing laws, by which he oversteps the bounds of executive branch power. b. My main point was not about legality of what Obama should or shouldn't do in this case. White House threatening journalist is not inapropriate, it is next to criminal.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362079292697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:21:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362080306810-5</Id><Topic><Title>Boy, wasn't that expected from this WH?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362014998328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:29:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shut up and admire the emperors new clothes</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1362080306810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:38:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362081750683-6</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives Regret Taking Woodward’s ‘Threat’ Story Seriously</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362080280076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:38:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WH is back pedalling full speed. Distorting the picture as usual. Woodward was shouted at, scolded. It was probably the first time Bob got disobedient and he discovered Obama administration behaving like dictators. So, since when Politico became conservative source?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362081750683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:02:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362082871944-7</Id><Topic><Title>BO-purest administration EVER!!!</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1362080933570</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:48:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That part about the Obama administration I'll agree with. It's hard to indict a public official for anything without a massive supporting press storm, and that's not gonna happen on Barry's watch. At least not unless the scandal is so overwhelmingly obvious that not even the New York Times can just ignore it, as they have other stories. I suppose the other great advantage is that it's hard to criticize someone when they really don't DO anything. So far more of his appointees have been happy to let the agency professionals run things while they sit back and collect a check, For instance it's fairly obvious that some of them are either asleep on the job or are inimicable to the agencies to which they've been assigned, like assigning a tee-totaling anti-gun liberal who doesn't smoke or like loud noises to run the BATFE (and whatever initials they might have added to indicate their "additional responsibilities"). Since he knows nothing about booze, cigars, handguns, and what explosive is best to use in which situation, well, wrong choice eh?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1362082871944</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:21:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362083145742-8</Id><Topic><Title>Boy, wasn't that expected from this WH?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362014998328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-27 20:29:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Woodward is right, Even INS has been releasing imprisoned illegals awaiting deportation because they "won't have the budget to hold them once the sequester kicks in". Never mind asking why instead of releasing them they simply didn't load them into boxcars and dump them off in Juarez? The Mexicans shouldn't be able to complain about it as we'll only send back the ones that snuck over from THEIR side of the border. So even if they're from Central or South America, well, you let them leak through your borders, so here you are, send them back south.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1362083145742</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:25:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362083387891-9</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives Regret Taking Woodward’s ‘Threat’ Story Seriously</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362080280076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:38:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem remains that the WH is threatening to use those cuts to target prime programs as if they were the ONLY place the fat could be trimmed. They're not, and many of the "dire consequences" of the sequester are things the Democrats knew they could afford to begin with. Basically Obama is sacrificing his Bishop in order to promote a Pawn (the next Democratic candidates in the midterms).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1362083387891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:29:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362083911032-10</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives Regret Taking Woodward’s ‘Threat’ Story Seriously</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362080280076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:38:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Emails are just part of the case and the only one WH disclosed so far. As Obama parrot you are deaf for anything beyond things that please your fine tuned biased ear. You don't listen to Woodward himself. So, Bob used to be a good boy until now. Remember! He brought down Richard Nixon.But he was useful than, now Obama can throw him under the bus.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362083911032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 15:38:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362086262104-11</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatives Regret Taking Woodward’s ‘Threat’ Story Seriously</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362080280076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 14:38:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you are confused. WH can humiliate its own emploees, if they are not happy, they would just let go. Bob is not a WH employee to be shouted and threatened, Bob represents us. So, who they were shouting at? Funny, you need that to be digested. I am sure you vote too.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362086262104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 16:17:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362086471801-12</Id><Title>Impeach Dumbo Now!</Title><Msg>'Gerbil' board him!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1362086471801</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 16:21:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362086620019-13</Id><Title>The media has crated their own Frankenstien</Title><Msg>Bob Woodward is a victum of his own creation. Now Obama's aids are trying to say he is old and senial.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362086620019</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 16:23:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362088990296-14</Id><Title>Dumbo vs. a Diaper</Title><Msg>Whats the difference between Dumbo and a Diaper?? At the end of the day, they are both full of Krap!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1362088990296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 17:03:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362093045055-15</Id><Topic><Title>Does Bush regret not finding any wmd?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362090542537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 17:29:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boosh thought he actually found some underneath his desk. But upon further inspection it turned out only to be a can of WD-40.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362093045055</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362093297550-16</Id><Title>Media has created their own Frankenstein</Title><Msg>Bob Woodword is now a victim of his own liberal doing. Obama's aids are trying to discredit him as being old and out of touch.... You vill not question the fuhrer. Old Billy Clinton tried that with Monica, but old mom had her save the famious dress stopping Billy from unleashing his hit team to trash her....you Democrats are a class act.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362093297550</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362093341245-17</Id><Title>Woodward to kick Obama's #$%$</Title><Msg>Woodward called Obama a fary and told him to step outside.</Msg><Username>boreheadisme</Username><Timestamp>1362093341245</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:15:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362093928264-18</Id><Title>Bob Woodward is a Legend for Telling the Truth to Power</Title><Msg>Obama would not know the truth if it crawled up his skirt.</Msg><Username>i_got_yer_big_finger_right_here</Username><Timestamp>1362093928264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362094987796-19</Id><Title>Obama Sez Susan Rice Sent the Threat</Title><Msg>. . HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>grope_this_sportivo</Username><Timestamp>1362094987796</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:43:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362099628715-20</Id><Topic><Title>Media has created their own Frankenstein</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362093297550</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 18:14:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Brak will go after Bobbyboy (the nixon exposer) he'll go after anyone he perceives is betraying him. Whether you're in love wif him or he's just your hero, you'd better not get caught crossing him. How long will it take you useful idiots to realize you is bein' used?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362099628715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 20:00:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362108137821-21</Id><Topic><Title>Does Bush regret not finding any wmd?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362090542537</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 17:29:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wmds were sent to syria. no worry they are being put to good use.</Msg><Username>barryfromthehood</Username><Timestamp>1362108137821</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-28 22:22:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>