<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-11"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368271156219-1</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for more of Dumbo's 'Composite Girlfriends' fake stories from one of his many autobiographical fiction novels.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368271156219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 07:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368274706170-2</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I re labeled a bottle of 2 buc chuck @ a private poker party, and sold each glass for 10 bucs, everyone like it..</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368274706170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:18:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368274994147-3</Id><Title>Loan reserves</Title><Msg>Home prices (sales) are getting multiple offers above asking price....this should lop off a cool billion on the bad loan reserves balance sheet should show between 500 million to 700 million positive</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368274994147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368277350275-4</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't stop jumping up and down with joy. A pile of poop popped out of me , that's how hard I was jumping up and down but the schadenfreude is well worth the mess on the floor, that I just moved my lazy-boy on top of, I even found a full can of Old Milwaukee under it to toast with. All is well and good in this, the best of all possible worlds.</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368277350275</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368278891326-5</Id><Title>a burrito proves things are as they are meant to be</Title><Msg>everything works out for the best in this, the best of all possible worlds! Amen! How else could I get a Sirloin Steak &amp; Egg Burrito with Fire Roasted Tomato Salsa prepared and served by poor people who make the minimum wage and who envy me because I can afford such a lavish burrito? I am so thankful God made me a genius and the inheritance was a nice bonus from above. Nothing like good genes and plenty of cash, I always say.</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368278891326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368278903433-6</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"OOh if Dumbo was Republican" I can see, considering the current lineup GOP politicians, that you could actually wish Obama was republican, but..... For your party to accept anything Obama - he would have to be white and old first. At that point - with all his accomplishments - you would hail him as the Reagan Reborn....... He sure is more conservative than Reagan ever was....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1368278903433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368283884475-7</Id><Topic><Title>CO2 Emissions have Dropped Since Obama in Office</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368243553264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:39:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait until the other Clinton gets sworn in for eight years. The rep's crying and wailing will be deafening. They don't realize that it is all self inflicted and well deserved..</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1368283884475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 10:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368290807830-8</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark Sanford stole from his govt. Lied to his wife. Lied to his mistress. Lied to his constituents. And now he represents the party of family values. Again. It seems now that all republicans are hypocrits. Pubs go crazy if they think Obama lies. But they elect a known liar and chaet.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368290807830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368291451835-9</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please everyone knows that "Good Old Time Family Values" is code for the 50's when men slapped their wives around and no body talked about it, where your daughter is afraid of Uncle Minty, but you don't wanna ask why there's a bloodstained clothes hanger in her closet, where Chet is thrown of out the house to join the Navy or die after he admits to his dad that boys aren't so bad afterall, and Father Donnelley took him to the recruiting station you know, as another one of his favors. The husband can cheat on the wife with the secretary, but she doesn't drive and isn't allowed at the office anyway, meanwhile she's mixing it up with the other bored wives of the neighborhood. Yeah, one could get nostalgic for the traditional family values of the 50's.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368291451835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 12:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368291721410-10</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If he's all that bad, and he just may be.. Imagine being the loser who lost the election to him LMAO!</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1368291721410</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:02:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368292023943-11</Id><Topic><Title>Loan reserves</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368274994147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:23:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SSHHHHHHH!!!!!! With any really really good luck we get ONE MORE DIP to buy. Just one. A short duck under $10 just for old times? Ahhh, I doubt it either. Decided not turn another bit of temporary position into permanent position. No such thing as too much in the way of long term gains. Particularly when I desperately need a bit of cash outside my brokerage account to start on the actual cabin in my remote hideaway. I spent all my immediately spendable cash money putting in the utilities and prepping the site for construction, and now I don't have a down payment lest I sacrifice my precious investments, and it ain't time right now when the market is experiencing an up kick, but yeah, I'm another one of those looking to build not only ONE house as a temp house/hunting cabin on my land, but another, MUCH MUCH larger when we're done with that one to live in permanently. I need IMC to pay $1.50/sh for Woulfe Mining or something like that, as this would certainly give me more than enough of a down payment for both projects. Remember, the best investment out there is to continue to expand your dwelling over your life until such time as you can fit all your stuff in it, and it represents about 12% to 20% (depending on YOUR risk tolerance) of your wealth (even if multiple dwellings are required, or some made oceangoing) when out of debt. It's sort of risky, but not as risky as being caught without enough real-estate in the right area to feed and house your dependents during a time of depression. Those 1920's bankers wouldn't have been falling like rain if all of them had thought to buy 500 acres of ranch land with some of that money they were #$%$ away. Of course with the luck of some of those chumps they'd have bought in the dustbowl.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368292023943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368292250120-12</Id><Topic><Title>Loan reserves</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368274994147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:23:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.S. Why isn't this board happier instead of wasting our time with yet more political rhetoric this far from an election cycle? I mean, all us longs put some reasonable gains on the board on Friday, and who cares what happens to shorts until they wantta start sharing their sources so we can emulate the remarkable timing they must have to make ANY money off a stock trading for a fraction of book value. Wanna bet short interest is down by another day at the 15th of May?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368292250120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:10:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368293381025-13</Id><Topic><Title>Loan reserves</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368274994147</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 08:23:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, I've been on a parallel path. I sold all of my real estate holdings in 2006 and 2007 (except my primary residence), and in 2010 started accumulating properties again via tax auctions, bank foreclosures, etc. One of the properties is a 4-acre parcel about 1 hour north of San Francisco, a beautiful hillside property in a mostly agricultural town known for cow's milk and eggs. Put in a deep well, and just finishing up the grading plan for a small granny unit (kinda like your cabin) AND a much larger primary residence. The plan is to build the smaller unit, and then wait to build the larger unit at some time in the more distant future. Also, picked up ~21 acres in the Sierra Foothills (gold country) in another very agricultural area. You are spot on, having some land that can actually sustain one's family (whether it be agricultural, streams with fish, cattle grazing, whatever) in the event of a major downturn is critical. Some people say hide in gold, but you can't fill empty bellies with gold nuggets.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1368293381025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368294679095-14</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beat's Islam and Burkas - women are NOT allowed to go out by them self's, can't drive, can't get education or a meaningful job, can't go to a library, can't.......................! Why don't you move there - starting with Pakistan or even Saudi Arabia, Obimbos friends! Even India, where women are treated like cattle would be a star for you bashers! "A sun of Africa got elected"! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1368294679095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:51:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368294834664-15</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well fortunately for your unfortunately incarnation as a bottle of poop, the bar at least got an attractive waitress to attempt to server you. Maybe they were hoping the client wouldn't notice the cloying taste of rat poop (only HALF of rat pellets are edible, and mostly only the rats known which ones) because of the legs, and indeed statistics bear that out. Add those unable to differentiate the scent along with the 98% reflexive poop vote and the 70% mostly reflexive "slight movement across a border" crowd and you have plenty enough to elect a poopy President for a Poopy Constituency, You, however, won't be able to enjoy the cesspoll, all because you were handed to someone who had something to DO with a bottle of poop . . . . Mug someone . . . . (a part of the rest of the constituency). One could take the moral from your predicament that even been a closed container of feces isn't too bad, as long as someone can find a use for you. I don't tend to mug people, and wouldn't need a bottle of poop to do it with, so for me . . . . Not worth so much. I say that with no small measure of relief. People who think its there business what other people spend their money on are some of the worst control freaks on the planet.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368294834664</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368295087948-16</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obimbo is toast - won't get nothing done/through and I think he won't finish his term - calls for getting him out of office are mounting - even from his own party!!! Even the left wing stations like CNN are turning on him! His only "Hanky" left is the Washington Post!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1368295087948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:58:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368295106391-17</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you defrauded your fellow poker players? Nice. Apparently you believe that crime is OK if the victims can afford it. Nice rationalization, schmuck.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1368295106391</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 13:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368295355779-18</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is this any different that the electorate continuing to vote in the criminal Maxine Waters? Blagojevich? Remember Marion Berry? Nice generalization. Sanford is a bad guy (which I agree with), so his entire party is bad? Your logic is flawed. That would be a stereotype.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1368295355779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:02:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368295929392-19</Id><Topic><Title>CO2 Emissions have Dropped Since Obama in Office</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368243553264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:39:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that why Cadillac (GM - he bailed out with tax payer money) is moving their operations/manufacturing to China??? Union free Audi &amp; BMW is producing here and selling to China, just like with our Gov. Walker opened up a sales office chain for Harley Davidson in China, but the product is MADE in MILWAUKEE!!! Thanks to the state turning REPUBLICAN for the first time, House, Senate, Gov. it moved under HIS watch from 41st in 2010 up to 14th in 2013 for Jobs/Manufacturing - now let OBIMBO match this progress - he is moving everything to China and overseas!!! Enough said! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1368295929392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:12:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296319272-20</Id><Topic><Title>Any Questions?....</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1368233531845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 20:52:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You described OBIMBORAMA at his best - more to come! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1368296319272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:18:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296484592-21</Id><Topic><Title>CO2 Emissions have Dropped Since Obama in Office</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368243553264</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:39:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary be no fool, she learned from the Obama administration and from the hindsight surrounding her husbands that its better to be the Kingmaker than the King. Or in her case perhaps the Queenmaker. Hillary has been playing the Game of Offices for some time now, and like Cersei Lannister nee Baratheon, isn't going to go meekly into that long castigation for Benghazi before shuffling it off on someone else, assuming the mistakes weren't SO egregious that they can't be "redeposited" the Clinton way.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368296484592</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296632673-22</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liberals are allowed to use Stereotypes when applied to Conservatives, it says so in their handbook. In fact it's encouraged. Guy name Mao wrote it, has a stupid name, the little red container of home roll cigarette leaves is what the guys called it in Korea. Works even better than the Gideon's because the fertilizer content is higher.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368296632673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296780553-23</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the product is plainly displayed and the price plainly market and both parties go away happy, that is called "capitalism". That you find this incomprehensible is not a surprise to me.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368296780553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:26:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368296874773-24</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>argh the price plainly marked . . . anyone want to sell part of their nervous system? I only need a few tends of grams of cells, just enough to get the intention tremors under control. If interested send a sample of brain tissue if a Democrat, you're not doing anything with it anyway.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368296874773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:27:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368297011499-25</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is it different ? Liberals don't espouse family values and holier than thou righteousness. They are realistic about life and know we are flawed. Pubs are just plain hypocrites.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1368297011499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368297425605-26</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it is mislabeled, then that constitutes fraud.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1368297425605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:37:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368298442977-27</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>depends what he relabeled it . . . $10 bud Mitt;s Chuck would be just fine . . . it's all in the fine print, and the dominant rule of thumb in retail has ALWAYS been Caveat Emptor. You want the government to protect you from your own bad judgement now with laws that essentially grow at the barrel of a gun. Nice to know you insist on getting your money's worth from liquor at threat of dire consequences. Please don't enter any bar I own. Then again it's not like someone who buy's their booze based on the label goes much further than the surface anyway. Besides, I don't own any bars, that was my father in law's gig for awhile, and seeing him tend bar was humbling. You just don't wanna enter a business where you know you can never hope to compete with he best.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368298442977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 14:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368315907429-28</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your kidding right? So you actually think he relabled a bottle of two buck chuck to something the consumer thought was basically an equivalent, and they STILL BOUGHT IT AT $!0 a glass? No, this is a classic example of KISS, he clearly relabled it as a MUCH more expensive bottle of wine. and that is fraud. Man you clearly are looking for a reason to debate, to take this flimsy side.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1368315907429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 19:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368320878517-29</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>defraud poker player/ ok so I shoot fish in a barrel...</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368320878517</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:07:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368320905691-30</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U must be from Wall street</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368320905691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368322559949-31</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>better solution: a bullet between the eyes of the defrauder</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1368322559949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 21:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368329699765-32</Id><Title>Reagan buddy genocidal killer</Title><Msg>Guatemala's Rios Montt found guilty of genocide</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1368329699765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:34:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368330583598-33</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives always claim the moral high ground. And then crawl in the gutter. Deny it.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1368330583598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368331082907-34</Id><Topic><Title>"Family Values" Pubs Re-Elect Proven Cheat and Liar</Title><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1368244221402</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:50:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easily, your use of the word "always" makes it easy, and if you understood logic you'd know what that's so.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368331082907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368331157478-35</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only visit, but I do know the rules, which is why I found someone engaged in the trading of securities complaining about mislabeled booze ironic.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368331157478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>