<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-30"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372597900834-1</Id><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Msg>And right wing troglodytes are bashing a couple small fires in electric cars. DETROIT -- A deal between the government and Chrysler over Jeeps linked to deadly fires isn't sitting well with many Jeep owners and auto safety advocates. In early June, after a nearly three-year investigation, the National Highway Traffic and Safety Administration recommended that Chrysler recall 2.7 million older Jeep SUVs because the fuel tanks could rupture, leak and cause fires in rear-end crashes.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372604127028-2</Id><Topic><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great post shorty</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1372604127028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 10:55:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372627047603-3</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Benghazi ?</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372433663970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try, but no cigar. How about President Billy (I didn't have sex with that woman) Clinton, ignoreding warnings for 8 years (other than bombing an occasional milk factory)...so it's OK with you that the four Americans were left for dead while the community organizer and Hilary were fast a sleep.. .pointing to other bad behavior doesn't excuse their disregard for their fellow Americans. Any way you dice it, these political hacks have blood on their hands</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372627047603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372627325538-4</Id><Topic><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why there moving some Jeep production to China...no unions thugs drinking and smoking dope on their lunch breaks to deal with. BTW, how many electric cars do you own?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372627325538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372628432856-5</Id><Topic><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jeep production is moving to China because it's the biggest car market on the planet. It's called Capitalism, maroon. Free market. But we know that Rush and Fox were bashing electric cars, so you have to parrot them. American ingenuity and creativity are something Republicans hate. They are still trying to destroy America to make Obama look ineffective. Ain't workin, dumbo. The Volt is still winner of highest customer satisfaction of all cars.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372628432856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 17:40:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372633249037-6</Id><Topic><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, Do you know the difference between "there" and "they're?"</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1372633249037</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:00:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372635097075-7</Id><Title>Keep On Selling ETFC Short! I'm Buying The Shares You Are Selling:</Title><Msg>I've already posted my "super high" targets on here for ETFC ($250.00+ After A Couple Of 2-1 Splits). Please sell your entire portfolios if you own ETFC. &amp; then sell as much as you can short. Thank-You ahead of time people. This will have been be the best stock to buy, looking backwards, in 3-5 years from now.</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1372635097075</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 19:31:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372637646139-8</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Benghazi ?</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372433663970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, From "Fast and Furious" to "IRS targeting conservative organixations only" every so called scandal has fizzled out and Rep. Darrell Issa has become the laughing stock of the GOP. Our President, AG Eric Holder, and Secretary Hillary Clinton were not impeached, because there is nothing to impeach them for, but Issa's mis- guided and fabricated accusations. Even some Pub Senators remarked that Issa was lying in many instances. In fact, he had to apologize several times. poor bidder - eat your heart out.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1372637646139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372638973698-9</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Benghazi ?</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372433663970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Without indictments and convictions it not a scandal, it's libel. These are what scandals look like: Executive branch Courtney Stadd, Chief of Staff to NASA, was sentenced to 41 months in prison for conspiracy. (2012)[5] Scott Bloch was appointed by George W. Bush to head the United States Office of Special Counsel and was sentenced to one month in prison for Contempt of Congress and sentenced to one year of un-supervised probation. Bloch had hired Geeks on Call to scrub his computer of files before they could be examined by Congress. (2010)[6] Lewis Libby (R) Chief of Staff to Vice President #$%$ Cheney (R). 'Scooter' was convicted of perjury and obstruction of justice in the Plame Affair on March 6, 2007 and was sentenced to 30 months in prison and fined $250,000. His sentence was commuted by George W. Bush (R) on July 1, 2007. The felony remains on Libby's record though the jail time and fine were commuted.[7] Lester Crawford (R) Commissioner of the Food and Drug Administration, resigned after 2 months. Pleaded guilty to conflict of interest and received 3 years suspended sentence and fined $90,000. (2006) [8] Claude Allen (R) Advisor to President Bush on Domestic Policy, Allen was arrested for a series of felony thefts in retail stores such as Target. (2006) He was convicted on one count and resigned soon after.[9] Darleen Druyun (D) Principal Deputy Undersecretary of the Air Force for Acquisition, Druyun pleaded guilty to inflating the price of the contract to favor her future employer and to passing information on the competing Airbus A330 MRTT bid (from EADS). In October 2004, she was sentenced to nine months in jail for corruption, fined $5,000, given three years of supervised release and 150 hours of community service. She began her prison term on January 5, 2005.[10] Jack Abramoff CNMI scandal involves the efforts of Abramoff to influence Congress concerning U.S. immigration and minimum wage laws.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372638973698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372639111944-10</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Benghazi ?</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372433663970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Convictions within the Bush administration include: David Safavian GSA (General Services Administration) Chief of Staff,[11] found guilty of blocking justice and lying, [12] and sentenced to 18 months[13] Roger Stillwell Staff in the Department of the Interior under George W. Bush. Pleaded guilty and received two years suspended sentence. [12] Susan B. Ralston Special Assistant to the President and Senior Advisor to Karl Rove, resigned October 6, 2006 after it became known that she accepted gifts and passed information to her former boss Jack Abramoff.[14] J. Steven Griles Deputy Secretary of the Interior pleaded guilty to obstruction of justice and was sentenced to 10 months.[15] Italia Federici staff to the Secretary of Interior, and President of the Council of Republicans for Environmental Advocacy, pleaded guilty to tax evasion and obstruction of justice. She was sentenced to four years probation.[16][17][18] Jared Carpenter Vice-President of the Council of Republicans for Environmental Advocacy, was discovered during the Abramoff investigation and pleaded guilty to income tax evasion. He got 45 days, plus 4 years probation.[19] Mark Zachares staff in the Department of Labor, bribed by Abramoff, guilty of conspiracy to defraud. [20] Robert E. Coughlin Deputy Chief of Staff, Criminal Division of the Justice Department pleaded guilty to conflict of interest after accepting bribes from Jack Abramoff. (2008) [17]</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372639111944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 20:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372641229682-11</Id><Topic><Title>Over a Million Jeeps could Catch Fire</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372597900834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 09:11:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What can I buy for "highest customer satisfaction"? Is it because of "Rush and Fox" I can barely see any Volts on the road? Or people are just smart enough to understand that they get too little value for too much $$$? And Volt isn't as much of a miracle to celebrate American ingenuity. Too much politics put into Volt hysteria. I have 270hp SUV and same power sedan for all my needs. There is no electric car which comes even close in performance. Average American, even with Obama bumper stickers(hypocrites), still prefer gas. It may take another Steve Jobs to create affordable and practical non fossil fuel car. But it ain't there yet. In 2012 it was almost anti-American to move production to China. Are we OK with that now? Or anything goes just to get elected?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1372641229682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:13:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372643579152-12</Id><Topic><Title>Where's Benghazi ?</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372433663970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-28 11:34:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To date, after almost FIVE YEARS, ZERO members of Obama's executive branch have been indicted or convicted of any crime. Compare with the Bush crime family statistics.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372643579152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 21:52:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372644317255-13</Id><Title>Jeb Bush to award Liberty Medal to Hillary Clinton</Title><Msg>Jeb Bush to award Liberty Medal to Hillary Clinton By Philadelphia Inquirer (PA) June 28, 2013 12:25 pm Hillary Rodham Clinton, who many believe can win the 2016 Democratic nomination for president, if she wants it, is the winner of the 2013 Liberty Medal. The award is to be presented Sept. 10 to Clinton by former Florida Gov. Jeb Bush, chairman of the National Constitution Center and a possible contender for the 2016 Republican nomination. Politics aside, Bush praised Clinton in a statement released Thursday announcing her selection. "Former Secretary Clinton has dedicated her life to serving and engaging people across the world in democracy," Bush said. "These efforts as a citizen, an activist, and a leader have earned Secretary Clinton this year's Liberty Medal." Clinton ended her four-year term as the 67th secretary of state Feb. 1, capping a career that included eight years in the Senate. She is the only former first lady to serve in that legislative body. She ran for president in 2008 and was widely viewed as the front-runner until Barack Obama surged into the lead. Clinton received 18 million votes during her campaign. Though Clinton has not declared any intention to run in 2016, a super PAC called Ready for Hillary is collecting checks of up to $25,000 for a possible campaign. Last week, Clinton cautiously addressed the subject. "Let me say this, hypothetically speaking, I really do hope that we have a woman president in my lifetime," she said June 20 in Toronto. Clinton did not issue a statement on being named the Liberty Medal recipient and had not mentioned it on her Twitter account as of late Thursday night. The Liberty Medal "recognizes individuals who have furthered the ideals of freedom, democracy, and equality, often against great odds," said Jeffrey Rosen, president and chief executive of the National Constitution Center. More specifically, Clinton is bein</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1372644317255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372647309018-14</Id><Title>Obama cried at Michael Jackson's funeral</Title><Msg>Villagairosa, too. WHat? Was Michael a muslim terrorist or something? No. Just respect among old boy-molesters.</Msg><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1372647309018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372647383165-15</Id><Topic><Title>Jeb Bush to award Liberty Medal to Hillary Clinton</Title><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1372644317255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:05:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There isn't a more powerful team than Bill and Hillary. If they decide to go for it, you better start investing in women's pants suits.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372647383165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372647412722-16</Id><Title>Spank her for Jesus</Title><Msg>Because there isn’t enough batpoo crazy things going on out there in the wide, wacky world of religion, a new source of crazy has come to light. It even has a name: Christian Domestic Discipline (CDD). There are, at this point, two main websites related to this “discipline”: A Domestic Discipline (DD) marriage is one in which one partner is given authority over the other, and has the means to back up that authority, usually by spanking. The application and practise of DD in each marriage is as unique as the individuals who make up that marriage. There is no “One Ring of Power” in the Domestic Discipline world, to which all DD couples must bow; no singular path to “true DD enlightenment.” What works well for one DD couple may not be a good fit for another marriage. Therefore, you may see many different suggestions espoused on this site and elsewhere. A Christian Domestic Discipline (CDD) marriage is simply a traditional, male-led, Christian marriage which utilises aspects of Domestic Discipline. It is set up according to Biblical standards.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372647412722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:56:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372647799236-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama cried at Michael Jackson's funeral</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1372647309018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should abort Obama and his sick administration.</Msg><Username>diane_lopresti0818</Username><Timestamp>1372647799236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 23:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372648207906-18</Id><Title>GOP leaders drooling again!</Title><Msg>Jim DeMint: Women want to be forced to have ultrasounds Source: Raw Story Some women like being forced to have an ultrasound before receiving an abortion, according to former Senator Jim DeMint (R-SC). Republicans in state legislatures across the country have pushed legislation that requires women to undergo an ultrasound procedure 24 hours before terminating their pregnancy. The so-called “informed consent” laws usually require women to be given a picture of the fetus and be shown a fetal heartbeat, along with general information about abortion. “The more the ultrasounds have become part of the law, where a woman gets the opportunity to see that there’s a real child, it’s beginning to change minds, and I think that’s a good thing,” DeMint said on NBC’s Meet the Press. “It’s time that the 3,000 babies we lose every day have some people speaking up for them.” MSNBC host Rachel Maddow pointed out that women weren’t given the opportunity to have an ultrasound, they were forced to have a medically unnecessary ultrasound by the state. She added that in many cases women were subjected to trans-vaginal ultrasounds.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372648207906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 23:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372648246662-19</Id><Topic><Title>Obama cried at Michael Jackson's funeral</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1372647309018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:55:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ill bet you cry at trailer park openings.</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1372648246662</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 23:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>