<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-21"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363872463317-1</Id><Title>Bush &amp; gop gave Iraq universal health care (Bush also provided a billion dollars to get it started)</Title><Msg>that must be the only good thing for Iraq that came from W's insane invasion which relaced one thug for another and, there is no doubt that the bush installed leader Nouri al-Maliki is a thug. He is the leader of the The Islamic Dawa Party that backed the Iranian Revolution and also Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini during the Iran-Iraq War and the group still receives financial support from Tehran. Article 31 of the Iraqi Constitution, drafted by the Bush administration in 2005 and ratified by the Iraqi people, includes state-guaranteed (single payer) healthcare for life for every Iraqi citizen. ( it was also kicked off with a billion $$ of USA tax dollars, btw)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363872463317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:27:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363873846298-2</Id><Title>Universal Healthcare is for Gerbil Stuffers</Title><Msg>Even loser Liberal/Progressive/Facists Gerbil Stuffers are starting to realize that Obamascare/Universal Hillarycare is a real pain in the yeahss, like Gerbil stuffing!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363873846298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:50:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363874552028-3</Id><Title>gop prove their honesty, knowledge and fitness to lead the nation</Title><Msg>/ "We know where they are. They're in the area around Tikrit and Baghdad and east, west, south and north somewhat....." "unless money is loosened up the sucker could go down......" "Reagan proved deficits don't matter......."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363874552028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:02:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363877013067-4</Id><Title>Gay Penguins Become Dads</Title><Msg>Defining "natural': Last edited Tue Mar 19, 2013, 09:57 AM USA/ET - Edit history (1) After nearly a year together at the Odense Zoo in Denmark, the same-sex couple attempted to become parents of their own. Keepers witnessed the pair trying to steal other couples' eggs. And during brooding season, the penguins even tried to incubate a dead herring. "(The two) seriously wanted to stay with an egg," zoologist Nina Christensen told The Star. The Odense Zoo reports that the penguins were recipients of an unexpected blessing when a female penguin laid not one but two eggs. She ultimately ditched the second egg, which afforded the male couple to become adoptive parents. However, before they were given the egg, the males had to practice on artificial eggs. Once proven capable, they received and successfully incubated the egg. The chick was born a month ago but the sex won't be determined for another eight months. Aawwww!</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363877013067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363877044235-5</Id><Title>Dumbo Cyprus Economics</Title><Msg>Cyprus is our future if we don't block all of Dumbo's Gerbil Stuffing ideas. Hillary is no better, perhaps worse. Nationalizing our I.R.A.'s has been pushed by BOTH Hillary and Dumbo. Hillary has pushed a 15% tax of ALL bank accounts. These sub-human gerbil Stuffers are SICK!!! Saul Alinsky low-lifes!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363877044235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363878787797-6</Id><Topic><Title>Bush &amp; gop gave Iraq universal health care (Bush also provided a billion dollars to get it started)</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363872463317</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you, knucklehead, admit that there was something positive coming out of Bush's war? Maybe it was a whole purpose of Iraq invasion? See, in the eyes of a liberal UHC is a model for every nation in the world. Giving all Iraqis healthcare for life is not a good humanitarian action? Are you saying Bush is justified? Or you just don't know what a hell you are saying, just mention word "Bush".</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363878787797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363879899123-7</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of what happenes when liberals are in charge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363721021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's pretty easy to understand why. If you have 10,000 people on one side, and 5 on another - it's far easier to find something for those 5 to do, than it is for those 10,000 to do. Now, California vs North Dakota are the same idea but on a much larger scale. There are just a LOT MORE people in California. California 2012 census showed a population of 38,041,430. North Dakota's population was 699,628. With a 9.8% unemployment in California and a 3.3% in North Dakota - California STILL employs 34,313,369 to North Dakota's employment of 676,540. So, there's what happens when liberals are charge. 34,313,369 find and have jobs. What happens when conservatives are in charge (since you want to frame this as liberal California and conservative North Dakota)? Only 676,540 find and have jobs. I can clearly see which one is employing more people, can you?</Msg><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363879899123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 11:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882303847-8</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR ETFC BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>shawncasteel300</Username><Timestamp>1363595873555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 04:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>thank you</Msg><Username>jesusmoreno755</Username><Timestamp>1363882303847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363882574101-9</Id><Title>Obunble embarrasses himself (and the USA) in Israel</Title><Msg>What else is new? The lightweight should stick to gues appearances on chick shows!!!!</Msg><Username>ufcw_shill</Username><Timestamp>1363882574101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363882694064-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obunble embarrasses himself (and the USA) in Israel</Title><Username>ufcw_shill</Username><Timestamp>1363882574101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Dumbo the Gerbil Stuffer also likes going on 'Chicks with Deeicks' shows like Jimmy Fallon!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363882694064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886542017-11</Id><Topic><Title>The US Invasion of Iraq Was a Crime and Its Perpetrators Are Murderers</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363831606028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why don't you move to Iran or N-Korea!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363886542017</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:22:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886652699-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obunble embarrasses himself (and the USA) in Israel</Title><Username>ufcw_shill</Username><Timestamp>1363882574101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think he should apply for Pierce Morgan's job when he is done, because he won't cut it for a Hollywood entertainer either! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363886652699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:24:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363886818697-13</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR ETFC BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>shawncasteel300</Username><Timestamp>1363595873555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 04:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice work, thanks</Msg><Username>fletcherwhitney</Username><Timestamp>1363886818697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363887547362-14</Id><Topic><Title>Gay Penguins Become Dads</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363877013067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You following #$%$ now JB?... And then Posting about it for attention? Sad....</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363887547362</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:39:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363887621546-15</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES ETFC</Title><Username>browndrake513</Username><Timestamp>1363270784976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great</Msg><Username>wworren</Username><Timestamp>1363887621546</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 13:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363888885308-16</Id><Topic><Title>Gay Penguins Become Dads</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363877013067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You into #$%$ now JB?... And posting about it for Attention?.... Sad!...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363888885308</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:01:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363888977443-17</Id><Topic><Title>The US Invasion of Iraq Was a Crime and Its Perpetrators Are Murderers</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363831606028</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 22:06:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, Rowdy. They are here to stay and constantly remind us that America is evil. Would this apply to Obama time too? You wish. Killing terrorists by drones on foreign soil is perfectly acceptable. They wouldn't bother question legality of this actions. The fact is, drone attacks create big collateral damage too. These regime surrogates will never go there, since that will put their icon on trial. But every dirty trick and misinformation goes to discredit Bush administration. Ooops! How many of those in Obama administration supported Iraq invasion back in 2002? They where for it before they were against it. So, can't go there either!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363888977443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:02:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890039212-18</Id><Topic><Title>gop prove their honesty, knowledge and fitness to lead the nation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363874552028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:02:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Michelle Bachmann's gay cure clinics are a typical gop thing...... charge people a fee to pray for a cure for being gay...... maybe it worked on her husband but he seems very gay. I wonder how they bill an insurance company for a cure by prayer.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363890039212</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363890057193-19</Id><Title>A message from an Iraqi</Title><Msg>Iraq war was a decade of failure and hardship Published: Tuesday, Mar. 19, 2013 - 10:03 am Re "10 years later, Iraq lessons echo as toll rises from many conflicts" (Page A1, March 18): Being a native of Iraq, I am in contact with Iraqis who lived through Saddam's dictatorship, about a decade of strict sanctions, and then the American invasion of March 2003. For these Iraqis the invasion (war as our media prefers to call it) was a total disaster to their country and all aspects of their life. It did not bring democracy. Iraq was taking steady steps towards a proud and promising future with equality for women, a high literacy rate, advanced medical care, a strong economy and total respect of the different ethnicities and religions. Presently, Iraqis have to put up with a high rate of unemployment, lack of safety and security, and the fear of being the next victim of religious violence. Corruption is abundant on all levels of the society. Who benefited but the oil corporations of the world -- Samira Z. Al-Qazzaz, Carmichael</Msg><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1363890057193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363890322074-20</Id><Topic><Title>A message from an Iraqi</Title><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1363890057193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:20:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can you guys stop this political #$%$.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1363890322074</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:25:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363891526372-21</Id><Topic><Title>Gay Penguins Become Dads</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363877013067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With gay marriage under attack as being "unnatural" what better "natural" example of fidelity and nurturing can be found than this discovery in the animal kingdom. Evangelicals are already demanding the baby be snatched from the pair and sent to an orphanage. LMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363891526372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 14:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363892421292-22</Id><Topic><Title>Gay Penguins Become Dads</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363877013067</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:43:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are trying to tie animals sexuality in with humans: and you want to make fun of others?.... Good luck with that!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363892421292</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363892708596-23</Id><Topic><Title>13 INDICATOR ETFC BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT</Title><Username>shawncasteel300</Username><Timestamp>1363595873555</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 04:37:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>awesome report!</Msg><Username>stevenbrewer358</Username><Timestamp>1363892708596</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894438502-24</Id><Topic><Title>gop prove their honesty, knowledge and fitness to lead the nation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363874552028</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:02:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easy! They stamp it "Planed Parenthood" and if that doesn't work then it's going to be billed thru "Acorn"! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363894438502</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363894493932-25</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of what happenes when liberals are in charge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363721021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does N. Dakota have to do with California, you are making no sence. This is a foolish way to make a comparision. It is about the number of unemployed vs. employed we are talking about here by %, California has the highest unemployment in the US...period. So stop with the silly comparision. N. Dakoda last time I looked did not have millions of illegals, and public pension obligations bankrupting that state....so wise up!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363894493932</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:34:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363895151699-26</Id><Title>Big Sis, why all the bullets?</Title><Msg>**The DHS has purchased over 1.6 billion rounds of ammunition over the past year – enough to wage a 20 year plus war** You dopes on the left ought to be concerned as well, what does DHS need with all these bullets. Your boy will not always be in office, what will you have to say if this continues under a Rebulican administration? BTW, I wonder if those two studies about lesbians being fat and drunk applies to big SIS. Big Sis Refuses To Answer Congress On Bullet Purchases Speaking at CPAC with Infowars and We Are Change reporter, Luke Rudkowski, Congressman Timothy Huelscamp revealed this week that the Department of Homeland Security has refused to answer questions from “multiple” members of Congress regarding its recent purchase of huge amounts of weapons and ammunition. “They have no answer for that question. They refuse to answer to answer that,” Huelscamp said. “I’ve got a list of various questions of agencies about multiple things. Far from being the most transparent administration in the world, they are the most closed and opaque,” the Congressman added. “They refuse to let us know what is going on, so I don’t really have an answer for that. Multiple members of Congress are asking those questions,” he added. The DHS has purchased over 1.6 billion rounds of ammunition over the past year – enough to wage a 20 year plus war. Earlier this month, Forbes Magazine called for a “national conversation” on the matter.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363895151699</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 15:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363896097841-27</Id><Title>Netanyahu, Special Forces Commander, National Hero for the Entebbe Rescue</Title><Msg>BIBi has a look on his face that says I made a #$%$ bigger than you.</Msg><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1363896097841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:01:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363899981439-28</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of what happenes when liberals are in charge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363721021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for teaching us your 2nd grade understanding of statistics. Very un-educational. In case it's new for you. It is just as easy to find 1 black ball in 10 as 1 million in 10 millions. Now, it may be another news for you, but CA is not only much larger state than ND, but has tremendous amount of natural resources and best climatic conditions in the US. This by itself attracts private enterprise and creates jobs. What does that have to do with you, liberals? CA population shrunk in last 4 years. Do liberals have something to do with that? It's a shame that a state with all these potentials has highest unemployment rates in the country. And you, idiots, defend that as normal. Mind boggling!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363899981439</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900408256-29</Id><Topic><Title>Netanyahu, Special Forces Commander, National Hero for the Entebbe Rescue</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1363896097841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeap. Obama looks soooo small when Netaniahu speaks! Makes you wish he is not US President.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363900408256</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363900899600-30</Id><Topic><Title>Netanyahu, Special Forces Commander, National Hero for the Entebbe Rescue</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1363896097841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 16:01:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The choise is clear...One dead serious, one dead wrong.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363900899600</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363902885908-31</Id><Title>Iraq not liberated, it was devastated</Title><Msg>The Sociocide of Iraq by Bush/Cheney All for what results? Before the invasion there was no al-Qaeda in Saddam Hussein’s secular dictatorship. Now a growing al-Qaeda in Iraq is terrorizing the country with ever bolder car bombings and suicide attacks taking dozens of lives at a time and spilling forcefully over into Syria. Iraq is a police state with sectarian struggles between the dominant Shiites and the insurgent Sunnis who lived together peacefully and intermarried for centuries. There were no sectarian slaughters of this kind before the invasion, except for Saddam Hussein’s bloodbath against rebellious Shiites. The Shiites were egged on by President George H.W. Bush, who promptly abandoned them to the deadly strafing of Saddam’s helicopter gunships at the end of the preventable first Gulf War in 1991. Iraq is a country in ruins with a political and wealthy upper class raking off the profits from the oil industry and the occupation. The U.S. is now widely hated in that part of Asia. Bush/Cheney ordered the use of cluster bombs, white phosphorous and depleted uranium against, for example, the people of Fallujah where infant birth deformities have skyrocketed. As Raed Jarrar, an Iraqi-American analyst observed: “Complete destruction of the Iraqi national identity” and the sectarian system introduced by the U.S. invaders in 2003, where Iraqis were favored or excluded based on their sectarian and ethnic affiliations, laid the basis for the current cruel chaos and violence. It was a nasty, brutish form of divide and rule.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1363902885908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363906252068-32</Id><Topic><Title>Iraq not liberated, it was devastated</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1363902885908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut up you stupid Gerbil Stuffing, 'Useful Idiot' dicKtator apologist!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363906252068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 18:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363908552154-33</Id><Topic><Title>Feds Spend $2.7M to Study Drunk Lesbians</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363811176110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No. Cause. Two #$%$. Are. Like. Two negatives. No electrical. Current. Flows</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1363908552154</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363909700430-34</Id><Topic><Title>Iraq not liberated, it was devastated</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1363902885908</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 17:54:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because of idiot homobellis like you the GOP is all screwed up. Crawl back under your rock, child- like Puke.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1363909700430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 19:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363911241945-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obunble embarrasses himself (and the USA) in Israel</Title><Username>ufcw_shill</Username><Timestamp>1363882574101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 12:16:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Du hast wieder einen Mist und einen Scheissdreck geschrieben. Wenn Du halb so dumm waerest, dann ginge es viel besser.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1363911241945</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363911573307-36</Id><Title>Ten Years Later, U.S. Has Left Iraq with Mass Displacement &amp; Epidemic of Birth Defects, Cancers</Title><Msg>In part two of our interview, Al Jazeera reporter Dahr Jamail discusses how the U.S. invasion of Iraq has left behind a legacy of cancer and birth defects suspected of being caused by the U.S. military's extensive use of depleted uranium and white phosphorus. Noting the birth defects in the Iraqi city of Fallujah, Jamail says: "They're are extremely hard to bear witness to, but it's something that we all need to pay attention to ... What this has generated is from 2004 up to this day, we are seeing a rate of congenital malformations in the city of Fallujah that has surpassed even that in the wake of the Japanese cities of Hiroshima and Nagasaki that nuclear bombs were dropped on at the end of World War II." Jamail has also reported on the refugee crisis of more than one million displaced Iraqis still inside the country, who are struggling to survive without government aid, a majority of them living in Baghdad.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363911573307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363911671005-37</Id><Title>JB....Uses 47 I.D.'s...Can't Move On...</Title><Msg>WOW!.... You are Really Stuck here... Do you realize how much you have Aged since you have been posting here?....</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363911671005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363912656849-38</Id><Topic><Title>Bush's War was ALL Borrowed $$$$$$$</Title><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1363724370216</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 16:19:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(CNN) -- The United Nations will launch an investigation into Syrian claims that rebels used chemical weapons against its troops, even as U.S. officials told CNN Thursday that initial intelligence reports suggest no such weapons were used. The announcement follows days of claims by the Syrian government and rebels that each side used chemical weapons against the other, raising concern the ongoing civil war had entered a new, more deadly phase. U.S. President Barack Obama and other American officials have said in recent days there was no evidence to substantiate the reports that rebels had used chemical weapons against Syrian troops. But now analysts are "leaning hard away" from the notion that Syria used chemical weapons against its own people, a U.S. military official directly familiar with the preliminary analysis told CNN. Were chemical weapons used in Syria? Obama: Chemical weapons a serious mistake Syria chemical weapons a 'game-changer' Chemical weapons attack alleged in Syria There are "multiple indicators" for this emerging conclusion, an administration official said. That official told CNN "there are strong indications now that chemical weapons were not used by the regime in recent days." The official would not detail the indicators but said it points to the preliminary U.S. conclusion that "weaponized chemical agents" were not used. The officials, who spoke on condition of anonymity, were not authorized to publicly release details of the intelligence analysis.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363912656849</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 20:37:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363914015458-39</Id><Title>Bambam's luck</Title><Msg>After five years, the one day he picks to go lie to the j0000z fireworks go off.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1363914015458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363916303667-40</Id><Topic><Title>Bambam's luck</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1363914015458</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, missiles fly, as Obimbo tells another lie!!! (And the Israelis see right thru him as he misrepresents the USA - should have sent Kerry) He still thinks that those camel drivers want peace, maybe a piece, who knows, all I know is that Israel wont put up with his kabuki dances. A bill Clinton, he is NOT - he is the clueless Chicago community organizer in chief and that's one community he won't be able to organize! God bless Israel versus Akbar Allah!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363916303667</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 21:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363921026485-41</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of what happenes when liberals are in charge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363721021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow...so you're saying even you don't read the articles you post here? What does North Dakota have to do with California? YOU are the one that posted the article comparing the two and now you're acting like that's out of left field, totally unexpected conversation topic. Just wow.</Msg><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363921026485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363921041425-42</Id><Title>A Message to Bush and Cheney From a Dying Veteran</Title><Msg>I write this letter, my last letter, to you, Mr. Bush and Mr. Cheney. I write not because I think you grasp the terrible human and moral consequences of your lies, manipulation and thirst for wealth and power. I write this letter because, before my own death, I want to make it clear that I, and hundreds of thousands of my fellow veterans, along with millions of my fellow citizens, along with hundreds of millions more in Iraq and the Middle East, know fully who you are and what you have done. You may evade justice but in our eyes you are each guilty of egregious war crimes, of plunder and, finally, of murder, including the murder of thousands of young Americans—my fellow veterans—whose future you stole. Your positions of authority, your millions of dollars of personal wealth, your public relations consultants, your privilege and your power cannot mask the hollowness of your character. You sent us to fight and die in Iraq after you, Mr. Cheney, dodged the draft in Vietnam, and you, Mr. Bush, went AWOL from your National Guard unit. Your cowardice and selfishness were established decades ago. You were not willing to risk yourselves for our nation but you sent hundreds of thousands of young men and women to be sacrificed in a senseless war with no more thought than it takes to put out the garbage. I joined the Army two days after the 9/11 attacks. I joined the Army because our country had been attacked. I wanted to strike back at those who had killed some 3,000 of my fellow citizens. I did not join the Army to go to Iraq, a country that had no part in the September 2001 attacks and did not pose a threat to its neighbors, much less to the United States. I did not join the Army to “liberate” Iraqis or to shut down mythical weapons-of-mass-destruction facilities or to implant what you cynically called “democracy” in Baghdad and the Middle East. I did not join the Army to rebuild Iraq, which at the time you told us could be paid for by Iraq’s oil revenues.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363921041425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363921136368-43</Id><Topic><Title>A Message to Bush and Cheney From a Dying Veteran</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363921041425</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I write this letter on the 10th anniversary of the Iraq War on behalf of my fellow Iraq War veterans. I write this letter on behalf of the 4,488 soldiers and Marines who died in Iraq. I write this letter on behalf of the hundreds of thousands of veterans who have been wounded and on behalf of those whose wounds, physical and psychological, have destroyed their lives. I am one of those gravely wounded. I was paralyzed in an insurgent ambush in 2004 in Sadr City. My life is coming to an end. I am living under hospice care. I write this letter on behalf of husbands and wives who have lost spouses, on behalf of children who have lost a parent, on behalf of the fathers and mothers who have lost sons and daughters and on behalf of those who care for the many thousands of my fellow veterans who have brain injuries. I write this letter on behalf of those veterans whose trauma and self-revulsion for what they have witnessed, endured and done in Iraq have led to suicide and on behalf of the active-duty soldiers and Marines who commit, on average, a suicide a day. I write this letter on behalf of the some 1 million Iraqi dead and on behalf of the countless Iraqi wounded. I write this letter on behalf of us all—the human detritus your war has left behind, those who will spend their lives in unending pain and grief. You may evade justice but in our eyes you are each guilty of egregious war crimes, of plunder and, finally, of murder, including the murder of thousands of young Americans—my fellow veterans—whose future you stole.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363921136368</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 22:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363921212736-44</Id><Topic><Title>Proof of what happenes when liberals are in charge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363721021498</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-19 15:23:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So pacifican54, let me see if I've got this straight. California has a big population and it's completely not because of any liberal policies, it's because of all kinds of OTHER unrelated reasons. California has a population decrease, and it's not anything else - it's definitely those 'liberal' ideas they have there. Yeah - that doesn't sound bias and completely incorrect at all.</Msg><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363921212736</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 23:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>