<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015890030-1</Id><Topic><Title>You will never guess who awarded father of the year...</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357766157575</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-09 16:15:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hi Caligula . . . Blondie told me I'd find you over here. I don't visit the ¥ boards much since the format changes but it's good to login every now and again. Nice post, I agree with your sentiments. I see you haven't changed, you can cover the philosophy of the second amendment, where it's under attack, and how that places us all under attack in a few paragraphs. Well done.</Msg><Username>pecuniary_emulator</Username><Timestamp>1358015890030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:38:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358032628419-2</Id><Title>Ann Gets It</Title><Msg>There is an academic, peer-reviewed, long-term study of the effect of various public policies on public, multiple shootings in all 50 states over a 20-year period performed by renowned economists at the University of Chicago and Yale, William Landes and John Lott. It concluded that the only policy to reduce the incidence of, and casualties from, mass shootings are concealed-carry laws. The Times will never mention this study.</Msg><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1358032628419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:17:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358047515846-3</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Gets It</Title><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1358032628419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:17:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just put a Burris Fastfire II reflex sight on my concealed carry weapon to increase my accuracy at intermediate to long ranges. Coupled with the FN FiveseveN it gives me an effective (50%) 300 meter range and a 100 meter primary (90%+) range on a standard silhouette (once I sight it in). Until then I'm on backup iron sights, which are good to, oh, maybe 20 yards, tops.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1358047515846</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:25:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358048603532-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ann Gets It</Title><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1358032628419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:17:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that model factory chrome tips on dual exhaust?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1358048603532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 22:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>