<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366202980769-1</Id><Title>Rush Limbaugh and lynch mob followers are a disgrace</Title><Msg>asked whether he was already blaming Muslims, Rush replied, “Yes, they’re evil. Let’s kill them all.” everyone should be ashamed of Rush's rush to judgement and fascist bigotry, it is a disgrace.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366202980769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 08:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366205729853-2</Id><Title>'DUCK' LIES about Rush</Title><Msg>It was 'Eric RUSH' who said the quote!! Get a friggin' Life!!! And stop Lying!! Propaganda freak!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366205729853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366206719419-3</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh and lynch mob followers are a disgrace</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366202980769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 08:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Erik Rush from Fox News tweets Muslims are evil, ‘kill them " sorry if anyone got upset by mentioning one bigot rush and another bigot rush in the same post. Rush Limbaugh and his lynch mob followers are a disgrace and so is fox news and so is eric rush. It is weird that the fat, drug addled slob Limbaugh has so many avid followers. Rush, the drug addict, cowardly draft dodger, bigot and loud mouth is a disgrace.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366206719419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 09:51:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366207368950-4</Id><Title>Rush Limbaugh blames left for "politicizing" Boston</Title><Msg>and in the same screed he more or less blames Obama for the bombing....(if not a muslim, then rush says he gets it that a home grown terrorist would want to do it , due to Obama., of course,......."I don't think you can rule out that we're in an economic disaster in this country. There are people who are at their wits' end over what to do economically. They can't find work, can't find a job, no apparent hope of it. This leads to all kinds of anger and chaos. So I wouldn't rule out the fact that the sociology of a depressed and in-ruins economy is leading to all kinds of frustration in all kinds of people all over this country. Now, nobody knows what happened." rush Limbaugh....... not ruling out that Obama could have made a Limbot do the deed.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366207368950</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 10:02:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366211690080-5</Id><Title>congrats ken G.</Title><Msg>how do you nail the high on 27 million share sale???????</Msg><Username>itsdifferentthistime</Username><Timestamp>1366211690080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366213115767-6</Id><Topic><Title>Religion of 'PIECES"</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366141785295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 15:49:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, you're right. There are Obama drones. By all indications you are one. Drones US military is using to kill Taliban thugs and terrorists are made of different material. The commonality real Obama drones is absence of critical thinking and total obedience to the master. Drones used on Pakistan border are not Obama's. They were used successfully by previous administration too. The legitimate complain is that here we can't "torture" mass murderers by pouring water, we offer them civilian trials under full protection of US law, but near Pakistan border it's perfectly "humane" to blow them into thousands of pieces. What's more? Justice Department memo suggests that this administration claims to be a sole decision maker for drone attacks even on US soil. Well, I do remember how much grief you on the left gave Bush administration with FISA warrantless wiretapping. Intercepting calls made by US individuals to rogue countries without judicial approval? That's egregious! But we can kill them today without due process? This kind of hypocrisy only emboldens the enemy. For others? Not taking Obama too seriously.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366213115767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366213279992-7</Id><Topic><Title>congrats ken G.</Title><Username>itsdifferentthistime</Username><Timestamp>1366211690080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's magic.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1366213279992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366214292234-8</Id><Topic><Title>congrats ken G.</Title><Username>itsdifferentthistime</Username><Timestamp>1366211690080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>saved 20% by dumping and another 20 on his short.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1366214292234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:58:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366214819949-9</Id><Title>Letter!</Title><Msg>The letter to OBIMBO tested positive for RICIN! Dumb move because OBIMBO doesn't EAT or READ any letters! So, we have one letter going to ademocRAT president and a republican senator???? Another photo - OP coming up for our "Fearless Leader"! Can't do the "Antigun show" any more, it's came apart! Can't do Obimbocare any more, it's coming unglued! Immigration isn't going thru, as he wanted it! His cuts and taxation hurts the wrong peoplenothing works for him! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366214819949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366220702929-10</Id><Title>Arrest imminent?</Title><Msg>CNN reporting that the suspect in the bombing has been identified and it would not surprise me if he is alredy under arrest! Why would you broadcast a warning, so the suspect can run? Good work! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366220702929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 13:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366221624442-11</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh and lynch mob followers are a disgrace</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366202980769</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 08:49:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Transcript please.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366221624442</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366222035429-12</Id><Title>Another top Democrat, Obamacare a "train Wreck"</Title><Msg>The wheels are falling off Obamacare wagon..."We need to read it to understand what's in it". **Sen. Max Baucus (D-Mont.) said Wednesday he fears a "train wreck" as the Obama administration implements its signature healthcare law."** Baucus warns of 'huge train wreck' enacting ObamaCare provisions Baucus, the chairman of the powerful Finance Committee and a key architect of the healthcare law, said he fears people do not understand how the law will work. "I just see a huge train wreck coming down," Baucus told Health and Human Services Secretary Kathleen Sebelius at a Wednesday hearing. "You and I have discussed this many times, and I don't see any results yet." Baucus pressed Sebelius for details about how the health department will explain the law and raise awareness of its provisions, which are supposed to take effect in just a matter of months. "I'm very concerned that not enough is being done so far — very concerned," Baucus said. He pressed Sebelius to explain how her department will overcome entrenched misunderstandings about what the healthcare law does. "Small businesses have no idea what to do, what to expect," Baucus said.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366222035429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366223671278-13</Id><Topic><Title>Another top Democrat, Obamacare a "train Wreck"</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366222035429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""we need to read it to understand..."" - yep - every conservatives nightmare = reading !!! They don't even read "THE book" - they have priest read and interpret it for them...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366223671278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366224602935-14</Id><Title>Romney 'very proud' of his Romneycare with a mandate</Title><Msg>Romney 'very proud' of Mass. health care law Mitt Romney is embracing his Massachusetts health care law.....Romney added that he was “very proud” of his signature on the 2006 law when he was governor of Massachusetts............</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366224602935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366224730516-15</Id><Topic><Title>Another top Democrat, Obamacare a "train Wreck"</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366222035429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can change the subject, but you can't change that Obamacare is a nightmare yet to be realized. The bill never was intended to address the cost side...and yes, even you will be effected in a negative way before it's over. Where is your objectivity?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366224730516</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366225060502-16</Id><Title>mccain wanted to tax employee health insurance benefits</Title><Msg>his healthcare fix......needed, he said because of the mess of health insurance in the USA ...... was to make you pay income tax on your employee health insurance benefit......... the idea being to END employer healthcare....... and force everyone to buy health insurance in market exchanges where you would get a subsidy if you could not afford the high prices..............the dems decided to go with the gop idea of a private insurers and a mandate ala Romneycare.......</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366225060502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:57:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366225298848-17</Id><Title>Romney on Romneycare: “It’s a Personal Responsibility Mandate"</Title><Msg>Romney on Individual Mandate: “It’s a Personal Responsibility Mandate” At a March 2006 press conference as the bill was moving through the legislature, then Governor Romney expressed his pleasure that the law included the “personal responsibility provision” (individual mandate). “With regards to the individual mandate, the individual responsibility program that I proposed, I was very pleased that the compromise between the two houses includes the personal responsibility mandate.” Romney then, in April 2006, reiterated that the penalty for employers was not a tax but the assessment of a fee. “It is a fee, it’s an assessment,” he said. He added that the fee was being assessed on those who were “abusing the free care pool.”</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366225298848</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 15:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366225565603-18</Id><Title>GOP Leaders Backed a Healthcare Mandate</Title><Msg>“Most Republican leaders supported a mandate, and the Romney plan came out of the Heritage plan,” Dave Keene, the president of the National Rifle Association and former chairman of the American Conservative Union, tells Newsmax. In fact, “The idea of an individual mandate as an alternative to single-payer was a Republican idea,” says health economist Mark Pauly of the University of Pennsylvania’s Wharton School. More recently, when asked on Fox News in February 2007 about the Romney plan, Republican Sen. Jim DeMint, chairman of the Senate Steering Committee and a favorite of the tea party movement, said, “Well, that’s something that I think we should do for the whole country.”</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366225565603</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 15:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366226179548-19</Id><Topic><Title>Another top Democrat, Obamacare a "train Wreck"</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366222035429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Objectivity ?! .... gee, lets see..... There is organization called Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) that includes 34 nations We had the current system for the last 100 years + right? In that time we managed to: - create the costliest health care system per capita in the world. - create a health care that costs 2.5 times more per person than average OECD (and OUR health care cost makes up that average) - become the only developed nation that does not have universal health care. - There are fewer physicians per person than OECD average - There are fewer hospital beds than OECD average - Life expectancy is lower than OECD average - Health care quality is DEAD LAST among OECD nations and ranks below many of the developing nations such as Costa Rica, Dominica, Chile etc etc etc etc. So yes - PLEASE ! Let's talk OBJECTIVITY!</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366226179548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 15:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366228825504-20</Id><Topic><Title>congrats ken G.</Title><Username>itsdifferentthistime</Username><Timestamp>1366211690080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 11:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is because he had his MM minions do the Bidding for him.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366228825504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:00:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366229446322-21</Id><Topic><Title>Another top Democrat, Obamacare a "train Wreck"</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366222035429</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 14:07:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The point is Obamacare is NOT the answer, never was intended to address these issues...just an attempt to take over of the healthcare insurance business...the government is nor equipped on almost all levels to run 1/6 of the economy...we need to start over where both parties have a say in the overhaul, and maybe then it will get more broad base support....that's being honest.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366229446322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366229493774-22</Id><Topic><Title>Letter!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366214819949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And yet - comes 2014 - there will be fewer GOP in both Senate and the house, and 2016 seems almost a slam dunk for any-likely-democrat vs. any-likely-republican White House race. The reason is simple: We all saw what letting GOP bullies run this country leads to. G.W. Bush "fooled us twice", and we will not let GOP embarrass us again.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366229493774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:11:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366229594527-23</Id><Title>Estimates?</Title><Msg>Ex-items I'm going .09 on 430 mil in revenue. With items probably .01 as they laid off tons of people this quarter.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1366229594527</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:13:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366232305637-24</Id><Topic><Title>Letter!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366214819949</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 12:06:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dream on CLOWN!!! This country had enough of the SOCIALISTIC ( COMMUNISTIC) OBIMBO SYSTEM, even the UNIONS and some democRATS speaken out AGAINST him and the Zcars already! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366232305637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 16:58:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366233608918-25</Id><Title>OBIMBOCARE falling apart left and right!</Title><Msg>What will the CLOWN, Folksnewsjunky, wingnut and so on do now since the OBIMBO GUN LAW background check fell apart on him too (In their own controlled congress)??? OH MY, OBIMBOCRATS will run into more trouble within the next 6 month then they EVER could foress!!! Maybe they should leave the country together with their MUSLIM, Michigan McD. chicken eating buddies! Crazy to get 700K over a sandwhich, which supposably had pork in it! Can 't eat pork unless a animal has a prayer said before slaughter? That must leave the F@#$%^ chicken out - maybe they are NOT aimals? Clean up America and throw all that garbage back to where it came from! Conform to AMERICAN customs, way of life and law, or go back where you came from - bed sheet IDIOTS and take your F#$%^&amp;*^&amp;* Allah Bakhar with you! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366233608918</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366233864632-26</Id><Title>Letter - 1st point!</Title><Msg>NO photo- op on gun control! I stated that the "Anti gun show" is coming apart - more to come apart! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366233864632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366234756850-27</Id><Title>remember the crazy rightwing christian lunatic known as the Olympic Park Bomber?</Title><Msg>Eric Robert Rudolph (born September 19, 1966), also known as the Olympic Park Bomber, is responsible for a series of bombings across the southern United States between 1996 and 1998, which killed two people and injured at least 150 others in the name of a pro-life and anti-gay agenda. As a teenager Rudolph was taken by his mother to a Church of Israel compound in 1984; it is connected to the Christian Identity movement.[2] He has called himself a Roman Catholic in "the war to end this holocaust" (in reference to abortion).[3] He has confirmed religious motivation, but denied racial motivation for his crimes.[4] Rudolph also confessed to the bombings of an abortion clinic in the Atlanta suburb of Sandy Springs on January 16, 1997; the Otherside Lounge of Atlanta lesbian bar on February 21, 1997, injuring five; and an abortion clinic in Birmingham, Alabama on January 29, 1998, killing Birmingham police officer and part-time clinic security guard Robert Sanderson, and critically injuring nurse Emily Lyons. Rudolph's bombs were made of dynamite surrounded by nails which acted as shrapnel.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366234756850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366235983252-28</Id><Topic><Title>remember the crazy rightwing christian lunatic known as the Olympic Park Bomber?</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366234756850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:39:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ducky - remember all those left wing nuts like Nero, Ceasar etc. which killed all those people, if they had bombs........how far you want to go back you racist! ROWDEY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366235983252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 17:59:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366236675497-29</Id><Title>New law!</Title><Msg>OBIMBO and little Joe says: All bomb makers and sellers of house hold cleaners/goods and fertilizer sellers must now undergo a back ground check! Why not - fire works sellers must get permits etc.??? A good M80, purchased legally in SD, packed into a garden watering can filled with nails can make a hell of a bomb - where does it stop??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366236675497</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:11:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366237183430-30</Id><Title>Bill/Hillary Clinton BURNED Blacks/Waco.</Title><Msg>Maybe 20% of Waco Vitims were white. Super Majority were BLACK. Bill/Hillary fried them! Total RACISTS! (if it was a republican President, you would already know this FACT!)</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366237183430</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:19:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366237304854-31</Id><Title>Shame on the law makers?</Title><Msg>Shame on OBIMBO with even coming up with his terms of gun control! Gun control should start in his own back yard - Chicago - by arming police with full automatics, a "stop and frisk" program and judges who throw the book at criminals, not just giving them slap on the wrist - hard time! I know 1/2 of Chicago's south side would be locked up together with Detriot, Savannah, Newark etc.! No prison room - farm the prisoners out to Mexico's jails - they will love the Dineros! Hello CA, just a short trip across the border instead of springing all those criminals - because they don't have enough money and there is over crowding and the gangs running rapid? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366237304854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366238750210-32</Id><Title>Antigunners, Liberals...............</Title><Msg>.............and Bob Beckel going ballistic, because their Community Organizer couldn't have his way to disarm the AMERICAN people and let the CRIMINALS have their way! "Little Joe looked like somebody ate his lunch"! I can hardly wait to hear from Pierce Morgan, the anti gun fanatic on CNN! Diane Sawyer is just talking about the SOLID DEFEAT of OBIMBO and his gun law by HIS DEMOCRAT SENATE on ABC! (The OBIMBOCRATS might have won the election and have the majority - but we got the VOTES!) Now OBIMBOCARE next! ROWDY (Where are all the dogooders on this board that predicted that the anti gun law will pass?????)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366238750210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:45:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366239718684-33</Id><Title>Sequester Cuts, selected by..............</Title><Msg>..................by OBIMBO are already falling aprt too. Congressional Democrats/ Senators are calling for for a end to this nuisance! They want cuts across and NOT just selected programs which excludes like benefits and give away programs! Another OBIMBO law coming apart!!! ;o) ROWDY (NO lucky........, no folknnews.......no wingnuts.........etc.)???????</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366239718684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366240571762-34</Id><Title>Dumbo's Boat; 'The Sea-QUESTER'</Title><Msg>It's where Dumbo and Tiger bang Tiger's Porn Stars!! If this boats a rockin'...</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366240571762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366240890320-35</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Cuts, selected by..............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366239718684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:01:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine getting a check-up at the Post Office...(Dumbo-scare)</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366240890320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366249718110-36</Id><Title>crazy #$%$ white man arrested for ricin letters</Title><Msg>Authorities arrest Mississippi man in ricin letters to Obama, senator (I could be wrong, as race was not mentioned..... but odds are, this is a crazy white man.... most likely suffering from white man disease: fat, short, bald.....impotent and .......CRAZY)</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366249718110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366250849455-37</Id><Topic><Title>Antigunners, Liberals...............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366238750210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, just wat for election time when even more Pub politicians will lose reelections and 2016 when another Dem President is elected. 88% of Americans want gun control and background checks. This defeat is not the end for gun control advocates but just the opposite and a new beginning. "Disarm the American people and they want to confiscate our guns." rodent, Bist Du verrueckt oder wahnsinnig geworden???</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1366250849455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 22:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366254942069-38</Id><Topic><Title>Sequester Cuts, selected by..............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366239718684</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:01:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Better yet - get examed by a nurse and then pick up your prescription at the local gas station!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366254942069</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366255911763-39</Id><Topic><Title>Antigunners, Liberals...............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366238750210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 18:45:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correction - 88% of LIBERALS wanted gun control - I don't have anything against the back ground checks, had to do it my self and more to get the conceiled fire arm permits in WI &amp; MN - just make sure they check the criminals too! (Good luck) Just in CH.5, KSTP (liberal MN station, KSTP -check it out your self) - only 48% of americans want stricter gun control laws, down from 56%, last month! Don't worry about 2016, 2014 is going to take care of the OBIMBORAMA already! Just like the gun control - them Immigration, OBIMBOCARE and all the other of his community reform programs - in the meantime pay your taxes for the wealth distribution and the broke state of CA! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366255911763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366256362424-40</Id><Topic><Title>crazy #$%$ white man arrested for ricin letters</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366249718110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 21:48:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Careful ducky, this description fits you! If the guy would have been black - he would have tasted it first to see if it's any good! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366256362424</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366256911535-41</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo's Boat; 'The Sea-QUESTER'</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366240571762</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 19:16:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obimbo is going to sequester himself to 3 days/week and 6 hours/day of work so he can reduce his taxes and prevent more screwups, then he is going to get a luxery apartment with Tiger and call his "shots" from there! This will also diffuse the N-Korea and Iran problem, just send Kerry with more money and food and if that doesn't work - try talking them to death! (But remembe he can always relay in Japan and Israel) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1366256911535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:48:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366256949714-42</Id><Title>The Children of Newtown are Ashamed of Republicans</Title><Msg>Repubs went against the will of 90% of Americans and voted against any bill restricting gun sales. Pubs want any whacko and crazy and criminal to be able to get an assault weapon easily. They even voted against increasing penalties for straw purchasers. Repubs used to be about family values. Now, they are totally in the pockets of weapons makers. They prefer to see crazies wipe out scores of children.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366256949714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>