<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369467229841-1</Id><Topic><Title>Special Prosecutor Inevitable</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1369249062544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:57:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2000, shortly after he left office, President Clinton entered the courtroom where he committed a number of the offenses charged in the articles of impeachment and plead GUILTY, surrendered his law license, and was placed on probation. In other words skip, the Senate blew it, and Clinton didn't even bother to TRY to assert double jeopardy as it could be argued that with a partisan Democratic Senate he wasn't in any jeopardy to begin with unless the intern was both underage and asserted rape.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369467229841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 03:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369467298962-2</Id><Topic><Title>Stockholm is burning: Why the Swedish riots bode ill for Europe...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1369436243219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 18:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't have to, I've been following the situation since Paris started burning for largely the same reasons.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369467298962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 03:34:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369485228778-3</Id><Topic><Title>republican scandal fest gets no traction</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369427657831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are, as usual, disingenuous: 1. the gop prevents the IRS from hiring more people 2. and more importantly. an application to the IRS to become a social welfare group is not even necessary as people donating to them can't write off the the donation as they can with a charity. Charites do have to apply, social welfare groups don't. "Unlike charities, which are supposed to apply for recognition, social welfare nonprofits can simply incorporate and start raising and spending money, without ever applying to the IRS."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369485228778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 08:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369487246634-4</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary-Dumbo scandal fest gets major traction</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369429062593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:57:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary/Dumbo/Lerner/Holder/Corrutocracy It's like the Clowns coming out of the Clown Car. Circus of Crime!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369487246634</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369488700483-5</Id><Title>Obamacare a HUGE Winner in California !</Title><Msg>Right wing hysteria is smashed down again ........... The results of Covered California's negotiations with health insurance companies belie predictions of massive premium increases under the law, at least for products that offer a range of benefits similar to those currently sold to small businesses. The average cost of a standard health insurance plan sold on the health insurance exchange will range from $304 to $321 a month in the Golden State next year, Covered California announced. Compared to existing plans with comparable benefits and factoring in available subsidies for low- and moderate-income people, prices like these represent either a small increase or a significant decrease in the monthly costs, the agency said. "This is a home run for consumers in every region of California," Peter Lee, the executive director of Covered California, said in a press release.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369488700483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369489295873-6</Id><Topic><Title>my Obamacare premium is up 120%</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369420809107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obamacare is a Crime! Invented by Criminals. Stop Obamacare NOW!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369489295873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369489504879-7</Id><Topic><Title>my Obamacare premium is up 120%</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369420809107</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Two sex changes don't come cheap. We shouldn't pay for your elective surgery.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369489504879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369494369545-8</Id><Title>My Obamacare premium now covers gerbils in strange places</Title><Msg>before I had to pay all out of pocket for gerbil removal, now it is covered, so I am better off with a higher premium ..</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1369494369545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369495624276-9</Id><Title>conservatism dying slowly</Title><Msg>by DAVID BADASH on MAY 24, 2013 The number of Americans who describe themselves and their beliefs as “liberal,” either on social or economic issues is growing significantly and reaching new highs, or meeting earlier ones, based on data from a just-released poll by Gallup, a generally conservative organization. Accordingly, the number of Americans who describe themselves and their beliefs as “conservative,” either on social or economic issues is dropping. Gallup reports “the trend suggests that ideological attitudes in the country may be shifting. Social liberalism has grown by six points since 2001 and now attracts half of rank-and-file Democrats and Democratic leaners.” This new survey shows changes in Americans’ ideology: economic conservatism is at a five-year low, while social liberalism has registered its highest support… Gallup reports finding “the percentage of Americans describing their social views as ‘liberal’ or ‘very liberal’ has achieved a new peak of 30% — in line with Gallup’s recent finding that Americans are more accepting on a number of moral issues. Thirty-five percent of Americans say they are conservative or very conservative on social issues and 32% self-identify as socially moderate.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1369495624276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369495767451-10</Id><Topic><Title>conservatism dying slowly</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1369495624276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The polling organization also notes that among Democrats, the shift is to the left: While the nation may be a house divided on social issues, self-identified or “leaning” Democrats appear to be moving toward consensus. Half now say their social views are liberal or very liberal; this figure was 35% in 2001 and 37% as recently as 2010. Fewer Democrats say they are socially moderate — down nine percentage points since 2001 — or socially conservative, down six points. A recent study not associated with Gallup found that politicians’ generally believe their constituents are far more conservative than they actually are, which might offer some explanation why expanding gun control background checks, which is supported by 91 percent of Americans, failed. The study, “What Politicians Believe About Their Constituents: Asymmetric Misperceptions and Prospects for Constituency Control,” by David E. Broockman and Christopher Skovron and presented at Vanderbilt University, notes “there is a striking conservative bias in politicians’ perceptions, particularly among conservatives: conservative politicians systematically believe their constituents are more conservative than they actually are by more than 20 percentage points on average, and liberal politicians also typically overestimate their constituents’ conservatism by several percentage points."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1369495767451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:29:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369501199795-11</Id><Topic><Title>conservatism dying slowly</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1369495624276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservatives will not disappear They are just embarrassed to be represented by Republican clowns who have been hurting their country. More conservatives are moving towards centrist Democrat policy.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369501199795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 12:59:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369504214103-12</Id><Topic><Title>conservatism dying slowly</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1369495624276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and together we'll meet in the middle. Maybe if both parties get rid of their fringes we can come up with something everyone can live with.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369504214103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 13:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369504274260-13</Id><Topic><Title>My Obamacare premium now covers gerbils in strange places</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1369494369545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 11:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, they sewed your #$%$ shut so it couldn't happen again, In fact with your #$%$ sewn shut you shouldn't be able to type, what's up with that?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369504274260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 13:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369504533124-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a HUGE Winner in California !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369488700483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All for it but . . . the Obama care program that I could have signed up for has been canceled because they found that people with complex pre-existing conditions are too expensive to cover, and that people who see the VA for care have no right to Obama care and MUST stick with the VA or simply pay cash for their entire insurance outlay. You see, the program you're so proud of, that Obama is so proud of, is too good for us disabled US veterans, God alone knows that an illegal immigrant from Guatemala will, soon after this becomes law, get free healthcare on the government tab from real doctors while I have to put up with the barely literate third rate doctors the VA recruits from . . . Guatemala. Another Democratic triumph executed by marching across the backs of American veterans.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369504533124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 13:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369504586519-15</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary-Dumbo scandal fest gets major traction</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369429062593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:57:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Holder has committed perjury to protect Obama so many times it should be in his job description.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369504586519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 13:56:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369504681424-16</Id><Topic><Title>republican scandal fest gets no traction</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369427657831</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 16:34:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, he isn't, and wouldn't care unless it was ACORN getting its government FUNDING (not just tax exempt status) challenged, then its all up in arms in indignity despite the evidence of misdoings directly recorded to video.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369504681424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 13:58:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369506882053-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a HUGE Winner in California !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369488700483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW any liberal sounding government entitlement program will be a huge winner in California even in cases like this where the program itself has yet to go into complete effect. For instance i could create a CaliFood Relief Bill, tell people where to go to sign up, and get them to march down an increasingly steep and slick ramp until they slide into my Soylent Green processor as long as I told them there was free food on the end of it. I won't mention that I intend to use that food as hog bait, or that the raw material of the food is the applicants, no, I'm gonna leave that buried in a brief paragraph in a subtrahend on Page 1743 of the bill, in the margins. Everything else will sound JUST dandy, making the program WILDLY popular, mostly because not many will miss the folks not coming out the other end. Not even, in many cases, their relatives. I think one person I'm familiar with complains more about the members of her own family living on unearned entitlements that she KNOWS they aren't eligible for without even considering that she largely withdrew from the paper economy over 5 years ago and never looked back. Of course she still files for federal programs (some of them, some she doesn't feel she needs, for people in her situation she's the model of restraint, as she has avoided Section 8, SSI, and so far only receives like $200 a month in TANF assistance) and of course her relatives probably say the same things about her. Funny thing is to one extent or another they're both right. Here's a proposed change, like the government whistleblower law where someone pointing out willful waste of government funds by a contractor and get a reward of like 10% of recovered funds, we implement a whistleblower program for entitlements such that if you turn in someone claiming entitlements illegally you get 10% of what money you prevented from leaking from the coffers (over the next 5 years maximum) if the person hadn't been detected? That'd create "private" oversight.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369506882053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:34:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369507582190-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare a HUGE Winner in California !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369488700483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 09:31:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VA happens to be pretty damn good coverage. And now you're whining for more ? My friend has cancer. likely from Agent O and the VA has been sending him to the best doctors available. He has been quite impressed with VA care. Maybe your issue is where you live ? You may be a long way from good coverage.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1369507582190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:46:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369507675247-19</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money..... Romney was right that Romneycare with a mandate is the "responsible" way to go.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369507675247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369508110985-20</Id><Title>Romneycare Didn't Increase Hospital Costs even with MORE people insured</Title><Msg>Study: Romneycare Didn't Increase Hospital Costs May 16, 2013 According to a new analysis, health care reform in Massachusetts, popularly known as "Romneycare," didn't cause hospital use or costs to increase, even as it drove down the number of people without health insurance.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369508110985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 14:55:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369509832408-21</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm hoping to be able to provide a policy to my live in nurse when I hire one. So far I don't see it as THE major factor in hiring one, but it's going to have to be considered "not part of compensation" for it to work otherwise the withholding on the money I have to spend on the policy is going to devastate her weekly check. Not even my wife, who's been effectively the administrator for a company with over 40 employees has been able to figure out exactly how it's supposed to work, and there's been little guidance from the IRS. When you can find something like "The Small Employers Compleate Guide To Obamacare" do let me know . . . I can't afford many people, so I need to find and retain ONE good one.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369509832408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:23:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369510094694-22</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was funny, I typed The Small Employers Complete Guide To Obamacare into Google and the first hit was a news article "Lawsuit says Obamacare crushing Small Employers". Looks like I'll have to take that job into the under economy where I hire my part time aide now, like everyone else who won't be able to comply with the regulatory requirements without totally eliminating their businesses profit margins, I don't want to hire someone and have MOST of the money head right back at the government and their cronies rather than the aides pocket. So, if I offer a competitive salary, I can't afford the compliance, and if I go with compliance, I can barely offer a salary at all. Then again another 3 years of Obama and there'll be plenty of skilled people willing to work for food, a place to stay, and relief from debt . . . I'll be searing serfs to my banners before the end of the decade.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369510094694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369510398195-23</Id><Title>Obamacare already Repealed</Title><Msg>Face the facts: You supporters posting about Obamcre are only doing it because your losing. This is after you had won...3 YEARS AGO! And your still trying to sell this Loser. Super majority of Americans Hate It! And now the Unions don't want it! Its over...face it! The I.R.S. is running it! Obamacare is already Repealed..the rest is symantics. Need I say more...</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369510398195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369511902556-24</Id><Topic><Title>Stockholm is burning: Why the Swedish riots bode ill for Europe...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1369436243219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 18:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Senate gang of eight working on the kamikaze immigration bill should be arrested.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1369511902556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369512699792-25</Id><Topic><Title>Stockholm is burning: Why the Swedish riots bode ill for Europe...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1369436243219</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-24 18:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many Illegals are Mooosleem murders...The unspoken Truth of Amnesty.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369512699792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:11:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369514741838-26</Id><Title>Clinton leads 2016 poll in Iowa</Title><Msg>Clinton leads 2016 poll in Iowa, Clinton leads 2016 poll: Hillary Clinton tops the latest poll of potential 2016 presidential candidates in Iowa. Clinton comes out ahead of Sen. Marco Rubio and Sen. Rand Paul.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369514741838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:45:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369515467206-27</Id><Title>have Oklahoma’s right-wing legislators been making anti-“Big Government” arguments lately?</Title><Msg>"In the wake of the tornado, you haven’t seen Oklahoma’s right-wing legislators making anti-“Big Government” arguments to deride the fact that their state receives more federal tax dollars than it contributes. Instead, you will likely—and rightly—see them lobbying to secure disaster relief funds from Washington. Likewise, you haven’t see Oklahoma’s archconservative demagogues like Republican Sen. Tom Coburn saying government shouldn’t help respond to the latest tornado. Instead, he’s now insisting “there’s a legitimate role” for government to play. He’s absolutely correct. It just shouldn’t take a tragedy for him or anyone else to realize that this will always be the case—at least if America is going to remain a truly civilized society."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369515467206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 16:57:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369521820696-28</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare already Repealed</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1369510398195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 15:33:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gerbil, ACA is doing just fine in California - eat your heart out, gerbil.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1369521820696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369522563332-29</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fubar, like all Pubs - you're predicting and guessing. Besides, there are insurance exchanges for small employers. fubar, I'm not going for your propaganda! You have no facts and that's it. No wonder some posters put you on ignore.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1369522563332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 18:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369523291515-30</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then google it yourself stooge. If you don't care for the answer, don't ask the question. Don't need to put "Liberal_hollywood" as your ID when the liberalism speaks for itself, how about something less obvious. Mine are outright cryptic.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1369523291515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 19:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369525996981-31</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fugbar, Here is something to read for you and I got it from google, From the minute that President Obama signed his landmark health reform bill into law, conservative critics have been issuing dire warnings about how expensive Obamacare will make employer-sponsored health coverage, asserting it would be cheaper for larger companies to drop coverage for their workers — and pay a fine if their employees obtain federally subsidized coverage through Obamacare’s insurance exchanges — rather than provide basic health benefits. As it turns out, those predictions aren’t actually becoming reality. According to Modern Healthcare, a new “survey of nearly 800 large and midsize employers found that just 6 percent of respondents intend to completely exit the healthcare system over the next three to five years” over concerns about the penalty that Obamacare will level against large companies that don’t provide adequate benefits for their workers. That assessment stands in stark contrast to some Obamacare opponents’ more outlandish claims. Major conservative institutions and healthy policy experts — including the Heritage Foundation and Douglas Holtz-Eakin, who is a former Congressional Budget Office (CBO) director — have predicted that anywhere between 20 million and 35 million Americans will lose employer-sponsored insurance because of Obamacare. Even respected consulting firm McKinsey and Co. predicted that “30 percent of employers will definitely or probably stop offering [employer-sponsored insurance] in the years after 2014,” the year that most Obamacare provisions — including the employer mandate — kick in. In fact, that kind of mass exodus would be fraught with risks for companies, considering that approximately 70 percent of Americans receive health coverage through their employer. The prospect of losing workers over decreased benefits is a powerful disincentive for the companies that might have considered ditching health coverage to cut costs.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1369525996981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 19:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369529873200-32</Id><Topic><Title>Special Prosecutor Inevitable</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1369249062544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-22 14:57:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and that is called side stepping the point and trying to change the subject. Nice try.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1369529873200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 20:57:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1369531464638-33</Id><Title>Is This the Perverted Republican Fantasy Board ?</Title><Msg>Never seen so much idiotic half wit speculation. Far right Log Cabin recruiters like slayer and bidder infest this board like a gay parade.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1369531464638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 21:24:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369533429674-34</Id><Topic><Title>PricewaterhouseCoopers: Obamacare will save businesses &amp; employees money</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1369315831071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-23 09:30:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh that is rich. I am still laughing at your post. Your proof that something is amiss with Obamacare is single lawsuit? Not even a lawsuit that was won, simply a lawsuit claim????</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1369533429674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 21:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1369540432500-35</Id><Topic><Title>Is This the Perverted Republican Fantasy Board ?</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1369531464638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 21:24:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Phew, it stinks in here w/the smell of Log Cabin Pub.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1369540432500</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-25 23:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>