<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368417863902-1</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat logic</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367598596906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Fortunately for you not everyone arguing your positions is as poorly informed." It would be refreshing to see you address the posters who represent 'your side' in the same manner. There is no shortage of ignorance and wildly righteous bias coming from the right. You seem completely tolerant of ignorance if it comes from your party. Ignorance is unacceptable from either side. You seem incapable of seeing both sides.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1368417863902</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 00:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368418496486-2</Id><Topic><Title>U. S. Jobs and Industrial Output Have Dropped Since Obama Has Been in Office</Title><Username>call_your_mommee</Username><Timestamp>1368385129384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>N***U***T***s</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1368418496486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 00:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368418534790-3</Id><Topic><Title>U. S. Jobs and Industrial Output Have Dropped Since Obama Has Been in Office</Title><Username>call_your_mommee</Username><Timestamp>1368385129384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 14:58:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>N***U***T***S</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1368418534790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 00:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368419135657-4</Id><Topic><Title>Capitalist Spring</Title><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1368409423462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-05-12 21:43:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Black, Red, Yellow, Green Angela Merkel and the Christian Democrats have taken a beating with their handling of the euro crisis and public in-fighting with their coalition partner, the Free Democrats. How long will the coalition last? And can the Social Democrats or the Green Party force Merkel out of office?</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1368419135657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 00:25:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368442985900-5</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary-Dumbo DEMOTING Mr. Hicks from the Benghazi chief post is all that is need to know what totally corrupt, anti-Anti-American, Tyrannical vermin these criminal thugs are all about.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368442985900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 07:03:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368453280844-6</Id><Title>Our Government is no longer on our side</Title><Msg>We need to wipe the slate clean, purge the bad actors and restart.</Msg><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1368453280844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368454475324-7</Id><Topic><Title>Our Government is no longer on our side</Title><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1368453280844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>may I suggest wiping your rear end first? you sound like a total rearend wipe, so wipe yourself. this is needed often for you poopy poop throwing types. FYI Mr Boehner is doing a great job so #$%$!!!!</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368454475324</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:14:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368454705219-8</Id><Topic><Title>Our Government is no longer on our side</Title><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1368453280844</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 09:54:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We need to send Hillary-Dumbo Benghazi corruptocracy back to Copenhagen or Kenya or whatever 'F'd up Liberal/Progressive/Facist planet these criminal thugs are from!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368454705219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:18:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368455870058-9</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American definition of treason is very hard to meet, which is why it's so seldom charged. For instance you'd have to jump through all sorts of hoops like actually proving it was intentional and not the inevitable result of a foreign policy that, for the previous period had been, shall we say, incompetent. We'd alienated our friends, tried to make nice with our enemies, embraced the Arab fraud in Palestine to a degree that previously would have indicated a serious lack of brain watts in a prospective President, and in general screwed the pooch at very opportunity. Now, given the LARGE pattern of incompetence and missteps that the Obama administration has with regard to matters of state, you're going to have a STEEP Hill to climb to prove this was anything other than stupidity as usual at the office.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368455870058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368455994781-10</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's intelligence but with real world experience, a lack of Ayers, Wright, and all other corrupting influences, but instead the creation and sale of his own business followed by an entry to politics, time in charge at the State House, and his parties nomination not because "he's black" but because "he's brilliant". But yeah, pretty much.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368455994781</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 10:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368458330462-11</Id><Topic><Title>rich pub paid $300 for a bottle of my conservative wine</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368241298632</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 23:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing U could find is a wine cork in a garbage tub...BTW.....I did eventually disclose the 2 buc chuck @ the end of the nite!! but then with ur sense of humor you would want ur money back U lost from playing bad poker!</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368458330462</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368458752665-12</Id><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Msg>You couldn't separate those girls with a crowbar. Bidder, slayer, cowboy, cgl, unlucky........ What a bunch of whiners. Must have run out of gerbils.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368459050529-13</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan buddy genocidal killer</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1368329699765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Ronald Reagan must be the nicest president who ever destroyed a union, tried to cut school lunch milk rations from six to four ounces, and compelled families in need of public help to first dispose of household goods in excess of $1,000...1f there is an authoritarian regime in the American future, Ronald Reagan is tailored to the image of a friendly fascist." - Robert Lekachman"</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1368459050529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:30:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368459593974-14</Id><Title>Hillary-Dumbo Benghazi corruption continues</Title><Msg>Liberals are freaking out. There is Blood in the Water. Jay Carney has lost the media. Hillary is toast. Look how even Liberals on this board are posting to change the subject of Hillary letting Americans die. Its all they got! Stay tuned, kiddies!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368459593974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368460840716-15</Id><Title>The Cruz Amendment</Title><Msg>MENDMENT by Americas Voice Online on 05/09/2013 at 1:42pm The following is a press statement from the Congressional Hispanic Caucus on Sen. Cruz’s amendment to prohibit immigrants from ever obtaining citizenship: Today, CHC Chairman Rubén Hinojosa (TX-15) and Members of the CHC released the following statement in response to the amendment offered by Senator Ted Cruz (R-TX) that would prohibit current and former undocumented immigrants from being eligible for United States citizenship: “As the CHC outlined in our Nine Principles of Immigration Reform, we will not support any legislation that does not provide a pathway to earned citizenship for the 11 million undocumented immigrants who are living in the shadows and exploited in the black market. Blocking 11 million undocumented immigrants from ever being able to fully contribute to our country is a huge step backward for our American values. “It is disturbing that Sen. Ted Cruz refuses to move past abstract, extremist rhetoric and see immigration reform in real life terms. The American people have consistently called on Congress to find a just, sensible solution. Sen. Cruz’s amendment however, would, in effect, institutionalize an underclass. Future generations will look back at his proposal with shame and shake their heads at how the senator dismissed some of our core American values.”</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1368460840716</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:00:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368461543165-16</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot to mention two of the giriemen - pacifican54 and rowdy_rodent. The group of Log Cabin Pubs would'nt be complete without them.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1368461543165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368463156119-17</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True dat. They are always bitcheen &amp; moanin. I think they need hormone pills.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368463156119</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:39:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368463393139-18</Id><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Msg>found this on another board: " I was born and raised in the UK, and am forever grateful to the UK National Health Service for the care and attention I received throughout the years (and yes, if I chose private care for any reason or condition, I could pay privately and still continue to use the NHS as I saw appropriate). The one startling thing about coming to America and becoming a US citizen has been trying to get my head around the utter stupidity - real, festering stupidity - of conservatives who are terrified of Universal Health Care, while having no experience of it. Care is NOT denied under the British system (American insurance companies, however, are happy to deny care when their profit margins are threatened)... and outcomes in the UK are better than in the US. And we spend less on health care! But all that underinformed Americans know of the NHS is the preposterous propaganda produced by the insurance companies, who don't give one whit about your health, just about making money out of you in your greatest need."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368463743858-19</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I use the VA, the system President Obama lauded as the very model for socialized health care. Let's just say that if this is what socialized heathcare is all about forget it. I'm "Category 1" their highest priority of service yet I have two shattered teeth in my mouth, my first new chair in 7 years has finally been ordered and will NOW be here in around eight weeks, the PT was horrified that I didn't have a backup chair when my main chair cratered, and we'll see about fixing that AFTER the broken chair is replaced (the backup chair is a manual chair that unlike my power chair will fit in a standard auto OR be used with bus/van tiedowns). As far as general medical care I haven't had a physical in perhaps 17 years now (its supposed to be done once yearly on an inpatient basis with MS patients), the Neurologist before this one was a total idiot and required direct orders NOT to touch my files or to fool himself with any pretense he was my physician, I finally found one though some 8 months in pain later . . . Oh yeah, the very example of socialized medicine. You have NO idea how frustrated I've been with the VA at times. They have if not broken my sanity at least severely bent it on several occasions.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368463743858</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:49:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368463944355-20</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An added FYI, the government exempted itself from the requirements of Obamacare, so I won't be getting a voucher from the government for the equivalent health care the VA would otherwise provide, instead I will be REQUIRED to continue to go to the VA so they can "control costs". Golly, imagine that, the US government exempting itself from a law that they're going to require of private industry, heaven knows we haven't ever seen THAT before!! (the list is so long that to attempt to post it would overflow the BBS post function, I just tried. Google the list yourself if your'e that bored).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368463944355</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368464352390-21</Id><Title>A Wager Lost.</Title><Msg>If you're holding off on going long until it dips under $10 again, oh well, that train has left the station at this point. Now you're hoping it'll dip back under $11, and it may . . . it's entirely possible. But if you're betting your position on it then you're making a bad bet. The only thing holding the price down right now are those shares Citadel dumped on the market waiting to escape for a fast profit, but that too will shortly pass and those with shares in their hands will become increasingly unwilling to part with them as a re-computaion of their loans given the changing circumstances might indicate a floor value for the company as a multiple of its stock price on the order of eight rather than two. The funny this is that when you're playing with this much money a SLIGHT change in the outlook on what are considered bad loans makes a HUGE difference in the bottom line when suddenly they aren't so bad after all.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368464352390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:59:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368464630628-22</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you LIE.... the government has NOT exempted itself from Obamacare...... that is just a really STUPID lie. and btw , liar Obamacare will also not affect care at the VA.... I presume you are a service connected welfare case and that will continue....... same as I can go to the VA and if i meet the poverty standard I could get free VA care there as can any veteran.............</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368464630628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:03:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368464986259-23</Id><Title>liars still repeating the lie that Congress has Exemption from ‘Obamacare’?......</Title><Msg>Congress and an Exemption from ‘Obamacare’? Posted on May 3, 2013 Q: Is it true that there are bills in Congress that would exempt members and their staffs and families from buying into “Obamacare”? A: No. Congress members and staffers will be required to buy insurance through the exchanges on Jan. 1. .. there is no bill in Congress calling for an exemption from the health care law. In fact, members of Congress and their staffs face additional requirements that most Americans don’t have to meet. Under the health care law, their insurance coverage will have to switch from the Federal Employees Health Benefits Program, the group of private insurance plans that cover 8 million federal employees and retirees, to the exchanges created by the law. Those exchanges are meant for those who buy coverage on their own, the currently uninsured and small businesses. Members of Congress and their staffs would be the only employees of a large employer in the exchanges, which are set to begin offering insurance in January. fact check dot org</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368464986259</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368465700713-24</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Reagan was trying to run for the last election - he would not even make it past his party vetting process let alone to the republican primary clusterf**k. Only crazies and lunatics can get into the GOP primary these days.... Good entertainment :)</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1368465700713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:21:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368465917191-25</Id><Topic><Title>A Wager Lost.</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368464352390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only dip I see is U</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368465917191</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:25:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368466037239-26</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan buddy genocidal killer</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1368329699765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure pick on the only guy that had guts to break Russia back...</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368466037239</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:27:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368466200646-27</Id><Topic><Title>Reagan buddy genocidal killer</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1368329699765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 23:34:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go find some dirt on Nixon, Spiro also will U how about LBJ, even better yet Obama..Bush Jr Bush Sn both Bushes have blood on their feet</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1368466200646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368466815363-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary-Dumbo Benghazi corruption continues</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368459593974</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:39:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary-Dumbo Benghazi just doubled down with Dumbo saying its 'Political side show" about 4 dead Americans. Sick that he says that after telling the families of the dead americans it was from a video. Liberals continue to defend. But they are sick too.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368466815363</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:40:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368467007658-29</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The VA has a long backlog of patients that has been long in coming and it did not originate under the Obama administration.</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1368467007658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368467701634-30</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>President Obama has never lauded the VA system as the very model for socialized health care. He compared it with Universal Health Care.</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1368467701634</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 13:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368468080991-31</Id><Title>German Healthcare</Title><Msg>Germany’s Health Care System: It’s Not The American Way by Uwe E. Reinhardt From an American perspective, Germany’s health care system represents a nettlesome challenge. Americans now spend 14 percent of their gross domestic product (GDP) on health care, while Germany spends less than 10 percent. Yet, for all that heavier spending, the U.S. health care system has never managed to provide all Americans with secure, portable health insurance. Evidently, for many low-income Americans without health insurance, the system now rations health care by income and ability to pay. By contrast, Germans of all ages have long enjoyed fully portable health insurance that provides what is effectively first-dollar coverage for a very comprehensive package of benefits. Furthermore, unlike U.S. patients, who increasingly find their choice of doctor and hospital limited through the technique of managed competition, German patients still enjoy completely free choice of provider at the time illness strikes. In cross-national opinion surveys conducted by the Louis Harris organization in conjunction with the Harvard School of Public Health, both German patients and physicians express relatively greater satisfaction with their health care system than their American counterparts express with their system.1 The relatively low level of health spending in Germany is all the more remarkable, because Germany’s population is so much older than America’s: 15.5 percent of the German population is age sixty--five or older, compared with 12.2 percent of Americans.2 In fact, the United States will attain Germany’s current age structure only in the year 2020.</Msg><Username>returnuspompus</Username><Timestamp>1368468080991</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368468309699-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo crying, literally, over Benghazi press question? The End is near! Drudge lead story.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368468309699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368468676447-33</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ding Ding . . . wrong again, and shows again how little you know about the VA. Priority 1 vets are all service connected either in combat, training accidents, or in some cases getting injured off the job (you'd be surprised at some of the #$%$ military folk do for "hobbies". When you work at a job requiring jumping out of airplanes, do you HAVE to go do it on your own time as well? Anyway, there are needs based categories for VA service, but they start past Category 4 or so I think (there were 8 categories last I looked, though that sort of thing changes). Tell ya what, you live in anywhere near Dallas, I want you go to in with me someday and get yourself into the system just so you know what you're dealing with. Schedule an HIV test or something like that where they might reason you wouldn't want to go through a normal provider, or complain about an old service related injury. Just get them to check you out. I want to watch. You may die of old age before you actually have an appointment with a clinician for reasons other than filtering out the lusers trying to take a free ride on the VA with the two to four years of active duty and alittle inactive service, many sometimes thinks that means they can use the VA no matter WHAT their needs status is. This is INCORRECT except in cases of receipt at an Emergency Room by ambulance in a life threatening situation. Then all they have is the duty to stabilize you and pass you on to a country hospital, for which you should be VERY thankful.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368468676447</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:11:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368468913802-34</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those guys aren't even patients yet, those are guys waiting to clear the paperwork to BECOME patients. Fortunately the military is starting to refuse to discharge people medically unless the VA takes IMMEDIATE control of them. This means some troops are kept in military hospitals until it the Army AND the VA have finished their paperwork and come to a disability determination (which is good because the way the VA does it in general lis better than the way the military services do it as few are skilled with the VA disability tables the way VA docs are). The VA has serious structural issues nationwide which need addresses, however the Dallas VA regional medical center is in a state of crises. I'm just waiting to see on the news some night that the guying living there had a combat engineer companies arms room shipped in and were taking over.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368468913802</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368469240987-35</Id><Topic><Title>A Wager Lost.</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368464352390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:59:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Citigroup swallowed up about 6 million of those shares per the most recent filings. All of which are still underwater.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1368469240987</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 14:20:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368471816528-36</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Er, I self identify mainly libertarian and if its not made up then its something I ought to know . . . What exactly differentiates a "Log Cabin" Republican from any other sort† The problem is that it's almost impossible to use one label to describe any group of people larger than one without narrowing focusing on whatever it is that group is assembled to do. Not even all members of the NRA agree on what our approach should be, from rigorous but with wider weapon ownership categories "you've got the training you can buy the weapon" types like me to those who want to ban all non rim fire weapons assuming they have one of the "characteristics of an assault weapon". You can get into the details but there are pro lifers who think ANY interference with conception is awful and you have types like me that want to keep it legal, safe, and rare. Then again I don't agree on a great many Republican positions, particularly as stated by the ignorant on this board, but I agree with far far less Democratic positions, particularly those as affect Federal Spending on entitlement programs, and, in particular among them, consideration of a complete ban on unearned entitlements. †(e.g, libertarians are like liberals who actually BELIEVE the liberal ideal rather than using it to create a government empire of bureaucracies. That being said it puts our interests in general far to the Republican side rather than the Democratic side since a Democrat never saw anything that he didn't think could be legislated, regulated, or taxed)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368471816528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:03:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368472127929-37</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, you are a republican, hidding as liberitarian, cause you think it makes you seem impartial.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1368472127929</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368472279575-38</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KO if this is such big news why do I find almost no mention of anything actually discovered at the hearings beyond that which was already widely known? What impeachable offenses, if any, do you see here? Lack of foresight? You're right, they wanted to impeach Bush for that, but fortunately they got hold of their baser instincts when realizing that Saddam had fooled all of them as well. Would have been hard to kick the President for believing everything that Saddam's intelligence agencies were feeding him, afterall, why not trust them, why would they fake information that was virtual suicide? Because they thought WE knew better (good old overestimating US intelligence) whereas their neighbors like Iran who they were trying to deter had to have no clue, and had to have a reason not to finish off the already maimed Iraqi military. Being President is a #$%$. One group of people tells you one thing, another group says no, that''s not true, and based on this land of "best, nominal, and worst" case scenarios you've got to make decisions on which people's lives hinge. Sometimes you call it wrong, but that's not an impeachable offense, it's just part of the job.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368472279575</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:11:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368472948115-39</Id><Topic><Title>a Brit comments on their National Health Service</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368463393139</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 12:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can always just try and buy health insurance, but I guess the preexisiting conditions puts you in with the regular people, including the many injured on the job and then dumped by the employer's health insurance....who can't get health insurance....... no profit in insuring people with work related (or any other) long term disablilty......... "dollar" bill Mcquire of united health corporation , the largest in the USA could have hardly given himself a billion dollar retirement package , as he tried to do, having to insure people with preexisting conditions, now could he?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368472948115</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368473288941-40</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This poster is playing a child's game. He insists on having Benghazi on top of all the other topics, but some topics can get very old, very quickly, when overused.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1368473288941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:28:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368475099932-41</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Impeached-Benghazi</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368216356492</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-10 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>elksmember, judging by that stain on your dress, I'd say you gave a mooshead.</Msg><Username>huntergroupc</Username><Timestamp>1368475099932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 15:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368475624122-42</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Impartial? Libertarians are NOT impartial. Like I said the politics on the economic end line up entirely with GOP values and aside from the God Squad no one in the party seems to want to expend a great deal of effort taking away Constitutional rights.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1368475624122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:07:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368475686398-43</Id><Title>installs $127,000 bed on his aircraft, which seems like great idea!</Title><Msg>Netanyahu's Plane Bed Bill Of $127,000 Brings Criticism ......................what's all the poopy about something as sensible as this? Mittens has beds on his planes and so does Grover and Rynce and many others who know what is needed and what is not.</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368475686398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:08:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368476299771-44</Id><Topic><Title>installs $127,000 bed on his aircraft, which seems like great idea!</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368475686398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, Netanyahu will pay for his onboard bed out of the millions of dollars we send Israel each and every year. And then, they turn around and spy on us.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1368476299771</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368477100565-45</Id><Topic><Title>Log Cabin Girls Cried All Weekend</Title><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368458752665</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 11:25:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The problem is that it's almost impossible to use one label to describe any group of people " That's funny - because the PUBS only use catchy LABELS in lieu of facts.... As for Libertarians.... the way I see them is "TEA PARTY without the BLIND HATRED" They don't want to pay taxes, don't want government to get in their way, and don't want to follow any rules BUT, they EXPECT services, protection and stability to be provided to them, so things can be just nice for them..... basically a parasitic approach to the idea of civilized nation...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1368477100565</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368477790265-46</Id><Title>Liberals Hate you! (Benghazi)</Title><Msg>Hillary-Dumbo totally LIED and blamed the video for Benghazi. Meaning that the United States is to blame for Freedom of Speech. Hillary-Dumbo, separately, are investigating, through the I.R.S., HUNDREDS of groups from the Right. Meaning, they are targeting ALL groups from the Right. This 'Culture of Corruption' is sick and EVIL . But Corrupt Hillary-Dumbo have no morals. Liberals loved the murderer Ted Kennedy and the Rapist Bill Clinton too.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368477790265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368478685539-47</Id><Topic><Title>installs $127,000 bed on his aircraft, which seems like great idea!</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368475686398</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:08:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Millions? Make that BILLIONS of dollars to help them keep the Palestinians living in concentration camps-like conditions.</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1368478685539</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:58:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368486808788-48</Id><Topic><Title>a burrito proves things are as they are meant to be</Title><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1368278891326</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-11 09:28:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Their not envious, they have manteca (lard) in their burritos.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1368486808788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 19:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368499250440-49</Id><Title>My ancestors had a guillotine and they did not let it get dusty</Title><Msg>Internal cost estimates from 17 of the nation's largest insurance companies indicate that health insurance premiums will grow an average of 100 percent under Obamacare, and that some will soar more than 400 percent, crushing the administration's goal of affordability.</Msg><Username>here_is_a_fiddy_cents</Username><Timestamp>1368499250440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 22:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368501787597-50</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals Hate you! (Benghazi)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368477790265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 16:43:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More hormonal whining from the Log Cabin girls. Are the ALWAYS on the rag ?</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1368501787597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 23:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368502901914-51</Id><Title>The Tea Potty should be investigated by the CIA !</Title><Msg>IRS is NOT enough. Tea Potties are breeding terrorists from within. They need to be shut down.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1368502901914</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-13 23:41:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>