<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365912974027-1</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There IS fat people in every state ? Might you mean there ARE fat people in every state ? Your grammar is as bad as bidder's. The point is ................... the biggest drags on our tax dollars are out of control obese, cig smoking, meth taking #$%$ jobless slobs. And they all vote republican.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365912974027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 00:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365918825536-2</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Nuts fabricate Gun nut stories</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365604339096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"But you display a typically myopic cynicism common in your kind." And if a white man said that to a black man publicly it would be condemned as hate speech. But, when you're talking non-Whateveryouare's, you just reach down into your bag of baseless slander. "Your kind" in this case I take to mean "people of intelligence" since neither you nor the originator of this sub-thread have displayed any.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365918825536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 01:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365919467024-3</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But they're also more likely to be mauled by bears. Well, if you count tourists anyway, if you count the natives its probably about even. There was one fatal bear mauling in New York in the first decade of this century, and several in Alaska and a frightening number at Glacier National Park along the border with Canada. In comparison during the first decade of the LAST century, when carrying guns into the bush was common, there were only two verified deaths from bear attacks (but many more dead bears). You want your nice safe world, but lets ban all the nasty guns and let the predators come back, let them adapt to the cities, and listen to the howls of the liberals as Mountain lions snack on their young'uns. They maybe they'll realize that the evolution of weapons has corresponded with the evolution of human ethics and the decreased desire for war among the world powers. Nobel was right in one respect and wrong in another. Dynamite didn't make total war unthinkable as he hoped, but Oppenheimer finished the job for him with the Hydrogen bomb.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365919467024</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 02:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365921154759-4</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Blacks have a 51 percent greater prevalence of obesity than whites, and Hispanics have 21 percent greater obesity prevalence than whites, according to researchers from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention." Over 90% of blacks and 71% of Latinos vote for Democrats. You are making unsubstantiated, moronic and ... racist statement. Offending large group of obese who helped Obama win last election? Put your quote on your T-shirt , or on big sign. "the biggest drags on our tax dollars are out of control obese, cig smoking, meth taking #$%$ jobless slobs." Walk into predominantly black neighborhood. Don't forget to record all on camera.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365921154759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 02:32:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365944066498-5</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, the point is the less guns the less gun violence, contrary to the liar gun nuts and NRA. get it, mr, apples and oranges? The fact is states with the weakest gun controls and the most guns have FAR MORE gun violence.....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365944066498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 08:54:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365950983610-6</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your write about the grammer but your still a looser. And the jobless slobs you have make reference too is Bambam's biggist vote block.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1365950983610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 10:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365952129195-7</Id><Title>Alaskans protect themselves with GUNS</Title><Msg>I love Alaska! You know who hates Alaska? Liberal/Lying Gerbil Stuffing Useful Idiots who push FAKE gun statistics on this board and elsewhere. U.S Federal Government's recorded in 2011: 11,493 Firearm Homicides. (16,799 non-firearm homicides). That's about 3 per 100,000 people as a national average. Take out he astronomical 'Gang Violence' murders and the rate is lower than 'Anti-Gun Europe'. Lubed-up loser have pushed a 'Alaskan are twice as likely to get killed with a gun than New Yorkers'. Where did this imaginary stat come from? Gerbil-Stuffer does not say. So why take grease-balls word on the fact? He got it from Obama financier and Liberal wack-job 'Keiser'. Read the report. It says it includes: All gun shots. That includes LAW ABIDING CITIZENS protecting themselves! And suicides, accidental discharges and other to pad this misleading crapola designed to take away your NATURAL RIGHT to protect yourself with a Gun!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365952129195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365955382498-8</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the less guns the less gun violence, contrary to the liar gun nuts and NRA. Just a fact.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365955382498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365955921049-9</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Slayer, you didn't stay awake in school. It's YOU'RE still a loser. ( nice name calling ) And ........ " slobs you have MADE " , and it's not TOO, It's TO. Three errors in two sentences. You fail. Same with your points. They fail. You are from "The Stupid Party"</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365955921049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365956069280-10</Id><Title>more guns &amp; weak gun controls = MORE GUN casualties , not less per the liar nra gun nuts</Title><Msg>just a fact. the states with the highest per capita gun deaths are red states with lots of guns and weak gun controls: As of 2010, Alaska had the worst gun death rate in the nation—20.3 deaths per 100,000 people, almost twice the national norm of 10.3 deaths per 100,000 people. other high gun death rate states are: arizona Mississippi Alabama Louisiana Nevada Montana Wyoming btw, New York and New Jersey have half the per capita gun killing rate as the states above.....An Alaskan or Arizonan is about TWICE as likely to be killed with a gun than a New Yorker</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365956069280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365957198670-11</Id><Title>Etrade Loans</Title><Msg>The housing market is insane out here in Cali. Heck, can the loan portfolio possible turn a profit? Any ideas what to expect.</Msg><Username>pghkidinla</Username><Timestamp>1365957198670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:33:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365957840349-12</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Nuts fabricate Gun nut stories</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365604339096</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-10 10:32:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously whoever taught you to stick the right end of the Ethernet cord in the wall and that 0/1 on a switch that made the lights go on usually means "on/off" decided that teaching you that sarcasm doesn't play well in text was a stretch for now, and so stuck to the basics. There, I've contributed to your education. See how much an insult it still sounds despite me being very specific about the target, subject, and intent? That's why sarcasm doesn't work, particularly when someone is NOT specific about target, subject, and intent. All you do is end up cranking people off.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365957840349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365959026759-13</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aye, the less gun violence, but the more you have to worry about other threats. I am "well regulated" as required by the 2nd Amendment, e.g. I train with those of my weapons I expect to use and keep LOAC compliant ammunition for my military weapons. I'm former military with multiple combat arms specialities which means I got lots of "cheap" training from Uncle Sam. Maybe I have a different perspective due to growing up in a house with firearms and a father, a Korean era Marine then an investigator for Ohio Department Natural Resources, who had training similar to what I'd later get in the Army during his Marine Corp stint. Perhaps firearms safety from a young age, NRA sponsored Junior Rifle competition, gun and hunters safety courses prepared me for a more rigorous approach to firearms safety and how I could possible have no had someone die on me by now (outside military service where its sort of the point). After all if one gun in the home kills more, how about a dozen, or two dozen, or however the heck many I have? So, if training IS the big difference (and believe me few police are inadequately trained and most Air Force enlisted personnel wouldn't last 15 seconds in a firefight and aren't usually trusted with automatic weapons), and quality of training does matter, why don't we instead create a curricula of firearms safety and teach a course at every grade level, to eventually include live fire of pneumatic and then rimfire single shot rifles? One people learn the basics of handling, the ethics of use, and the finality of the decision, we'll ALSO see a great deal fewer firearms accidents. As an added bonus the gangbangers in the cities will actually learn to hit each other instead of every innocent bystander in the immediate area.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365959026759</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 13:03:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365961955155-14</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade Loans</Title><Username>pghkidinla</Username><Timestamp>1365957198670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:33:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at some point, ETFC's loan book will hit an inflection point, and we will start to see dramatic write-ups. however, it is difficult to predict exactly when this will happen, because the loan book is filled with so many HELOCs, which are effectively a subordinate lien to the 1st mortgage, meaning that they have no intrinsic value unless/until the total value of each home exceeds the total secured debt on each respective home. when it does happen, though, I think that we will see an amazing move upward in the stock price. I think that we will hit $50 by the end of 2015, barring any macro catastrophe. I base this on: (1) a huge improvement in the loan book; (2) a general return of retail investors to brokerage services; and (3) a huge increase in Net Interest Margin as the Fed stops artificially suppressing interest rates. JMHO</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1365961955155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 13:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365963537086-15</Id><Title>i keep my musket ready and power horn full, just as the founders intended!</Title><Msg>I am ready for a slave uprising or moonshine crazy neighbors and their gun craziness . A musket is all you need, THE weapon of the 2nd amendment!. Mint Julep anyone? Guns are as American as apple pie, slavery walking with dinosaurs, and women at home in the kitchen and boudoir where they belong!</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1365963537086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 14:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365964587849-16</Id><Topic><Title>i keep my musket ready and power horn full, just as the founders intended!</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1365963537086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 14:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya know you do make a very subtle point ( which usually goes over the heads of the marroons here ). The right wing gun #$%$ want the very latest tech in mass murder weapons. But an electric car strikes fear in their tiny brains.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365964587849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 14:36:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365964822172-17</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and slayer, I think you meant " loser ", NOT looser. Looser is how you adjust your belt under your pot belly and manboobs. So that's 4 errors in just 2 sentences. I think you only made it the third grade.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365964822172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 14:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365969081644-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about Dumbo</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365716478097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:41:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbo is the product of the Party of Hate, Stupid, Racist, Gerbil-Stuffing</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365969081644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 15:51:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365969317382-19</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep going maroon. When you have finally found them all, you'll have earned a juice box.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1365969317382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 15:55:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365975981408-20</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's always the same with these phony white hating liberals. They all live in areas surrounded with well behaving white folks so in their mind they feel safe, yet are the first to defend folks of color who by percentage do most of the killing. It's easy to talk silly when your neighbors are all well behaved.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365975981408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365976443395-21</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just can't deal with reality can you? The fact is you are much more likely to get killed with a gun in white assed, nra gun nut red states like Alaska , Montana, Wyoming or Arizona, than in blue states like new York or massachusetts . Per capita gun killings in Alaska are twice what they are in New York.........more guns and weak gun laws equal more gun deaths contrary to the liars at the nra and liars like you.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365976443395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:54:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365976720758-22</Id><Topic><Title>more guns &amp; weak gun controls = MORE GUN casualties , not less per the liar nra gun nuts</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365956069280</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 12:14:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why are republicans always 100% all in for such insane, destructive and just plain wrong ideas such as the nra notion that more guns means less gun deaths ( the opposite is true, of course)......You all were the same with charging into Iraq like a bunch of jackasses.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365976720758</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:58:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365976724187-23</Id><Topic><Title>i keep my musket ready and power horn full, just as the founders intended!</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1365963537086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 14:18:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**But an electric car strikes fear in their tiny brains** First, I thought you were going to reframe from name calling, second, you are right...we are afraid of running out of a battery charge in a intercity where folks of color are armed with the latest in mass murder weapons.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365976724187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 17:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365977024920-24</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans protect themselves with GUNS</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365952129195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Killing criminals before they kill you. Liberals Hate logic!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365977024920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:03:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365977072558-25</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are hopelessly naïve....BTW, I haven't seen any "W" bashing from you today, what's up?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365977072558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365977108597-26</Id><Topic><Title>The Truth about Dumbo</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365716478097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-11 17:41:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ignored</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1365977108597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365977899939-27</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**the biggest drags on our tax dollars are out of control obese, cig smoking, meth taking #$%$ jobless slobs** Aren't those the folks in Obama's new budget he is relying on taxing to fund his bonehead idea of universal pre-school?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365977899939</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 18:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365987419342-28</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As usual, bidder, you miss the point. All red states. Get it ? You and slayer have a real tough time with facts.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365987419342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 20:56:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365987603635-29</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans protect themselves with GUNS</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365952129195</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 11:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In Alaska, you need a gun. Big animals see you as food. You, on the other hand, are far more likely to be consumed by gerbils.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365987603635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 21:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365993078938-30</Id><Topic><Title>Alaskans are nearly twice as likely to get killed with a gun as New Yorkers</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365888207451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 17:23:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude that study fails to discount suicides and treats self defense shootings the same as homicides. In other words, it's flawed beyond the right to be used in a reasonable argument.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365993078938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 22:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365995635883-31</Id><Title>Two Shot in Gun Shows. Gun Suicide at NASCAR !!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Guns, guns, guns !!!!!!! The Holy Shrines of guns are being Defiled by, yes, Guns. Right Wing maroons want any crazed whacko to be able to buy a gun. They crazier, the better ! A drooling Mafia, Ghetto Lord Drugged out Whacko is protected by the NRA.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365995635883</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 23:13:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365997953052-32</Id><Topic><Title>America's Fattest States ... All Red States</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365868631190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-13 11:57:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>10 seconds of research produce: What is the evidence regarding the President’s statement that “Every dollar we invest in high-quality early childhood education can save more than seven dollars later on”? The one study most relevant to President’s statement is the Chicago Longitudinal Study which reported a $7.14 to $1 benefit-cost ratio (Reynolds, Temple, Robertson, &amp; Mann, 2002). The Chicago Child Parent Centers (CPCs) were highly similar to current state pre-K programs in design and cost, and they incorporated the features of high-quality programs listed by the President’s proposal. The CPCs served more recent and broadbased (though low-income) populations on a large scale and were operated by Chicago public schools. It is notable that the estimated effects of the CPCs on achievement at kindergarten entry are very similar in size to those found for Oklahoma’s universal pre-K program. In the context of the larger literature that links initial and later effects, it is reasonable to draw inferences from the Chicago study regarding the economic benefits of Oklahoma’s universal pre-K program. However, this requires more than simply applying the CPC benefits estimates to Oklahoma without adjustments, and, as discussed below, more recent estimates of the CPCs’ benefits are highly relevant. The $7 to $1 figure is prominently featured in the abstract of the Chicago benefit-cost analysis cited above so it is hard to see how critics of the President’s pre-K proposal could have missed it. Perhaps they missed it because later follow-ups produced higher estimates of the return that are about $11 to $1 (Reynolds, Temple, White, Ou, &amp; Robertson, 2011). Thus, the President did not mechanistically apply the Chicago figure to his proposal to claim that every dollar invested in pre-K would produce the same benefits as the CPCs. He claimed a substantially smaller benefit. As discussed in the remainder of this section, his claim is not mechanistic</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365997953052</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-14 23:52:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>