<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362805388444-1</Id><Title>If You Need Help</Title><Msg>Call anyone but the coward of Benghazi. Trust us. We know. That is one useless, yellow, mfing good-for-nothing coward. Sean Smith Christopher Stevens Glen Doherty Tyrone Woods Neve forget.</Msg><Username>union_dude255</Username><Timestamp>1362805388444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 00:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362810895390-2</Id><Title>ACQUISITION</Title><Msg>I heard through the grapevine that charles schwab is going to acquire e-trade. is there any truth to this. does anyone know? i would like to hear from someone that may know about this.</Msg><Username>hhhowardabe</Username><Timestamp>1362810895390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 01:34:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362813569806-3</Id><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Msg>Watch the video and come back and tell me again how we are heading toward socialism. Like I have said, most pubs have NO CLUE how the wealth is distributed in America.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362820174110-4</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He left that task to you, dude, but you wouldn't budge. There are some good people who helped to discover bad apples in Catholic church. But is this the only evil in the world? Or just the other evil doesn't interest you? The church, any church, is private institution. It doesn't take my money unless I am willing to give. ACORN used to take my money without my consent and used it to put some Mickey Mouses on registration forms so they could vote certain way, or some of its employees are willing to participate in human trafficking. I am glad ACORN collapsed. Yet, it makes you unhappy! You know what it is called? Hypocrisy. And you don't even see it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362820174110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 04:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362821618274-5</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boring... "Thou Shalt Not Covet". Sounds so simple. Yet, so hard to grasp for some. What was your point again?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362821618274</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 04:33:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362836603440-6</Id><Title>etfc</Title><Msg>this baord sucks all talk about political #$%$ not a word about petrilli leaving.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1362836603440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:43:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362836656628-7</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>restore USA progressive taxation to where is was in the Eisenhower years. In 1955 the top 400 returns paid an avg 50.2%; recently they paid 16.6% on as astounding avg income of $345 million...also recently 9 wall streeters took a billion in bonuses, which they demand be taxed at 15% as 'carried interest', even while they preach that the old and the disabled and veterans must make 'sacrifices' and take cuts in social security, VA disability and so on. the gop is a disgrace, a shamless disgrace....... right now the guy making $ 450 million pays the same rate as the one making $45 million or $4.5 million or $450K... no progressivity....except for the 'little people' the guy making 150K does pay a higher rate than the one making 50k... which is as it should be. the more you benefit from our great nation, the rate of tax should go higher... FOR ALL incomes, the super rich should not be exempted........gop get back to your roots: The Square Deal was President Theodore Roosevelt's domestic program formed upon three basic ideas: conservation of natural resources, control of corporations, and consumer protection. Thus, it aimed at helping middle class citizens and involved attacking plutocracy and bad trusts while at the same time protecting business from the most extreme demands of organized labor. ... Roosevelt was a Republican who believed in government action to mitigate social evils, and as president denounced “the representatives of predatory wealth” as guilty of “all forms of iniquity from the oppression of wage workers to defrauding the public.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362836656628</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:44:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362838838715-8</Id><Topic><Title>tax dollars went to gop "faith based" community organizers..where was O'keefe &amp; his pimp costume?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362794741646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:05:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny how the gop is OK with tax dollars going to some commununity organanizations.......(as long as they are not black........ well, actually the gop was OK with acorn even.... until a black man ran against them for prez..... and hey.). some of those righty groups were no doubt connected to the catholic church, which judging by righty logic are all rapists....... if some employees are criminals, it means the entire organization is, right?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362838838715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 09:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362842921347-9</Id><Title>Franke, Utton, Petrilli shakeup</Title><Msg>Their is a total mgt shake-up at E-Trade and all this board can talk about is Obama !!!!! Any intelligent comments regarding this shake-up? If the new guy so horrible to work with or is he cleaning house?</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1362842921347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:28:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362845902698-10</Id><Topic><Title>Franke, Utton, Petrilli shakeup</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1362842921347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 10:28:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know who any of those ppl are but any change is probably a good one. this thing has been in the tank for more than 6 years. I am glad they are still in business but I want my investment back.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362845902698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 11:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362845974138-11</Id><Topic><Title>etfc</Title><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1362836603440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who is petrlli? is it good or bad??</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362845974138</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 11:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362849387146-12</Id><Title>GOP demanding expansion of Obamacare!!</Title><Msg>By Igor Volsky on Mar 8, 2013 at 9:34 am Republicans voted to repeal the Affordable Care Act more than three dozen times, ran on a pledge to eliminate the law on “day one,” and sought to underfund the measure at every opportunity. But since the Supreme Court upheld the ACA and President Obama won re-election the political dynamics of reform have changed: Republican governors are slowly embracing elements of the law and Congressional Republicans are no longer scheduling votes to repeal it. In another sign of the growing political support for health reform — or the sense that opposing its most popular elements has become politically perilous — a group of top House Republicans have written a letter to President Obama asking him to preserve a temporary program included in the law that provides health care coverage to people with pre-existing conditions.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362849387146</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:16:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362850918766-13</Id><Title>the 47% that Mitt &amp; the gop hate?</Title><Msg>Since the beginning of the Great Recession, I’ve been waiting for a documentary to make the case that low-income people and the middle class are now in the same boat—that old distinctions people created to divide them are obsolete, with so many people living near poverty, or an illness, lost job, or disaster away from poverty. A hundred and six million Americans, or more than one in three, now live below twice the poverty line—on less than $36,000 for a family of three, forced to make choices between basic necessities like food, housing, healthcare and education, and with little to no savings to help through tough times; wealth is increasingly concentrated, with the richest 1 percent now possessing 40 percent of the nation’s wealth. Certainly the numbers suggest a convergence of interests among the poor and non-rich. Now, finally, a movie has arrived that shows the precariousness of the US economy for the majority of Americans, refusing to distinguish between a deserving and non-deserving poor: American Winter. Filmed over the winter of 2011–12 in Portland, Oregon, the documentary tells the stories of eight families, showing the human costs of a frayed safety net and a proliferation of low-wage work. Emmy Award–winning filmmakers Joe and Harry Gantz, creators of HBO’s Taxicab Confessions, worked with the nonprofit organization 211info in Portland, monitoring calls from distressed families who were turning to the emergency hotline in search of help. They then followed the stories of some of these callers over many months. Most of these families never imagined they would be in the situation they suddenly find themselves in, needing support to get through a tough time, and finding that that support just isn’t there: a husband loses his job, he and his wife try to support their three kids on her minimum-wage work, losing heat and electricity in the dead of winter in order to pay the mortgage; a 50-year-old accountant is laid off and struggling to care for his...</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362850918766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:41:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362850933022-14</Id><Topic><Title>the 47% that Mitt &amp; the gop hate?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362850918766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:41:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>......10-year-old son who has Down Syndrome, now faces the loss of his ranch and sole asset to provide for his son’s future; a husband loses his $22-per-hour job, and his wife and their two sons turn to a women’s shelter for assistance; a college-educated woman is laid off and so she sells scrap metal and donates plasma to help support her family of five—even after she finds minimum-wage work; a woman’s husband dies, and she and her 11-year-old son can’t keep their home—they sleep in a garage and in their car before ending up in a shelter; another mother has to take three months off of work to care for her daughter who is hospitalized with a stomach condition—she’s stuck with a $49,000 bill that insurance won’t cover. “Forget the dreams, how do we make it to tomorrow?” says a father. Laid off from the credit branch of a car company, he and his wife lose their home to foreclosure and now struggle to provide their kids with the basics. “Tomorrow’s the dream. This dinner is the dream. You can turn the water on, turn the lights on—that’s a dream.” Woven into the film are interviews with local economic experts, policy analysts, religious leaders and social workers, all of whom provide context for the families’ stories. “If capitalism is not regulated or checked, there is a harsh logic and it will always seek out the lowest costs, highest return, which is why we have historically viewed government as a check and a balance on that,” says Portland City Commissioner Nick Fish. “Over the last quarter century, we have reduced regulations, degraded wages, cut back on health care, we’ve reduced taxes, and now people are more vulnerable…. We have a “one strike, and you’re out’ economy.” As we now begin sequester cuts that will further strain supports to working families and families that are unable to work, this is a timely movie, to say the least.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362850933022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362852544318-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment Hits 4 Yr Low ! Stocks hit record Highs !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362757687079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is reducing the size of govt. Which is what you marroons have always wanted. And our economy is improving, unemployment is down. Which is what you marroons hate. Republicans have been wanting America to fail for so long, it's part of the GOP platform.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362852544318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:09:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362854065811-16</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment Hits 4 Yr Low ! Stocks hit record Highs !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362757687079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodentrowdy, I'm doing well in the stock market - are you? Real estate prices are going up in my neck of the woods. I may sell my castle and buy a yet bigger one. Unemployment is going down!!! rodentrowdy, President Obama will emerge asone of the very best presidents of our time!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1362854065811</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362854112153-17</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are working, I would recommend government to tax your income above $35K at 90% rate. I just feel you get enough, so you don't deserve it. If you are not working, than shut up and stop talking about other people's money. "Thou Shalt Not Covet".</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362854112153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:35:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362854385458-18</Id><Topic><Title>the 47% that Mitt &amp; the gop hate?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362850918766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 12:41:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Duh, thats the way the system works. Money is like gravity, they more you have of it, the more you attract to yourself. A huge disparity of income/wealth inequality is the natural outcome of our current system. When fewer and fewer people have control of more and more of a countries assets, they are able to better dictate terms of trade. 30 years ago, for every 1$ of value a regular joe produced working for someone else, they might of been paid 70 cents. Now for that same 1$ of value they are only being paid maybe 40 cents. And thats because the terms of trade have been tilted in favor of big buisness. That, more than anything else is why we've seen such a huge gap form between the rich and everyone else. Its not that they're working harder now then they were 30 years ago or everyone is working less, its that the rich have significantly improved their terms of trade.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1362854385458</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:39:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362854886073-19</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should we get rid of anti-trust laws too? Just let whoever has the most power/influence make the most money and dictate what they want? Why don't we just get rid of government entirely and let the strong enslave the weak? Don't the rich have the most to lose if our country becomes unstable, shouldn't they pay more to support it, when they are the ones that benefit the most?</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1362854886073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 13:48:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362855829789-20</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really that is all that video makes you think. You are truly beyond redemption, if that video does not make you think something is not quite right, healthy in America today. Here is a simple question, do you think we will be a better, stronger nation if this wealth gap continues to grow? and when the wealthy control 99.9999% of wealth, we will hear the Romneys\Pacificans of America lament the lazy 78% of Americans that do not pay federal taxes.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362855829789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 14:03:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362857353206-21</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have never understood why the wealthy would ever want to see a US where they have to fear to walk the streets, fear that their kids will be abducted for ransom, etc. Pacifican would have told a slave to "Stop Coveting"</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362857353206</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 14:29:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362857779990-22</Id><Topic><Title>etfc</Title><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1362836603440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he was the chairmen that was hired not long ago.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1362857779990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 14:36:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362862295025-23</Id><Title>GOP internecine warfare</Title><Msg>Just hours after Sens. John McCain (R-Ariz.) and Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) slammed Sen. Rand Paul on the "Senate floor, conservatives are turning on the Republican Party's "old bulls." In a floor speech this morning, McCain accused Paul of using the filibuster to "fire up impressionable libertarian kids." Graham claimed Paul was ignoring national security threats, using a ludicrous chart to illustrate his point, "It was embarrassing," a senior Republican Senate aide told Business Insider. "It definitely looked like two guys whose time has passed. They are behind history, and they are the only people in the room who don't know it yet." By Thursday afternoon, conservative grassroots group FreedomWorks was already asking supporters to sign a petition demanding McCain apologize to Paul. "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362862295025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:51:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362863233162-24</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My redemption doesn't come from you, lady, it comes from the other place you don't know. Your regurgitating ideas of social justice doesn't add a scintilla to correct my worldview. I made it here from very bottom, and thank G-d for everything he has given to me. I don't need help with your edumacation. Fairness propaganda intensely promoted in the last 4 years makes me sick. Wealthy didn't take a cent out my bank account, I have no right to take away from his. Is that so complicated? This country was never stronger at the times it took its primary responsibility to preserve what founders have given to us. It makes it weak and disrespected when main focus is shifted elsewhere.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362863233162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 16:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362863766824-25</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Do your best and let God do the rest.” “Happiness doesn't result from what we get, but from what we give.” “Success is determined not by whether or not you face obstacles, but by your reaction to them. And if you look at these obstacles as a containing fence, they become your excuse for failure. If you look at them as a hurdle, each one strengthens you for the next.” ― Ben Carson</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362863766824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 16:16:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362866924905-26</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican, you seem really evil. how did you get that way? evil and dumb, but the 2 are related. the fact is people above $35K ARE taxed progessively higher rates than those making less, same for those making $135k........ but the special rich and wealthy ARE NOT........ right now the guy making $ 450 million pays the same rate as the one making $45 million or $4.5 million or $450K... no progressivity..............and it is a disgrace, a shameless disgrace. and of course, only a rotten low life and evil and warped person such as yourself quotes the bible in regard to lowering tax rates for the super rich and powerful and giving them special treatment over everyone else.... Progressivly higer rates should not stop just because someone makes $100s of millions a year... progressive taxation is as it should be , the more you benefit from our great nation, the higher the rate of tax that should be paid. ""The subjects of every state ought to contribute towards the support of the government, as nearly as possible, in proportion to their respective abilities; that is, in proportion to the revenue which they respectively enjoy under the protection of the state." adam smith</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362866924905</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:08:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362867068933-27</Id><Topic><Title>GOP internecine warfare</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362862295025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 15:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>soon, the gop /tea will start up a new "mccain has a black love child" smear.....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362867068933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 17:11:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362876271088-28</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So yes, you do think we will be a better\stronger nation if this wealth gap continues? and given that video, can you still claim we are at risk of becoming a socialist nation? Really?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362876271088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 19:44:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362884423589-29</Id><Topic><Title>etfc</Title><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1362836603440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 08:43:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i see a big spike on friday shortly after the open. they made sure that sold off in a hurry. was it becase of petelli news?</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362884423589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 22:00:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362885643538-30</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you think by repeating same question again you can get a different answer? It's'not the fact that we have very wealthy people in this country that makes it capitalistic, it may as well be so. But it's the common view that there is something wrong with this picture that makes you think capitalism is in danger.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362885643538</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 22:20:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362886458377-31</Id><Topic><Title>Go to yahoo and type in "Wealth Inequality in America "</Title><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362813569806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 02:19:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"giving them special treatment over everyone else"? You mean taxing wealthy 15-20% corporate tax vs 50% of income earners paying virtually 0%? Very special!!!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362886458377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 22:34:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362888278808-32</Id><Title>We Won't Live Long Enough to See Another Pub President.</Title><Msg>Fact.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1362888278808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 23:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362890358367-33</Id><Topic><Title>We Won't Live Long Enough to See Another Pub President.</Title><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1362888278808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 23:04:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why cut your life short? It's not worth it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362890358367</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-09 23:39:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>