<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367688504650-1</Id><Topic><Title>Volume is very subdued today</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367512152880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it's a bit of a dangerous way to trade though unless you see a tipping point in the near future and can't nail the timing down well enough for shorter term options. If you're a couple weeks off on a monthly purchase you've lost it all, but if you buy for next January or even the max LEAP period you generally only lose the time value between the delay and the stock price rise. I rode that formula to success using VERY small investments in Apple of my "next computer fund" to jack up my equity to the point where when I came time to buy I was purchasing high end Mac Pro units instead of iMac's (though there was that year of the Mac Mini, but I'd prefer to forget it, it was punishment, not a reward. The things been sitting in the lab spin-locked for like almost two years now). My problems with options almost always involve timing. So I've largely changed my strategy to buying on margin during serious dips then working my way out of the margin debt when it appears the market will go stale. Then I saw how much I was paying for using their money and laughed. I'm making more on "side bet" trades than I'm paying interest on margin, so I'm not feeling the hate. Still, this thing better pop up soon, there's nothing I hate worse than dead money, and if this fish don't start to learn to swim in a few years, I'm gonna think about returning him to the pet store which, in a bit of twisted irony, he runs.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367688504650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 13:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367688872268-2</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat logic</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367598596906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The under 26 rule I believe only applies if the child is enrolled at an accredited post secondary education program and/or was recently discharged from the military. There may be other caveats. Further it's not that at 15 you're an adult, it's that the decision to take this is, by any rational measure, not one that effects anyone but the person for whom the purchase was made. It works in SUCH a narrow windows after (or sometimes before) conception to prevent wall implantation. In other words what follows is an essentially normal period. Decided to do THAT rather than raising a child while trying to go to high school and add that to all the other teenage stresses and frankly despite the fact that I disagree with actual abortion, I'd rather my daughter take this pill than take a chance on pregnancy that will significantly curtail her future options when they should be wide open.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367688872268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 13:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367689207559-3</Id><Topic><Title>Volume is very subdued today</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367512152880</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 12:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I started using options because they usually cost about 10% of the value. Stocks like ETFC can lose 20% in a few days. I look at it as a way to save money while being able to obtain a good quantity of shares.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367689207559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 13:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367695238494-4</Id><Topic><Title>FORECAST: In 20 Years E-Trade Is The Worlds Largest Bank!</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1367521094828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 14:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like you're pretty savvy about the markets, and about your trades. Good job! But I've see bull markets where a .05 cent contract, on the call side, (that's $5.00), went all the way up to $95.00! So that's really $9500.00 for one contract. Imagine that! And this type of action wasn't really all that rare in an all out bull market. The problem with these trades is that markets can't be timed. So most people trade out of a position well before the big money. Just like buying straight stock itself. For example SIRI was all the way down to five cents per share in like 2008 or 2009 but now is at around $3.25. Imagine having bought $10,000 worth in like 2005 and having later sold at five cents on fear that you'd end up with nothing? This is what most investors end up doing and they will only return to the stock market at the very top again only to see their money vanish all over again. LOL. The point is that markets change, and that bull and bear cycles do happen. I'm only guessing about the 10 year bull cycle thing but my guess is a little bit better than the average persons guess as I'm still making money after 15 years, and having been a student of market cycles for almost 35 years. Happy investing to you, and may the BIG pay-outs come your way!</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1367695238494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367695724959-5</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cigi_fubar Cummunists are socialists? Since when and where?</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1367695724959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 15:28:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367697994411-6</Id><Topic><Title>Democrat logic</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367598596906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-03 12:29:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have made it clear from my point of view that the morning after pill is the best crime prevention measure the Democrats have come up with. I was just pointing out the lengths in which the Democrats will go to try and fool the willing folks with double speak. The more slings and arrows (name calling and personal attacks) one receives from posters on this board, one becomes convinced they are making their point.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367697994411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367698740431-7</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Further he CAN'T unilaterally change who can and can't stay in this country** I would only point to his attempt to enact parts of the "Dream act" through executive order. He clearly over stepped his authority.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367698740431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367699735118-8</Id><Title>Gov. Moonbeam cleans up the GOP mess</Title><Msg>California tax revenue yields multibillion-dollar surplus Source: LA Times California has been flooded with revenue this tax season and is on track to finish the fiscal year with a surplus of billions of dollars, according to officials. State coffers contain about $4.5 billion more than expected in personal income tax payments. Nearly $2.8 billion of it arrived April 17, the third-highest single-day collection in California history, according to government figures. Business taxes have also rebounded and are likely to be $200 million ahead of projections. Gov. Jerry Brown will reveal his latest spending plans this month. State law may require much of the surplus to go to schools and community colleges.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367699735118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:35:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367700748236-9</Id><Title>Reversing the GOP assault on democracy</Title><Msg>TALLAHASSEE, Florida (Reuters) - Still smarting from jokes about Florida's inability to run statewide elections, Florida lawmakers approved a package of revisions on Friday to give voters more time and locations to cast their ballots. Reuters "We all took a lot of flak for elections last year," said Senator Jack Latvala, a Republican who chairs the Senate Ethics and Elections Committee. "We were the butt of jokes on late night TV." Senate Minority Leader Chris Smith, a Democrat, said the package was an improvement over restrictions imposed in 2011, when the number of days polls were open for voting prior to November's Election Day was drastically reduced, but he said there was still a long way to go. "This is only a start," he said. "We had a tremendous opportunity to do great things with this bill, but we stopped well short of the goal posts." The bill, which Republican Governor Rick Scott has said he would sign, allows county elections supervisors to increase the number of early voting days to 14 from eight. To reduce waiting time at courthouses and election offices, they could also use more and larger sites for popular early voting, such as civic centers. "This reform was essential for the people of Florida and the Legislature is to be congratulated for this bipartisan collaboration," said Deirdre Macnab, president of the League of Women Voters of Florida, which lobbied for reforms.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367700748236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367703273655-10</Id><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Msg>Obama is swinging smooth as glass and has his putting game going!!!!</Msg><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367715348612-11</Id><Title>Job creation</Title><Msg>Job Creation of record of post-WWII Presidents With Completed Terms, Plus Kennedy, Average Annual % Increases : (Sorted from best to worst by average annual percentage increase in jobs. Republicans in red, Democrats in blue. Notice that -- with the tiny exception (0.02% difference) of Nixon to Kennedy -- the worst Democrat has a better record than the best Republican). And actually, Kennedy did not have a chance to complete his term -- had he done so, and had he had the same job creation numbers in December 1963 through January 1965 as Johnson had (a 3.48%/year annualized rate of increase), he would have easily topped Nixon. President ----- Jobs % increase Johnson----4.12% Carter-----3.2% Truman---2.71 Clinton----2.59 Nixon----2.37 Kennedy----2.35 Reagan----2.21 Ford ----1.09 Eisenhower ----o.88% G.H. Bush---- o.60% G.W. Bush------o.10% The average annual % increase in jobs is a much fairer way to compare presidents than just the raw job creation figures in thousands because the latter is unfair to the earlier presidents who were working with much smaller labor forces to begin with. For example the number of job holders at the beginning of Truman's administration was only 38% as many as at the beginning of Clinton's administration, and 31% as many as at the beginning of G.W. Bush's administration. So Truman's pathetic-looking 93,570 jobs/month creation record turns out to be even better than Clinton's 236,875 jobs/month record when adjusted for the size of the labor force. In raw thousands of jobs created, both Reagan and Nixon beat Truman. But when adjusted for the size of the labor force -- again, by looking at average annual percentage increases in jobs -- Truman beats them both.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1367715348612</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 20:55:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>