<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365314010171-1</Id><Topic><Title>Gunfail 12</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365268544222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 13:15:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glocks and all striker fired pistols without mechanical disconnect/interrupter bar safeties are a freaking hazard. I have one as a NATO ammo firing standard sidearm, but mine is the military model which makes no pretense of safety (and among the Glock models is the only one without a magazine safety) and is primarily for battlefield use. The firearm I CARRY has an interrupter safety, an actual switch which has to be pushed down before the weapon can be fired. With a Glock that has a round in the chamber ANYTHING that can engage the trigger within the trigger guard can fire the weapon. Consequently I would NEVER, even on a typical battlefield (on which a pistol is virtually useless anyway), put a round into the chamber unless I intend to use the weapon in the IMMEDIATE future. They just aren't safe. I frankly can't imagine how they became one of the most popular handguns in the world save that without all those safeties even a low grade moron can figure out how to get it to fire regularly. Someone not trained well enough to disengage their safeties before attempting to fire probably isn't trained well enough to be carrying anyway.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365314010171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 01:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365318823252-2</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Half truths, as usual. March 7, 2003: UNMOVIC Executive Chairman Hans Blix tells the Security Council that Iraq's cooperation with the inspectors in providing information about past weapons activities has improved, although Baghdad has not yet complied with its disarmament obligations. UNMOVIC and IAEA inspectors had stated during briefings to the Security Council on January 27 and February 14 that Iraq was gradually increasing its cooperation with the United Nations. Yet, both deemed the cooperation insufficient. After 3 months of inspections - INSUFFICIENT!!! Yes, Saddam did kick off weapon inspectors in December 1998 and would not allow them to get in until UN res. 1441 Nov. 8, 2002. Saddam used chemical weapons on his own people, yet never showed how and where they were destroyed. This fact was major reason of mistrust and lead to conclusion he never destroyed anything. I can provide a long list of prominent Democrats who were just as adamant as Bush to disarm Saddam up until decision to invade Iraq. The only name that is missing there is Obama. He was busy agitating streets of Chicago at the time. He is the only one who was against invasion. Why? He had no price to pay for being wrong. A backbancher.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365318823252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 03:13:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365338819838-3</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nope YOU report BS spin and lies from the BS media.... Blix stated at the time and afterward that Bush was wrong to remove the inspectors and he lied about it as well, Bush is the one who removed them and he did so because they reported in jan 2003 that Iraq had no wmd so far, that Iraq was cooperating . Blix requested more time to complete the inspection... bush denied them, bush kicked them out, he did not want the truth out : that there were NO WMD..... so Bush stopped the inspections and charged in with his illegal and immoral invasion as per the Pope... or "brain fart" as per fmr US Marine Corps Commandant and mid east expert General Zinni.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365338819838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 08:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365339975361-4</Id><Title>typcial gop tax plan: cut taxes for the rich, raise them on the poor</Title><Msg>Texas's Tax Code: Poor Pay More Who Pays? found that: •Texas families earning less than $18,000—the poorest fifth of Texas non-elderly taxpayers—pay 12.2 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes. •Middle-income Texas taxpayers—those earning between $31,000 and $51,000—pay 8.5 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes. •But the richest Texas taxpayers—with incomes exceeding $463,000 per year—pay only 3.3 percent of their income in Texas state and local taxes Louisiana Governor Jindal's popularity slumps after bold tax plan NEW ORLEANS (Reuters) - Louisiana Governor Bobby Jindal, one of the nation's most prominent Republicans and a possible 2016 presidential candidate, has fallen out of favor with local voters, and his bold plan to scrap the state income tax is running into trouble. Jindal was re-elected to a second term with two-thirds of the vote in 2011. But his Louisiana approval rating was down to 38 percent in a recent poll, worse than Democratic President Barack Obama in one of the most conservative states. The poll suggested voters think he is spending more time traveling outside the state and burnishing his credentials for a possible White House run than tending to local matters. As the Louisiana Legislature prepares to kick off its two-month session on Monday, Jindal's signature proposal to eliminate the state income tax is facing resistance. His detailed plan would do away with all state personal and corporate income taxes. It also calls for a 56-percent increase in the state sales tax, a much higher cigarette tax, and the elimination of some tax loopholes to make up the $3 billion shortfall from scrapping the income taxes</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365339975361</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365341535712-5</Id><Title>Say No to Obama using chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Msg>chained cpi is just plain baloney</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365341535712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365348446942-6</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obama using chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365341535712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a doosh aint he? He needs to start with cuts in programs that give free handouts to those who never have or never will work for it -- force some of them to get jobs -- then go from there. Don't he? You'd be surprised what a hungry belly can all of the sudden do for one's work seeking motivation.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1365348446942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365349235451-7</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obama using chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365341535712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you miss it that walmart workers are among the biggest users of food stamps and Medicaid? This is another example of your type whining about people demanding a livable wage , and also whining when they have to use food stamps because they don't get paid a livable wage.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365349235451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365350014088-8</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obama using chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365341535712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah but I aint the one destroying the dollar causing food and fuel prices to rise while pilfering old people's savings either.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1365350014088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365350308271-9</Id><Title>Say No to Obamascare Slavery Chain</Title><Msg>1- Stop it now. 2- Stop it now. 3- Stop it now.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365350308271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:58:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365350627469-10</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obama using chained cpi to cut social security</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365341535712</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 09:32:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what a liar you are! the US dollar compared to the Euro is the same now as it was in 2007... and inflation is low as well...... you are totally full of shizer.( and fyi the gop wants to cut social security far MORE than the small hit of using the chained cpi, so you even lie about that.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365350627469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365350841549-11</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obamascare Slavery Chain</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365350308271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure, Romneycare, er obamacare is slavery. what a twit and brat you are. is your name Reince Priebus or grover norquist? I think you need your diapers changed.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365350841549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365353160504-12</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're ignorant fool. Kofi Annan withdrew UN weapons inspectors from Iraq following Bush administration decision to use military force. US had no power over UN workers. They could stay if they wanted, under fire! It was Saddam who kicked inspectors off in 1998. Clinton bombed Baghdad for a week after that. 3 years later, alter numerous UN resolutions and threat of force Saddam finally agrees to let inspectors back. He didn't show a single site where chemicals were destroyed. 3 months of fooling around UN inspectors wasn't enough for that?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365353160504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365353230626-13</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obamascare Slavery Chain</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365350308271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are members of "the stupid party" They prove it daily.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365353230626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 12:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365355176896-14</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUSH LIED: Bush said: “The larger point is, and the fundamental question is, did Saddam Hussein have a weapons program? And the answer is, absolutely. And we gave him a chance to allow the inspectors in, and he wouldn’t let them in" that is a bald-faced lie. the inspectors were there, they reported a month before the invasion that Iraq was cooperating and they requested more time to complete the job. what was the hurry? was saddam going to nuke the usa.......jeez,, pacifican... you are just pathetic. Set on invading, Bush forced the U.N. inspectors to wrap up their work and to leave Iraq in March 2003, a departure that was followed within days by his “shock and awe” attack on Iraq, beginning March 19. and YOU liar and moron...... Kofi Annan said the BUSH invasion was ILLEGAL and he removed the inspectors because BUSH was going to invade despite failing to get UN approval for the ILLEGAL invasion. here is the sequence of events: After failing to secure U.N. authorization to use force to disarm Iraq, President Bush gave Saddam 48 hours to step down or face war in a speech Monday night U.N. Secretary-General Kofi Annan on Monday ordered all U.N. inspectors and support staff, humanitarian workers and U.N. observers along the Iraq-Kuwait border to evacuate Iraq after U.S. threats to launch war. .</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365355176896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 13:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365362544522-15</Id><Title>Benghazi Mom Threatened by Dumbo</Title><Msg>Whitehouse thug demanding she shut up or ELSE!! What do you expect form a piece of #$%$, heartless Facist #$%$ like Dumbo! heh, Liberals, Keep sticking up for your Stupid, Evil Dumbo! Your all the same!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365362544522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:22:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365364642230-16</Id><Topic><Title>The police will not protect your family</Title><Username>darwinvoyagebeagerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365200700134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 18:25:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not the job of the police to "protect" your family. It's their job to maintain public order and to collect evidence for the Prosecutor, detain and guard suspects, and that's it, the total limit of their mandate. Pretending otherwise, that the police are there to "protect and serve" is a misconception that is born of those few local police and Sheriffs offices that do more than that for their communities.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365364642230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:57:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365364804478-17</Id><Topic><Title>How long will it take........</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365269792841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 13:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We have a nuclear bomber penetration task force at DG where its about the same flight time to either Iran or North Korea. AFAIK their bomb bays are already full of standoff land attack missiles. WITH W-65 warheads.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365364804478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 16:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365365680882-18</Id><Topic><Title>N-KOREA!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365109383648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:03:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In case you missed the news it was North Korea that nullified the cease fire, not the UN/US . . . you know, everyone BUT North Korea, which constitutes "the other side". The Chinese might have helped North Korea once when the risk was small and contained, and there was some degree of fellowship, but even the Chinese are getting totally sick of North Korea and would probably approve of giving it a good spanking right about now, as long as we didn't hang around. The subsequent economic disaster in the North would give them reason to send "humanitarian" support and pull the North back into their sphere of influence. Yes, I think we could EASILY work out a deal with China to remove Kim the Turd.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365365680882</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 16:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365370617477-19</Id><Topic><Title>Say No to Obamascare Slavery Chain</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365350308271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 11:58:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does your mother know that you are name calling again?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365370617477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 17:36:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365383021995-20</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"the inspectors" he was speaking of were US inspectors, not UN inspectors. We had reason to believe that the UN inspection process was being compromised. Admittedly it came from false intelligence generated by Saddam's intelligence organs themselves, but there it was. Saddam was dancing a deadly dance, trying on one hand to convince his neighbors he had such weapons, so he would feel secure from attack or revolt, and on the other hand trying to convince us he didn't so he'd be free from sanctions and bombing raids. I don't suppose he ever imagined that his ruse would not only convince George Bush, but also cause him to launch a major ground offensive. Further, bizarrely enough, he believed he could WIN against this offensive using a strategy that a second year Academy cadet would find repulsively stupid. You want to know who caused the Iraq war, look right to the main instigator, Saddam himself.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365383021995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 21:03:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365389247344-21</Id><Title>Repubs Cave on Illegal Immigration !</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.) said Sunday that the Republican Party as a whole has abandoned its opposition to allowing a pathway for citizenship for undocumented immigrants. "................ I think the best solution is for Pubs to self deport to a small govt country. Somalia is the Pubby Ideal.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365389247344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365389259852-22</Id><Topic><Title>N-KOREA!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365109383648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:03:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rowdy, when are you going to wise up??? The only reason why Pubs receive more thumbs up or thumbs down is because there are more Pubs participating in this board. Besides, Pubs will never admit to the truth in a Dems post. rowdy, grow up and act like an adault, or better yet keep on clowning. rowdy, Warum bist Du so a Depp? rowdy, slayer is looking for a roomate - don't let him wait too long cause them homos can get very rowdy.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1365389259852</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>