<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-16"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363409795008-1</Id><Topic><Title>Oh yeah, that's fair and balanced!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363394591187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone offered him the "buck stops here" sign, but he was afraid Ted Nugent would start leaving deer heads on his desk.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363409795008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 00:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363411816708-2</Id><Topic><Title>The Ryan Plan: Cutting Benefits For Poor Women To Protect Millionaires</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363357690294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:28:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well I will need to look into this more. The last time you quoted the CBO, you ended up looking like and a--. You quoted the worse case scenario as a fact, when there was also given a most probable prediction. Remember...yeah of course you do.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1363411816708</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 01:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363413641324-3</Id><Title>Citadel</Title><Msg>I am personally happy Ken and Citadel company are out of E*Trade.</Msg><Username>jeffreyali1202</Username><Timestamp>1363413641324</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 02:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363421119499-4</Id><Topic><Title>The Ryan Plan: Cutting Benefits For Poor Women To Protect Millionaires</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363357690294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:28:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I quoted from article about GAO report. Not from CBO, and not from direct source as I did now. I can't refer to the report itself. Here is GAO conclusion I took from National Review: "The baseline scenario is far more optimistic, largely because it does not take into account the concerns — expressed by the Congressional Budget Office (CBO), the Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services (CMS) Trustees, and Medicare’s chief actuary — about “whether certain cost-containment mechanisms included in PPACA can be sustained over the long term.” However, the GAO report concluded that even under these “more optimistic assumptions,” Obamacare’s cost-control provisions “were not sufficient to prevent an unsustainable increase in debt held by the public.” The alternative scenario, which incorporates the more realistic “alternative projections” suggested by CBO, the CMS trustees, and the chief Medicare actuary, is even more dire. Under this scenario, the “primary deficit” increases by 0.7 percent of GDP over the 75-year period. The GAO does not put a dollar value on that figure, but Senate Budget Committee staff has calculated, and GAO has confirmed, that it would amount to a $6.2 trillion increase in the federal deficit. " The most rosy scenario presumes that "cost-containment mechanisms included in PPACA can be sustained over the long term". Apparently, CBO and CMS have serious concerns about that. Now read careful. Alternative scenario is suggested by... CBO and CMS trustees. So, please, note, both scenarios will add to deficit. Just for the rosy one GAO didn't provide exact figure. You, on the other hand, presented it as unlikely scenario. Wonder which source gave you this assurance.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363421119499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 04:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363422961334-5</Id><Title>Did Citigroup purchase 27 million ETFC shares for $11.28 per share?</Title><Msg>The SEC filings appear to indicate shares sold for $11.28 per share. Will Citigroup make a tender offer for the rest of the company? Do they have retail brokerage?</Msg><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1363422961334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 04:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363434317651-6</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES ETFC</Title><Username>browndrake513</Username><Timestamp>1363270784976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 10:19:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cool one</Msg><Username>albertogonzales1486</Username><Timestamp>1363434317651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 07:45:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363445612287-7</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Rob Portman comes out in favor of gay marriage after son comes out as gay</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363358751602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other People’s Children by Paul Krugman at the NY Times Matthew Yglesias beats me to a point I was planning to make. Sen. Rob Portman has made headlines by declaring his support for gay marriage after learning that his own son is gay, and apparently we’re supposed to praise him for his new enlightenment. But while enlightenment is good, wouldn’t it have been a lot more praiseworthy if he had shown some flexibility on the issue before he knew that his own family would benefit? I’ve noticed this thing quite a lot in American life lately — this sort of cramped vision of altruism in which it’s considered perfectly acceptable to support only those causes that are directly good for you and yours. We even have a tendency to view it as “inauthentic” when people support policies that aren’t in their self-interest — when a rich man supports higher taxes on the rich, he’s somehow seen as strange, and probably a hypocrite. Needless to say, this is all wrong. Political virtue consists in standing for what’s right, even — or indeed especially — when it doesn’t redound to your own benefit. Someone should ask Portman why he didn’t take a stand for, you know, other people’s children.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363445612287</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 10:53:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363448522005-8</Id><Topic><Title>27.4 Million Shares are Sold.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1363381805544</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 17:10:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep. Hard to play that "hedging game" without the inside info Citadel was getting. Kenny boy put on quite a show in public with his rants about selling the company. He made 800 million on this deal, I wonder how much of that was your money elvis? Go to Hawaii and get it back!</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1363448522005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363455216512-9</Id><Topic><Title>Oh yeah, that's fair and balanced!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363394591187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 20:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This boy is a teenager for Pete's sake. He is a high school student with his conservative world views and moral standards. What did he do wrong? Are you trying to make him a Washington political hack? What morons!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363455216512</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363455731355-10</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Rob Portman comes out in favor of gay marriage after son comes out as gay</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363358751602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ Cheney hated gays until he found out he has one. It's the typical Repugnican view. Screw everybody, until the problem is yours. Socialism is good if it helps a Pugnican.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1363455731355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 13:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363462550526-11</Id><Title>CEMENT FLOOR at $10 Do not sell etfc.</Title><Msg>CEMENT FLOOR at $10 and ETFC will not trade lower than that. Do not sell etfc, because there will be a rebound from 10 to 11.20 -11.30 imho Do you agree with me that this is the time to buy ETFC shares? Rebound</Msg><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1363462550526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363462940803-12</Id><Topic><Title>Sen. Rob Portman comes out in favor of gay marriage after son comes out as gay</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363358751602</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:45:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rob Portman's "change of heart" makes him nothing more than political tool. I don't see Cheney as an activist for changing definition of marriage. You drag his name here in vain. What bunch of yours don't accept is that definition of marriage is thousands years old. What you're trying to do is to throw in the garbage a long standing concept still strongly engraved in the minds of at least half of the population in favor of relatively small group of people. in a free country like ours people can choose their own lifestyle, and what's important, having same rights as others(married heterosexuals). But, don't touch the definition, it offends huge category of our population! Changing this definition is not an act of socialism, it is an act of totalitarianism.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363462940803</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473095718-13</Id><Topic><Title>Another win for ACORN</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363101289881</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 11:14:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw interviews with at least 3 (possibly more) different ACORN offices. Do you think they'd have lost their funding for the acts of ONE rogue office staffer? Suggest you do a bit of reading . . . Although all Catholic Priests aren't kiddy diddlers the entire church was punished for keeping it quiet, and US military members DO include murderers of innocents, rapists, and torturers, in case you haven't noticed. It' just that the military, unlike ACORN or the Catholics generally discipline their own without requiring a huge media outcry first. And where was the 'you say "I don't recall" ....' Funny because I never said "I don't recall" in the text you're replying too. Perhaps you fell back on criticizing my original reply to your babble since your previous reply, shattered by the unstoppable march of logic is no longer useful, or perhaps you're just reaching, but it's not NECESSARY that I recall EVERY news story I read on ACORN at the time, it's only necessary in your argument for you to FORGET all but one. Unfortunately Yahoo doesn't allow the posting of URL's or I could show you, but I guess if you really want to know you'll have to actually learn how to use Google on your own. You might want to look up "bigot" there, reread this thread, and reconsider your placement of the word. You can make it part of your ID and it'd fit no tighter.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363473095718</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:31:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473200535-14</Id><Topic><Title>Did Citigroup purchase 27 million ETFC shares for $11.28 per share?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1363422961334</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 04:36:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Citibank funded a private offering for the shares among their investment clients. If the shares went on the market from there it's because those customers sold them themselves. Citi might have kept a small bit for their own funds, but I doubt they kept more than a fraction of what they brokered out.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363473200535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473424390-15</Id><Topic><Title>The Ryan Plan: Cutting Benefits For Poor Women To Protect Millionaires</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363357690294</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 10:28:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SS is trust fund. It must provide for itself. There is no authority to take away money from it without special legislation. Paying for war in Iraq with SS money is a product of your imagination. Or otherwise called political schtick. When this president at the approval of Democrat House cut 2% from payroll tax, that was a true SS robbery. House of Republicans agreed with president to extend this robbery for another 2 years because House GOP lost its core principles. Still, the idea was originated and implemented first by the other party. Write that on your forehead: funds to pay for Iraq war were not borrowed from SS funds. This president in just 4 years accumulated $6T in debt. 40% increase! That wasn't borrowed from SS either, but from future generations of taxpayers. Was that for the right purpose at least? I have my reservations.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363473424390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473801909-16</Id><Topic><Title>apparently pubs think "right of the people to keep and bear arms" means you have a right to a tank or a nuke or any 'arms' whatsoever</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363299153841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grandfathered in means they continue to exist in civilian hands and can be transferred from owner to owner, thus machineguns are NOT illegal, just restricted. Further owners of registered conversion devices (e.g. M-16 AutoSears, HK Trigger Packs, FN/FNC sear groups, etc) can move them from semi-auto receiver to semi-auto receiver at will, thus making one semi-auto conversion device mountable in a number of host devices. I love the way you say "your usual dishonesty". Do you need photographs? Further this last act may, OR MAY NOT, be Constitutional, it's never been challenged, and the NFA itself has never been challenged on a Constitutional basis. It's likely that given the restrictions added in the 1980's as well as the original phrasing of the law would result in it being found unconstitutional since it was based on the Governments ability to gather REVENUE, and the net revenue gathered from licenses is a PITTANCE compared to what it takes to regulate them. be it a Form 1,3, or 4 transfer or licensing of gun dealers or licensing of manufacturers. the money gained from ALL by state sales tax isn't meaningful. Now how do you claim that's anything but undo infringement if the ONLY reason for the taxation is an excuse to open the door for regulation? Tell you what ditzydirtscraper, if you think such weapons are so restricted, will you pay for all that I can buy, in, say, a week? I'll pay the $200 transfer taxes, you just have to pony up for the weapons themselves? Afterall, if you're right you won't have to pay a dime!</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363473801909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363473909956-17</Id><Topic><Title>apparently pubs think "right of the people to keep and bear arms" means you have a right to a tank or a nuke or any 'arms' whatsoever</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363299153841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has taught has that community organizer's who've never held a job in the real world or bother to voice an opinion on the record before the election are extremely electable.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363473909956</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:45:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363475561904-18</Id><Topic><Title>apparently pubs think "right of the people to keep and bear arms" means you have a right to a tank or a nuke or any 'arms' whatsoever</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363299153841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pubs don't think. They have Rush to do that for them.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1363475561904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 19:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363479896063-19</Id><Topic><Title>apparently pubs think "right of the people to keep and bear arms" means you have a right to a tank or a nuke or any 'arms' whatsoever</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363299153841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally unprovoked he opened fire on an FBI attack dog and killed it. That means the dog was most likely within 25 yards (typical combat shotgun range) or 25 feet (to kill a German Shepard with birdshot), and most likely approaching based on their report. Since most shotguns with a tube not plugged for migratory waterfowl (maximum capacity 3 shells) can carry 5 or more rounds loaded at once, I would guess that the guy unloaded on the snarly attack dog coming at him and was, as they already said, immediately cut down despite never having fired at an actual officer. It's typical FBI policy to NOT turn dogs loose on a fleeing suspect who cannot escape as many folks are more afraid of the dog than the police. Sounds like he was going to surrender, and the FBI couldn't have that happening, so they set the dog on him, creating the incident they needed. Certainly dogs would never normally be used on a suspect barricaded in a building. Kinda smart of them, they loose a dog compared to the possibility of loosing an officer and now no one will CARE why he did what he did, if there was any reason at all other than plain craziness.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1363479896063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 20:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363482947108-20</Id><Topic><Title>apparently pubs think "right of the people to keep and bear arms" means you have a right to a tank or a nuke or any 'arms' whatsoever</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363299153841</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-14 18:12:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have much to show for that? Can you prove your IQ is higher than room temperature? Nah. Never mind. A monkey can do better than you.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363482947108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 21:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363490658082-21</Id><Topic><Title>CEMENT FLOOR at $10 Do not sell etfc.</Title><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1363462550526</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 15:35:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well if the news out of Cyprus is true, 10 might not be the floor after all. They voting on whether to make DEPOSITORS take a 9.9% haircut, (6.7% if under 100k euros). That is a slippery slope indeed.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1363490658082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:24:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>