<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-01"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367381579710-1</Id><Title>Paul Ryan Caves on Gays !</Title><Msg>You can't find a straight Republican any more ! Rep. Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) said Monday during a town hall event in Janesville, Wis., that he has changed his position on gay couples adopting children, WKOW reports. An audience member at the event asked Ryan why he doesn't support same-sex marriage. Ryan said that while he continues to believe marriage should only be between a man and a woman, he now regrets voting in 1999 to ban same-sex couples in the District of Columbia from adopting children. Heck, their last Prez nominee had gay prancing horses. You can't get any gayer than Mittens !!!!!</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1367381579710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367383790845-2</Id><Topic><Title>Paul Ryan Caves on Gays !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1367381579710</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK. Lets start talking about "caving on Gays". Anyone who set the caving record? Look no further than... Barack. He was for gay marriage before he was against it and than yet for it again. Those Republicans are falling far behind in changing hearts on the issue. After all, this is going to be the most important issue after this country falls into financial black hole.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367383790845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 00:49:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367392405471-3</Id><Title>President Pantywaist Considering Sanctions Against Syria</Title><Msg>If all diplomacy fails, he may ban imports of camel paddies or whatever the heck Syria makes. But don't count on it.</Msg><Username>mark355tysnn</Username><Timestamp>1367392405471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 03:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367410943319-4</Id><Title>Website down again?</Title><Msg>was on,now it's down at 8.22 et</Msg><Username>jimmiller735</Username><Timestamp>1367410943319</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:22:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367412890779-5</Id><Topic><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>etfc could have made a bigger profit for the investors if they didn't keep paying no talent hires that are replaced every couple years !!I wonder who gets the kick backs? But making a profit for investors it seems has never been a goal of over paid management!!!!!IMHO vote them out</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1367412890779</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367413123778-6</Id><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Msg>like they have some knowledge of the matter. it is funny to watch them try and defend topics they didn't have the capacity to understand in school. i particularly like watching a "journalist" attempt to make a scientific argument.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367415806274-7</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>heck, even uneducated louts like you argue about science. and oddly enough, there are liberal arts grads who have won the nobel price for science: Harold Varmus, American Nobel Prize -winning scientist and the 14th and current Director of the National Cancer Institute Varmus holds a B.A. in English literature and a graduate degree in English before entering medical school. Steve Jobs, who was neither a computer programmer nor a hardware engineer, famously told graduates of Stanford University in 2005 that one of the most influential and lasting experiences in his brief tenure at Reed College was his dabbling in calligraphy.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367415806274</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416041582-8</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>case in point - lucky there isn't a topic in the world that he won't try to convince you of his viewpoint. he's a legend in his own mind on all matters.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367416041582</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:47:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416051005-9</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, you always have Rush. Who tells you all you need to know.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367416051005</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367416488374-10</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why your catty whining and judgement about academic degrees.? most likely you disagree with the current consensus of real, professional climate scientists, don't you?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367416488374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 09:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367417105313-11</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>climate scientist. might as well be an alchemist. but you go lucky - you understand this complicated mathematical model and how to control it - correct? pass some laws - change some behaviours - and what happens exactly? i mean exactly what happens? please be very specific. you #$%$ dolt.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367417105313</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:05:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367417426917-12</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go..... I suppose you also deny the chemistry of combustion...being worried about "how to control it - correct? pass some laws - change some behaviours " as you put it....and etc........ you sure are a laugh...... in your mind politics trumps science anyway......but do note that gop science includes dinosaurs on Noah's ark and women's bodies that can repel a rapists sperm.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367417426917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367417972380-13</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it seems logical to throw water on a grease fire - until you do it. lucky subscribes to the "turn the knobs" control theory. lets just start turning knobs on stuff we don't undrerstand and hope it behaves how we want. and since we only have certain knobs to turn - let's turn them. you'd be the first one lining up to sacrifice a goat - if your climate scientist told you to do so. hehehe</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367417972380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418110660-14</Id><Topic><Title>New President Hired at Etrade....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1367355408624</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 16:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like they use this continual hiring and firing to milk the investors instead of making money for investors. I wonder who gets the kick backs? no one they hire ever makes a difference except draining the bank!!!! This is a true pos!!IMHO where are the profits? going to bowling buddies?</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1367418110660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418184778-15</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elvis, we can measure the seas and photograph the glaciers. If the latter are melting faster than recorded history, and the seas are rising, what do your scientists say it is ? Has the moon gotten larger ? Is the sun hotter ? You must have an explanation for those two varifiable facts ! ??</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367418184778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367418772134-16</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he dumbsh!!t - what did the pictures look like 100 years ago? 1,000 years ago? 1,000,000 years ago? How do you propose to control a system that you don't understand? That you can't describe? That you can't model? So what exactly do you want to accomplish with those glaciers? make em the same size as they were 50 years ago? are your laws going to make them that size again? is that the right size? does anything that you do have an effect on their size? maybe we should make em the size they were 200 years ago. or maybe make em the size of 1 million years ago. what a joke.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367418772134</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 10:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367421803007-17</Id><Topic><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merrill Lynch and Blackstone are not bad companies to be poaching from for talent. Both seem like good hires and seeing the old crowd go out the door is also good. Upton, Framke, Curcuio, etc needed to go, overpaid and stale.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1367421803007</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:23:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367422233254-18</Id><Topic><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morgan Stanley and Blackrock...Not ML and Blackston....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1367422233254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 11:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367428090965-19</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The first step to better mental health is to eliminate denial. You seem unwilling to do anything ! Except fling slurs at people who disagree with you. You conservatives seem absolutely helpless. Whereas Liberals at least are trying to find solutions.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367428090965</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367428419719-20</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you lefties won't admit is that Obamacare is freezing companies from hiring anyone, skilled or not. Nobody has a clue as how this will turn out. At best total confusion for years, and at worst a train wreck. Be "honest" for once and admit this bill is killing any recovery, not to mention the hit to consumers in additional premiums costs. We can't afford the entitlements we have now, and Obama piles on this unfunded disaster...and now he wants to add pre-school entitlement to millions. We are now 17+ trillion dollars in debt...either Obama is this devious or plain stupid.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367428419719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367429050595-21</Id><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Msg>You liberals are always talking about taking care of folks here at home before investing money overseas, sooo don't you think Obama hometown needs some well needed intervention to stop the mayhem. Oh, that's right their just poor black folks getting dead and shot.... BTW, I don't see the families of these dead people getting a ride on Air Force One like the "white families" did from Newtown....more phony compassion from the left.... 3 dead, 17 wounded in shootings across Chicago overnight Chicago Tribune reporter Adam Sege recaps the night's crimes, including several shootings that left 17 people injured and at least 3 dead. (Posted on: May 1, 2013). At least three people were killed and 17 wounded in shootings across Chicago overnight as the city saw its warmest weather in seven months. In one of the fatal shootings, three men were shot in a parking lot across the street from the headquarters of the UIC Police Department, police said. The shooting happened around 10:40</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367429391436-22</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor old bidder. Still looking for reasons to hate Obama. But Chicago is not the most violent city. Bidder doesn't care. Obama is from Chicago, so bidder hates Chicago. Bidder should spend some time trying to clean up the cesspool he lives in. His city is #1 in violence and foreclosures. I'll bet he has four locks on his trailer door.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367429391436</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367431063519-23</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, Your posts are for the most part hateful. ignorant, distasteful, malicious, and without merit. bidder, Most of your posts blame the President for something when you should concentrate more on politicians, and the Senate and the House. bidder, We don't need any boots on the ground in Syria. Let the Arab League intervene in Syria. We don't want another Iraq. bidder, show us some intelligence in your posts.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1367431063519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432283116-24</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When an urban population has been propagandized for decades ( for largely political reasons) to believe that guns are bad and linked to crime and then they see stories like this one it just tends to reinforce the link. What they need is an early positive experience with firearms to help insure a healthy respect while still eliminating the unreasoning fear.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367432283116</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432575305-25</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, wrong again, pal. Housing industry is picking up big time. Problem is there are no qualified workers to be found to build new houses. During the housing bubble, they left for other industries, but they will be back. Companies are hiring in California again. lucky is is correct - the President deserves credit for the rise in our economy. Things are getting better all over. Problem is bidder can't see it.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1367432575305</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367432786184-26</Id><Topic><Title>President Pantywaist Considering Sanctions Against Syria</Title><Username>mark355tysnn</Username><Timestamp>1367392405471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 03:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we don't need another war like in Iraq.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1367432786184</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 14:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367434949491-27</Id><Topic><Title>Obama loves capitalism hence RECORD corporate profits for 2011,2012 !!!!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367341239084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 13:00:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**No qualified workers to build new houses** Where you doing hard time or freeze dried. How about millions of illegal Mexicans who built the houses during the last boom...last time I looked they are still here. When you said lucky is correct, that all but disqualifies you on most any subject...good grief!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367434949491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367436872029-28</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>** hateful. ignorant, distasteful, malicious, and without merit** I can picture you stomping your feet while typing this silly remarks. What is sad that you liberals just can't admit I am right on this point so you attack the messenger. Same old playbook. How many times do I have to say it to get through your thick heads...you can't point to other bad behavior to justify bad behavior. That is Obama's adopted home town, why doesn't he stop the killing. Why! (rhetorical question)The problem is that you are so invested in the President that you have lost all objectivity, if you ever had any. I don't recall advocating sending troops to Syria, to the contrary I think the administration should stay out of that hornets nest...the time to do something has long past.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367436872029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 15:34:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367438457153-29</Id><Topic><Title>President Pantywaist Considering Sanctions Against Syria</Title><Username>mark355tysnn</Username><Timestamp>1367392405471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 03:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What good would sanctions do? They build they own ammunition, they build their own small arms, they even build a number of more complex systems under license from Russia. What exactly are we going to sanction that won't hit the civilians the worst?? This is the same sort of trap GW Bush allowed himself to get pinned in. As long as he kept sanctions on Iraq Saddam wasn't going to be a major regional threat, but he's going to have to use what hard currency he has to appease those who keep him in power rather than using it to buy goods like medicines, so as a result of those easy implemented "sanctions" the only people suffering weren't who we intended. On top of this we ALSO knew that if we DID life sanctions the ink wouldn't be dry before Saddam was using the income to rearm. That's one reason the WMD threat was peddled so heavy. Most brainless civilians can see an imminent threat even if there isn't one, but very few can see an obscure future threat, much less know what to do about it.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367438457153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367439097198-30</Id><Topic><Title>President Pantywaist Considering Sanctions Against Syria</Title><Username>mark355tysnn</Username><Timestamp>1367392405471</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 03:13:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes, we pubbies can whine and grandstand no matter what Obama does! That we will whine and grandstand is a given, a constant. It was brilliant, our whining about Obama killing OBL! And we whine about drones and we would whine if drones use is ended! Being a republican is an auto-pilot no brainer, we can just kick back and whine our fannies off!!</Msg><Username>investorpelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367439097198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:11:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441183262-31</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us, old ignorant one, why Obama should spend all his time trying to fix Chicago ? What about all the other violent cities ? If Obama did spend his energy there, you'd be blasting him for not being President to all of America. We have your number, maroon. Your number is zero. get a life.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367441183262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:46:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367441888370-32</Id><Topic><Title>Here we go again with the new management !</Title><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1367366565489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-30 20:02:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, all these newbies get sign on bonuses , the terminated get golden parachutes and the shareholders get to pick up the tab!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367441888370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 16:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367442086149-33</Id><Title>Hope this new crop of executives can grow something besides their wallet !!!!</Title><Msg>The others have pretty much set the stage for them. If they can't improve things then they are pretty much another worthless overpaid exec!!!!!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367442086149</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443038243-34</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**What about all the other violent cities ?** Let me put simply so even you can understand. These cities are predominately poor blacks and hispanics, nothing in it politically for him.... You may not like the answer, but that's a fact. Try to reframe from name calling, give it a try!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367443038243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:17:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367443978458-35</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, It is the job of a city police department to fight and stop crime in that city. The President can't be held responsible for crimes commited in a city. Nice try, bidder, but............... bidder, take our advise and concentrate less on the President, because his power is very limited.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1367443978458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 17:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367445648026-36</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anotherloser - we all feel great about you liberal arts types "trying to find solutions" to probems you clearly don't grasp - problems that may not exist. i sleep like a baby knowing that you are on task to address such things. its comforting. sort of like a #$%$ surgeon telling me to lay back on the table and he'll poke around inside and see if he can fix my "aging" process. clearly i'm broken becuase 10 years ago he has a picture of me with my tlts slightly higher on my chest. what a joke you are</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367445648026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 18:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367450431955-37</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Will Argue About Science</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367413123778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 08:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like your brain sleeps like a baby, too.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367450431955</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 19:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367453893642-38</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bidder, You always want to have the last word, but we don't agree with you.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1367453893642</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 20:18:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367461671529-39</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I KNEW bidder would have dark skinned people as his target ! He is consistent in his racial hate. And because Obama is dark, bidder attacks without reason, or intelligence. He doesn't see all the other cities that are worse for crime. He sees only that Obama adopted Chicago. So bidder hates Chicago. Small minds are all that's left of the "Stupid Party".</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367461671529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367461715584-40</Id><Topic><Title>Forget Syria, Chicago needs heavy weapons</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367429050595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 13:24:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidder's last words are like a child's first words.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367461715584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367462857529-41</Id><Title>Right Wing Maroons Say Nothing About Gas Prices</Title><Msg>Shouldn't Obama get credit for bringing prices down ? The "Stupid Party" has plenty to say when prices are up.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367462857529</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-01 22:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>