<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-04"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365074934372-1</Id><Topic><Title>Top Democrat has no clue how a gun operates</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365028623680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Diana probably thought she needed a new Pez dispenser every time she got new Pez.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1365074934372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 07:28:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365078741350-2</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like ETFC Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend...!!</Title><Username>l_stave</Username><Timestamp>1364912273532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:17:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, that would rock!</Msg><Username>lisaphillips522</Username><Timestamp>1365078741350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 08:32:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365081170948-3</Id><Topic><Title>yep, tax cuts for the rich did no good for the economy, they just made the rich richer and everyone else poorer</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364932336604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are such a dolt! fyi, if I say it is true that 2+2=4 , and you disagree, I might bring in someone like you, a jerk conservative republican, who at least can see that 2+2=4 is indeed true in an attempt to convince you of the fact. that does not mean, as you stupidly say, that i'm "relying on opinion' of someone else.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365081170948</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365081932850-4</Id><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Msg>bush &amp; crew spend trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea If only N korea had some oil ,,, then the bush crew might have been interested.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365084537181-5</Id><Title>Fax is fax!!</Title><Msg>Eleven children escaped Newtown classroom while Adam Lanza was reloading (Hartford Courant) "We learned, the way that no other parents should learn, that the most dangerous, dangerous part of an assault weapon is the magazine," Nicole Hockley, whose son Dylan, 6, was killed Dec. 14, said at a press conference with other parents at the Capitol Monday morning. "The horrible, brutal truth is that 154 bullets were fired in four minutes, killing our children, our daughters, our wives. The shooter carried 10, 30-round large-capacity magazines," Hockley said. "We have learned that in the time it took him to reload in one of the classrooms, 11 children were able to escape. We ask ourselves every day — every minute — if those magazines had held 10 rounds, forcing the shooter to reload at least six more times, would our children be alive today?"</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365084537181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:08:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365086978783-6</Id><Topic><Title>yep, tax cuts for the rich did no good for the economy, they just made the rich richer and everyone else poorer</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364932336604</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:52:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan tax cuts brought near 20 million new jobs. That's 2+2=4.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365086978783</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:49:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365087331628-7</Id><Title>Things conservatives rarely mention when talking about President Reagan:</Title><Msg>" 1. Reagan was a serial tax raiser. As governor of California, Reagan “signed into law the largest tax increase in the history of any state up till then.” Meanwhile, state spending nearly doubled. As president, Reagan “raised taxes in seven of his eight years in office,” including four times in just two years. As former GOP Senator Alan Simpson, who called Reagan “a dear friend,” told NPR, “Ronald Reagan raised taxes 11 times in his administration — I was there.” “Reagan was never afraid to raise taxes,” said historian Douglas Brinkley, who edited Reagan’s memoir. Reagan the anti-tax zealot is “false mythology,” Brinkley said. 2. Reagan nearly tripled the federal budget deficit. During the Reagan years, the debt increased to nearly $3 trillion, “roughly three times as much as the first 80 years of the century had done altogether.” Reagan enacted a major tax cut his first year in office and government revenue dropped off precipitously. Despite the conservative myth that tax cuts somehow increase revenue, the government went deeper into debt and Reagan had to raise taxes just a year after he enacted his tax cut. Despite ten more tax hikes on everything from gasoline to corporate income, Reagan was never able to get the deficit under control. 3. Unemployment soared after Reagan’s 1981 tax cuts. Unemployment jumped to 10.8 percent after Reagan enacted his much-touted tax cut, and it took years for the rate to get back down to its previous level. Meanwhile, income inequality exploded. Despite the myth that Reagan presided over an era of unmatched economic boom for all Americans, Reagan disproportionately taxed the poor and middle class, but the economic growth of the 1980′s did little help them. “</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1365087331628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:55:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365087470443-8</Id><Topic><Title>Things conservatives rarely mention when talking about President Reagan:</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1365087331628</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:55:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Since 1980, median household income has risen only 30 percent, adjusted for inflation, while average incomes at the top have tripled or quadrupled,” the New York Times’ David Leonhardt noted. 4. Reagan grew the size of the federal government tremendously. Reagan promised “to move boldly, decisively, and quickly to control the runaway growth of federal spending,” but federal spending “ballooned” under Reagan. He bailed out Social Security in 1983 after attempting to privatize it, and set up a progressive taxation system to keep it funded into the future. He promised to cut government agencies like the Department of Energy and Education but ended up adding one of the largest — the Department of Veterans’ Affairs, which today has a budget of nearly $90 billion and close to 300,000 employees. He also hiked defense spending by over $100 billion a year to a level not seen since the height of the Vietnam war. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1365087470443</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 10:57:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365088757178-9</Id><Topic><Title>The Citadel Curse....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364932529575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:55:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those $11.23 secondary buyers are down an immediate 10%. Thanks Kenny......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1365088757178</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365090612538-10</Id><Topic><Title>The Citadel Curse....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364932529575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:55:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Discount Brokers: S&amp;P Capital IQ gives Sell-from-Hold slashes to Charles Schwab (SCHW) and E*TRADE Financial (ETFC).</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1365090612538</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365090660683-11</Id><Title>any guesses</Title><Msg>on what kind of trouble etfc will claim so they don't have to show a profit? there must be a skeleton in the closet to come out, law suit, losses. something! this has been and seems to be nothing but a scam for the management to make huge salaries with nothing gained for investors,except the hedge fund.why would the ex ceo get over 10 million while the stock falls? go short etfc never fails to dissappoint!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365090660683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365091447922-12</Id><Topic><Title>The Citadel Curse....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364932529575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 15:55:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That was from yesterday....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1365091447922</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:04:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365092262829-13</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on democracy</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1365024324389</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 17:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a life JB - Wisconsin is next! (Even MN is voting on it!) When I had to go to a Doctors office in MN, across the border to a specialist - Picture ID was required on check in (They tell you this when you make your appointment), even that I had my Medica and SS-ID! In ND honest people like to keep it honest and that is what the rest of the nation should do -keep the LIBERAL trash out! If Obimbo want's to follow/implement the European SOCILAIST MODEL, he better understand that everybody in Europe has to CARRY a picture ID at all times, starting at age 16, NO ID when asked for - you going DOWNTOWN till somebody can identify you.!!! When I had my 2013 Physical last month, I was also told to bring a PICTURE-ID and I have been going to (on record) that Hudson Medical Center, same doctor since 1996!!! SO GET OVER IT!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365092262829</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:17:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365093409655-14</Id><Title>What will make ETFC move higher</Title><Msg>1) Profit 2) use of DTA's 3) Reduced provisions and write-offs.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1365093409655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365093963477-15</Id><Topic><Title>What will make ETFC move higher</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1365093409655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get bought out by a company with integerity !IMHO why did thye ex ceo get paid so much? payola? imho</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365093963477</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365094227747-16</Id><Topic><Title>any guesses</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365090660683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They fired a lot of people this quarter so they'll probably have a lot of charges related to that. Plus revs are gonna drop big time down to the 420 range. My guess is they post something like .05 profit.</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1365094227747</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:50:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365094686508-17</Id><Topic><Title>any guesses</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365090660683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 11:51:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no way its earnings time .remember the hedge fund wants to make money they will break even at best.all that manipulation to 10.80 they want returns . they want low nines for their money. get short make money!IMHO remember they never fail to dissappoint</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365094686508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365094963977-18</Id><Title>take 10 million off the top</Title><Msg>every so often for some yokel to come in and polish knobs in the head office for a while and after awhile it takes a toll on investors money!!!IMHO</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365094963977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365096215615-19</Id><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Msg>Nonresident stone-throwers always predict the death of California (and with it, the nation), but yet...we're still here. Doomsday's been coming for over 100 years. Still hasn't happened! Much like dummies with Obama Derangement Syndrome believe, anything good that happens in California can't possibly be California's doing, but rather, it's in spite of California's best efforts to stomp it out...and anything bad that happens related to California, well of course, that's California's fault! Meanwhile, we in the greatest state in the greatest nation ever to exist just keep on keepin' on, blissfully ignoring the utter ruin that, if it doesn't happen tomorrow, will surely happen the next day. It's another beautiful day in California! Wish you were here!</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365097838005-20</Id><Title>Schw or TDAMTD should just buy ETFC. $16 Get It over With!</Title><Msg>HEHEHEH</Msg><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1365097838005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:50:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365103919701-21</Id><Title>Let's Get Them ALL!...</Title><Msg>.. Report Exposes Secrets of Off-Shore Tax Havens CBS MoneyWatchBy Constantine von Hoffman | CBS MoneyWatch – 1 hour 51 minutes ago... . Email Recommend 304 Tweet 12 0 Print .... . . FILE - In this May 10, 2011 file photo, billionaire co- founder of Galleon Group Raj Rajaratnam, left, enters Manhattan federal court with his attorney, John Dowd, in New York. Rajaratnam, the former Wall Street titan convicted of making a fortune by coaxing a crew of corporate tipsters to give him an illegal edge on blockbuster trades in technology and other stocks, is scheduled to be sentenced Thursday, Oct. 13, 2011 for his conviction at trial earlier this year. (AP Photo/ Louis Lanzano, File). Associated Press - FILE - In this May 10, 2011 file photo, billionaire co- founder of Galleon Group Raj Rajaratnam, left, enters Manhattan federal court with his attorney, …more .. . . The off-shore tax havens of least 30 Americans accused of fraud, money laundering or other financial crimes have been unearthed in a groundbreaking report by The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists and a global consortium of news outlets. The first articles based on a cache of 2.5 million files were published Thursday, exposing secrets of more than 120,000 offshore entities -- including shell corporations and legal structures known as trusts -- used to hide the finances of politicians, crooks and others from more than 170 nations. These havens are harboring an enormous amount of money. One study estimated the total could be as high as $32 trillion. That's roughly the size of the U.S. and Japanese economies combined. The documents give a first-ever look at how agents for giant private banks would incorporate companies in Caribbean and South Pacific micro-states. These companies would then have front people called "nominees" to serve, on paper, as directors and shareholders -- creating another layer of secrecy and protection for the companies' real owners. The ICIJ's review of documents from just one company which sets up off-short companies and trusts, Singapore-based Portcullis TrustNet, identified 30 American clients who are in legal trouble for their financial dealings. According to the ICIJ, these include Paul Bilzerian, a corporate raider who was convicted of tax fraud and securities violations in 1989, and Raj Rajaratnam, a billionaire hedge fund manager who began serving an 11-year prison sentence in January for his role in one of the biggest insider trading scandals in U.S. history. The documents also reveal detailed information about the financial dealings of array of notorious people and companies including international arms dealers, smugglers and a company the European Union says is a front for Iran's nuclear-development program. Records have also been found on: -- Maria Imelda Marcos Manotoc, daughter of the late Philippine dictator Ferdinand Marcos. Following the release of the data, Philippine officials said they hope to learn if any of the money now held by Manotoc is part of the estimated $5 billion her father amassed through corruption. -- Individuals and companies who stole $230 million from Russia's treasury in a case which strained U.S.-Russia relations and led to a ban on Americans adopting Russian orphans. -- A Venezuelan man accused of using offshore companies to fund a U.S.-based Ponzi scheme and spending millions of dollars to bribe a Venezuelan government official. -- A corporate mogul who got billions of dollars in contracts from the government of Azerbaijan while serving as a director of offshore companies owned by the Azerbaijani president's daughters. The ICIJ and 86 investigative journalists worked for more than a year to make sense of the cache of 2.5 million files. The reporters came from new outlets in 46 countries, including The Guardian and the BBC in the U.K., Le Monde in France, Süddeutsche Zeitungand Norddeutscher Rundfunk in Germany, The Washington Post, the Canadian Broadcasting Corporation and 31 other media partners around the world.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1365103919701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 15:31:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365105713717-22</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like ETFC Is On The Verge Of A Massive Up Trend...!!</Title><Username>l_stave</Username><Timestamp>1364912273532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-02 10:17:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks simple enough. I will be watching to see what they are going to be doing so I can get in on the gains.</Msg><Username>pplaleen</Username><Timestamp>1365105713717</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:01:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365106218334-23</Id><Topic><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>S-CA was still nice when I left it from my Laurel Canyon Condo to move to MN, to do start my new position/promotion and doubled my pay check! On our last big trip from WI, we took a long vacation through 11 states including N-CA. Ther should be a split, just like NC/SC, ND/SD..........NCA/SCA because its two different "countries"! The states we liked the best were OR, ID, WY, SD, MT, UT and CO, the least WA, CA, NV and besides the Roosevelt Park, there is NOTHING to see in ND!!! It's another beautiful TAX day in California! Hope you stay there! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365106218334</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365106727229-24</Id><Topic><Title>What will make ETFC move higher</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1365093409655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People and institutions competing to buy shares. You know, the thing that always makes stocks move higher regardless of revenues or book value.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365106727229</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:18:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365106789306-25</Id><Topic><Title>Schw or TDAMTD should just buy ETFC. $16 Get It over With!</Title><Username>webyufuibf</Username><Timestamp>1365097838005</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:50:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That wouldn't be nearly as much fun as riding the eTrade Rolly Coaster.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365106789306</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:19:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365107076068-26</Id><Topic><Title>Top Democrat has no clue how a gun operates</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365028623680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-03 18:37:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And keep in mind that this is one of their BRIGHTER bulbs in the intellect department. Imagine the utter stupidity of the ones that DON'T allow to appear on camera to speak. Even when they do allow someone on camera they usually HAVE to follow the party script, assuming they can digest the gist before the interview/appearance. You can tell a new scripts been issued when the same catchphrases and buzzwords show up in the speech patterns of democrats all over the country almost overnight. This is a sign that a carefully engineered campaign that was been set aside for JUST the right "tragic moment" has been implemented.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365107076068</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 16:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365109254267-27</Id><Topic><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Meanwhile, we in the greatest state in the greatest nation ever to exist just keep on keepin' on, blissfully ignoring the utter ruin** I could not have said it better myself. If you want to stay here and continue to pay higher taxes to pay for government pensions and benefits for illegals that is up to you, but many as myself are planning on leaving or have already left. Just wait to your friends in Sacramento find away around Prop 13 and your property taxes skyrocket to pay for pensions and millions of Mexicans, even you may throw in the towel and come to the conclusion it's not worth it. I don't want to be around when all those 100 of billions of pension liabilities come due...anyway, most people here are a mile wide and an inch deep.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365109254267</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:00:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365109383648-28</Id><Title>N-KOREA!</Title><Msg>CUT THE BS and hit them MF right now, we know where they move the missiles to - take them out, hit their major bases and take those out and destroy all air strips and just have S-KOREA move in and take over. I bet that most of the N-Korean population will go right along with S-Korea and even the puppet soldiers will throw their weapons down and enjoy the benefits and life of the south - maybe they will finally get some REAL food!! Attack is the best defense - it's been proven through out the times! Ping Pong Un had enough FUN screwing around with his pinguin puppets. Afterall they declared WAR on S-Korea! Then do a short trial just like Yugoslavia - 5 min. and then shoot the whole brut - better yet HANG them SLOW! But NO, we are going to F@#$% around again till hell brakes lose - we need a REAL Commander in Chief, not a Community Organizer and Campaigner in diapers!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365109383648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:03:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365110560312-29</Id><Topic><Title>What will make ETFC move higher</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1365093409655</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 12:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if I buy more</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1365110560312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365112187249-30</Id><Topic><Title>N-KOREA!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365109383648</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:03:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dust off our Nukes and melt that fat-tubby 22 year psycho into the earth, Scorch'em and make the whole North Korea in to a nugget of glass. Take at his word and kill him first. otherwise we are idiots, When Dumbo sends Dennis Rodman to do diplomacy, this is what you get! But then again Dennis Rodman is much, much smarter than Dumbo!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365112187249</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 17:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365112918002-31</Id><Topic><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>W and crew didn't bother with the real wmd in N. Korea . W spent trillions getting rid of imaginary wmd in Iraq instead. N korea has no oil so bush &amp; his oil cronies didn't see much money to be made for themselves there, I guess.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365112918002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:01:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365115893147-32</Id><Title>Obama: worfless</Title><Msg>What a worfless waste.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1365115893147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365116005986-33</Id><Title>Never send a boy to do a man's job</Title><Msg>Little tinpot Barry needs a life-coach.</Msg><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1365116005986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365117764350-34</Id><Topic><Title>Never send a boy to do a man's job</Title><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1365116005986</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 18:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks as the newly minted Koran leader all of 28 years old has Barry up at night, but not to worry we have Chuck(lapdog)Hagel as Secretary of Defense. Threats of bombing them into the stoneage isn't very effective when they are already there.... only 26% of the folks who live there have electricity.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1365117764350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 19:22:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365120468176-35</Id><Title>NRA caught defending straw purchasers</Title><Msg>Thu Apr 04, 2013 at 10:32 AM PDT by tytalus Wayne LaPierre being rudely interrupted by reality "Keep guns out of the hands of criminals" eh? The Hill reported yesterday on this, seems worth mentioning. The Senate's package of stronger gun laws includes straw purchasing of guns -- specifically, making it a federal crime, a tougher new law to crack down on one of the methods criminals use to acquire guns. And so naturally the NRA is demanding that this legislation be changed, making it harder on law enforcement and easier on the straw purchasers. Because you know, they're all about keeping guns out of the hands of criminals, except when the NRA chooses to defend the criminals. So, this is what's happening to the first legislative measure that passed muster in the Senate Judiciary Committee. Increased penalties on straw purchases of guns sailed through the Senate Judiciary Committee and looked like a safe bet to win Senate approval even as other provisions — including the expanded background checks that remain a goal for gun control supporters — ran into trouble. Now the straw-purchasing bill could be in danger because of NRA demands to change the language so law enforcement officials would have to prove that a straw purchaser intended to commit a crime or further the commission of a crime by buying a gun for someone else.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120468176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365120570354-36</Id><Topic><Title>NRA caught defending straw purchasers</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120468176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As for the NRA, they're busy trying to make it tougher for this crime to stick, and they're even trying to take out a provision to confiscate the guns and ammo of convicted straw buyers. Even those who manage to get convicted of this crime -- should any aspect of that survive the NRA's assault and become law -- even those convicted and facing 25 years in prison ought not have their guns taken away, according to the NRA. On the one hand it's ridiculous, outrageous; and yet for the NRA, this seems natural for them, expected. This is the NRA's predictable response to any stricter gun law: opposition. Even when they say they want to keep guns out of the hands of criminals. That's proven false by this; they're shown (yet again) to be liars and hypocrites. Their only interest here is the facilitation of gun sales. And they achieve this new low after being caught defending domestic abusers, and defending felons from being disarmed. So, again, it's only natural that the NRA would fight for straw purchasers as well. Even the gunmakers ought to be ashamed of the NRA's spirited defense of criminal straw purchasing of their products, but I expect not a peep of protest "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120570354</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365121049015-37</Id><Topic><Title>NRA caught defending straw purchasers</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120468176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" The NRA wants criminals with guns to ratchet up the fear to justify more gun sales to people thinking guns will protect them from those very criminals. In effect they're arming both sides in a war. You can't assassinate the character of any of modern conservative. You'd have to find where it was buried, dig it up, resurrect it, then kill it. And killing a zombie isn't really assassination, is it? "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365121049015</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365121278370-38</Id><Topic><Title>NRA caught defending straw purchasers</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120468176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"As the NRA has transformed their messaging from a focus on hunting to the need to own weapons for self-defense, they have proven that they will stop at nothing to boost the profits of the organization's main backers, the gun manufacturers. As more and more of our country's population shifted from rural to urban environs, the manufacturers knew they needed to switch marketing tactics in order to maintain sales. Hunting was a sport that was wasting away as fewer and fewer homes (as percentage of American households) had a gun in them. So what did the NRA do for their sponsors? Ratchet up the scare tactics and self-defense pitch in order to sell semi-auto weapons, large capacity magazines and more. I continue to marvel at some of the posts here from seemingly sane people who somehow believe that they need 30-round magazines to ward off roving bands of marauders. These seemingly sane people have internalized the scare tactics of the NRA and the gun manufacturers to the point where they express truly bizarre fears. This just shows how effective this messaging has been. We have portions of our population who believe that they need 30-round magazines to ward off the evil hordes. Of course, the same gun proponents will turn around and tout the decrease in the murder rate and violent crime." One would think some of these folks live in Somalia, the way they talk about warding off home invaders."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365121278370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:21:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365122882975-39</Id><Topic><Title>NRA caught defending straw purchasers</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365120468176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:07:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Furnishing alcohol to a minor is a Class A misdemeanor in Florida and carries a similar charge in most states. For even a first offense, an offender may serve up to 1 year in jail and be penalized with up to a $4,000 fine. " "According to the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives (ATF), straw purchasers “represent a significant overall crime and public safety problem.” When a person with a clean background intentionally buys firearms for prohibited persons, she or he thwarts the background check requirement and allows firearms to be funneled to criminals, domestic abusers and gangs." "Authorities say it’s hard to convict someone for a straw purchase — and even harder to convict a store owner for “knowingly and willfully” selling a gun to a straw buyer." There's something terribly wrong when it's harder to convict a straw buyer of weapons than of alcohol. In some states the penalties for straw buying alcohol are greater than for guns. The NRA and their GOP stooges should be proud.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1365122882975</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 20:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365127300834-40</Id><Topic><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, With income tax day next week, it's a good time to compare California with some other states-- red states--that are often regarded as low-tax, consumer friendly. So, here's the challenge. Assuming a taxable family income of $60,000 (the median family income in Sacramento County is about $57,000, according to Census figures), rank the following states--including California-- from highest to lowest in taxes on that $60,000 income for those who are married, filing jointly. Idaho, South Carolina, Georgia, Utah, California Can't fool you, can I? Yes, they're already ranked. Even Utah's flat 5% would mean a tax bill of $3000 compared with California's $1,628. How about Kentucky, home of two high profile tax-hating Senate Republicans? Sorry, $3,299, or another $139/month. The grass elsewhere may be greener (ok, maybe not in Utah) but it's not always as cheap as some would like to think.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365127300834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 22:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365128402430-41</Id><Topic><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biddermon_ca, Still not too late to pack up your #$%$ and get out - and do us a favor and take pacifican54 with you. I prefer my wine from Napa Valley - not from individuals who are "half empty"</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1365128402430</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 22:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365128995278-42</Id><Topic><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>private contractors stole and cheated to the tune of billions of dollars. The American taxpayer will have to pay for these stupid wars in Iraq and Afghanistan for many more decades to come.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1365128995278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 22:29:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365131145965-43</Id><Topic><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WMDs on Iraq is a "slam dunk case." - George Tenet, December 12, 2002. March 16, 1988, 5,000 Kurds probably had simultaneous sudden heart attack. Nothing to do with WMDs. Don't worry, if Obama does nothing about N. Korea, than it doesn't have WMDs either. Why are you getting so nervous?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365131145965</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 23:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365132634876-44</Id><Topic><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican54, Have you ever seen the picture of Don Rumsfeld shaking hands with Saddam Hussein? What do you think that was all about?</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1365132634876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 23:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365133393597-45</Id><Topic><Title>bush &amp; crew spent trillions getting rid of imaginary WMD in Iraq &amp; never mind about the real ones in N Korea</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365081932850</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush became the Iraqi ATM machine. He shoveled so many billions of untraceable cash into Iraq that they could burn the cash to keep warm.</Msg><Username>borderxingbeaner</Username><Timestamp>1365133393597</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 23:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365133637964-46</Id><Topic><Title>A message for biddermon_ca</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1365096215615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 13:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please bidder. Move to Texas and leave California to productive people. You are an old hormonal bee otch. We don't need you. Not here, or any other decent place. You always will have Texas. Bring your white hood.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1365133637964</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-04 23:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>