<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-11"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370923744149-1</Id><Title>Impeccable timing</Title><Msg>"June 10, 2013, New York— Today, the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals dismissed a lawsuit brought against President Barack Obama, the head of the National Security Agency (NSA), and the heads of the other major security agencies, challenging warrantless government surveillance of telephone calls and emails in the U.S. under the program first disclosed in December 2005 by the New York Times. Ironically, the dismissal comes just as a series of new stories about astonishingly broad domestic NSA surveillance have broken in the news. The suit, CCR v. Obama, was filed by the Center for Constitutional Rights (CCR) on behalf of itself and its legal staff working on national security cases whose communications fit the criteria used by the NSA for targeting calls and emails under its surveillance program. CCR Attorneys argued the program was unconstitutional and had forced them to take costly and burdensome countermeasures to minimize the risk of having their privileged client communications intercepted by the NSA. The case, initially filed in 2006 against President George W. Bush, sought an injunction that would prohibit the NSA from conducting warrantless surveillance within the United States. When, in response, the government claimed it had shut down the program in January 2007, the CCR asked the court to order the government to destroy any records of surveillance that it still retains from the illegal NSA program. The lower court refused to do so and the case moved to the Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals, which held that a plaintiff challenging a secret surveillance program must be able to prove they were actually eavesdropped upon by the program in order to be able to challenge it in court. Today, the Ninth Circuit panel affirmed that decision, relying on the Supreme Court’s February 2013 dismissal of a similar challenge to the 2008 FISA Amendments Act, Clapper v. Amnesty International. "...</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370923744149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 00:09:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370944736649-2</Id><Topic><Title>United STASI of Amerika</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370890040156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:47:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary wears a black leather Pant Suit and uses a Whip. 'BANG'azi diplomacy with the Cocaine and Prostitutes. That's your hard earned money 'Hellary' spends while the 4 die in Benghazi. Jail for Hillary. Jail fir Dumbo.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370944736649</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 05:58:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370955591724-3</Id><Topic><Title>Doesnt anyone on this board talk about Etrade??</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370806680255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted that these a-holes should go elsewhere, i guess they are too stupid to understand. There are many sites to discuss POLITICS, leave this board to ETRADE discussions.</Msg><Username>grandpa_6</Username><Timestamp>1370955591724</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 08:59:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370972691109-4</Id><Title>Nothing helps this stock....</Title><Msg>Higher interest rates? Better home prices? Smaller loan book? and this stock can't break a buck twenty pre split. Hopeless investment here.....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370972691109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370974044149-5</Id><Topic><Title>Doesnt anyone on this board talk about Etrade??</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370806680255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, not even the bashers or pumpers post here anymore.</Msg><Username>long_short_007</Username><Timestamp>1370974044149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:07:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370974284939-6</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing helps this stock....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370972691109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see all of your points as part of the compelling strong buy. You want to buy stocks before the broader market figures it out.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370974284939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370974635157-7</Id><Title>many Americans are just to fluffy to make a sacrifice for our Country</Title><Msg>they won't serve in the military they whine about taxes/ they don't want to be inconvenienced in the slightest by a war in which other Americans make the supreme sacrifice............ they don't even want their privacy affected in anyway by data mining done to protect the nation....... maybe they should be drafted into the military and then they can see how much privacy the troops have. I have an idea. let's end the wars and then nobody will have to suffer a loss of privacy! bring the troops home from the mid east and and all islamic lands and stop all aid to Israel... it is in violation of UN resolutions and international law, as everyone knows....... and presto...... just like when we left nam there was no more violence against Americans from the viets and next thing you know even McCain is hugging his former captors and we are doing business with the very same people we were at war with.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370974635157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370975009794-8</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing helps this stock....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370972691109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can you name another company with 5 ceos in the past 3 years and a BOD that turns over what seems like every quarter? It's hard to gather investment money when your focus is paying out a huge percentage of profits to about 5 top execs. Heck, even when they lose money, those boys and girls get paid. There are thousands of people on WS looking for under valued stocks every single day and that is their job. How do you think you are going to find one trading stocks part time? This sector is not growing and etrade is a distant 3rd or 4th in the sector. Also, they have churned out the same lame slide deck for 2 years now showing a pie in the sky 1 billion in profit. Have you timed out how long it will take for the loan book to roll off in entirety and everything else they forecast? Answer-----about 7-8 years. You could probably buy any one of a 1000 companies and get a better return in the next 7-8 years. That is the problem.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370975009794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370976747718-9</Id><Topic><Title>many Americans are just to fluffy to make a sacrifice for our Country</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370974635157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is a matter with you. Just because your guy is in the Whitehouse your OK with the government data mining your private business. If it work so well why did the two punks blow up a bunch of folks in Boston. You are the worst type of American, one who's sells out their own best interest and their fellow Americans for their twisted ideology ..... "when they came for me, there was no one left to speak out".</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1370976747718</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370977951245-10</Id><Title>Obimbo the CLUELESS...........</Title><Msg>........stuck his foot in his mouth again (getting like Biden) by calling Turkey a "Model of a peaceful democratic Transition of a Muslim Nation"! MY #$%$ - this left wing, commie ba$$ard has to go! He is circling the wagons and putting his Zcars up front for defense of his ongoing building of a DICTATOR SHIP!!!Crowd control at all cost - just like Turkey - riots to come!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370977951245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370978914795-11</Id><Topic><Title>'BANG'-hazi (Hillary style)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370892196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be talking about yourself, because after all you are "THE-left- WINGNUTLOSER!" Does you care have right turn signals??? - If not drive by Obomposis's property - all streets are ONE WAY and LEFT TURN only! Enjoy! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370978914795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:28:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370980164448-12</Id><Topic><Title>many Americans are just to fluffy to make a sacrifice for our Country</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370974635157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are pathetic</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1370980164448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370980999743-13</Id><Title>Privacy concerns</Title><Msg>Curious how most Americans don't care. Leaders of both parties seem to want to maintain it. It's those on the far right and especially on the far left that want to curb the practices. Today a "bi-partisan " group came out with a "solution". Best guess, all will be painted as "weak on defense" in the upcoming political season. Bipartisan group of senators introduce bill to declassify FISA court opinions A bipartisan group of eight senators introduced new legislation Tuesday that would require the Attorney General to reveal how the administration interprets the laws governing the massive surveillance programs conducted by the NSA. It would require the declassification of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court's opinions, a press release from Sen. Jeff Merkley states, "allowing Americans to know how broad of a legal authority the government is claiming to spy on Americans under the PATRIOT Act and Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act." “Americans deserve to know how much information about their private communications the government believes it’s allowed to take under the law,” Merkley said. “There is plenty of room to have this debate without compromising our surveillance sources or methods or tipping our hand to our enemies. We can’t have a serious debate about how much surveillance of Americans’ communications should be permitted without ending secret law.” He's joined by Sen. Ron Wyden (D-OR), who along with Sen. Mark Udall (C-CO), has been trying for two years to have these secret interpretations aired. Sens. Mike Lee (R-UT), Patrick Leahy (D-VT), Dean Heller (R-NV), Mark Begich (D-AK), Al Franken (D-MN) and Jon Tester (D-MT) have signed on.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370980999743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370982128954-14</Id><Topic><Title>many Americans are just to fluffy to make a sacrifice for our Country</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370974635157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are fluffy.Too fluffy.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370982128954</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 16:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370991279735-15</Id><Topic><Title>Nothing helps this stock....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370972691109</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 13:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm in this for the buyout and cheap assets (loan book ). I had the same philosophy on Sprint and it's paid off very nicely. In fact I will likely close out my Sprint position soon and put more into ETFC. I don't know why we couldn't double the stock price over the next 12 months.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370991279735</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 18:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370992967072-16</Id><Topic><Title>many Americans are just to fluffy to make a sacrifice for our Country</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370974635157</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 14:17:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pelvis, You are idiotic!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1370992967072</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370993815779-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obimbo the CLUELESS...........</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370977951245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Du spinnst mal wieder ganz schoen.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370993815779</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 19:36:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370997428977-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obimbo the CLUELESS...........</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1370977951245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 15:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ! I love the smell of panic and hysteria among the ignorant and clueless.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1370997428977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 20:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371009539570-19</Id><Topic><Title>'BANG'-hazi (Hillary style)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370892196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suggest you read your own posts. You should be embarrassed to come from an American school system. When they talk about the failures of our education ........ you are the example.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371009539570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-11 23:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>