<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361375865813-1</Id><Topic><Title>GOP dilemma</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1361375108556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:45:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clownie's dilemma Do I appear stupid for my misspellings or do I proofread? Up to this point he's always chosen the former.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361375865813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 10:57:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361381111265-2</Id><Topic><Title>Two billion spent on illegal immigrant baby deliveries</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361058147775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:42:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California, former home of the free lunch. Soon to be home of the Fleeing Business. Later to be home to the exodus of the useless as the taxbase expires and the former California Free Folk look elsewhere for their Free Lunch as the State won't be able to provide it for them anymore. Immigrants are suppose to infuse a nation with new life, not attach to it like a parasite and suck the life out of it while multiplying recklessly until the host finally dies.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1361381111265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:25:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361381566839-3</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES ETFC.</Title><Username>adam.edward</Username><Timestamp>1361378379115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good report!</Msg><Username>aquinodavid252</Username><Timestamp>1361381566839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:32:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361382179556-4</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES ETFC.</Title><Username>adam.edward</Username><Timestamp>1361378379115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>whiteed14</Username><Timestamp>1361382179556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:42:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361382597065-5</Id><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Msg>President Obama on the sequester cuts - November 21, 2011 “My message to them is simple: No. I will veto any effort to get rid of those automatic spending cuts to domestic and defense spending. There will be no easy off ramps on this one." President Obama on the sequester cuts - February 19, 2013 "Border Patrol agents will see their hours reduced. FBI agents will be furloughed. Federal prosecutors will have to close cases and let criminals go. Air traffic controllers and airport security will see cutbacks, which means more delays at airports across the country. Thousands of teachers and educators will be laid off. Tens of thousands of parents will have to scramble to find childcare for their kids. Hundreds of thousands of Americans will lose access to primary care and preventive care like flu vaccinations and cancer screenings." Any other network beside Fox News will stick that to him? What a travesty of journalism...</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361383419186-6</Id><Topic><Title>Top Analyst UPGRADES ETFC.</Title><Username>adam.edward</Username><Timestamp>1361378379115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 11:39:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>useful report. thanks a lot!</Msg><Username>sjeff53</Username><Timestamp>1361383419186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:03:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361385414197-7</Id><Topic><Title>Two billion spent on illegal immigrant baby deliveries</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361058147775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-16 18:42:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The stupid Mexicans(redundant) won't even notice, thet will think they are back home.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361385414197</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361385882724-8</Id><Title>Epitaph of a city run by the left</Title><Msg>This is the outcome when liberals are at the helm. Detriot has finnaly run out of other peoples money. Obama wants to do to the rest of the country what the folks of color have done to Detriot. Detroit faces financial crisis, has no plan to fix it Detroit — For the second time in a year, a state review team has found Detroit is in a financial emergency that requires Gov. Rick Snyder to intervene in City Hall. But this time, if Snyder agrees that a financial emergency exists, the governor's choices are more limited. He could appoint an emergency manager to keep Michigan's largest city from plunging into bankruptcy, experts say, or he could continue state financial supervision through a new consent agreement, which seems a faint possibility. The six-member review team unanimously concluded in a report released Tuesday that the city failed to restructure its debt-laden bureaucracy under the financial consent agreement signed in April and that Detroit's financial crisis requires Snyder's intervention "because no satisfactory plan exists to resolve a serious financial problem." "We gave the city every chance to avoid the outcome we're recommending to the governor today," said Dillon, who led the review team.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361385882724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:44:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361386386986-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh sure, it so compliacted! This little president introduced, promoted and authorized sequester as an alternative to GOP proposed budget. Of course, little more than a year ago he didn't make it sound so horrible. Now he scares everyone off from his own idea. So this horrible sequester idea is going to happen because GOP budget doesn't punish business enough. Not to mention little man 's plan to punish business is chump change in balancing budget. This guy doesn't want compromise. he strives on war with opposition. A theater for uneducated public.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361386386986</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:53:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361387838431-10</Id><Topic><Title>Epitaph of a city run by the left</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361385882724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:44:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama was overwhelmingly supported in his last election by the good people of Detroit and they feel he owes them their bailout. Detroiters are counting on their good buddy Brak to NOT renege on the implied kickback arrangement.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361387838431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361392268448-11</Id><Topic><Title>Epitaph of a city run by the left</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361385882724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:44:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kinda like watching the GM bankruptcy coming down the tracks...You could see it from 5 years away!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1361392268448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 15:31:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361394413845-12</Id><Topic><Title>gop prez candidate trump went bankupt several times</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361389143577</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:39:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well it is pretty hard to bankrupt a company when the last two Democrats never ran anything. Billy Clinton was a career politican, and (Berry) Obama a community organizer...when you run out of money and you just raise taxes on your nieghbors.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361394413845</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:06:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395052144-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bush took a projected $6 trillion surplus &amp; turned it into a $5 trillion addition to the national debt</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361389858198</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 14:50:58 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**US budget that resulted in the largest deficit in US histoy... deficits have been lower every year since** NO, that would be your boy running up the largest deficit in history and climbing. I think you are suffering from fuzzy math. Bush had to deal with 9/11 after Billy Clinton had other things on his mind other than dealing with radical Islam which cost us dearly. Just like Jimmy(I'll never lie to you)Carter did with the Soviets. Reagan had to come in and spend money to rebuild the military that Jimmy destroyed...as will the next President will have to do as Comrade Obama will disamate the military in favor of social justice.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361395052144</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:17:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361395439837-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican...you notice only a quip with no substance from our friends on the left.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361395439837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:23:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361397458641-15</Id><Title>Biden says to women: Go get you a shotgun</Title><Msg>If you hear a strange noise, shoot into the air. Trouble wif that is she'll be jumped when she tries to reload. Luckily however Biden has a back-up plan, a plan "b" if you will, which is for the woman to #$%$ herself, state she has an STD, claim she's menstruating or offer up a golden shower.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361397458641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 16:57:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361397644954-16</Id><Topic><Title>Epitaph of a city run by the left</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361385882724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 13:44:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>michigan has been a red state, run by gop govs for 2/3rds of he last 40 years. What a failure the gop is!</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361397644954</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:00:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361398248293-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nothing to be sorry about dear. I only pointed out that just one network covered this. But the video with our little president commited to sequester is all over Youtube available for everyone. Is that the news you don't want me to watch?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361398248293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:10:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361399635771-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeap. "you don't get it". These people don't worry about substance. Just sticking labels. Notice, they never even try to chanllenge any posts, just throwing more of their own nonsense. Though, Yahoo helps to clean the garbage. HIlarious. Never know where the help comes from.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361399635771</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:33:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361402372854-19</Id><Topic><Title>poor John Boehner lasted only 8 weeks in the Navy</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1361399051211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 17:24:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder how long would Obama last? Never mind. He wouldn't try. Pot smokers always have way superior ideals in mind.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361402372854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 18:19:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361408270177-20</Id><Title>Obama's economy on a role</Title><Msg>Of cource unless you want to take a car for a test drive.... A big jump in gas prices nationwide is not only hitting drivers in the pocket book but car dealerships too. In California before you get the keys for a test drive at some auto sales centers you must agree to bring it back with the same amount of gas you left with.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361408270177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 19:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361410394670-21</Id><Title>Subject</Title><Msg>Man, why weren't you crucifying Bush in 2008 when gas was over 4$ a gallon and a barrel of oil was almost 150$?</Msg><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1361410394670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:33:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361421433885-22</Id><Topic><Title>What Frightens Republicans the Most ?</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1361417687145</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 22:34:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sir, you're so annoying. Is it hard to find another MB to post garbage you call light? It is a free advise. As Obama supporter you must like free.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361421433885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:37:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361422533978-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I will veto any effort to get rid of those automatic spending cuts to domestic and defense spending." This what sequester is. It is sequester he is talking about, it is removal of sequester he threatens to veto. His idea, he proposed and defended sequester in November 2011. Who is promoting something that never meant to happen? Idiocy. This president doesn't want compromise, he wants blame game.</Msg><Username>formykidsfuture</Username><Timestamp>1361422533978</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 23:55:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>