<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661254986-1</Id><Topic><Title>Issa to convene a committee to look at guns in schools</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357658740507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:25:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad your narcissistic, all knowing hero #$%$-canned hisass. All Stanley did was hurt poor Brak's feelers by calling him names.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1357661254986</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:07:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357661567795-2</Id><Topic><Title>Issa to convene a committee to look at guns in schools</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357658740507</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 10:25:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell them not to forget that there was an almost repeat of the Colorado shootings in San Antonio on December 17th, but it's not being reported in the press. Wanna guess why? The dude entered the theater and someone with a gun put 4 neat little holes in his chest. Problem . . . Meet solution.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357661567795</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:12:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357663390884-3</Id><Topic><Title>more proof that USA is racist</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357662130075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:22:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tyrone of course! Because he is maybe of color and he might have "worked so hard" and is maybe "not so well off" and also we have to "balance our diversity" so we look good in the eye of the government and of course we are a "equal opportunity": employer!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357663390884</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:43:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357663866313-4</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is said to have discovered the United States?? Sounds like the co founder of CAIR is as much an idiot as his general membership. If the US ever enters a war of annihilation it will be in a conflict with Muslim nations. The alternative is that they succeed in their attempt to conquer us from within. The Islamic doctrine is as solid as the requirements of the book is derived from. Eventual worldwide domination. Now that the previous doctrine, communism, that believed in eventual world domination through infiltration where possible and violence where needed, is effectively dead, Islam is the next we need to drive a stake through the heart of.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357663866313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 11:51:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357664415022-5</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm wondering where my annual report, ect, is... and my proxy . . . . I've been holding this for a couple years now and have yet to get either. Are they just NOT consulting minority shareholders? While it might be cheaper for them I don't consider my "minority" core position of 2500 shares to be trivial to me, at least from a "percentage of total portfolio" position. I'd sure like a better picture of what's going on rather than having to dig it up out of SEC filings sans the spin. It's not that the spin is significant in and of itself, but I also like it as it gives me an idea of where a company DOESN'T want you to look where it comes to their business model and future product impact. There's not much of that to do with a financial company as there is with a technology company (most of the rest of my portfolio), but I'd STILL like to see it. Holding back for now as ETrade slipped out of my strong buy area, though I'd be buying if I didn't already have a nice core position, but I've shed my temporary position for now even though I added 1,000 shares to my core last year.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357664415022</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 12:00:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357665670000-6</Id><Topic><Title>Not good. My first 2013 bi-weekly paycheck</Title><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1357395271231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:14:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you know you have a MORAL responsibility to share and help those less fortunate continue their life of trying to succeed by purchasing $40 worth of lottery tickets with their EBT cards every month hoping to "hit the big one", while spending the majority of the rest on necessary sustenance (beer) and food items (chips), and saving a bit to trade for some [fill in drug of proles choice]. Then they go to their section 8 housing with its subsidized internet and watch porn until the football game comes on so they can watch in on their 54" flat screen TV's. A needed item since they save money by also allowing you to connect your PS/3 and your Computer to it. Every two years they get a job for 4 months so they'll qualify for unemployment again, then get let go, and collect unemployment and whatever else for the next two. It's an amazing system. I have section 8 tenant on my property out in the hinterlands and while I got a better batch of folk than most small property owners (ok, not so small, its on a legal 1 acre subdivision of my 40+ acre forest), I can't say my tenants done a DAMN thing to get herself back into the real world since I took her on. When she moved in I was still working (now my MS is bad enough to take me out of the work force, so I trade stocks to try to supplement my income) and was more disabled than she was. Admittedly she was a wreck from fleeing an abusive spouse but still, it's been over 10 years and not only is she is much better shape than when she arrived, she has 4 less kids under her roof than she did then. What's she waiting for? Ahh, right . . . as long as the spigot is open, she'll keep tapping it. There is absolutely NO incentive for her to work toward rehabilitative work since she effective has a far higher net income receiving public benefits than she would being a 40 year old woman entering the work force with virtually no recent real world skills (she had a fairly high paying factory job at one time so gets reasonable SSDI payments compared to a minimum wage worker), despite the fact that she's highly intelligent. As long as our social welfare and disability system disincentivize work by eliminating benefits immediately on a 1:1 basis and terminally at the end of 9 months there will be NO reason for a previously highly paid employee to seek work at a level significant under that which they previous worked at. I'd GLADLY work again if I could, and if I could find someone to hire me. I totally can't understand the mindset. P.S Brilliant and bored software/firmware/sensor engineer, former CTO of an internet gaming company and inventor of technology that allows a game whose total game area encompasses just about every other internet game out there, seeks part time employment on project oversight or development in the Dallas/Fort Worth are, prefer telecommute with as few in office vists as possible. Can operate telepresence hardware, can set up VPN to home. Have in house high speed commercial internet connection vis Verizon FIOS. See resume, CV, whatever I've posted on it via LinkedIn. Look for Stephen W. Evans, Grapevine, TX former employee MIT, IENT, and Playnet. Army veteran. Disabled vet (I think you'd get a tax credit for that). Bored Bored Bored Bored . . . Going out of mind. I don't know how the so called "welfare" class can freaking stand it.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357665670000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 12:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357668844044-7</Id><Topic><Title>Not good. My first 2013 bi-weekly paycheck</Title><Username>reboundstocks</Username><Timestamp>1357395271231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-05 09:14:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you gross $9,350 per week.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1357668844044</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:14:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357672722636-8</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't agree with most of your positions, but I am no fan of organized religion for the reasons you have stated. Yet most religions have gone through their reaissance, Islam has not. I am afraid it will take a catastrophic event for them to come to the conclusion that religion should be part of your life, not control every aspect of it. History has shown us that these conversions don't come without consequence to the true believers that their religion should dominate, such as Islam. As they say, its not if, its when this will come about...mostly likely in our life time.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357672722636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:18:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357673066609-9</Id><Topic><Title>gun nuts say causes of gun violence: 1. too few guns....2. too many people......</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357671554219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:59:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is it about guns that frightens you..is it that too noisy.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357673066609</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:24:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357674188098-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Threat: Cut Social Security and Medicare or We’ll Kill the Economy</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357668242921</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 13:04:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will be no recession, no depression. We will have total collapse of US economy, poverty and misery after Obama pushes US debt over $25T. He is well on its way! So, yeah, keep talking about unnecessary spending cuts.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1357674188098</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 14:43:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357675437568-11</Id><Title>This is SUCH a bad day . . .</Title><Msg>That the ONE stock I had that was up (a low volume mining stock) is now DOWN because a low ball limit buy order I put in actually executed about a half hour ago. We could use alittle good news . . . . Just a wee crumb. Not just for eTrade but for the whole economy. Given that AIG is suing the government for "ripping them off", maybe the tax payers can sue the DNC for ripping THEM off.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357675437568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357675731595-12</Id><Topic><Title>This is SUCH a bad day . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357675437568</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:03:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never mind, another trade executed returning it to the days opening, so that trade resulting in a $10 net gain on that stock for the day so far. I guess not even I can hold ALL losers. Even on a rotten day like today.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357675731595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:08:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357675968989-13</Id><Title>Unemployment rises to a new hig.................</Title><Msg>...............in the Euro Zone! (ING ticker-Google) Nice going "Reform" and Socialism! Distribute the wealth - sounds familiar??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357675968989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:12:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357677053060-14</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I figure they conned Clinton into slicing off a HUGE chunk of Serbia for them, and he was significantly more aware of foreign political events than Obama. For them so far Obama has been easy, doing pretty much what they demand when they demand it. We'll see if that continues when the new "Democracies" in Egypt and Syria turn their guns on Israel.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357677053060</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:30:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357679404930-15</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment rises to a new hig.................</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357675968989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:12:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hardly . . . Look at France . . . Jack up taxes on the wealthy and, guess what, the wealthy leave. Surprise! Not only leave, but leave for freaking Russia.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357679404930</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:10:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357680529650-16</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment rises to a new hig.................</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357675968989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:12:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Dummy - you are so far LEFT, that you can't comprehend the message! The GOP doesn't reform or distribute wealth - get it? Obamas SOCIALISM and Obama wealth distribution, taxing the rich and the middle class doesn't work - get it?? Obamacare is a killer and fuels unemployment! (But I/we don't really care we got pensions, IRA's, good TOP insurance paid for the company with a HRA and a lot set aside, best, NO payments everything bought and paid for in cash! - How about you?) Even the rich French moving, of all places to Russia, where they are welcome, pay low taxes and building/employing their broken system! (New places to move money/investments to: Monaco, Lichtenstein, Monte Carlo, forget the Caymans - learned that on our last Europe Trip) You must be living in Pelosi town where the street signs are all "ONE WAY" and LEFT TURN" only! Who are you paid for "distributing" all the LEFT WING GARBAGE? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357680529650</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:28:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681525662-17</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fubar - agreed, Obama has no experience or a clue about world politics, he can't even manage the US! That's why he appoints Hagel because he has a more easy opinion/stand on the middle east and is more critical of Israel; plus he can say now by appointing a Republican that he is "reaching across the isle"!!! (All politics - no substance!) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357681525662</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:45:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357681986570-18</Id><Topic><Title>Bush and the gop INCREASED spending 42% in his first term</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357680387214</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:26:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More left wing garbage! Aren't you getting tired of all the negative ratings of your uninformed, twisted #$%$??? With all your time for postings you must be on unemployment or wellfare and food stamps - so what are you doing on message boards, since you have no money to trade??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357681986570</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 16:53:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357685744566-19</Id><Topic><Title>rowdy lies regarding gop INCREASED spending 42% in his first term</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357685181943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Show me where I published $$$ amounts - I publish facts and NOT left wing fiction! (I refer to articles when I post figures, but you ,are too lazy to read before you publish your #$%$) There are only 3 left wing air heads on this board - but you won first place!, almost tied with Foksjunkie! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357685744566</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:55:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357686699729-20</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fubar - correct and we need more Al Gore's to help them right along with their propaganda by allowing them media in the US! The "super democrat" all the sudden prefers money over the nations priorities (safety). Now he can buy another Jet to pollute the clean air, which he all teaches us, he so dearly loves! All LEFT WING HYPOCRITES! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357686699729</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357688535332-21</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment rises to a new hig.................</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357675968989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:12:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rowdy, for all lefties on this board socialism is perfectly fine. They are not scared at all to live in misery as long as everyone else is in the same #$%$. See, the worse can happen to a socialist lefty is when someone has more. That really stinks! This people don't have a sense of appreciation for what they have everywhere they turn in America. The sense of appreciation is numbed. What makes them agitated is inequality. It's leech mentality. They salivate when hear our marxist president talking about "fair share". Sick, but unfortunately true.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1357688535332</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:42:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357689240503-22</Id><Topic><Title>rowdy lies regarding gop INCREASED spending 42% in his first term</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357685181943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey doofus, George W Bush could submit a budget even twice bigger. Why it matters? The economy under his presidency produced the revenue which allowed to pay for most of expenses. The ACTUAL deficit under Bush was never above $450B. I wish we could get today at least to this level. Deficit is 3x higher today than under Bush, US government is spending way more than it can afford. Can you stick that into your sick head?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1357689240503</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 18:54:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357690686491-23</Id><Topic><Title>rowdy lies regarding gop INCREASED spending 42% in his first term</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357685181943</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 17:46:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican...........you asking to much from a left wing block head! He was trained by Wasserman-Schulz, a disgrace for two good German names!!! Next stop - pushing gun control law changes - more left wing garbage coming! (Gun dealers had another record day - the registration computers for all types of fire arms were overloaded again! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357690686491</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357691205362-24</Id><Topic><Title>***FLASH*** Muslims descovered America</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357336479683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-04 16:54:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually it's sort of handy for me. Before this change I had to watch Al Jeers At You on YouTube, and now I can just record All Al Queda's Greatest Hits on FIOS with my DVR. Win win as far as I'm concerned. Besides, it''s not like Al Jazeera makes any bones about where they stand on certain issues, unlike MSNBC or CBS which make claims to the contrary. You can always count on them to take the Islamic side of any issue. I like people who not only state their agenda but make no bones about it. One reason I find Obama contemptible is that his stand on firearms issues was known long before this recent tragedy, he just choose to pretend it wouldn't effect his governing right up until the first chance that he could declare that he'd changed his mind. The Muslims will straight up tell you that you're an infidel who's going to burn unless you embrace the Prophet, that Palestine is Dar Al'Islam and that therefore Israel cannot exist as a Jewish state (no matter Zionest or not, all land once conquered by Islam is part of all Islam and to defend it is Jihad, no matter what, no conquest of such land by any infidel can be accepted . . . and thus far, historically, they've made good on that threat, that is Islamic law). They'll also tell you that their ultimate goal is to bring Islam to all the world, by force if needed most will admit is part of the Quran. You'll get no such admission from closet socialists, though you'll get it from some of the more outright varieties like Ayers. One reason he'd be unelectable for anything. Further the only difference between a Socialist and a Communist is the Communists admitted willingness to use force to achieve his goals. Otherwise they're pretty much one in the same. So far Obama has proved himself willing to use, if not direct force, at least the suffering of others to achieve his goals, as unwilling to admit it as he might be, and that's even more contemptible.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1357691205362</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 19:26:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357693392854-25</Id><Title>Wakup Call!</Title><Msg>Gooooooooooooooog Mooooooorniiiiiiiiing America - how are you???? Already we hear the first #$%$ and moaning from Obimbocrats when they opened their first paychecks (here on Ch.5 from Minneapolis - the all democRAT Senate, House and governor) and there is more to come, because some companies haven't made their adjustments yet! Wait till all see their new health care insurance premiums, some increases as high as 56%! Welcome to Obimbocare and round 2 is to follow in 2014, better be rich or you won't have insurance! More taxes, higher premiums, less health care providers, more inflation, another recession and more "GOOD" left wing rules to come! Let's hope that there isn't an other war which could easly be started by Israel, if we don't give the bricks to Iran! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357693392854</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357696016347-26</Id><Topic><Title>GOP heros</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1357694471613</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:21:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should know the plural of “hero” is “heroes”, not “heros”. Just one more tragic example of how bad the American educational system has become.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1357696016347</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 20:46:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357704362219-27</Id><Topic><Title>Skywanker</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1357489503250</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-06 11:25:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bless you</Msg><Username>kptodya</Username><Timestamp>1357704362219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 23:06:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357707349643-28</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment rises to a new hig.................</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1357675968989</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 15:12:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifism Pilgrim, listen up. There's no greater anti-Capitalist than a Capitalist. Trust me on this. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( I once worked for a Socialist Bossman-he was a multi-millionaire. We went to dinner in Chicago, so I had da tab on my expense. When it came time for da friggin tip, guess what he told me, huh? Anybody? I tried to leave 20%, since he gave da poor girl a hard time and was getting pretty testy after 5 drinks. Ans: "What da #$%$ are you doing Bear, don't give her more than a couple of bucks. She's just a friggin waitress. " So much for da Man who supported every friggin welfare program, but, took every tax loophole on da books, and some not. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1357707349643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-08 23:55:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>