<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-27"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359266019565-1</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>agreed... provided e-trade wasn't the originator... which i think they were</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359266019565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 00:53:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359266105545-2</Id><Topic><Title>E-Trade buyout inevitable</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1352730299528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>E-trade is the perfect merger candidate... without the one-time losses associated with the early extinguishment of high-rate debt... E-trade would have been profitable... loans balances have come down to a much more manageable level... only $10.1 bill... so between commissions being as low as they are for everyone... real estate recovery limiting E-trade’s loan losses... economies of scale &amp; elimination of duplicate expenses... merging with another discount brokerage makes perfect sense.</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359266105545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 00:55:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359269652723-3</Id><Topic><Title>E-Trade buyout inevitable</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1352730299528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Merging with another discount brokerage does not make sense...Ameritrade and Schwab don't need E*Trade, they have their own infrastructure, people, and trading platforms. It would be more economical for competitors to simply offer large amounts of money to E*Trade customers to switch. I think it makes more sense for a large money center bank (Citi, Wells, BofA) to acquire the company. They have the expertise to manage the rest of the loan book, AND they have been trying to build retail stock brokerage businesses with less-than-stellar results.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1359269652723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 01:54:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359271413491-4</Id><Topic><Title>E-Trade buyout inevitable</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1352730299528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gora, I remember the brokerages used to show how much it cost to bring on new a/c's... it was like $600-700 as i recall... so you're right... a takeover by Citi or BofA would give merged entity instant gravitas... boost earnings... and would be a win-win for everyone. Let's hope so.</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359271413491</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 02:23:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359287983587-5</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Etrade purchased essentially all of the mortgage portfolios from other parties. I think they can prove that these mortgages were misrepresented to them. Why are they not taking action? Many companies have filed lawsuits and collected damages for these toxic mortgages that were packaged and sold. Etrade was the first publicized victim of holding these toxic martgages. These mortgages destroyed the company causing it to lose 95% of its value. Etrade has the best case to pusue and collect damages so why are they doing nothing and not pursuing litigation to restore shareholder value.</Msg><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359287983587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 06:59:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301441706-6</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>race... you could be on to something... per 4Q08 transcript... And fifth, we stopped purchasing mortgage loans in mid-2007 ... so why hasn't etrade tried to put these loans back on the sellers... not sure</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359301441706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359301791284-7</Id><Topic><Title>Super Bowl Ad for Etrade</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1359143976935</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 14:59:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>E*trade buying commercial in this year’s Superbowl... why... who is going to switch brokerages over a baby... waste a money imho</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359301791284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 10:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359305615942-8</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lawyers for E-trade made the decision over two years ago that they did not have a case. Yes ETFC did buy some baskets of mortgages and sold those off to Citadel early '08 for pennies on the dollar. Where ETFC made a huge gamble and lost was in the "Home equity" loans, anybody walking in the door essentially got a loan with little credit research on those individuals and many had been underwater on 1st mortgages. Thats what happens when you work commission, you make the sale and be dammed the consequenses. There are more lawsuits against E-trade than the company itself is persuing.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1359305615942</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 11:53:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359306122217-9</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do not agree with you. Why wouldn't Etrade have a case to collect damages from miss represented mortgages? The home equity loans were not the main issue. It was the $3-4 billion CDO that was sold to Etrade and misrepresented. Etrade should be able to litigate and collect damages like all other parties have done that were sold these products.</Msg><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359306122217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:02:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359307367801-10</Id><Topic><Title>Should new Etrade CEO file lawsuit against banks and mortgage lenders?</Title><Username>racebanner2</Username><Timestamp>1359241295475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-26 18:01:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is up to the company that is making the purchase to do their own "due diligence" by doing their own audit or paying a firm to do it for them. CAT just lost $500 million by buying a sham company in China, they said they will take a hit on earnings for it. E-trade made huge mistakes, AMTD and other discount houses stayed far away because they had good advise. Best thing is to just let it go and learn a lesson, I got burnt by E-trade by believing Layton when he said publicly that the company would be profitable in '08 and we all know what happen and the second kick in the balls was the reverse split two momnths before they actually posted a quarterly profit. I feel your pain. And I have no legal recourse here.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1359307367801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 12:22:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359313756934-11</Id><Title>contest</Title><Msg>Can anybody describe Dianne Feinstein's face in 30 words or less without using the word "rat"?</Msg><Username>hydronicoctopussy</Username><Timestamp>1359313756934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:09:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359316498182-12</Id><Title>Ain't no cure for stupid!</Title><Msg>Man gets shot at gun show? Good that he knew which direction the gun shots. Stupid is as stupid does: Rahm Emanuel injured his right middle finger during beef slicing incident at Arby’s. Don't worry, he is a mayor of one of the largest cities in the entire world. No wonder it is in such a mess! Boy! This man can't even show his middle finger without being laughed at. Well, may be Rahm wouldn't injure his middle finger if butcher knives sales were banned? Pressing gas accelerator pedal instead of break kills a lot of people. So, shall we stop making cars with gas accelerators?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1359316498182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:54:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359318246859-13</Id><Topic><Title>E-Trade buyout inevitable</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1352730299528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B C W. What's yours. But I am dreaming the impossibles. G M A</Msg><Username>usaus21</Username><Timestamp>1359318246859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:24:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359320102061-14</Id><Topic><Title>E-Trade buyout inevitable</Title><Username>o.investor</Username><Timestamp>1352730299528</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Best fit is BofA, but I am not sure that they will be so bold. My guess is Wells. Best outcome is all three making a bid. But it is too early. Wait until H2'14. Lots of value to rebuild.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1359320102061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 15:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359344993899-15</Id><Topic><Title>Big strong volume</Title><Username>perryk01</Username><Timestamp>1359139113478</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-25 13:38:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The recent spike of the general stock market is a bit wary. Don't know when the trend will reverse. By then, ETFC will reverse with the general market. If given time, there is a chance to climb to the middle 11-12 range near term, just judging the shape of the chart without using any rules. I guess the best game is to buy calls continuously, namely, buying $11 now, and when it moves to $11, buy the $12 calls. Then wait for a pull back from 11-12 to the new base of $10 to refill. 2012, the best stocks I traded on were SCHW and PTEN. I kind of wash-traded the whole year's stock loss against the gain on SCHW and PTEN. That was, for your info, about $80,000 loss versus $80,000 gain from mainly SCHW and PTEN. How did it happen? Another new experience I gained. Never itchy to pull a trigger any time. But save the bullets for the change of the market. When that happens, throw in the kitchen sink to play the market. I threw in $150k in Jan 2012, and another $150k in June 2012 to manage to extract gains to offset the loss incurred at the turn of 2011-2012. So, the tip is that if you have a few thousand dollars, just put it in a checking account. Even for an IRA account of some 30,000, do not bother to invest in the stock market. You just need to trade 1-2 months of the year with a one time splash of $100k+ and then pull out. I pulled out since Nov-Dec 2012, and I did not miss the missed opportunity. There is always another opportunity. I did not tolerate a loss of even ten cents now. So, I had refrained from buying stocks. I would continue to sell puts on good quality stocks, and with 100k+ funds, you could sell puts and still make good money. ETFC is not one of the good stocks to sell puts. Out of range puts are fine.</Msg><Username>etfc2013</Username><Timestamp>1359344993899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 22:49:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359349182807-16</Id><Topic><Title>contest</Title><Username>hydronicoctopussy</Username><Timestamp>1359313756934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 14:09:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES! - Pelosi! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359349182807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-01-27 23:59:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>