<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367850665317-1</Id><Title>New problem mortgage loan rates fell - ETFC owns $10B in mortgages, market cap is only $3B</Title><Msg>New problem mortgage loan rates fell to 0.84% in March, according to Lender Processing Services (LPS), the first time below 1% since 2007 (it averaged 0.55% from 2000-2004). Negative equity is the key, says LPS' Herb Blecher, and it's falling fast thanks to rising prices http://seekingalpha.com/currents/post/1000181</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367850665317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858050078-2</Id><Topic><Title>FORECAST: In 20 Years E-Trade Is The Worlds Largest Bank!</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1367521094828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-05-02 14:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm understanding you on the full and full. In fact I have one stock that I have 50,000 shares of on a speculative (and not really that speculative) Tungsten play. The company started to screw up, the stock price went down, then languished, and I managed to get in REALLY cheaply compared to most other investors. Sure, I may have to hold the sucker for 10 years to see full value as the mine starts to prove production and tungsten prices go through the roof as China essentially gains a monopoly on this strategically important metal. I can live with that. Compared to what I have in eTrade what I have in Woulfe isn't that much, and my only real objection to the position is that it's not really marginable. In fact even one of my two "short term game plays" is capitalized more than the mine is (Apple of course, I've been making money on Apple since the 1990's. It isn't always a buy, but it frequently is).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367858050078</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367858410732-3</Id><Topic><Title>New problem mortgage loan rates fell - ETFC owns $10B in mortgages, market cap is only $3B</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367850665317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argh . . . quit pointing out that ETrade's book value is far far FAR higher than its market cap. The fractional decline in equity due to deflationary action isn't going to even put a serious scratch on that total, and the housing market is coming back, as I expected it would. So, let's NOT nose around what stinking steal this stock is until we've had the chance to suck all of it up that we can possibly get before the rest of the street figures it out. Right now ETFC is, aside from the SuperBowl commercial tradition, staying pretty dark, and they're being closemouthed about elements of their holdings because they have NO desire to make a promise it may turn out they can't keep. On the inside though, and ignoring all discretion required on the inside, they're bubbling with joy. The new officers took a TON of restricted stock and options as part of their contracts and are looking to see a HUGE payday in the future. We'll get paid then as well.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367858410732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 12:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367862089738-4</Id><Topic><Title>New problem mortgage loan rates fell - ETFC owns $10B in mortgages, market cap is only $3B</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367850665317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If things were so obviously bright, then why did Kenny sell all his shares? Part of me says it is bad ,but I have seen many hedge funds cash out their equity. I also noticed that the stocks started to become volatile after the sale. IMO, these hedge funds feel they will make more money trading than holding the shares.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1367862089738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 13:41:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367865589764-5</Id><Topic><Title>Gov. Moonbeam cleans up the GOP mess</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367699735118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:35:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP has not been in charge for decades in terms of the legislature, and Moonbeam raised taxes, not balance the budget...wise up! Surprise, surprise the money goes to teacher unions...hey, the wheathers good.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367865589764</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 14:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367867076679-6</Id><Title>Give us you poor, your tired masses, longing to be free</Title><Msg>**the cost of benefits and services to millions of newly minted citizens would reach nearly $10 trillion** Free to free load of the American taxpayer. Why are we bringing in people who can't take care of themselves, can't buy homes, and blow up are citizens. This is insanity no matter what party you are affiliated with. The country is broke, how many more push cart operators do we need, poor peasants, and people who hate the country other than what they can get...The American people are the biggest SAPS on the planet bar none. Oh yea, the first dpoe who says that we are a land of immigrants will prove my point about being a sap. Amnestied Illegals Will Get $9.4T in Benefits; Increase Debt $6.3T' Granting amnesty to illegal immigrants would cost $6.3 trillion, according to a new report by the Heritage Foundation. “Unlawful immigration and amnesty for current unlawful immigrants can pose large fiscal costs for U.S. taxpayers,” states the report by Robert Rector and Jason Richwine, Ph.D. Not only would the federal deficit increase, but the cost of benefits and services to millions of newly minted citizens would reach nearly $10 trillion. “Over a lifetime, the former unlawful immigrants together would receive $9.4 trillion in government benefits and services and pay $3.1 trillion in taxes,” the report states. “They would generate a lifetime fiscal deficit (total benefits minus total taxes) of $6.3 trillion.” Rector and Richwine took into account direct benefits, such as Social Security, Medicare, unemployment insurance, and workers’ compensation, as well as means-tested welfare benefits, public education costs and population-based services in reaching their findings.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367867076679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367870966016-7</Id><Topic><Title>Give us you poor, your tired masses, longing to be free</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367867076679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the societal costs of 1million unwanted children yearly following the criminalization of abortion?</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367870966016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:09:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367871372381-8</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He obsessesabout four Stae/CIA pros who knew the risks when they signed up. Hundreds of thousands of innocent Iraqi civilians and uncounted dead from terrorists inspired by our illegal and immoral invasion and occupation are ignored.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367871372381</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 16:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367876433509-9</Id><Topic><Title>Give us you poor, your tired masses, longing to be free</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367867076679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>George W bush pumping housing for all: "You see, we want everybody in America to own their own home. That’s what we want. This is – an ownership society is a compassionate society. More and more people own their homes in America today. Two-thirds of all Americans own their homes, yet we have a problem here in America because few than half of the Hispanics and half the African Americans own the home. That’s a homeownership gap. It’s a – it’s a gap that we’ve got to work together to close for the good of our country, for the sake of a more hopeful future. We’ve got to work to knock down the barriers that have created a homeownership gap. I set an ambitious goal. It’s one that I believe we can achieve. It’s a clear goal, that by the end of this decade we’ll increase the number of minority homeowners by at least 5.5 million families. (Applause.)" Bush and crew boasted that the housing boom was proof of the success of the gop , before the bubble burst, anyway.......after it was W mumbling "unless money is loosened up, the sucker could go down"</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367876433509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 17:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367878675495-10</Id><Topic><Title>Give us you poor, your tired masses, longing to be free</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367867076679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 15:04:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Mom wishes she would have aborted me. Bidder</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1367878675495</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:17:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367880265417-11</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The losing team has only one play. And they play it over and over.</Msg><Username>monsewer_america</Username><Timestamp>1367880265417</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367880893659-12</Id><Topic><Title>New problem mortgage loan rates fell - ETFC owns $10B in mortgages, market cap is only $3B</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367850665317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only technical I learnt was the flag and pole I first came across 20 years ago. According to this flag and pole, Etrade should go from 10.80 to above $11 in a similar length as what it previously launched from, namely, 10.80 minus the base line at 10.20 to yield an upside potential of 60 cents at minimum. This means a sure price of $11.40 in the coming days.</Msg><Username>etfc2013</Username><Timestamp>1367880893659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 18:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367881245936-13</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Creepy. But typical opinion from cynical left. A soldier who goes to war knows he can die, but even he expects all possible support from his commanders and peers. Those 4 dead in Benghazi didn't go to war or on suicide mission. They expected to be protected. In fact they begged for it. They were left to die. They didn't have to die. But this administration issued them a sentence.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367881245936</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 19:00:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367883128658-14</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter is ashamed of Obama. Benedict Arnold is ashamed of Obama!</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1367883128658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 19:32:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367885198912-15</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>America is ashamed of Republicans.Their hate for Obama is greater than any patriotism for America.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1367885198912</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 20:06:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367887058031-16</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama worshiping is your understanding of the word patriotism? Very deep!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367887058031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 20:37:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367892036862-17</Id><Title>Is E*Trade the next Sprint?</Title><Msg>I was in on Sprint when it was in the 2s. I owned a small piece for several years and was a customer. I could see the incredible value locked up in the company. When looking to talk about the stock web forums like thsi were just dead of activity. I've also owned ETFC for quite some time and have loaded up to a significant position. I just feel that the value in ETFC is not respected or understood but will be unlocked. I can see Cramer pumping the stock soon as part of his trend to look for hidden value in housing stocks.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367892036862</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367893772718-18</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one stopping you from going over there and trying to help them is there?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367893772718</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:29:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367894302465-19</Id><Topic><Title>New problem mortgage loan rates fell - ETFC owns $10B in mortgages, market cap is only $3B</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1367850665317</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 10:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kenny sole his shares because they wouldn't let him strip the company of capital leaving it a hollow shell for Citadel to move into, that's why. The value in eTrade isn't going to come out in what a modern "executive" would consider a fast enough time to properly reward HIM. They want to turn any value into instant liquidity so they can invest it elsewhere, and eTrade wasn't making it happen enough for him or his friends.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367894302465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367894370966-20</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since always. The only significant difference is the willingness of Communists to use EXTREME violence to achieve their ends.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367894370966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 22:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367895774520-21</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Former President Jimmy Carter delivered a 4-minute video address to the Democratic convention, saying Obama offered a "clear choice" for voters. As Carter's image beamed into the arena, Republican Mitt Romney's campaign issued a news release declaring, "Welcome Back, Carter!" Republicans have tried to tie Obama to Carter, comparing the current unemployment rate of 8.3 percent to the economic "malaise" of the late 1970s. A Romney spokesman said by choosing Carter to appear on the opening night of the convention, Obama "chose a fitting surrogate." In the video address, Carter credited Obama with helping middle-class families, saying he "always put the interests of middle-class Americans above those who often, with the larger wallets, have an ever louder voice."</Msg><Username>oldtimer60</Username><Timestamp>1367895774520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:02:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367896565208-22</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Racial hate is your understanding of patriotism ? A different color of President has driven most in your party absolutely, irrationally mad. To the point where your party chooses to hurt America in order to defy Obama.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1367896565208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:16:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367896925855-23</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My grandfather fought for the Kaiser. So, by your thinking, I should hate all Germans. And Austrians. And Swiss, etc. Fortunately for we Cro Magnon, your type is dying out.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1367896925855</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:22:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367897438105-24</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference between socialism and communism: Socialism has a lot to do with the economic system, whereas communism in addition to economic system would concentrate more on the political system as well. Communism believes that the removal of capitalism is the way to achieve classless society. Socialism on the contrary believes that class society can be brought about even trough capitalists. Thus socialism believes in the involvement of as many people as possible to bring about economic control.</Msg><Username>rampant_rose</Username><Timestamp>1367897438105</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-05-06 23:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message></Date>