<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367233601282-1</Id><Topic><Title>IMO Company Needs To Issue Shares-At Least $300 million</Title><Username>nickbritt02</Username><Timestamp>1367174690050</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-28 14:44:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can wait the year. This is my long term hold, and was priced presuming it would be spending SEVERAL years as dead money. That it'll spend considerably LESS time as dead money than originally thought is where the real news is, and why the stock is holding its own despite the $200M in loss provisions for this year.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367233601282</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 07:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367233863286-2</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We had no "terrorist list" per se in 1982, and if we did the Mudjahideen were not on it. In fact we were funneling them so much material that the ONLY thing surprising is we were giving them a MANPAD than some main Army formations hadn't gotten yet. (those units were still fielding REDEYE when we were giving a limited number of Stinger units to the Mudj) Groups on our "terrorists list" back then were almost entirely communist backed and socialist aligned. Red Brigades, Baader-Meinhof Gang, Shining Path, etc etc etc.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367233863286</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 07:11:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367243135136-3</Id><Title>the consensus of real scientists</Title><Msg>al gore is fat , therefore global warming does not exist. as if we even need the science. It still snows a lot in winter too! and plus the bible says there will be no global warming: in Genesis 8:22, we’re told of a promise by God never to use global floodwaters again as a means of destroying life on Earth. In that promise, the Bible explicitly states: “While the earth remaineth, seedtime and harvest, and cold and heat, and summer and winter, and day and night shall not cease.”</Msg><Username>investorpelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367243135136</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 09:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367245247362-4</Id><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Msg>shoddy weather science is gospel</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367245993684-5</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>silly, silly man! why would anyone who can think , think that science is biblical dogma? science is falsifiable. the fact of global warming is a verifiable fact which NO scientist , or honest person denies or could prove false. And there is a consensus among climate scientists that the recent rise in global average temperature is caused by human fossil fuel burning, although there are one or two climate scientists who disagree.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367245993684</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:33:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367250909815-6</Id><Topic><Title>We named the airport in our national capital for a man who sold weapons stolen from Pentagon warehouses to Ayatollah Khomeini</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1366982802422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-26 09:26:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obimbocare will go DOWN in flames and he will be remembered as the WORST wannabe president, (the communinty organizer) that voted one time in the congress as PRESENT, the only legacy is - that he was the first black one! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367250909815</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 11:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367260579387-7</Id><Title>Here's our idiots list . . .</Title><Msg>These poor "un"-share holders who's only upcoming decision is if they should cover now, or take more losses later. Latest SI report. 4/15/2013 Shares Short 17,918,619 Avg Vol 3,668,700 Days to Cover 4.884188</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367260579387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 14:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367269521586-8</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The evidence is powerful, straightforward, and damning. NASA satellite instruments precisely measuring global temperatures show absolutely no warming during the past the past 10 years. " Forbes 6/2011, citing NASA Satillite data.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1367269521586</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 17:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367271527657-9</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you quoting your own lying letter to the editor or what? ( maybe it was NASA data as misinterpreted by a moron?)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367271527657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 17:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367272382786-10</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep, your quote comes from a rightwing lawyer from the Heartland Institute. His article is just a lie, and he obviously doesn't know what he is talking about. but what could be expected from a guy who majored in government and went on to get a law degree and then a job writing bs op-ed for his oil money/tobacco money/rightwing nutcase bosses at the heartland institute who also tell you that cigarette smoke is not bad for you.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1367272382786</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 17:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367274434597-11</Id><Topic><Title>Here's our idiots list . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367260579387</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 14:36:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, you would have to think about call buying as a hedge for a short position. Second, do you really think those shorts are retail? Those are big firms in the know, and that trade has worked well for quite a while now. Those boys and girls will stay on it until the trade no longer works.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1367274434597</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 18:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367278351566-12</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on again lucky! You and Al Gore must be related? Come up here for global warming -ice still on the lakes and 40F on coming Wednesday - should be 70s!!! Fishing opener wont happen and most of the resorts are still closed, but we did have a nice 70s weekend! A vulcano errupution spews more toxins and carbon in the air then even CA can create in 100 years - and we won't even talk about Russia, China and the rest of the polluting world!!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367278351566</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 19:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367278990297-13</Id><Title>Liberal GAY CA ......</Title><Msg>........needs to make sure that after the gun law failed that there is a ban on knifes!!! If the 8 year old girl would have gotten shot, there would have been a chance that the guy missed vital organs, but a knife wound bleeds you to death and its a slow death! But then again Schaffhausen, which slit his 3 daughters throat here.............at least he got 3 life sentences, no parole, the people didn't buy his insanity play - to bad we don't have the death sentence here in WI, something I have to talk to Gov. Walker about! But we have too many bleeding hearts here, remember WI used to be a democRATic state for over 50 years! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367278990297</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 19:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367279179156-14</Id><Title>Obimbo!</Title><Msg>That was a well fitting hairpeace at the press meeting - all he needed was a DUNCE cap to go with it and then we han send him to Iran and N-Korea for negotiations! I think the Ayatola and Ping Pong would be impressed! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367279179156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 19:46:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367282324728-15</Id><Title>Republican Backlash Claims 5 More Senators !</Title><Msg>It gets worse every day for the Pubs who voted against the gun bill . Sen. Lisa Murkowski's (R-Alaska) net approval rating dropped 16 points, as she shed much of her previous cross-party appeal. Sen. Rob Portman (R-Ohio) saw his numbers dive 18 points, from a positive to a negative rating. Not all of the change can be attributed to the vote. Portman, for instance, saw his approval drop among Republicans when he announced his support for gay marriage in March. But in Alaska, Arizona, Nevada and Ohio, at least 60 percent of voters supported background checks, and many expressed disappointment with politicians who voted otherwise.................. IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE END FOR CAVE DWELLERS ! hehe</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1367282324728</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 20:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367282628486-16</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Absolutely no warming ? How do they explain the massive melting of glaciers ? The northern seas opening up with no ice ? Sea levels rising ? Only a right wingnut could see glaciers melt and think nothing changes.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367282628486</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 20:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367282715730-17</Id><Topic><Title>Liberal Arts Majors Agree</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1367245247362</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 10:20:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It takes a very small mind to think your local climate reflects the entire planet.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1367282715730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 20:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367292866351-18</Id><Title>Grover Norquist move over!</Title><Msg>Internet sales tax bill roils GOP alliances The tax pledge fanatic is wetting his pants, because more politicians reject the anti-tax pledge he created. The internet sales tax billcleared its finalhurdle on a bipartisan Senate vote 63-30. Final Senate pessage is scheduled for next Monday, and that tally is likely to be even more strongly in favor. Earlier test votes won as many as 75 yeses. And House action, once unthinkable, mabe unstoppable. Many Pubs have just shrugged. The bill's supporters include tea party conservatives like Sen. Ron Johnson, R-Wis, and GOP leaders like Sen. John Thune of South Dekota. They argue that the bill, which could generate $24 billion in new tax revenue, is not a tax increase at all. It only ensures that taxes already owed are actually paid.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1367292866351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-29 23:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>