<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367900063427-1</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"believes that the removal of capitalism" Hence the violence and incitement of violent revolt for whatever cause wherever they could cause it. One of the central ideas behind hijacking population revolutions was the former leaders could later be liquidated in the process of "purifying" the revolution. etc etc etc. All the excuses socialists use to try to explain why socialism never works can no more plainly be seen than in the excesses of the communist state.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367900063427</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 00:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367904436551-2</Id><Topic><Title>Gov. Moonbeam cleans up the GOP mess</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367699735118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 16:35:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just a few months ago, the wingnuts told us CA was falling into the sea.....</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1367904436551</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 01:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367911231952-3</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those with larger wallets are having louder voice? Quite an exaggeration. No, they don't control over megaphones, they only have larger bank accounts. Loudest voices are on the side of our demagogue in chief, who wouldn't stop talking about fair share, which has no definition, of course. Fair share is just more. Idea is to keep it open ended, so next time to satisfy the mob he can always demand more again. He says "you didn't build that". So, when govt comes asking to have bigger skin in the game, don't resent, you just got lucky, you didn't deserve your wealth. Now, what is fair share for middle class? Is this unfair question? It's no coincidence that every single dictator in the world came to power with talking points about staying on the side of middle class, the poor and oppressed. As a result, the poor only gets poorer and more oppressed than ever. Well, we got much more poor people in the past 4.5 years. This part of the plan successfully accomplished. What's next? Build more prisons for the opposition?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1367911231952</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 03:20:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367937751515-4</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't John Holmes a cummunist?</Msg><Username>shineola_98</Username><Timestamp>1367937751515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 10:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367938892725-5</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For someone who doesn't know the difference between 'where' and 'wear,' why do you expect anyone to care what you think. Who'd want to work for you anyway?</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1367938892725</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367940349817-6</Id><Title>Fat boy announces prez bid!</Title><Msg>Source: Wall Street Journal He says he did it for his wife and kids, not for his political ambitions. But either way, the political world gobbled up news early Tuesday that New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie had secretly undergone stomach surgery to lose weight. The story, first reported in the New York Post, quotes the governor on why he chose the lap-band procedure to shrink the size of his stomach. “I’ve struggled with this issue for 20 years,” he told the paper. “For me, this is about turning 50 and looking at my children and wanting to be there for them.” Asked whether it might have something to do with any potential 2016 presidential ambitions, Mr. Christie said, “It’s so much more important than that.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367940349817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367941673757-7</Id><Title>Do shineola and his gay buddies have a pattern?</Title><Msg>Nothing on Sunday. I think s/he woke up under somebody very fat and disgusting on Sunday. And was completely in love. Yesterday, they were absent until afternoon. Probably took their new beefaloe love to the Golden Corral. Then they posted a few times in a few hours and shut it down. They were not here first thing, but they showed up. Hey, shiney, did the Beefaloo go to work?</Msg><Username>incompetent_kendonesian</Username><Timestamp>1367941673757</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367941702522-8</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am curious, what exactly is the rights belief on this, what exactly did the president do, and what were his motives in issuing them a death sentence?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1367941702522</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367944200755-9</Id><Topic><Title>Fat boy announces prez bid!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367940349817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try again with your Washington Post crummy reporting and only speculating toilet paper! He has come out and said publicly: I am 50 and want to lose weight - I am NOT running for president! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367944200755</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:30:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367944318205-10</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most, if not all, of the Skandinavian countries adhere to a socialist system, but they also have no qualms with regulated capitalism. cigi_fubar, As far as I can see, you're beating around the bush in regard to this issue and as a Pub you usually want to have the last word.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1367944318205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 12:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367948302061-11</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With foot long organ - he was definetly a CAPITALIST!!! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367948302061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 13:38:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367950401618-12</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I ain't the one following up on another persons question to me out of turn. In fact the differing views on the use of violence and the value of human life aren't the ONLY differences, but they're the most significant, and short of equipping each reader with at least a BSc in Political Science I think it'll have to do. Socialism, people are still people. Communism, people are an extension of the state. The death, violence, and stupid decisions follow from that fallacious position.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367950401618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951128054-13</Id><Topic><Title>Fat boy announces prez bid!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367940349817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, I have really learned to appreciate the governor. He not only realizes that his health is very important to his family, but he also is a politician who wants to the best he can for his constituents and not necessarily the party. The Republican party is bashing and ridiculing this man because he talked with the President about help for his tate after the tornado. He should run for president as an independend.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1367951128054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367951552713-14</Id><Title>The perils of GOP style regulation</Title><Msg>Ammonium Nitrate Was Cause of Texas Explosion, State Agency Says Source: Reuters Ammonium nitrate was cause of Texas explosion, state agency says Tue May 7, 2013 8:45am EDT SAN ANTONIO, Texas (Reuters) - Investigators have determined that ammonium nitrate was the cause of the explosion at a West, Texas, fertilizer plant last month that left 14 people dead and some 200 injured, a spokeswoman for the Texas state fire marshal's office said on Tuesday. "The investigators have been able to narrow down the origin to the fertilizer and seed building on site, and we also know that what caused the explosion was the ammonium nitrate," said Rachel Moreno, a spokeswoman for the Texas State Fire Marshal's Office. "What we don't know is exactly why." The fire marshal's office has been leading the investigation of the April 17 blast, along with the federal Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives agency (ATF). Ammonium nitrate is a dry fertilizer mixed with other fertilizers such as phosphate and applied to crops to promote growth. It can be combustible under certain conditions, and was used as an ingredient in the Oklahoma City bombing in 1995 that left 168 people dead.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951552713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367951996825-15</Id><Topic><Title>The perils of GOP style regulation</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951552713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"They had as of 2012 , 270 tons of ammonium nitrate in storage, which is 1350 times the amount that they were permitted to have. And the company should have reported that they had this much as this how it is to be done. Self reporting and no over sight. Any farmer who has to blow up a stump or two knows that ammonium nitrate is what to use to blast the stump out of the ground. So many people know this is a very explosive chemical as it is what was used in Oklahoma City by Timothy McVeigh. The owner of the plant only carried a $1,000,000 liability insurance policy. The company itself is unlikely to survive the legal fallout, but the company is just a shield for the individuals who already got rich cutting corners. Probably hundreds of millions in damages, when all the suits are filed. I'm sure the owners will find a way to liquidate most of the company's assets and drop them into a legal defense fund while giving themselves a 200% raise for the decade-long duration of the trials. Then when the first round of decisions comes down against them, the company will declare bankruptcy and the perps will walk away richer than they would have been had the explosion not happened, while the victims get nothing. I cite generally the meat-packing, tobacco, oil, and pharmaceutical industries as prior examples of how to get rich and escape personal liability while running out the clock and waiting for the aggrieved to grow old and die."</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951996825</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955152837-16</Id><Topic><Title>The perils of GOP style regulation</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951552713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"So many people know this is a very explosive chemical as it is what was used in Oklahoma City by Timothy McVeigh." It's not a "very explosive chemical". In fact technically it doesn't produce a detonation under most circumstances but rather a deflagration, or rapid burning. Sometimes that burning is so rapid it produces an explosion, but in order to do that it has to also be compressed. C4, Semtex, and other "very explosive chemicals" have no such restrictions.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1367955152837</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:32:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955446145-17</Id><Topic><Title>The perils of GOP style regulation</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951552713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry, but this happen while under the regulation and over-site of the the Obama administration! Had Obama not stole the election this never would have happened! Certainly Obama's behemoth of a government should have the manpower to not allow this kind of gross violation of his regulations to occur. This is 100% on Obama's plate! Maybe a little less golf and constant campaigning and he'd have enough time to take care of business!</Msg><Username>tomfranklin96753</Username><Timestamp>1367955446145</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367955489955-18</Id><Topic><Title>The perils of GOP style regulation</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1367951552713</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 14:32:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not sure hat your point is. That 270 tons of this stuff wuld not be compressed, it was what, lying out over a square mile spread out?</Msg><Username>iizconfused</Username><Timestamp>1367955489955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367956780698-19</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Communist and Socialist both seek to transfer an individuals personal responsibility to the government. They indoctrinate the people into believing that they can only survive with the help of government, that government is the source of all needed for life and will always take care of them. All of this is a lie! In the end Communism and Socialism ALWAYS fails because of the nature of humans, when taken care of they get very lazy (just like animals) and fail to produce the goods and services needed by a country to survive and many loose the ability to take personal responsibility for their life and when these Communism and Socialism governments fail, and they ALWAYS do, MILLIONS ALWAYS DIE and cycle starts again with people being forced to take personal responsibility or die! If we could only find a way back to personal responsibility without so many having to die each time a country reaches the point of it's takers electing people that will give them more free stuff, rather than a person that can bring true prosperity by all citizens taking direct responsibility for their lives!</Msg><Username>tomfranklin96753</Username><Timestamp>1367956780698</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 15:59:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367958869075-20</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that why they say John Holmes was hung? Because he was communist?</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1367958869075</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 16:34:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367962067149-21</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rowdy is our board expert on Penii</Msg><Username>drill_baby_drillllllll</Username><Timestamp>1367962067149</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 17:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367965190547-22</Id><Topic><Title>Fat boy announces prez bid!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367940349817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have to agree with you on that one, because he is respected in a democratic state and he tries to balance the wellness of his constituents and the hostil unions and very left wing democrats! When the unions wouldn't let the volunteers from AL in to help out the victoms, that blew my cork!!! We had the same #$%$ here in WI, except even a lot of demcrats voted for governor Walker when the ultra left wanted him and my rep. senator Harsdorf in Madison recalled! Now all the sudden they like him because there is a surplus instead of a deficit, jobs increased, we have a "sunshine fund" for the first time and there are no increases in sales, property and gasoline taxes! Also the union must contributions are NO longer, so even the government unions like it! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1367965190547</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367966557058-23</Id><Topic><Title>Fat boy announces prez bid!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367940349817</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 11:25:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He should run.. around the block often.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1367966557058</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 18:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367978638709-24</Id><Topic><Title>I despise communists!</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1367075457994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-27 11:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your assessment reeks of Pub BS. In Scandinavian countries socialism and regulated capitalism go hand in hand.</Msg><Username>california_dem</Username><Timestamp>1367978638709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1367981376879-25</Id><Topic><Title>Shame about Ty Woods, Glen Doherty, Sean Smith and Christopher Stevens</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1367703273655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-05-04 17:34:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The coward needs a diversion. Watch for an aspirin factory in Syria to get blown up!</Msg><Username>the_shellac_man_cometh</Username><Timestamp>1367981376879</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-05-07 22:49:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>