<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-07"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357571963222-1</Id><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Msg>I'm a long term holder of this stock, think they have a great trading platform, are very slowely turing things around, but as most would agree have an awful mgmt team in place. With that said, has anyone ever received a response from IR? I send in a question on the CEO search about two weeks ago, and nothing, not even a generic thank you, someone will respond shorlty. This guy has been in place for quite some time, and taking a hefty salary, and it needs to stop. I realize attracting someone to a potential sinking ship is tough, but this search (without an update) is BS. ok, I'm done with my rant.</Msg><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357576112295-2</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you ever get the feeling there are a ton of managers at Etrade, sitting back collecting big salaries who add very little value? The money paid out to Freiberg over a couple of years is really staggering. Something like 25 million in cash......all while the stock price fell 50% in value. The current Chairman is clocking 500k per month as the interim CEO. Old wall street at it's finest.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1357576112295</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 11:28:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357591217573-3</Id><Title>fooled ya!</Title><Msg>Effective Jan. 1, the Social Security withholding tax rate on wages earned by employees has been increased from 4.2 percent to 6.2 percent. Under this change, a worker earning $60,000 in 2013 will have $1,200 more in Social Security tax withholding deducted from their paycheck. The Social Security wage base in 2013 is $113,700. Individuals who earn more than $200,000 will also see an additional .9 percent of Medicare tax on wages when their income exceeds that threshold.</Msg><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1357591217573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 15:40:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357593032219-4</Id><Title>What's another trillion dollars...in new taxes</Title><Msg>Damn those Obama phones are expensive. Dems look for up to $1T in new revenues Democrats say they want to raise as much as $1 trillion in new revenues through tax reform later this year to balance Republican demands to slash mandatory spending. Democratic leaders have had little time to craft a new position for their party since passing a tax deal Tuesday that will raise $620 billion in revenue over the next 10 years.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357593032219</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:10:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357593247710-5</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, you can't deny these hardworking money changers an addition on their Hampton home.... lighten up!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1357593247710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:14:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357594257216-6</Id><Topic><Title>a fact that republicans really hate</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1357593728485</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:22:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes. Republicans hate the fact that Barack Obama balooned defict 3x times. He added new $6T to the debt (versus Bush's $5 in 8 years), and we borrow more than 40c per dollar we spent(versus Bush's 15c). What's not to hate here?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1357594257216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 16:30:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357598699273-7</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep in mind that IR might not be able to answer your question under SEC rules a lot of the time everyone needs to be given the same information at the same time. Also I'm sure that'll come up on the next call. I to am long and am waiting for the turnaround to get some serious momentum. This should be the year.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1357598699273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 17:44:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357600686798-8</Id><Topic><Title>Investor Relations</Title><Username>excessofloss</Username><Timestamp>1357571963222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 10:19:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perfect Example..... TD just announced a launch of an "investor based index". Great idea huh? I have always thought the OLBs had great inside information regarding the sentiment of the individual investor and that information was very useful. How about an etf (free of commissions) which included the top holdings of individual investors? Well Etrade bought out Cake Financial for an undisclosed sum a few years back. That was exactly why Cake was established, sort of social media for stock investors. INSTEAD of doing something with it, etrade simply sat idle and now TD is front running the idea. Total dipsticks at Etrade......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1357600686798</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-07 18:18:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>