<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-10"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370837608884-1</Id><Title>Cummings calls Issa’s IRS bluff:</Title><Msg>‘I’ll release’ transcripts clearing White House if he doesn’t Last edited Sun Jun 9, 2013, 01:49 PM USA/ET Source: Raw Story ...................... “He’s the chairman of the committee, we’re not in power,” the Maryland Democrat pointed out. “If he does not release them, I will. Period.” “I’m willing to come on your show next week with the chairman, with the transcripts, if he agrees to do that,” he added. “But if he doesn’t, I’ll release them by the end of the week.” Crowley observed that in a portion of the transcripts that had been released, an IRS screening group manager in the Cincinnati office told Issa’s committee that he had “no reason to believe” that the White House had ordered the targeting of conservative groups. “He was a 21-year veteran,” Cummings said of the IRS manager. “He described himself in the interviews in response to a Republican attorney’s question as a conservative Republican. Very significant. He is a conservative Republican working for the IRS. I think these interviews and these statements go a long way to showing the White House was not involved in this.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1370837608884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 00:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370839013145-2</Id><Title>The O'Reilly Factor is wrong, again</Title><Msg>Now this is confusing. O'Reilly has been telling his viewers over and over again that Shulman visited the White House 157 times. Now he's waffling; Obama "defenders" deny it, but the records show he was "cleared" into the White House. Huh? The whole point of this story is to connect the White House to the IRS scandal over targeting conservative groups for additional scrutiny of their tax-exempt applications. The problem is that the story O'Reilly has been telling his viewers is not true. He picked it up from the right-wing website Daily Caller (5/29/13), which claims Shulman visited the White House far more often than any of Obama's cabinet officials. If that sounds a little hard to believe, that's because it is. As Garance Franke-Ruta explained at the Atlantic (5/31/13), those records do not show actual visits; the 157 number refers to instances where Shulman was approved to attend a meeting, mostly about the new healthcare law. (Slightly more than half of them, 80, were a regularly scheduled biweekly gathering of deputies working on the healthcare reform project; another 40 were with the director of the Office of Health Reform.) A large majority of the meetings Shulman was cleared to attend, 115 in all, were in the Old (Eisenhower) Executive Office Building, not in the White House itself. According to the same record-keeping, Shulman is known to have actually attended only 11 meetings in the White House complex between 2009 and 2012. And as far as the comparison with Cabinet members goes, the Daily Caller acknowledged in its original story that "it is probable that the vast majority of visits by major Cabinet members do not end up in the public record."</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1370839013145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 00:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370843664680-3</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amazing how simple concepts elude you. What is so hard to grasp about the difference between CLEARED to attend and actually attended? If you are invited to a wedding does it mean you were actually there? Answer...nope.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1370843664680</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 01:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370845089189-4</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So smart! Sorry. Didn't know request to attend WH meeting is equally important as to come to a wedding ceremony as guest. Don't remember ignoring my boss's meeting invitations that many times. I actually thought WH invites only those whose presence is needed.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370845089189</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 02:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370847563608-5</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nowhere near all of these meeting were with Obama. AND maybe this is new to you in your trade job, or behind the grill, but there are MUST ATTEND meeting invites, and OPTIONAL meeting invites (and he would have been cleared for the optional as well). IT is also quite common to invite high position people as an OPTIONAL invite, as a FYI, that they can attend if they like. This must be very confusing for the #$%$ pubs out there to grasp.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1370847563608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 02:59:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370850117852-6</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Er, no, he was asking if there was a reason for the disparity between the number of accorded clearances and the number of actual visits. Many times high administration officials are cleared to enter the White House, but never actually see the President himself. Some never see more than the inside of a waiting room, with VIP's getting a nicer one.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370850117852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 03:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370850361273-7</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Is Going All The Way Up To $120.00 Per Share. Here's Why:</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1370667422490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 00:57:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well the way things are now, if you're right, ill be rolling in it. Otherwise, I won't be too terribly disappointed. I settle for a double or so around that $24 to $30 range, at least with the 18 month LEAPS I have ;-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370850361273</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 03:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370850458328-8</Id><Topic><Title>The O'Reilly Factor is wrong, again</Title><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1370839013145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 00:36:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem comes from using "cleared to visit the White House" and using it like you meant to say "met with the President". There's a VAST difference.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370850458328</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 03:47:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370850588780-9</Id><Topic><Title>Doesnt anyone on this board talk about Etrade??</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370806680255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone knows we're in a "hurry up and wait" state. Since everything there is to be known seems to BE known and we have virtually no bears on this board with brains installed in their heads, basically we're all sitting around waiting for the inevitable recognition to be reflected in the stock price.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370850588780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 03:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370850782766-10</Id><Topic><Title>Another Angry Mooos-leem Nut Commits Massacre</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370786257465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:57:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually Muslims are encouraged to vote Democratic for forward the plans of the Uma.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370850782766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 03:53:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370868050230-11</Id><Title>the trillions spent on Iraq were well worth it!</Title><Msg>Bushy and the neocons wisely spent trillions and thousands of lives on Iraq Regime change which has made us and them better off! My gerbil says so what if the Chinese now get half of Iraq's oil production, still US companies made out nicely on the invasion, occupation and did make lots of oil deals.</Msg><Username>unluckyspankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1370868050230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 08:40:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370870086792-12</Id><Title>Discount Broker Group - ETrade is a lagger in the group</Title><Msg>Bloomberg is running stories about the discount broker group this morning, turns out ETFC is a minor lagger compared to Schwab and TD Ameritrade. This is GREAT NEWS as this means to me that there has been almost no extra value attributed to the stock based on what can only be massive improvement in the $10B loan portfolio. And yes the market cap is only ~$3.4B. How can we not double from these levels?</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370870086792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370870572386-13</Id><Title>'SPANKER' is quite the Unhinged Liberal</Title><Msg>What's wrong 'SPANKER'?? You're 'Chia Pet' (Gerbil) plnt died?/ Was it in the shape of 'CHE'?? Your ''CHE'-a-Pet' DIED??!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370870572386</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:22:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370870731061-14</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that fat lying liar O'reilly is also a Limbot, mindlessly repeating the lie that Shulman "visited the WH 157 times"</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870731061</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:25:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370870823234-15</Id><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Msg>NSA has massive database of Americans' phone calls Updated 5/11/2006 10:38 AM ET By Leslie Cauley, USA TODAY The National Security Agency has been secretly collecting the phone call records of tens of millions of Americans, using data provided by AT&amp;T, Verizon and BellSouth, people with direct knowledge of the arrangement told USA TODAY. The NSA program reaches into homes and businesses across the nation by amassing information about the calls of ordinary Americans — most of whom aren't suspected of any crime. This program does not involve the NSA listening to or recording conversations. But the spy agency is using the data to analyze calling patterns in an effort to detect terrorist activity, sources said in separate interviews. QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS: The NSA record collection program "It's the largest database ever assembled in the world," said one person, who, like the others who agreed to talk about the NSA's activities, declined to be identified by name or affiliation. The agency's goal is "to create a database of every call ever made" within the nation's borders, this person added. For the customers of these companies, it means that the government has detailed records of calls they made — across town or across the country — to family members, co-workers, business contacts and others. The three telecommunications companies are working under contract with the NSA, which launched the program in 2001 shortly after the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks, the sources said. The program is aimed at identifying and tracking suspected terrorists, they said.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370873256428-16</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you are a fan of government invasion of privacy - no matter who is in charge. you are pathetic</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1370873256428</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:07:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370875071625-17</Id><Topic><Title>Discount Broker Group - ETrade is a lagger in the group</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370870086792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:14:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stocks been a lager for years trading 1.20 presplit, I like the chart set up here as it seems to be breaking out off a 2 year base. Volumes are up and the loan book has to be much improved so the run up is based on returning to profitability. Its still way too cheap here compared to its peers.</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370875071625</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370875326779-18</Id><Title>Someone selling their LEAPS cheap</Title><Msg>$10 strike Jan '15 10 contracts offered at 3.2 I'd take them myself by I already loaded up at 2.75 (20) and 2.70 (5) when people made offers to sell on those inside the normal spread. Suck'em up, I'm already so heavily biased towards ETFC that even if I could invest more this month I'd probably hold back. Ownership on 2,500 shares and LEAPs on 2,500 shares which pre-split is about 50,000 shares is a bit more than my original goal of 10,000 or so (before the reverse split).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875326779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370875442847-19</Id><Topic><Title>Someone selling their LEAPS cheap</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875326779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never mind, the guy grew a brain and pulled them out of the queue. Ah well.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875442847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:44:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370877409311-20</Id><Topic><Title>Beck: "I wish I could take back everything I said"</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1370638711767</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is this important to YOU??? You claim not to be a racist, so stop asking people about their race and gender! He/she writes in plain English. Do you think you will understand the CONTENT better if you know his/her race or gender?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1370877409311</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370877750409-21</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since before 9/11 I've always assumed Gvt. had or could easily get access to my phone and e-mail. Will it now be the policy of the GOP to deny them access?</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1370877750409</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370877918188-22</Id><Topic><Title>Perhaps the gop should offer some honest ideas instead of hissie fits?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370353253225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-04 09:40:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"cognizant of the fact that you can't change human nature with legislation" Human NATURE ???? Do you even know what you are talking about? You can't change certain physical aspects of being human - like needing to eat or go potty -...... at least NOT YET, but what you refer to is NOT human NATURE - it's human BEHAVIOR. And that CAN be changed and IS changed all the time, And YES - legislation is precisely what is needed to change human behavior - especially any behavior that is damaging to society...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1370877918188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370878696341-23</Id><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Msg>Standard &amp; Poor's on Monday revised its credit outlook on the United States government to stable from negative.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370878696341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370878703695-24</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I started using encryption and setting up my own servers the instant I could. I know what's technically POSSIBLE, and if its possible I have to assume the government either has done it, or is working on it.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370878703695</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 11:38:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370886023759-25</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pelvis, Just about every administration has been accused of "invasion of pravacy" and the accusers don't know what their talking about. This surveillance program is nothing new and has been active and used for years. Senator Lindsey Graham and Senator Harry Reid have attestet to that members of the house and senate were briefed and know about this surveillance program. I have nothing to hide and if our intelligence agencies want to to spy and snoop into my phone calls, faxes, emails, etc., they have my permission. I would do almost anything to help our president to prevent another 9/11, or other terrorist acts. pelvis, The NSA doesnt give a darn tootin' about your extra Log Cabin affairs with gerbil, slayer, rodent, pacificant, bidder, etc. We should be much more concerned about hackers getting into our bank accounts, credit cards, SS acounts.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1370886023759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 13:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370886175938-26</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never heard of "OPTIONAL invites". Means your presence may be unnecessary? If you come it may be a waste of time? Did you just make it up? New rule? Or we can expect any kind of nonsense from this administration?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1370886175938</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 13:42:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370886623172-27</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they should stop it - and we should all be in agreement - dem/pub common ground the politburo is out of control in the USA</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1370886623172</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 13:50:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370890040156-28</Id><Title>United STASI of Amerika</Title><Msg>Stupid Obama is DEEKtator of the United STASI of Amerika. Big Brother is Watching?? Well, Stupid Obama is a Brotha.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370890040156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:47:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370890129894-29</Id><Title>Option writers sure don't want this above $12</Title><Msg>As then they start losing money bigtime . . . the $12 barrier is the only thing keeping it from moving into the 12.50 range before earnings, though it may take two more weeks to crack it at this rate. That'd take it out of my buy zone, but then I already have enough of this issue to wait for it to mature properly into those nice tax free long term capital gains on couples making less than $250k a year. That's a great relief to many retired people living on a fixed income who's only non-pension savings might be in in fund equities they may be holding since God knows when.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370890129894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370890415838-30</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The operative phrase is " cleared for visit " , NOT actual attendance. One could be cleared, but never actually arrive. There are many meetings at the WH. Depending on the nature of the meeting, groups could be cleared for visit, but may never attend.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1370890415838</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 14:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370891029235-31</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>trader, All of a sudden, some in the GOP want to use this so called "revelation" as a political football and to create another "scandal." In one way or another, our governments have always had access to our phone records, faxes, and now emails to be one step ahead of terrorists..</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1370891029235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:03:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370891082408-32</Id><Title>Hillary's #$%$</Title><Msg>Hillary's inner circle banging #$%$. One dressed in a Pantsuit sent to Presidential SWEEET for the wide-thigh Hillary. Cocaine and #$%$ parties all over the World. That is how Hillary spent your hard earned tax dollars. Now 'Benghazi' is easy to see why it happened.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370891082408</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370891701535-33</Id><Topic><Title>Someone selling their LEAPS cheap</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875326779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heh for all the thumbs down, there's still been more activity in that issue today than on almost any other day . . . people are seeing where ETFC is going and apparently more than I think this might be the start of the break out point. Buy it if you don't have it, hold it if you do, and cover if you're short,</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370891701535</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370891976329-34</Id><Topic><Title>nothing but a Fox Lie: the bs that IRS Shulman made 157 visits to the White House is a LIE</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370809653709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clearly you are blue collar.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1370891976329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:19:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370892196000-35</Id><Title>'BANG'-hazi (Hillary style)</Title><Msg>Banging Prostitutes and Cocaine with your hard earned tax dollars. Hillary taking notes from The Rapist Bill Clinton</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370892196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:23:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370893352050-36</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"they should stop it - and we should all be in agreement - dem/pub common ground the politburo is out of control in the USA" You're so FOS!!! Had BO shut down those programs, the GOP and hypocrites like you would be slamming him for being weak on terror. Go ahead GOP, tell the NSA to shut it down, I dare you.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1370893352050</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370894158710-37</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the GOP - is so wrong on: abortion spying on citizens (no matter what the reason) and a host of other topics end the end - our government has created a hive of worker bee citizens that can't fend for themselves - and remain at the mercy of these two parties that have a strangle hold on power.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1370894158710</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370894618791-38</Id><Title>clgl_fubar</Title><Msg>Let's review! From your public pronouncements: You're clearly anti-government planning a survivalist retreat. You display tendencies some might associate with racists or skinheads up to and including a hatred of POTUS. You claim to be ex-military with expertise in weapons up to and including tanks and other seriously destructive armaments. You claim serious expertise in tech and encryption disciplines. Given the above, HSA would be derelict if they weren't watching you. In fact, the "good citizen" in me is tempted to drop a dime on you and your friends.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370894618791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 16:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370896303375-39</Id><Topic><Title>clgl_fubar</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370894618791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 16:03:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course they're watching me you idiot, that was the point I was trying to make in one post, further, you've gotten some thing wrong, it would be ATF, not HSA, as I'm not a homeland threat, but I do have NFA weapons. I have had to fill out fingerprint cards probably more times than most criminals you know, and yet none was ever for a crime. I've had like 5 background checks, and my security clearance is probably semi-active. As for my military training, most combat arms vets can say the same if they've been in a unit with diverse armament. You not only learn your role but the other guy's role well enough you can fill in say, if your tank is a casualty but you're not. A Heavy Armored Cavalry Regiment (BO turned the last one into a Stryker brigade) has LOTS of different weapons even within a single troop (company) size formation and you tend to get more or less familiar with all of them. I don't "hate" Barrack Obama, I think I'd enjoy his company, it's just that he needed at least 10 years more seasoning to become President. I don't think he'll start to shine in the role until the second half of this term. I think we'd have probably been better off if Hillary hadn't been head of state, certainly I think that was one of his poorer decisions, but so far I don't have any problems with his domestic policies. Frankly I'd have let the Bush era tax cuts expire in their entirety and return them only to be applied in years where the government ran a surplus and debt was below 10% GDP. And what friends? I seem to be here alone in my body. Or are you referring to anyone you've labeled a "Tea Party" Republican, or a something Hat Conservative? I don't remember all the attempted epithets, but you do tend to lump all rocks in one pail. I'</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370896303375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 16:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370898082307-40</Id><Topic><Title>Someone selling their LEAPS cheap</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875326779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>43 contracts is nothing. Selling call options in this stock has been like a printing press for years.....</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1370898082307</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:01:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370898718766-41</Id><Topic><Title>Someone selling their LEAPS cheap</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370875326779</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 10:42:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Writing short term calls around earnings, yes . . . about LEAPS I'm not so sure. Still the last time I wrote calls against my position the stock went vertical and I only ended up with 20% of the profit I would have had without selling them.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1370898718766</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 17:11:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370902151262-42</Id><Topic><Title>Discount Broker Group - ETrade is a lagger in the group</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370870086792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:14:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am amazed at how the $10B in loans are seemingly not valued at all, what if we could sell the loan book at 70% of face value? That's still $7B in cash.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370902151262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 18:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370902399516-43</Id><Topic><Title>Doesnt anyone on this board talk about Etrade??</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370806680255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:38:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I do, politics are a waste of time. I suggest you post about E*Trade and also comment on the actual on topic threads. I also ignore these people using the system that are posting about politics.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1370902399516</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 18:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370905949960-44</Id><Topic><Title>the shocking revelation of government data mining!</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370870823234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 09:27:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pelvis No wonder you worry about being spied on - the politbuero has ordered you to you use encrypted emails. pelvis, you're too far out with your Neocon crapola.</Msg><Username>elksmember</Username><Timestamp>1370905949960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 19:12:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370906812026-45</Id><Topic><Title>Scandal: In the days after 911 W told Americans, to "Get down to Disney World in Florida"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370036549510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, Where was Darrell Issa then??? Where were the committees then??? Where were the scandals???</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1370906812026</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 19:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370911392713-46</Id><Title>Chartists</Title><Msg>Is there any chartist out who can offer an opinion on the highs of the last three months? We have challenged 11.87-88 three times and seem to hit a brick wall at that mark ... TIA</Msg><Username>long_view_2000</Username><Timestamp>1370911392713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370911681790-47</Id><Topic><Title>Scandal: In the days after 911 W told Americans, to "Get down to Disney World in Florida"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370036549510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-05-31 17:42:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What you mean is: Where were the dems then, right? Why were they (the dems) not investigating the malfeasance then? Likely they were to busy playing hide the sausage and lucky was getting lucky :)</Msg><Username>long_view_2000</Username><Timestamp>1370911681790</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:48:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370913632168-48</Id><Title>Michael Moore agrees with Glenn Beck. Trump &amp; coulter and the WSJ and obama agree otherwise</Title><Msg>You can draw your own opinions based on the following quotes of a bunch of famous people and news organizations who are wildly split on the NSA snooping issue. 1. Donald Trump. The once and possibly future presidential candidate and reality TV host isn’t a big fan of Edward Snowden, the former CIA analyst who leaked the classified info about the NSA. “To me, he looks like a grandstander,” he told Fox News. 2. Michael Moore. Snowden is “Hero of the Year,” says Moore on Twitter. 3. Ann Coulter. She believes the type of intelligence gathered by the NSA is OK, if it’s done by the right kind of administration. “You need a virtuous man in the presidency, so choose wisely next time, America,” she told Fox News. 4. Jack Welch. The former head of General Electric and former Obama critic on Twitter: “Two Presidents, and multiple split Congress’ all agree we need. Good enough for me.” 5. Glenn Beck. “I think I have just read about the man for which I have waited. Earmarks of a real hero,” Beck said on Twitter about Snowden. 6. The WSJ Editorial Board. The Journal editorial staff argues that the Obama data-mining operation is “legal and necessary” for national security. 7. The New York Times Editorial Board. The editorial says, “The administration has now lost all credibility on this issue” after saying something stronger (before a copy edit). 8. President Barack Obama. “You can’t have 100 percent security and also then have 100 percent privacy and zero inconvenience. We’re going to have to make some choices as a society. There are trade-offs involved,” the president said in defending the program. 9. Senator Dianne Feinstein. “Terrorists will come after us if they can and the only thing we have to deter this is good intelligence,” says Feinstein, who co-chairs the committee that oversees the program for Congress. 10. Senator Saxby Chambliss. “It has proved meritorious because we have gathered significant information on bad guys, but only on bad guys, over the years,”</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370913632168</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370914245469-49</Id><Topic><Title>Chartists</Title><Username>long_view_2000</Username><Timestamp>1370911392713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 20:43:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My take is we are trading above the 5 day ema which is a buy signal and also as you noted bumping up against resistance. I would like to see more vol though and maybe we will get it if the stock can trades above 12. The brokers have done very well and ET seems to be on the verge of a breakout looking at the 2 year chart. The stock has been making higher lows since Aug 2012 which is always a good thing.</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1370914245469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:30:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370914332461-50</Id><Title>how strange is it that Snowden fled to Hong Kong, which is run by the Peoples Liberation Army?</Title><Msg>everyone knows who runs Hong Kong.... the troops in the former British barracks there are the People's Liberation Army..... Hong Kong is the sovereign territory of Communist China, which allows it to have some autonomy and a capitalist system...... but they do limit personal freedoms ..... and they likely would have disappeared Snowden if he had messed with THEIR classified info.........and sent his family a bill for the bullet..... and anyway.... there is nothing new about his revelation....... the SAME data mining has been going on since 2001............................and that is exactly what Senator Saxby Chambliss said the other day and he should know, he sits on the Senate intel committee responsible...................... Americans should decide if we want to limit this type of intel tool and be less effective at watching for terrorism. here is how one person decided: I'm glad the NSA is trying to find out what the terrorists are up to overseas and in our country." Former Congressman Newt Gingrich here is another: Lindsey Graham ‘glad’ NSA tracking phones June 6, 2013 “I’m glad the NSA is trying to find out what the terrorists are up to overseas and in our country,” said the South Carolina Senator on “Fox &amp; Friends” this morning.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370914332461</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:32:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370914788373-51</Id><Title>Partisanship reigns ?</Title><Msg>"Pew is out with the first poll asking the public what it thinks of the NSA phone record surveillance program. Unsurprisingly, the public thinks it's just peachy, by a margin of 56-41. What is surprising, though, is the epic size of the change in partisan attitudes since 2006. Back then, Republicans approved of the (recently revealed) NSA program by 38 points more than Democrats. Now, Republicans disapprove by 12 points more than Democrats. This isn't the last word on the subject. The wording of the question is different this year compared to 2006, and that might account for a bit of the difference. But probably not much. Basically, when Bush was president, Republicans thought that monitoring telephone traffic was a great idea. Now, when Obama is president, they're not so sure—but Democrats think it's fine and dandy. This is about as remarkable a turnaround as I've seen on any subject in recent years." Bottom line, as long as they're not listening to your calls sans a warrant, no one cares. The phone co. log who you dial and for how long , for billing, service and marketing anyway, assumption Gvt. can get this is assumed IMHO.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370914788373</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:39:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370915368859-52</Id><Topic><Title>how strange is it that Snowden fled to Hong Kong, which is run by the Peoples Liberation Army?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1370914332461</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:32:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't get Snowden either, smells a bit like a publicity seeker. The whole thing is "recycled outrage", not much new info IMO. Here's what a future POTUS has to say: "Its Senator Al Franken talking about the NSA surveillance program. I don't always agree with my Senator. And he has certainly never shied away from challenging President Obama. But when it comes to trust - this guy is pretty close to the top of my list. To summarize, he points out that as a member of the Judiciary Committee - he has availed himself of the briefings about NSA and nothing that was made public lately surprised him. He said, "There's certain things that its appropriate for me to know that its not appropriate for the 'bad guys' to know...So anything the American people know, the 'bad guys' know...I can assure you that this isn't about spying on the American people. This is about having the data available so that if there are suspicions about foreign persons or persons that have connections with terrorist organizations that we can connect the dots."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1370915368859</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 21:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370922439304-53</Id><Topic><Title>'BANG'-hazi (Hillary style)</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1370892196000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 15:23:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your record of being 100% wrong about everything you post remains intact. Ignorance and hysteria are your signature.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1370922439304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-10 23:47:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>