<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-05-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367987664993-1</Id><Title>Facts that make the GOP gag!</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON -- Extended unemployment benefits Congress put in place at the outset of the Great Recession didn't discourage people from taking jobs, according to new research from the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco. Princeton University economics professor Henry Farber and San Francisco Fed economist Rob Valletta found that extended benefits might have encouraged people to continue to look for work longer so that they could remain eligible for benefits. While the longer searches for jobs could have boosted the unemployment rate by four-tenths of a percentage point, the compensation didn't make the long-term jobless unwilling to work. "It did not reduce the job finding rate," Farber told HuffPost. He added the benefits probably helped the economy, however, not to mention the individual people who otherwise might have had no income. "These are people who spend the money you give them." The findings are similar to 2011 research by Jesse Rothstein of the University of California, Berkeley. Since continuing to search for work is a condition for receiving jobless aid, more people may have continued to search for a job longer in order to keep receiving benefits. People are not counted as unemployed in the government's monthly survey if they say they haven't looked for work in the previous four weeks.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367987664993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 00:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1367987915291-2</Id><Title>NRA goes "bold"!!</Title><Msg>FAIRFAX, VA—Saying that he embodies the organization’s core values and beliefs, members of the National Rifle Association elected Aurora, CO mass shooter James Holmes as their new president Monday, sources confirmed. “Mr. Holmes is not only a powerful symbol and advocate of Second Amendment rights, but he’s also a high-profile gun owner himself,” said NRA member Tyler Paulson, 46, who claimed he could think of no one better to lead the group through its current challenges than the man who shot and killed 12 people in a Colorado movie theater. “The fact is, Mr. Holmes isn’t afraid to stand up for what he believes in. We support James Holmes 100 percent and are excited to see where he decides to lead us going forward.” At press time, Holmes and NRA Executive Vice President Wayne LaPierre were spotted laughing with one another and shaking hands during Holmes’ visiting hours. The Onion</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367987915291</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 00:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368018248611-3</Id><Topic><Title>Facts that make the GOP gag!</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1367987664993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 00:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzzz z z z z z yawn zzz z z z zzzz</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1368018248611</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:04:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368018646081-4</Id><Title>The Opinions of a Couple Ghey Professors from SanFrancissy Does Not Constitute Fact</Title><Msg>according to professor Nute Kracker of the University of Obamaisamamasboy, the principal factor that has kept working Americans unemployed, is the destructive communist policies of Obama.</Msg><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1368018646081</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368018666492-5</Id><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Msg>Stephen Hawking Joins Israeli Academic Boycott Renowned theoretical physicist Stephen Hawking, 71, has decided to pull out of a major conference, hosted by Shimon Peres, that Hawking was scheduled to headline in Jerusalem. Hawking said it was "his independent decision to respect the boycott, based upon his knowledge of Palestine, and on the unanimous advice of his own academic contacts there." Renowned theoretical physicist Stephen Hawking, 71, has decided to pull out of a major conference, hosted by Shimon Peres, that Hawking was scheduled to headline in Jerusalem. Hawking said it was "his independent decision to respect the boycott, based upon his knowledge of Palestine, and on the unanimous advice of his own academic contacts there." Einstein also denounced the injustice of israel right wingers such as the Irgun , denouncing their methods as "fascist" and "terrorist"</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368019728443-6</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe he should roll his wheelchair through Jerusalem - make a real statement</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1368019728443</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368019990660-7</Id><Title>average workweek hrs about the same now as in 2006</Title><Msg>average workweek is about the same now as it was in 2006, contrary to liars here . "The length of the average workweek fell by 0.2 hours to 34.4 hours in April. This compares to an average of more than 34.5 hours in the 2006 and 2007" this shows that the reason for slack hire is LACK of DEMAND...... right now the economy and jobs are matched to the current DEMAND.... and what happened to DEMAND?????? " Well, it's pretty damn simple, we had a housing bubble driving the economy before the collapse and there is nothing to fill the gap created. The bubble led residential construction to soar to more than 6.0 percent of GDP at the peak of the boom in 2005. It is now a bit over 2 percent of GDP implying a loss in annual demand of more than $600 billion" Dean Baker Phd economics</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368019990660</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368020381058-8</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>his statement was widely noted....many in Israel are deeply ashamed of their land grabbing and illegal occupation. Israel doesn't want peace (and never has) Gideon Levy, Ha’aretz .......it has to be said: Israel does not want peace. The arsenal of excuses has run out, and the chorus of Israel's rejection already rings hollow....... ....But, time and time again, Israel avoids the most basic prerequisite for any just peace - an end to the occupation. ......[and why no end to the occupation?]..... ....The answer: real estate. The real estate of the settlements.........</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368020381058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:39:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368022148763-9</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And all with the backing to the USA, which is costing this country many, many lives and trillions of dollars. It is the tail wagging the dog case which people are beginning to notice. I guess that makes Hawkins an anti-Semite (?).</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1368022148763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:09:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368022619588-10</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stephen Hawking should stick to what he knows in the area of science, pretty embarrasing for what was once a scientific mind to totally disreguard that Argentina is accusing England of its illegal occupation of the Falklands!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1368022619588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368023399640-11</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are the embarrassment for comparing Falklands where there are no native inhabitants oppressed by a military occupation, to the illegal occupation of the West Bank where a Palestinians can't get job or drill a water well without permission from the occupying Israel army... who of course have confiscated all the water and resources and never allow the Palestinians to drill a well....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368023399640</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368023742010-12</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>/ many people in Israel also hate their illegal occupation: Mr Halevy, a fmr head of the Mossad,.... ."........... But 40 years after the 1967 war, a Palestinian state does not exist. The politically consequential question, therefore, is whether Israel recognises a Palestinian right to statehood, not the reverse....." The Arabs, too, have dreams and needs. ...... We cannot keep a Palestinian majority under an Israel boot and at the same time think ourselves the only democracy in the Middle East. There cannot be democracy without equal rights for all who live here,..... We cannot keep the territories ........by means that are humane and moral ......... . Avraham "Avrum" Burg was a former Speaker of the Knesset.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368023742010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368025107416-13</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Argentina does not agree with your assesment about the Falklands!</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1368025107416</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 10:58:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368032373831-14</Id><Title>Hillary Arrested</Title><Msg>Benghazi Hillary is caught with her pants-suit down. Doing a Huma!! Hillary curruptocracy is being stopped.</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368032373831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368034724864-15</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no matter, your comparison is still silly and childish. You might want to consider the facts before spouting off: population of the Falklands in 1980 was 1,813 ...........the vast majority being of British descent.................. The UK bases its claim on the islands on continuous administration of the islands since 1833 and the islanders having a "right to self determination, including their right to remain British if that is their wish' in 1982, Argentina's ruling military junta invaded and claimed that Falkland Islanders do not have a right to self-determination..........</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368034724864</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 13:38:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368037975194-16</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Israel will exist and will continue to exist until Islam will obliterate it, just as it obliterated others before it.' Guess where this quote is coming from?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1368037975194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368038819177-17</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are crazy people in Israel who say the same exact thing about islam.... the fact remains, Israel is the illegal occupier, and there are plenty of smart people in Israel who agree that Israel must give up the illegal territories, as I showed with quotes from a head of the Mossad and a speaker of the Knesset. and other prominent Israel____is.......... and just think people as bright and decent as Stephen Hawking, Albert Eintein, Jimmy carter, Desmond TuTu, have expressed contempt for the type of racist and religious bigotry you stand for........Israel doesn't want peace Gideon Levy, Ha’aretz The moment of truth has arrived, and it has to be said: Israel does not want peace. The arsenal of excuses has run out, and the chorus of I_sraeli rejection already rings hollow....... ....But, time and time again, Israel avoids the most basic prerequisite for any just peace - an end to the occupation. ......[and why no end to the occpation?]..... ....The answer: real estate. The real estate of the settlements.........</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368038819177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 14:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368041777809-18</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read Hamas charter, shmucky. This is where the quote is coming from. It may be about real estate. Although, without Israel.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1368041777809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 15:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368045828724-19</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no you creep, bigot and racist, I will take it from the fmr head of the MOSSAD who says such blather as you post is just plain bs and is no excuse for Israel stealing land and it's illegal occupation : "...Why should Israel care whether Hamas grants it the right to exist, Mr Halevy asked. Israel exists and Hamas’s recognition or non-recognition neither adds to nor detracts from that irrefutable fact. But 40 years after the 1967 war, a Palestinian state does not exist. The politically consequential question, therefore, is whether Israel recognises a Palestinian right to statehood, not the reverse....."</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368045828724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1368046239774-20</Id><Title>My President Is A Disgrace</Title><Msg>How's yours?</Msg><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1368046239774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368052046823-21</Id><Topic><Title>My President Is A Disgrace</Title><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1368046239774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be talking about the president of your local Log Cabin chapter.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1368052046823</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 18:27:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368056233287-22</Id><Topic><Title>Stephen Hawking protests injustice of Israel's illegal occupation</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1368018666492</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 09:11:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take it from former head of Mossad or from your own rear end. In 1967 Israel didn't take the land from Palestinians, they didn't even exist at the time, the land belonged to Jordan, which doesn't claim neither land nor its occupants back. It's suicidal to negotiate with country sworn to destroy your statehood. United States does not negotiate with terrorists. Shmucks demand it for Israel.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1368056233287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 19:37:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368064702649-23</Id><Topic><Title>My President Is A Disgrace</Title><Username>caribou_barbre</Username><Timestamp>1368046239774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 16:50:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like Marco Rubio said **I can't find a straight Republican anymore!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1368064702649</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 21:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1368065115766-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hillary Arrested</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1368032373831</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 12:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The latest guy to testify is paid by the GOP. If Hilary runs she will still win Benghazy or no Benghazy. The whole world realizes this is a put-on by the extreme neocons.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1368065115766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-05-08 22:05:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>