<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-30"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359529143572-1</Id><Topic><Title>What Happened to the Squeaky Fromme Post?...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359498792295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 17:33:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor creature is obsessed with assassination attempts on Republican Presidents. Little details like who and when are not important. Wouldn't worry much about making sense either. Only regrets that much hated Republican survived.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1359529143572</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 01:59:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359541898502-2</Id><Topic><Title>dividend from e*trade</Title><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359458952030</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-01-29 06:29:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On dividends... E*trade mentioned timeframes &amp; such... didn’t give a lot of specifics... my review shows between brokerage operations and interest margin... along w/ cost-cutting and real estate market coming back... it looks to me like normalized earnings will result &amp; some type of dividend can be paid...</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1359541898502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 05:31:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359556750852-3</Id><Topic><Title>Expert stock analyst</Title><Username>lelia_cherry</Username><Timestamp>1333907539000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-04-08 13:52:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its Useful</Msg><Username>feliciamortine</Username><Timestamp>1359556750852</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 09:39:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359557743235-4</Id><Topic><Title>Et tu Gomer?</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1359556875867</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 09:41:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Umm JB... That was known since the 1970's.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359557743235</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 09:55:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359571933899-5</Id><Title>Hearings on gun control laws!</Title><Msg>Following the hearings, I am missing the 3 most important questions: 1. How do we stop criminals, gangs, felons or mentally unfit persons from obtaining fire arms? (On the streets or from break ins, they obviously wont apply for a permit) 2. How do we disarm above from their current illegal possession fire arms? (That's why Mayor Rybeck of Minneapolis said after the summit with law enforcement - buyback programs do NOT work) 3. How do we stop above from obtaining fire arms in the future? Banning certain fire arms or magazines does not solve the problem, one boy in the hospital, critical, and one girl dead already, shot this morning with PISTOLS by gang members at a school party! (SOLVE THOSE PROBLEMS) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359571933899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:52:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359572789935-6</Id><Title>Just in!</Title><Msg>Police confirm 3 shot in AZ mortgage building - no AR-15 used!!!! (Now what? - Metal detectors in all office buildings???) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359573144627-7</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Early reports are the guy was irked because he felt, as a US citizen, he was entitled to free housing.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1359573144627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:12:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359575732635-8</Id><Title>What does the S&amp;P have in common with Chicago</Title><Msg>Both set records in January. Mr. President, you need to travel to your hometown and stop the killing of your people...phoney liberal(redundant). Deadliest January In Chicago In More Than 10 Years CHICAGO (CBS) – The murder toll in Chicago for the month of January now stands at 42, making it the most deadly January in Chicago in more than 10 years. The last time there were this many murders in January was in 2002, when there were 45 homicides.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359575732635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:55:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359576698734-9</Id><Title>42 murders in Chicago this year</Title><Msg>The murder toll in Chicago for the month of January now stands at 42, making it the most deadly January in Chicago in more than 10 years. Blame it on church-going, white, married, straight, working, tax-paying males!!!</Msg><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1359576698734</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:11:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359576948354-10</Id><Title>The government background checks failed to stop the Tucson psycho</Title><Msg>In Obama's feeble mind, if something does not work, you do more of it. Kenyan root-cause analysis at work.</Msg><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1359576948354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:15:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359577100792-11</Id><Topic><Title>The government background checks failed to stop the Tucson psycho</Title><Username>demsworshipalqaeda</Username><Timestamp>1359576948354</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:15:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The government failed, so blame the NRA. Can't we blame Raygun?</Msg><Username>donng_hung_lo</Username><Timestamp>1359577100792</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:18:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359577665234-12</Id><Topic><Title>-= =- Major ETFC Pre Promotion Report (LEAKED!!!!) -= =-</Title><Username>fosterjoseph487</Username><Timestamp>1359407914135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:18:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is awesome report. THX</Msg><Username>fosterjoseph487</Username><Timestamp>1359577665234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:27:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359578205665-13</Id><Title>GDP Shocker</Title><Msg>It look as though the community agitators job programs and tax increases are beginning to take hold. This will only help the "RICH" that he despises the most by allowing Ben to continue pumping....Obama needs to get some shmuck insurance. **raise fears about the economy's ability to handle tax increases** GDP Shows Surprise Drop for US in Fourth Quarter The economy posted a stunning drop of 0.1 percent in the fourth quarter, defying expectations for slow growth and possibly providing incentive for more Federal Reserve stimulus. The economy shrank from October through December for the first time since the recession ended, hurt by the biggest cut in defense spending in 40 years, fewer exports and sluggish growth in company stockpiles. The Commerce Department said Wednesday that the economy contracted at an annual rate of 0.1 percent in the fourth quarter. That's a sharp slowdown from the 3.1 percent growth rate in the July-September quarter. The surprise contraction could raise fears about the economy's ability to handle tax increases that took effect in January and looming spending cuts.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359578205665</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:36:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359578923106-14</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As dumb as always! Next question you going to ask if one can bring loaded guns to a gun club!!!! Answer: No, once at the range the guns get loaded to practice and must be empty when entering the club house or leaving the premises. Exception: Police officers and licensed concealed carriers! Pistols if encased in a hard case with a lock, or a trigger lock, or empty in the front of the car, empty with ammo in the trunk (rear of the car). In TX the loaded gun has to be displayed on the dash board (used to be when I was stationed in Ft. Bliss) Next time THINK before you type! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359578923106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 15:48:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359579785989-15</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White liberals don't mind getting ducked tape and abused by thugs in their home, because the alternative of owning a gun makes them uncomfortable...their heavy and they make a loud noise when discharged.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359579785989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:03:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359580324449-16</Id><Topic><Title>BO rides wave of adulation</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1359579795156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:03:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**"President Obama's popularity among constituents is rising in the early days of his second term** So is the federal deficit...no surprise here... Remember when you rob peter to pay paul, you can always depend on Paul's support.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359580324449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:12:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359580543693-17</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FONTANA, Calif. (AP) — The high-powered semiautomatic rifles recently shipped to school police in this Southern California city look like they belong on a battlefield rather than in a high school, but officials here say the weapons could help stop a massacre like the one that claimed the lives of 26 students and educators in Connecticut just weeks ago. Fontana Unified School District police purchased 14 of the Colt LE6940 rifles last fall, and they were delivered the first week of December — a week before the shooting at Sandy Hook Elementary School. Over the holiday break, the district's 14 school police officers received 40 hours of training on the rifles. Officers check them out for each shift from a fireproof safe in the police force's main office. Fontana isn't the first district to try this. Other Southern California districts also have rifle programs — some that have been in operation for several years. Fontana school police Chief Billy Green said he used money from fingerprinting fees to purchase the guns for $14,000 after identifying a "critical vulnerability" in his force's ability to protect students. The officers, who already wear sidearms, wouldn't be able to stop a shooter like the one in Connecticut, he said Wednesday. "They're not walking around telling kids, 'Hurry up and get to class' with a gun around their neck," the chief said. "Parents need to know that if there was a shooter on their child's campus that was equipped with body armor or a rifle, we would be limited in our ability to stop that threat to their children." Some parents and students, however, reacted with alarm to the news that school resource officers were being issued the rifles during their shifts. The officers split their time between 44 schools in the district and keep the rifles in a safe at their assigned school or secured in their patrol car each day before checking the weapon back in to the school police headquarters each night. "If the wrong person gets ahold of the gun, then we have another shooter going around with a gun. What happens then, if that situation occurs?" said James Henriquez, a 16-year-old sophomore who just enrolled at Fontana High School this week after moving from Texas. Other students said they felt disillusioned that officials would spend money on semiautomatic rifles while the district eliminated its comprehensive guidance counseling program two years ago. "They should get guns, but not as many and not spend so much money on them," said student Elizabeth Tovar. "They should use the money to get back our counselors because a lot of us really need them." The district saved millions by restructuring guidance services, said Superintendent Cali Olsen-Binks. "I understand that people are looking at the layoffs, but $14,000 and $7 million is a huge disparity," she said. The 40,000-student district came up with the school rifle program after consulting with top school safety experts and looking at what other large districts had done, said Olsen-Binks. Santa Ana Unified School District, in nearby Orange County, has had a rifle program for about two years that operates similarly to the one Fontana has started, said police Cpl. Anthony Bertagna. The Los Angeles School Police Department also deploys rifles to its officers as needed, the department said in a statement. It would not say how many rifles district police have but said the weapons are kept in the department's armory and are handed out and returned daily. The San Bernardino City Unified School District police force purchased four Bushmaster semiautomatic rifles last July, said Linda Bardere, a district spokeswoman. Fontana is a city of about 200,000 people east of Los Angeles. "I came from a teaching background, and it's appalling to think that we'd have to have security officers — let alone armed police officers — on our campuses. But the bottom line is ... everybody has anxiety over school safety right now," Olsen-Binks said. "Our police officers said they would take a bullet for these kids and because they are willing to put their lives on the line, they need to be equipped for all scenarios." Only sergeants are authorized to check out the rifles from the police armory, where they are kept. All officers have been trained for years to use the rifles. The Fontana rifle purchase did not require approval from the school board but member Leticia Garcia said she believes there should have been a public discussion before they were purchased. "We're talking about a war-zone rifle, and so are we going to militarize our public schools?" Garcia asked. "We have to provide a safe haven for people to learn ... but this, to me, seems a little bit too much."</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359580543693</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:15:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359581005697-18</Id><Title>junglebop-esque in length but worf the read</Title><Msg>Posted: Friday, November 23, 2012 11:20 pm | Updated: 12:05 am, Mon Jan 28, 2013. BY MARK BOWES Gun-related violent crime in Virginia has dropped steadily over the past six years as the sale of firearms has soared to a new record, according to an analysis of state crime data with state records of gun sales. The total number of firearms purchased in Virginia increased 73 percent from 2006 to 2011. When state population increases are factored in, gun purchases per 100,000 Virginians rose 63 percent. But the total number of gun-related violent crimes fell 24 percent over that period, and when adjusted for population, gun-related offenses dropped more than 27 percent, from 79 crimes per 100,000 in 2006 to 57 crimes in 2011. The numbers appear to contradict a long-running popular narrative that more guns cause more violent crime, said Virginia Commonwealth University professor Thomas R. Baker, who compared Virginia crime data for those years with gun-dealer sales estimates obtained by the Richmond Times-Dispatch. "While there is a wealth of academic literature attempting to demonstrate the relationship between guns and crime, a very simple and intuitive demonstration of the numbers seems to point away from the premise that more guns leads to more crime, at least in Virginia," said Baker, who specializes in research methods and criminology theory and has an interest in gun issues. The significance of Baker's analysis was questioned by one of the state's ardent gun-control advocates. "I'm not surprised that it would appear that more guns is going along with less crime, because there's been a downward trend in violent crime anyway," said Andrew Goddard, president of the Virginia Center for Public Safety. One of Virginia's most outspoken gun-rights supporters, Philip Van Cleave, president of the Virginia Citizens Defense League, was not surprised for a different reason. "My opponents are constantly saying, 'If you got more guns on the street, there's going to be more crime.' It all depends on who has the handgun," Van Cleave said. "As long as it's going into the hands of people like you or me, there's not going to be a problem. Criminals are going to continue to get their guns no matter what." At the request of The Times-Dispatch, Baker examined six years of data compiled by Virginia State Police through the Virginia Firearms Transaction Center that breaks down the number of gun transactions for every federally licensed firearm dealer in Virginia. It includes the number and types of guns they sought to sell based on requested state background checks of the purchasers. Baker then compared the data with state crime figures for those years. The data, Baker said, show a low probability that more guns in the hands of Virginians is causing more violent crime. "So while it's difficult to make a direct causal link (that more guns are resulting in less crime), the numbers certainly present that that's a real possibility," Baker added. The opposite - that more guns are causing more crime - cannot be derived from the numbers, he said. "It's mathematically not possible, because the relationship is a negative relationship - they're moving in the opposite direction," Baker said. "So the only thing it could be is that more guns are causing less crime." "From my personal point of view, I would say the data is pretty overwhelming," said Baker, who is new to VCU and studied under Florida State University professors Gary Kleck and Marc Gertz, whose nationally recognized research on guns and homicides in the District of Columbia was cited in a landmark U.S. Supreme Court decision in 2008 that overturned the district's handgun ban. "But we're pretty cautious in the social sciences in talking about causality. We only talk in probabilities." The multiple years of data for gun purchases and gun-related crime help strengthen the premise that more gun sales are not leading to an increase in crime. Using what Baker calls the "lag model," the data show that an increase in gun purchases for one year usually is followed by a decrease in crime the next year. Baker said a more detailed analysis may find pockets of the state where increased guns sales have been followed by an increase in gun-related violent crime. "But I'm not interested in that small, nuanced component," he said. "As a scientist, you don't want to focus on individual instance. That's what gets people into making these overgeneralizations about things like some of the tragedies that have been gun-related in the United States." The estimated number of gun purchases based on requested background checks rose from 243,251 in 2006 to a record-breaking 420,829 sales last year, according to gun-dealer transaction data compiled by state police through background checks. Over that same period, the total number of violent crimes in Virginia dropped from 23,431 offenses in 2006 to 18,196 in 2011. The total gun purchases cover all types of firearms, including pistols, revolvers, shotguns and rifles. Similarly, total gun-related crime includes offenses committed with all types of guns, including firearms whose type was unknown. Handgun-related offenses account for the majority of violent crimes committed in Virginia. Because rifles and shotguns are used far less often to commit violent crimes, Baker said, one could argue that the purchase of those types of weapons is falsely inflating the total gun purchases in relation to total gun crime. So Baker also examined the relationship between handgun purchases and handgun-related crime. He found a similar trend. Handgun purchases in Virginia increased 112 percent from 2006 to 2011, but violent crimes committed with handguns fell by nearly 22 percent. When adjusted for population increases, handgun purchases rose a little more than 100 percent, but violent crimes committed with handguns dropped 26 percent, according to Baker's analysis. Baker said this general pattern remains even if all crimes reported to police where the gun type was unknown are assumed to be handguns. "In fact, if all unknown gun types used in violent gun crimes are assumed to have been handguns, then handgun-related violent crime decreased just over 24 percent from 2006 to 2011," he said. However, Baker noted the pattern does not seem to hold in one crime category: aggravated assaults. Increases in gun purchases might increase the percentage of aggravated assaults involving a gun. The data show that while the actual number of aggravated assaults decreased from 2006 to 2011, those committed with a gun increased nearly 2 percent. Baker said that's not surprising. Studies have shown similar results for an increase in the number of guns and an increase in the percentage of suicides by a gun. The percentage of aggravated assaults in which guns are involved may increase, but it has little effect on the actual rate or number of those offenses, Baker said. "This is why we do not see an increase in aggravated assaults associated with an increase in gun sales, but rather an increase in the percent of aggravated assaults which used a gun," he said. Baker said some researchers suggest that the use of a gun in an assault increases the lethality of such encounters, and that a similar assault without a gun reduces the probability of a homicide occurring. But Baker said it bears noting that Virginia's homicide rate, like violent crime generally, has dropped from 5.21 killings per 100,000 Virginians in 2006 to 3.77 per 100,000 in 2011. Baker, who owns a handgun and had a concealed-carry permit when he lived and worked in Florida, described himself politically as "moderate to conservative." But he says his research is nonpolitical. "I try to think of myself as a scientist," he said. Van Cleave, the gun-rights advocate, said Baker's analysis confirms what he already suspected. "Doing what I do, I have my finger on the pulse of gun sales, and I know they've been soaring because I'm at gun shows and I've talked to dealers and all I hear is the stories about how guns are selling at a higher rate now than ever," Van Cleave said. Simultaneously, "we've been hearing in the news about how violent crime has been dropping in the United States for over a decade." "Never before have you had so many new guns come into the market," Van Cleave said. "That probably helped (Baker's) analysis and dramatized more than anything that all those guns - for whatever reason - didn't make crime go up." Gun-control lobbyist Goddard, whose son was wounded during the Virginia Tech massacre five years ago, doesn't dispute the numbers but questioned their significance. "It's quite possible that you can sell a whole lot more guns and crime is still going down," Goddard said. "But is the crime going down because more people are buying guns, or is the crime going down because the crime is going down?" Goddard said he would not have expected a rise in crime from a rise in legal gun sales, because legal gun buyers are not usually criminals - otherwise they would not pass a background check to get them. "Predicting the actions of criminals by analyzing the behavior of legal gun buyers is not likely to be productive," he said. What is more significant, Goddard said, is that the large reduction in violent crime has not produced an equivalent reduction in total gun deaths and injuries. "If you look at the numbers of people who are dying from guns every year, including suicides and accidents, then you're not going to see a difference," he said. "Gun sales are going up, and the annual death rate in Virginia is staying pretty much constant." Baker said the perception that guns cause crime is pervasive because criminals use an effective tool to carry out their misdeeds. "It does an effective job for what it's supposed to do," he said. "And because criminals use them, I think it becomes a hot-button issue, it becomes a political issue. And people focus on the wrong component of what the problem is." "Instead of trying to figure out why are these people committing crimes - and using the most effective tool to commit those crimes - they focus on the tool," he continued. "So the gun is causing the crime."</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1359581005697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:23:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359581620648-19</Id><Topic><Title>Hearings on gun control laws!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359571933899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:52:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then you disagree with the Mayor's statement after the summit meeting between the all the Mayor's of WI/MN and their police chiefs and Sheriffs???? project, the politicians are going to just create a bigger mess, we - the people - have to take action! If you offered $1000, you would see RECORD BREAK INS because a criminal can get a gun for from $50 up on the street and turn it in! This wouldn't even work if the police would ask for Identification and proof how the gun was obtained!!! (For example the gun could have been stolen in Chicago and turned in, in Minneapolis!) Now it's NO questions or ID asked and if a gun gets turned in with the SN filed out wouldn't one like to ask questions??? Do you have an answer as to that, after this "panic run" to obtain fire arms and ammo, which in my state, WI, emptied all the shelf's this mess can be controlled??? The OBIMBO grand standing, photo op, prompted the largest sale on those Items! I can only speak for WI, MI, MN, ND and SD where the firing power of the civilians outnumbers the National Guard! Maybe we should have civilian posse's go after the gangs/criminals, they might have more power/rights then the police! In LA police is outgunned 100:1!!! Police officers got pistols and shotguns, criminals got AK's Tec9's...... etc.! Correct me if iI am wrong, only supervisors are allowed to carry "UZI's" in the squad cars??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359581620648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:33:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359582210316-20</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Like the Sheriff from Milwaukee said on TV, you have 3 options, when your home is intruded! 1. Ask for mercy! 2. Hide under the bed! 3. Obtain, register, take training and defend your self!!! I already took #3, ever since my military discharge! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359582210316</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:43:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359582370797-21</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade remains a compelling buyout candidate</Title><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1359396644840</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 13:10:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really, son. Most of the banks have enough capital to do an acquisition this size. Cash balances are required to meet liquidity needs of depositors. has nothing to do with provisions. Note too that a WFC or USB transaction will be paid for in STOCK.</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1359582370797</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:46:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359582550813-22</Id><Topic><Title>BO rides wave of adulation</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1359579795156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:03:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pretty bad when 37% of the people who voted for Barry have an unfavorable view. But just remember this. Most of Barry's supporters never sign the front of a paycheck, most of them ride in the wagon of welfare.</Msg><Username>maynardkrabs</Username><Timestamp>1359582550813</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:49:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359583133605-23</Id><Topic><Title>McCain warns GOP</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1359580632091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:17:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we DEPORT them, with the rest of the undesirables, then they won't be able to vote for OBIMBO! ;o) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359583133605</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:58:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359583975919-24</Id><Topic><Title>Hearings on gun control laws!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359571933899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:52:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AK's and TEC-9's are #$%$, the criminals can keep them. Far rather get hit with a 7.62x39 AK round than a US 7.63.51 NATO round, or 5.56mm, one of which I'll be throwing back. Hopefully they'll fire them sideways, insuring they never get near their target, but since they really don't care about bystanders one of those usually gets shot instead of the intended OTHER gang banger. Some days I want to go to Chicago and train 30 members of a street gang so they know basic infantry tactics and how to shoot. They can train the others and kick all the other gangs out of Chicago, like the Mayor and his buddies, after all, as you said, they probably outgun the police, it's just that they're not as organized and they can't seem to hit anything. I don't even think the Chicago PD would ISSUE Uzi's unless they are complete idiots. The Uzi fires from an open bolt, unlike the MP5, and is therefore wildly inaccurate. I can put a 5 round burst from my MP5SD (full auto, not semi) into a spot the size of a silver dollar at 15 yards, with an offhand shot. With an Uzi or Mac-10 (which like the Uzi is open bolt, only even MORE of its mass is bolt carrier/bolt) you're lucky if you can keep a 5 round burst on the paper. Police departments should NOT issue open bolt weapons, they are a hazard anywhere but a battlefield where you have LOTS of room to accept collateral damage. Most likely their police have Colt carbines, similar to the M4, only without the 40mm Grenade launcher attachment. At times I think the bangers really WANT to hit anything, just shoot their weapons and make great deals of noise being their idea of fun, so we can make "Chicago Specials" or Obambam's as we'll call them, with only partially bored barrels for use special blanks that make tons of noise, and spew confetti. That way the gang bangers can have their fun, make their statement, and no one gets hurt. Or, to put some risk in it, we could fill .01% of the blanks with RDX, thus causing the shooter to severely mangle his own hand while shooting it, similar to the effect you get when firing many street guns.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359583975919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:12:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359584736700-25</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359572789935</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 14:06:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's a new "traveling" rule in Texas, as long as the weapon isn't concealed on your person (unless you have a carry license, which I do) loaded firearms are legal as long as you're going from one place to another, both of which allow it. They don't have to be immediately obvious (a friend of mine carries his in hollow of his door in the maps space), and you DO have to inform law enforcement you have them in case of a pullover. just as a CHL holder must display his CHL anytime asked for ID and inform the officer of if they are armed currently or not. You don't, however, have to lock them up if you don't intend to leave them in the vehicle. Back when I was stationed at Ft Bliss you were still allowed to put guns in the rack of your truck, those days are long since gone, now they have to be out of plain sight and either cased in condition 0, be "traveling", or the person with a weapon must be a CHL holder. OPEN carry of loaded weapons, except while hunting or in performance of duty, is NOT allowed in Texas (e.g. you can't just wander the city with a loaded weapon, even if everyone can see it). Many others DO allow open carry without a permit (Florida is a good example).</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359584736700</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:25:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359585203580-26</Id><Topic><Title>"squeaky fromme" getting Reagan shows circle jerk mentality gun</Title><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1359583259375</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:00:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, it was Ford, not Reagan she tried to shoot (I think you're thinking of John Hinkley) and she tried it with an M1911A1 pistol with 4 rounds in the magazine and NONE in the chamber, meaning she didn't even get a shot off before a number of SS Agents were sitting on top of her. Hinkley's attempt on Reagan, which hit alot of other people, involved a .22 caliber revolver, more distance, and extremely bad luck on the Presidents part in some ways, and good luck (after getting hit) in others. A weapon that, it might be noted, would be unaffected by any legislation being discussed as they all exclude rimfire firearms (low power) from most of the provisions, and revolvers from all of them. And yes, once most people have invested a certain amount of emotional capital on a political or social position, it's almost impossible to get them to admit they were wrong, a possible explanation for Obama's re-election.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359585203580</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:33:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359585277045-27</Id><Title>Chicago Gets Better and Better...Inauguration Teen Killed!</Title><Msg>Hadiya Pendleton, all of 15 years old, was gunned down at a park in Chicago As Congress holds a much-anticipated hearing on gun control, there was a disturbing reminder that gun violence in America never takes a break. It's been reported that Hadiya Pendleton, a 15-year-old girl from Chicago, was gunned down on Tuesday, just days after she performed with her school band at President Obama's inauguration. Pendleton — an honors student, volleyball player, and majorette at King College Prep — was shot at a park just blocks away from her school. According to reports, Pendleton was among 12 teenagers who had taken shelter from the rain under a canopy in Vivian Gordon Harsh Park. An unidentified gunman then jumped the park's fence and allegedly opened fire. In addition to Pendleton, who later died from her wounds, a teenage boy was shot and is currently in serious condition at the hospital. SEE MORE: Why gun owners should want to amend the Second Amendment Details of the incident remain unclear, though initial reports suggest that Pendleton was not the primary target of the attack. Since the school massacre in Newtown, Connecticut, in December, more than 1,400 people have been killed in gun violence across the country.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359585277045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:34:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359585707689-28</Id><Topic><Title>Hearings on gun control laws!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1359571933899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 13:52:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They do one of those programs here I'm going to get a 3d printer and knock off AR-15 receivers with DIAS installations and get the bounty for turning in a real machine gun, albeit one that could only fire maybe two or three rounds before the plastic receiver cracked. Hey though, no questions asked eh? Funny thing, if you MAKE a weapon yourself, for your own use, there are NO FEDERAL CONTROLS WHATSOEVER, provided that it doesn't use commercially available ammunition. If you intend to sell your creation, however, you must get a Class 2 FFL, and the created weapon has to be submitted to the ATF for examination and approval before it can be marketed. If guns are outlawed only people with 3d printers and machine shops will have guns.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359585707689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:41:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359589356780-29</Id><Topic><Title>Ernest Hemingway Slams Lil Barry</Title><Username>harrd_dick_cafe</Username><Timestamp>1358388341220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:05:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can read the report on the economy, but Hemingway already summed it up for us. "Never confuse movement with action."</Msg><Username>harrd_dick_cafe</Username><Timestamp>1359589356780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:42:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359590267432-30</Id><Topic><Title>BO rides wave of adulation</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1359579795156</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 16:03:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Most of Barry's supporters never sign the front of a paycheck".... That is probably the most True, and Most Frightening thing I have read in all my life! Kudos to you Sir!...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359590267432</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:57:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359590592051-31</Id><Topic><Title>Home invasions are rare and avoidable</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1359590269550</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 18:57:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So if you balls are big enough...You should have No problems. And that means that You are Scared to Death!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359590592051</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 19:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359595268670-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ernest Hemingway Slams Lil Barry</Title><Username>harrd_dick_cafe</Username><Timestamp>1358388341220</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-16 21:05:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like another Log Cabin member has joined.</Msg><Username>lonelygaybillie</Username><Timestamp>1359595268670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 20:21:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359604865473-33</Id><Topic><Title>Chicago Gets Better and Better...Inauguration Teen Killed!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359585277045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 17:34:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many of these reported killings are fake. It is part of the plan to de-arm citizens so the obama posse can take total control. beware !!</Msg><Username>obama_is_no_hero</Username><Timestamp>1359604865473</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-01-30 23:01:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>