<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-02"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359810505099-1</Id><Topic><Title>Don't Make a Mistake...</Title><Username>avispolenxkhhja1085</Username><Timestamp>1307634191000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2011-06-09 11:43:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I agree with that.</Msg><Username>henryjoshep</Username><Timestamp>1359810505099</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 08:08:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359816829608-2</Id><Topic><Title>Whoops! Unemployed numbers jump</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359666261244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-31 16:04:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He got rid of a number of government jobs added as part of the stimulus as well as cutting other monies that supported "initiatives" of his that simply hadn't gone anywhere. He still hasn't figured out that requirements for cellulose derived alcohol fuel additives won't work until someone actually PRODUCES some (though that gives me an idea of what to do with all those extra Fir trees on my property), but he's starting to realize, I suspect, that spending money on people who live largely in their own heads so he can get advice on the real world is POINTLESS. He doesn't really want the advice anyway, he just wants the appearance of getting advice, that way he can claim his ideas have expert vetting.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359816829608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 09:53:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359828739355-3</Id><Title>The #$%$ broke into my neighbors house!</Title><Msg>I heard strange noises at about 2 AM. I did not know what was going on so I went to see. Nothing at my house. The problem was at my neighbor's house. I saw two guys come out of their house with their big new television. So I have my .357 in one hand and a phone in the other. I thought about my neighbors. They are against and all-around bleeding heart liberals. I yelled at the perps. "There is a nice Macbook next to the desk."</Msg><Username>billybubbaweeziee</Username><Timestamp>1359828739355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:12:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359837574640-4</Id><Title>Highest price ever for gasoline</Title><Msg>Where I live regular unleaded, $4.15, highend $4.45. Damn, I should of bought one one dem Chevy Volts. Write this down so you don't forget...Ben the banker says there is no inflation, no consequences to printing endless dollars. But, don't blame the community agitator, he has moved on to more important issues like gun control, and importing more uneducated and poor Mexicans to add to the entitlement roles. Gasoline at Highest Price Ever for This Time of Year U.S. drivers are now paying more to fill up their gas tanks than they ever have at this time of year. The national average price of retail gasoline posted its biggest one-day increase in 23 months on Friday, rising four cents to $3.46 a gallon, according to AAA. The average price has risen 13 cents -- a 4 percent increase -- in the past week. Gasoline prices have followed in part the climb in the stock and oil prices. Oil and equities have risen sharply over the last few weeks, as the Dow Jones Industrial Average reached 14,000 for the first time since 2007, Brent crude oil futures hit at 4-month high near $117 a barrel, while the U.S. oi lprice is near $98 a barrel.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359837574640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:39:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359838706824-5</Id><Topic><Title>Well folks, what happened last time the DOW broke 14K?</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1359759212055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deja vu! Last time the dow was at these levels the banks were pumpimg trillions into the system through the housing bubble, now you have the FED doing the same thing pumping trillions into the markets creating another bubble. Remember a con only works when the person being conned thinks he is getting something for nothing....folks better be careful of those Wall Street Boys, they are just well dressed conmen.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1359838706824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 15:58:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359841594864-6</Id><Topic><Title>The #$%$ broke into my neighbors house!</Title><Username>billybubbaweeziee</Username><Timestamp>1359828739355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 13:12:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't do anything unless you have a mutual defense pact with your neighbor anyhow. That's the way it works in Texas anyway. If someone says "watch my stuff" and someone tries to take the stuff, you can shoot him if all else fails, but you've at least got to try, UNLESS he's armed, then he's an immediate threat in which case his first clue that he's been busted should be a bullet. Keep in mind it's nice to know who else is ALLOWED to touch the "stuff" involved. Don't want to shoot a relative come to pick up a loaned tool or something, gotta definitely be bad guys or you can go to jail for murder. Adding "defense of life or property" instead of just self defense allows you to both protect your stuff, and to nullify threats to a third person even if they're a complete stranger. Not like some cities where people are raped in the street and no one moves to help, in Texas such an act would almost certainly result in something very bad happening to you.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359841594864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:46:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359842006867-7</Id><Topic><Title>Well folks, what happened last time the DOW broke 14K?</Title><Username>project2069</Username><Timestamp>1359759212055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-01 17:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And their game though it's more subtle than most cons, is based on the same principles as most cons, appealing to greed. Dragging you back and forth to the "next big stock" while piling up commissions and charging out the nose on margin rates. But, as long as you're aware of the rules (not many) and the players (that part is MUCH harder), you can still make money participating in their cons, as long as you can figure out who's getting the big end of the stick, the retail investor is so small and insignificant that you can hitch a ride on the bark and still make money. Just gotta identify the undervalued companies that are both profitable and NOT neck deep in debt and paying most of their net out as debt service. They have to have real assets, not just a not particularly clever bit of software that got popular for awhile, but real sustainability. That's what puts ETFC on the risky end, the key comes to, what will the loan portfolios shake out to in the end and how much of that value can they recover. That's the big dice we're throwing investing in ETrade. Certainly the brokerage itself is profitable, but it's not profitable enough in and of itself, at least yet, to justify this valuation absent the assets.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1359842006867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 16:53:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359850752142-8</Id><Title>Good News for Slayer at Indian Casino</Title><Msg>Slayer walks into casino wif $100 and walks out 3 hrs. later with $2700. Always max bet (which is 3x) Started on .50 machine, moved up to dollar machine and finished on a $2.00 machine. Look for him to deposit 2 grand into his checking and spend the rest on incidentals.</Msg><Username>spenditol98_l</Username><Timestamp>1359850752142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 19:19:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359867053235-9</Id><Title>DARTS Going Up</Title><Msg>DARTS = Daily Average Revenue Trades is the core part of E*Trade's revenue. With retail coming back into the markets E*Trade must be make more money than estimates. http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-02-01/u-s-mutual-funds-reaping-record-deposits-as-markets-rise.html</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1359867053235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-02-02 23:50:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>