<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363147248338-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why spend $1.5 million to understand why Lesbians are overweight</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363119880078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 16:24:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Speaker John Boehner. "Spending is the problem here in Washington," he likes to say. But behind the scenes he joined a bipartisan group of Senators and Congressman to insert $181 million in funding the Army does not want for an upgrade program at the Abrams Tank manufacturing plant in Lima, Ohio, just a few dozen miles from Boehner's own Ohio Congressional district. The Army has already announced that it plans to phase out the cold-war era tank, and had sought to wind down production in Lima. Last May, the Obama Administration, citing a "fiscally constrained environment," formally objected to the new funding. And the tank goes on. Meanwhile, Boehner is happy to let the sequester go on and on. Because in the end, he knows that he can take care of the folks back home. "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363147248338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 00:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363170734447-2</Id><Topic><Title>When was the last time this thing was over 12??</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363033641644</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-11 16:27:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wednesday, March 13th, 2013!</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1363170734447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 06:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363178088370-3</Id><Title>ETFC Will keep moving higher!</Title><Msg>ETFC bad loans continue to decline, stock continues to RISE. Strong BUY! Selling at .66 of book vs near 3X for the rest of the online brokers, STRONG takeover candiate. Also naming a board member to run the company screams WE ARE FOR SALE! $16-18? likely. $18-20???????</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363178088370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363178700714-4</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Will keep moving higher!</Title><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363178088370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Allowance for loan losses also coming down nicely!</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1363178700714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:45:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363178806948-5</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Will keep moving higher!</Title><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363178088370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buyout soon, or at this rate of PPS increase it will be 25/shr by the end of 2013, for a buyout price. With #s like 4-6% per month improvements in loans, ETFC could be in the 20s PPS by EOY as it has left the single digits behind and rocketed up from 7s to 11s in just a few short months....More good news like today and it is off to the races. Buyers better be looking fast at getting in or they will be paying hansomly for ETFC next year. Cheers</Msg><Username>lrng2sail</Username><Timestamp>1363178806948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363180544412-6</Id><Topic><Title>Catholic Church accidentally buys a gay sauna</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363146951808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 23:55:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i wonder if fox news or breitbart have some "journalists" in pimp and ho costumes covering the story?</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1363180544412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 09:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363182021223-7</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Will keep moving higher!</Title><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363178088370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it wouldn't hurt if e-trade officially put themselves on the auction block.</Msg><Username>ted_geo</Username><Timestamp>1363182021223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 09:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363183867229-8</Id><Title>Another GOP scandal</Title><Msg>Posted on Wed, Mar. 13, 2013 Lt. Gov. Jennifer Carroll resigns from post By Tia Mitchell Herald/Times Tallahassee Bureau Florida Lt. Gov. Jennifer Carroll resigned, Gov. Rick Scott’s office announced Wednesday morning. On Tuesday, she was interviewed by the Florida Department of Law Enforcement, which is assisting in a national probe of Allied Veterans of the World, a Florida-based nonprofit that operates a chain of internet cafes. Carroll once owned a public relations firm that represented Allied Veterans, and she did work for the company at the same time she served in the Florida House. Gov. Scott will address the media after an afternoon news conference on the matter conducted by law enforcement.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363183867229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363184870530-9</Id><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Msg>Millionaires are less likely to live in taxpayer-provided housing. They are less likely to live on food stamps, AFDC and unemployment. They are less likely to collect disability for exaggerated, fraudulent or self-inflicted maladies. They are less likely to be in jail, on probation or in rehab. We do not need to provide police, fire trucks and ambulances to the millionaires' neighborhoods every Saturday night to stop them from shooting their drinking buddy, setting dumpsters on fire or knifing their old lady. We do not need to send the street cleaning machine to clean urine, broken glass and vomit off the sidewalk where the millionaires live. Millionaires will not tackle you, kick you in the head and run off with your wallet. Millionaires will not smash out your car window and ransack your car.</Msg><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363185316804-10</Id><Title>TX regretting GOP assault on women</Title><Msg>By Tara Culp-Ressler on Mar 11, 2013 at 10:45 am Faith leaders in Texas pray to restore women's health resources Over the past year, Texas officials have attacked women’s health resources from all angles — slashing funding from family planning programs, cutting off funds to the Planned Parenthood affiliates in the state, and attempting to shut down dozens of abortion clinics. Those decisions have jeopardized thousands of low-income women’s access to affordable health care, and faith leaders are praying for Texas to reverse its course. Religious leaders in Texas joined together last week to emphasize that women’s health is a religious issue. Jewish and Christian leaders prayed for increased access to preventative health services, like family planning programs and birth control, in a state that has become increasingly hostile to women’s health care: Gathered in the rotunda of the Texas Capitol Extension, leaders from Christian and Jewish faiths voiced frustration with funding for women’s health care services. Their prayer included a plea to state lawmakers to restore the $73 million cut from family planning services during 2011 and to make contraception more readily available to low-income women.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363185316804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363186332865-11</Id><Title>Armed and delusional</Title><Msg>People who keep guns in their home........... are 22 times more likely to shoot a relative than a burglar. Watch the video of a social experiment called : "Proof that Concealed Carry permit holders live in a dream world, Part One " Then try to make the case that arming citizens has serious value.</Msg><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363186332865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363186398766-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bambam should mandate neighborhoods be setup within urban areas where like-minded lowlifes can rob, murder, rape each other and do drugs 'til their heart's content.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1363186398766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363187262508-13</Id><Topic><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course millionaires will not tackle you, kick you etc. They hire others to do it for them. But frankly - I have not heard more idiotic justification for their tax breaks in a long, long, time....</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1363187262508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:07:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363187685748-14</Id><Topic><Title>TX regretting GOP assault on women</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363185316804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:35:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As to women's health issues, this is why i dod not vote for the Rpublican party in 2012. I like Romney but Ryan and his followers are anti women and are destined to destroy women's health facilities. When will the Catholic church leaders go prochoice? How abt a woman cardinal?</Msg><Username>jiang987</Username><Timestamp>1363187685748</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363187948157-15</Id><Title>George Will tries to rewrite Watergate.</Title><Msg>George Will is under fire for distorting the history of Watergate from an expert source -- Richard Ben-Veniste, chief of the Watergate task force. Will, in a March 6 column, deceptively portrayed Robert Bork as a hero who protected the Watergate prosecution, but his defense of Bork rests on omitting critical details -- including the fact that Bork actually moved to abolish the task force that was looking into the scandal. In his ode to Bork, Will pointed to Bork's role in firing Archibald Cox, the Watergate special prosecutor, arguing: On an October Saturday, when Nixon ordered Richardson to fire Archibald Cox, the Watergate special prosecutor, Richardson and his deputy resigned, urging Bork to execute Nixon's lawful order, which he did. By the two resignations, Bork became acting attorney general, in which capacity he protected the ongoing investigation of Nixon. In reality, as Ben-Veniste noted in refuting Will's campaign to make Bork a Watergate hero, Bork quickly began undermining the investigation: Indeed, far from championing an independent investigation that would allow recourse to the judicial process, Bork signed an order on Oct. 23, 1973 -- three days after firing Cox -- abolishing the Office of the Watergate Special Prosecution Force. Bork's support for Nixon's position, if successful, would have kept secret the most devastating evidence against Nixon and his closest associates. It was only after the firestorm of public revulsion following the Saturday Night Massacre that Nixon backed down -- producing seven subpoenaed tapes (less 18½ minutes of deliberately erased conversation on one of them) -- and acceded to the demand to appoint a new special prosecutor to replace Archibald Cox.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363187948157</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363188538309-16</Id><Topic><Title>E*Trade's Highly Attractive</Title><Username>gogoka01</Username><Timestamp>1362662403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 08:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like 11.50 was a good guess. Once we passed it today volume increased and share price continues to go up. What is next? Who knows? But one thing is sure, the more it goes up the more shorts will have to cover, and so on ... Let's hope for a good time for all longs.</Msg><Username>gogoka01</Username><Timestamp>1363188538309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363188853744-17</Id><Topic><Title>Armed and delusional</Title><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363186332865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must work for ABC Snews.... The "Citizen" was wearing a Helmet, Gloves, and an Oversized T-shirt....and was Targeted every time by a Professional Shooter. Real scenario?....Not Really! Just more Left wing Staged BS....but I'm glad it got your panties wet...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363188853744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363188988014-18</Id><Topic><Title>TX regretting GOP assault on women</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363185316804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:35:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The pragmatic French French Government Gives Teens Free Birth Control December 19, 2012 By Natasha Burtons The French pretty much do everything better. Fashion, chocolate-filled baked goods, leisurely lunches, actually taking their vacation time, and, now, birth control. Starting in January, young women between the ages of 15 and 18 can get free oral contraception without getting permission from their parents first. Currently, teens who want to get birth control anonymously, and without parental consent, have to pay for their doctors' visits in cash, then submit for reimbursement. However, the French government is hoping that this new measure will help reduce teen pregnancy rates by providing contraceptive access. While one group, CLER, a Catholic organization, thinks the decision reduces sex to a medial issue and wishes the government would focus more on sex education, health officials are behind this unprecedented access to birth control for teens, particularly because it will (hopefully) really help out low-income girls who can't always afford to pay under the current system.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363188988014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363189235658-19</Id><Topic><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets see who are you talking about. Barack Obama, John F Kerry, Bill &amp; Hillary, Diane Feinstein, Nancy Pelosi, Jay Rockfeller all kick you etc. Did you vote for any of them? Supported? Does it make you co-conspirator? You self exposed. Didn't come as surprise, though.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363189235658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363189249369-20</Id><Title>would Jesus live in a 12 room apartment ?</Title><Msg>The entrance to the Europa Multiclub gay sauna is marked by classy phallic topiary. The club’s proximity to a prince of the church was yet another reminder of the #$%$ scandals that are tarnishing the cross. Last week, Scotland’s Keith Cardinal O’Brien resigned and admitted to improper “sexual conduct.” And weeks before Pope Benedict announced his resignation, he received a report that revealed high-ranking clergy were frequenting gay orgies at a Rome sauna, a suburban Rome villa and a beauty parlor, according to Italian reports. Vatican owns building that houses cardinals and Europe’s biggest gay bathhouse Ivan Cardinal Dias lives upstairs from Europa Multiclub. Vatican owns the majority stake in the apartment building. NY daily news.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363189249369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363189606755-21</Id><Topic><Title>TX regretting GOP assault on women</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1363185316804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:35:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your mom didn't have birth control pill, so she gave birth to you. Sorry lady, you're mistake.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363189606755</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363190129459-22</Id><Topic><Title>E*Trade's Highly Attractive</Title><Username>gogoka01</Username><Timestamp>1362662403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 08:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea and how much money over the last FOUR MONTHS???? Stock straight up and new 52 week high today. When the fundaments change and you ignore them....watch out!! Bought ETFC for the first time 6 weeks ago after watching it for 7 years!!! Will be sold for above $16 in next 12 months.</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363190129459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:55:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363190196988-23</Id><Topic><Title>E*Trade's Highly Attractive</Title><Username>gogoka01</Username><Timestamp>1362662403000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 08:20:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you can't even read a chart......NEW 52 WEEK HIGH TODAY!!! ON BIG VOL. this morning!!!</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363190196988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:56:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363190263295-24</Id><Title>NEW 52 week high</Title><Msg>Get on board, fundamentals improving, takeover potential big!</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363190263295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:57:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363192438621-25</Id><Title>Shorts Bear &amp; Moon Silent</Title><Msg>so nice...they were annoying the XtdX%dd out of me. Now if all the political junk would go away.</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1363192438621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 12:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363194343015-26</Id><Topic><Title>Shorts Bear &amp; Moon Silent</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1363192438621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 12:33:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like watching ETFC move up and watch the shorties disappear</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1363194343015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:05:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363194418547-27</Id><Topic><Title>would Jesus live in a 12 room apartment ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363189249369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on Jesus burn the place down</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1363194418547</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363194501295-28</Id><Topic><Title>Why spend $1.5 million to understand why Lesbians are overweight</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363119880078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 16:24:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>could it be too much muffin joy juice?</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1363194501295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363196181690-29</Id><Topic><Title>Armed and delusional</Title><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363186332865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They made a good faith effort to test CCW response, any idiot can argue with methodology. But fax are fax, People who keep guns in their home........... are 22 times more likely to shoot a relative than a burglar.</Msg><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363196181690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363196824825-30</Id><Title>Etrade is going to $35 in next 3 months! Housing is BACK and Etrade write downs are OVER!!!!</Title><Msg>This stock was a screaming buy 3 months ago when the housing data went positive! Shorts are FUCed!:)</Msg><Username>telaviv767</Username><Timestamp>1363196824825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363198347006-31</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade is going to $35 in next 3 months! Housing is BACK and Etrade write downs are OVER!!!!</Title><Username>telaviv767</Username><Timestamp>1363196824825</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 13:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'll play along....Weeeeeeee!</Msg><Username>gedownonit24me</Username><Timestamp>1363198347006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:12:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363199622415-32</Id><Topic><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope whatever you just wrote makes sense to you.... I'm obviously not #$%$ enough...</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1363199622415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363199696681-33</Id><Topic><Title>Why spend $1.5 million to understand why Lesbians are overweight</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363119880078</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 16:24:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being Fat (and friggin' UGLY) made them Lesbian!! Dumbo can pay me the $1.5 Million!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363199696681</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:34:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363200373493-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why #$%$ should pay higher taxes than millionaires</Title><Username>dgsrpogh</Username><Timestamp>1363184870530</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:27:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because it is the Christian thing to do?</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1363200373493</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363200631265-35</Id><Topic><Title>would Jesus live in a 12 room apartment ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363189249369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact that this Cardinal lives above a popular gay bathhouse is not proof that he invites people up, but really.... Also, the fact that the recently-resigned Pope has had the same boyfriend, er, secretary for 30 years, and he happens to be drop-dead gorgeous doesn't mean there's any hanky-panky, but really... The Catholic Church (and by extension the Tea Party and the Republicans) are so hypocritical it's amazing that they can call themselves Christians with a straight face (no pun intended).</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1363200631265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 14:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363202960049-36</Id><Title>A bunch of BUY orders at the :30 will hit in 1 minute:</Title><Msg>Going higher!</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1363202960049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363205194984-37</Id><Topic><Title>Armed and delusional</Title><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363186332865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JB...the only Idiot here is YOU! There is No way Anybody could survive That setup... There was Nothing good faith about it!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1363205194984</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363205206563-38</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Will keep moving higher!</Title><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363178088370</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 08:34:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here’s a little nugget on why e-trade goes much higher.... per E*Trade’s balance sheet.... for 12/31/12... Available-for-sale, trading &amp; held to maturity securities of about $29 bill... per the last 10k... the holdings consist mainly of gov’t agency debt... given lower-of-cost gaap accounting... and the collapse in interest rates... the market value is probably much higher depending on maturity length... here’s the nugget... the avg effective yield on these holdings is about 2.85%... then $10.1 bill in loans receivable - yielding about 4.7%... Margin receivables of $5.8 bill - yielding around 4%... vs. “Sweep deposits” - which is the #1 class of deposits - yielding less than one-tenth of 1%... bottom line... some things are goin right... i believe E*trade will become very profitable in the following quarters... &amp; yes... will start paying a dividend like they discussed on the last confer call in 1Q14.</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1363205206563</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:06:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363205516702-39</Id><Topic><Title>would Jesus live in a 12 room apartment ?</Title><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1363189249369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 11:40:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you could just make some sense of what you are saying! Tea Party, Republicans and Christianity? Are you saying they are walking with big crosses forcing you to become born again? Or talking away your birth control pills? Anyone with shred of brain mass knows it's #$%$. What do you know about roots of Christianity or Judaism to say everyone in those groups are hypocrites? Didn't you hear our president claiming he is a Christian? And I can prove it to you in one sentence he is not by any means. Is he a hypocrite? Open your eyes. It may help.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1363205516702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363207489211-40</Id><Topic><Title>Armed and delusional</Title><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363186332865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 10:52:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"In their 2003 study published in the Stanford Law Review, Ian Ayres and John J. Donohue concluded that a proliferation of laws that permit concealed-carry licenses based on specific criteria (“shall-issue” laws, as opposed to laws that permit licenses based on proof of need) does not reduce crime and instead correlates to higher crime rates. Their study was in response to a 1998 book, More Guns, Less Crime, written by John R. Lott of the Yale Law School [5]." "Using publicly available media reports, the Violence Policy Center claims that from May 2007 through the end of 2009, concealed carry permit holders in the U.S. have killed at least 117 individuals, including 9 law enforcement officers (excluding cases where individuals were acquitted, but including pending cases). There were about 25,000 murders by firearm that period, meaning that concealed carry permit holders committed less than 1% of the murders by firearm. Furthermore, a large number of the victims were killed in extended suicides, most of which took place in the home of the shooter, where arms can be possessed without special permits.[8] Ironically, putting more guns into the hands of law-abiding citizens means that more guns will end up in the hands of criminals. Mark Duggan of the University of Chicago estimates that 500,000 guns are stolen annually. Stolen guns mean more gun violence[9]."</Msg><Username>sixgunsarnmy</Username><Timestamp>1363207489211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363208202044-41</Id><Title>100%</Title><Msg>they are also 100% more likely to shoot a burglar than someone without a gun</Msg><Username>notasap</Username><Timestamp>1363208202044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:56:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363208379768-42</Id><Title>Citadel Dumping Shares</Title><Msg>check it out</Msg><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363208379768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:59:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363208403182-43</Id><Title>Kenny G just killed the rally monkey</Title><Msg>i knew it was too good to be true.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363208403182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:00:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363208565013-44</Id><Topic><Title>Citadel Dumping Shares</Title><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363208379768</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 16:59:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do they own these shares or are the just being created out of thin air?? whats up with the 12% loan please tell me.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363208565013</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:02:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363208962266-45</Id><Topic><Title>California Seizes Guns as Owners Lose Right to Keep Arms</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1363146041968</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-12 23:40:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They will be kept busy disarming 100,000 gang banners in LA....good grief!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363208962266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:09:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363209251746-46</Id><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Msg>the secondary offering is not dilutive to existing shareholders since no new shares are created, not sure if this is such bad news, get kenny G out of here</Msg><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363209384636-47</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But he will need Buyers...</Msg><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209384636</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363209851944-48</Id><Title>"People who keep guns in their homes are more likely to shoot a realitive then a burglar"</Title><Msg>Probably not a bad idea around the holidays.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363209851944</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:24:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363209947153-49</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree but it will put downward pressure on the stock until offering is closed. You have to wonder if things are getting that much better at ETFC why is Kenny getting out now?</Msg><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363209947153</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:25:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363209957927-50</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is not bad news. The shares will go from a weak holder to a stronger holder. Citadel has been wanting to exit this position for two years now. And remember, their cost on these shares is much less than the current price, so they are leaving with a nice profit. Remember, they saved this company with their initial multi-billion dollar investment. There's a time to buy and a time to sell. I believe there will be plenty of new buyers ready to grab these shares, especially if they can be purchased below today's closing. The fundamentals of the company are improving quarter to quarter and that's all that really matters. Alien</Msg><Username>alienfarm</Username><Timestamp>1363209957927</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:25:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363209988727-51</Id><Topic><Title>Kenny G just killed the rally monkey</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363208403182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was the only thing left in the shareholders corner. Now he has no skin in the game.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1363209988727</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363210003342-52</Id><Title>10 % float flush = down 20% tomorrow</Title><Msg>p/e is way too high</Msg><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1363210003342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363210164020-53</Id><Topic><Title>10 % float flush = down 20% tomorrow</Title><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1363210003342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:26:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>share count is not goin up... so should have no real effect on stock price</Msg><Username>lucky_lenny_1964</Username><Timestamp>1363210164020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363210217798-54</Id><Title>Kenny got everything he wanted as an activist shareholder</Title><Msg>Now he can return to trading the heck out of ETRADE, just like the good old days.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1363210217798</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363210464324-55</Id><Title>Note this offering is only 10% of total Kenny owns</Title><Msg>Looks like he also wants to get rid of the other 90%</Msg><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363210464324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363210485561-56</Id><Topic><Title>Kenny G just killed the rally monkey</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363208403182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was NOT a good thing for the tock.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1363210485561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:34:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363210533138-57</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pribb, The shares will find a new home. The shares will be sold - at what price is the question. Probably 11.35 if the after market is any indictor. Now you know where the 20 million shorts comes into play. Ever wondered why short interest went up :). The scary part is why is Kenny G wanting out on the last 27 million shares (break even price). I am sure he has skinned this cat enough (other shares he sold at 17, 16 etc., shorting, options, 12.5 intereste etc..). Him being on board and choosing to sell at this juncture does not bode well (in the short run). There will be no change in the outstanding shares.</Msg><Username>invlongtrm</Username><Timestamp>1363210533138</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:35:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363210544457-58</Id><Topic><Title>10 % float flush = down 20% tomorrow</Title><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1363210003342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:26:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, uhh, no.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1363210544457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:35:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211079659-59</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Announcing an intention to sell doesn't mean you HAVE to sell right away right? For example - if he thought something was going to drive it up in price, and he was worried the announcement would kill the upward motion later he could announce now, then wait for whatever might drive the price up to actually sell his shares without having to announce the sale a 2nd time.</Msg><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363211079659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211383609-60</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, we are back on the side lines now, we sold everything @$11.80 when we checked our accounts coming back from our other place in Minneapolis! I don't think we are going to be back in, because holding from the $7s average was a good "cashin' in"! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363211383609</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211419624-61</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>invlongtrm, all great points, I have been watching some institutions take positions recently BNY Mellon, comes to mind most recent. I am hoping Kenny just needed to diversify more.... All the cost cutting and board changes creates so much uncertainty along with continuing low interest rates and the loan portfolio ... its quite the guessing came..</Msg><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363211419624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:50:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211605879-62</Id><Topic><Title>Secondary Offering</Title><Username>pribb45</Username><Timestamp>1363209251746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:14:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude, he gets out because he can get out breakeven after 5 years. How many positions do you have in your portfolio that you wish you could get back to breakeven on? This frees up ETFC in the long run, and is not dilutive, as noted above. This aftermarket drop will be sopped up in the next few days. ETFC was hitting highs for a reason, and that hasn't gone away.</Msg><Username>mavi027</Username><Timestamp>1363211605879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211654343-63</Id><Topic><Title>Kenny G just killed the rally monkey</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363208403182</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:00:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BINGO.</Msg><Username>mavi027</Username><Timestamp>1363211654343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363211818548-64</Id><Topic><Title>Note this offering is only 10% of total Kenny owns</Title><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363210464324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you talking about? "5:18 PM ET 3/13/13 | Dow Jones By Debbie Cai E*Trade Financial Corp. (ETFC) said its largest shareholder, Citadel Equity Fund Ltd., which had previously rescued the online brokerage with two capital injections, is selling its entire stake in the company. Shares slipped 4% to $11.35 after hours. The stock is up 43% over the past three months The hedge fund, an affiliate of Citadel LLC, holds a 9.6% interest in E*Trade and plans to offer about 27.4 shares. As of Feb. 22, the brokerage had more than 286.6 million shares outstanding."</Msg><Username>mavi027</Username><Timestamp>1363211818548</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363211858384-65</Id><Title>Maybe KennyG Needed To Let His Syndicate of Shorts</Title><Msg>out of this in a controlled manner. maybe little lord fauntleroy had no choice but to float the news today.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1363211858384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363213476167-66</Id><Title>Seems to be a glowing</Title><Msg>endorsement of the new CEO and Etrade's prospects going forward. LMAO!!!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363213476167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:24:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363213871667-67</Id><Title>Yep</Title><Msg>Hmm, shorts did seem to constantly be increasing, then on a major up day suddenly he has to sale. Does make one wonder.</Msg><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363213871667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:31:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363214165091-68</Id><Title>And who is the bank for this offering. E*Trade's nemesis.. Citi</Title><Msg>The SOB's that nearly destroyed E*trade.. Kenny and cit executives should be in prison..</Msg><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363214165091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363215527572-69</Id><Title>best thing that could happen</Title><Msg>getting rid of citadel and the faw griffin. they must have been losing money on his short position. getting rid of the hedge fund will give the investors a chance. maybe that buyout is closer then you think after he dumps his shares!!!!imho LET HIM ESAD</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1363215527572</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:58:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363215529060-70</Id><Topic><Title>And who is the bank for this offering. E*Trade's nemesis.. Citi</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363214165091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Analyst Who Trashed E*Trade May Buy It By Dan Freed 07/25/11 NEW YORK (TheStreet) -- E*Trade (ETFC) has been in a hole for nearly four years, and the analyst who dug the hole may now be in a position to throw it a rope. Prashant Bhatia, dealmaker for E*Trade's most likely merger partner TD Ameritrade (AMTD) -- is a former Citigroup (C) analyst that began questioning E*Trade's balance sheet and initiated years of turmoil for the company. The online broker's shares plummeted in November 2007 after Bhatia, then an analyst at Citi, argued that E*Trade's mortgage-related investments could trigger a bank run, The New York Times reported at the time. Even after E*Trade secured a $2.55 billion investment from Chicago hedge fund giant Citadel, Bhatia maintained his sell rating on E*Trade shares. Flash forward to last week, when an exasperated Citadel, now E*Trade's largest shareholder, wrote a stinging letter to the online broker's board of directors, urging a sale of the company. That letter revived longtime speculation that TD Ameritrade would snap up its troubled rival. TD Ameritrade has publicly expressed an interest in a possible deal for E*Trade, and, according to a report in The Wall Street Journal, will discuss the matter at a board meeting on Tuesday. Thanks in part to Bhatia's bearish analysis, Ameritrade ought to be able to demand a low price. So it is perhaps only fitting that Bhatia has joined Ameritrade as its chief dealmaker. According to an Ameritrade spokeswoman, Bhatia is now in charge of business development at Ameritrade, having joined the company in March 2009. In that role, he leads a team that will provide a detailed analysis to Ameritrade CFO Bill Gerber about whether Ameritrade should acquire the company Bhatia helped trash as an analyst. The Ameritade spokeswoman said Bhatia wasn't available for an interview, and she decl</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363215529060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:58:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363215584455-71</Id><Topic><Title>Yep</Title><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363213871667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea sell 27 mill shares on a day the stock is up 4%. f em</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363215584455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:59:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363215690543-72</Id><Topic><Title>And who is the bank for this offering. E*Trade's nemesis.. Citi</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363214165091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow - that's fresh. man walks on moon.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1363215690543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 19:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363216265071-73</Id><Topic><Title>Note this offering is only 10% of total Kenny owns</Title><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1363210464324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:34:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>read the report he is selling the entire stakes in etfc</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1363216265071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 19:11:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363217995896-74</Id><Title>Should be a interesting opener!</Title><Msg>Glad we are out - All 16K shars, must have happen within the last few minutes, WFC is supposed to send an email on a transaction - but????! I thought it would take till Friday to dump @ $11.80. (Set a AON of $11.98 on Monday but changed it yesterday before we went to our other place in Minneapolis!) Between our accounts we managed to get About $4+/share! Will see what tomorrow brings - Just looked at AH and this thing is taking a fall??? Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363217995896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 19:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363218561441-75</Id><Topic><Title>And who is the bank for this offering. E*Trade's nemesis.. Citi</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363214165091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bloomberg: "Citadel LLC, the largest shareholder in E*Trade Financial Corp. (ETFC), is selling the rest of its equity stake after the online brokerage rejected pressure to find buyers and the shares rallied 32 percent this year. The Chicago-based hedge fund run by Ken Griffin will sell about 27.4 million shares through an affiliate, Citadel Equity Fund Ltd., based on a release from New York-based E*Trade. The shares fell 4.8 percent to $11.25 as of 6:36 p.m. in New York. Citadel in 2011 asked E*Trade to hire a bank to review strategic alternatives and take immediate action to maximize shareholder value after “catastrophic losses” that had driven the shares down 97 percent since 2007. The hedge fund invested $2.55 billion in E*Trade in November 2007 to help the company survive mortgage losses. While E*Trade refused to put the company up for sale last year, it ousted Chief Executive Officer Steven J. Freiberg in August and named Citadel’s Griffin to the search committee. Freiberg was replaced by former Barclays Plc executive Paul Idzik in January as the company’s fifth top executive in five years. The sale represents about $323.9 million, based on today’s closing price of $11.82. E*Trade won’t get any proceeds from the sale, according to today’s release. The offering of stock at market price is expected to close by about March 19. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1363218561441</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 19:49:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363218567976-76</Id><Title>Why People Hate Bankers/Brokers</Title><Msg>This is perfect......follow the technicals, buy signals for ETrade, stock is moviing against the trend, and boom......they do this. Bankers and brokers are parasites.......ruined the country in 2008, drive the market to the bottom, and screw investors. Bought some ETFC at 9am........shoulda known better. May they all have poor health.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1363218567976</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 19:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363220083452-77</Id><Title>Margin dept. is nasty, contemptible and nit-pickey....the day I moved my</Title><Msg>account of this nightmare broker was like being SAVED-- A DEEP RELIGIOUS EXPERIENCE</Msg><Username>thebottomlime</Username><Timestamp>1363220083452</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363220155971-78</Id><Title>WHO WOULD BUY STOCK IN THIS NIGHTMARE OF EVIL PEOPLE?</Title><Msg>WORST BROKERS AND STAFF IN INDUSTRY</Msg><Username>thebottomlime</Username><Timestamp>1363220155971</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363221242637-79</Id><Topic><Title>And who is the bank for this offering. E*Trade's nemesis.. Citi</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363214165091</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:36:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OMG! CITADEL sell out! That is the best news in years! Good riddence!</Msg><Username>lrng2sail</Username><Timestamp>1363221242637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363222308930-80</Id><Title>I don't think the Citadel news is a big deal</Title><Msg>It's not an issue of new equity and the sale is underwritten. The Citadel relationship was a drag anyway. I don't think this will impact the share price beyond the short term, and I'd been looking to buy more. Not going anywhere. :-)</Msg><Username>redheadinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1363222308930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363222447519-81</Id><Topic><Title>Yep</Title><Username>ualdayan</Username><Timestamp>1363213871667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 18:31:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad we sold! Got lucky - will see where this ends up??? Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363222447519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:54:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363222632627-82</Id><Topic><Title>I don't think the Citadel news is a big deal</Title><Username>redheadinvestor</Username><Timestamp>1363222308930</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:51:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Citadel was a drag and wanted to double their money, no this stock has to find a new direction! I at this point would NOT buy -( we re-buy!!!) Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1363222632627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 20:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363222908363-83</Id><Topic><Title>.99 cent share sale!!!!</Title><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1358449947296</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-17 14:12:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>big ol deflated tiggies</Msg><Username>jimmynashville</Username><Timestamp>1363222908363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363223238809-84</Id><Title>why kenny sold</Title><Msg>I think the folks at the bank told him they were going to take a lot of write downs on their loans this year so that they can be amply prepared for the stress test in September. Even though E-trade's core earnings are going to be better this year than last year (more darts, lower debt costs and higher interest earnings) their reported earnings are going to be lower and kenny (maybe rightfully so) thinks the stock will be dead money the rest of the year</Msg><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1363223238809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363223347135-85</Id><Topic><Title>Strong Support at $7.48!</Title><Username>stmoon2000</Username><Timestamp>1341945743000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-10 14:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad I marked this.</Msg><Username>davids4714</Username><Timestamp>1363223347135</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363224093360-86</Id><Title>Only 4 days volume. New high in 2 weeks!</Title><Msg>After Market decline is an over reaction! Citadel stake ONLY 4 DAYS VOLUME based on today's heavy upside action. News of declining bad loans more than offsets. 52 week high today, 52 week higher in 2 weeks!</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1363224093360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:21:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363225134328-87</Id><Topic><Title>why kenny sold</Title><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1363223238809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:07:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think he needs the money for another reason. he may be losing big elsewhere or maybe the board got some balls and adiosed him.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1363225134328</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 21:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363226720979-88</Id><Title>86% institution held</Title><Msg>Will be 76% after Citadel sell. I hope the rest institutions will step up and support E. We also need another buy out rumor.</Msg><Username>chairman1600</Username><Timestamp>1363226720979</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363227801152-89</Id><Topic><Title>10 % float flush = down 20% tomorrow</Title><Username>sfvip</Username><Timestamp>1363210003342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 17:26:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It should not go lower than 10 bucks per share what is the 10% down from now. Bought 7000 shares in AH at 11.24 to sell immediately at 11.50 at the open, because ETrade is in trouble temporarily, because there is no profit. imho Huj on u</Msg><Username>huj_on_u</Username><Timestamp>1363227801152</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363228008257-90</Id><Title>Yahoo is super slow. Wow !!!</Title><Msg>Every time I login to Yahoo after a few months it works slower. How you people can handle it? No wonder posters go to other places....</Msg><Username>huj_on_u</Username><Timestamp>1363228008257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:26:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363228246387-91</Id><Title>The crooks pumped the price knowing about the 10% dillution</Title><Msg>and they shorted etrade if not all the way up than above 11.50 for sure. Huj on u</Msg><Username>huj_on_u</Username><Timestamp>1363228246387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:30:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363230418236-92</Id><Topic><Title>The crooks pumped the price knowing about the 10% dillution</Title><Username>huj_on_u</Username><Timestamp>1363228246387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 22:30:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It isn't a dilution - Citadel is selling existing shares. No new shares are being issued</Msg><Username>drchemy</Username><Timestamp>1363230418236</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-13 23:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>