<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374037619039-1</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Fox is OK now? I watched Pierce Morgan's interview with Zimmerman's brother. My stomach was turning upside down with Morgan's bias. Even my wife, who prefers CNN, was disgusted. Zimmerman won 100% on all accounts. Anyways. - Main charge was 2nd degree murder all the way until prosecution figured they have nothing for a proof. Than they desperately put forward manslaughter, which didn't have much proof either. When one guy sits on top another beating his had against concrete, it's tough call to say that using lethal weapon as defense is not appropriate. - Case was racially motivated, but charge again had no evidence. - If all those 20 lawyers are in the jury, you still get not guilty verdict. All you watched on Fox was people with different opinions. Not a jury. It was unevenly split. But nothing beyond the reasonable doubt, and that's what guilty verdict requires. Live with it.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374037619039</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:06:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374038932992-2</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear Option by............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373915048396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, You still don't know how to distinguish the House of Representatives from the Senate. WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Senate Democrats backed away on Tuesday from a possible historic crackdown on filibusters in exchange for a Republican commitment not to use the procedural hurdles to stop some of President Barack Obama's long-stalled nominations. The bipartisan agreement, reached after days of talks and jockeying for political position, will allow Obama to fill out his second-term team with top administrators overseeing efforts to protect workers, consumers and the environment. It will also permit Republicans to retain their right to stop future nominees with filibusters, which have been used for years by the Senate's minority party against the majority. "They (Republicans) are not sacrificing their right to filibuster, and we for damn sure aren't sacrificing our right to change the rules" to ban them, Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid, a Nevada Democrat, declared after tense negotiations.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1374038932992</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 01:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374065720553-3</Id><Title>whites should profile whites since whites are the murderer of 83% of all whites murdered</Title><Msg>since white people murder 83% of all white people murdered, who should white people profile? obviously, if you are white you are way more likely to be murdered by a white. that is from FBI statistics which also show people are most likely to be murdered by family, friends or acquaintances. DUH</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374065720553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070039307-4</Id><Topic><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Associated Press SANAA, Yemen July 17, 2013 (AP) The Yemen-based branch of al-Qaida confirmed on Wednesday that the group's No. 2 figure, a former Guantanamo Bay prisoner, was killed in a U.S. drone strike. The announcement, posted on militant websites, gave no date for the death of Saudi-born Saeed al-Shihri. The confirmation was significant, however, because al-Shihri had twice before been reported dead but the terror group later denied those reports. His killing is considered a major blow to the Yemen-based al-Qaida branch, known as Al-Qaida in The Arabian Peninsula. Yemeni security officials said al-Shihri died of serious injuries sustained when a drone strike targeted him in November last year. Al-Shihri had survived an earlier drone attack, in September 2012, the officials added, speaking on condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to talk to media. Wednesday's announcement came in a video purporting to show the group's chief theologian, Ibrahim al-Robaish, eulogizing al-Shihri. In the video, al-Robaish said al-Shihri was hit by the drone while speaking on his mobile telephone in the province of Saadah, north of the Yemeni capital of Sanaa. The authenticity of the video, which was first reported by the U.S. monitoring service SITE, could not be independently confirmed but it appeared on militant websites commonly used by al-Qaida. Al-Shihri, also known as Abu Sufyan al-Azdi, fought in Afghanistan and spent six years in Guantanamo. He was returned to Saudi Arabia in late 2007 and later fled to Yemen to join the al-Qaida branch there.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374070039307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070268672-5</Id><Title>yes, the south has changed, since 1965 LEGAL oppression ended</Title><Msg>but many now whine about how civil rights legislation should be undone and never done in the first place. that is what Ron Paul Says. Of course he represents an area in Texas where the KKK was active and doing violence into the 70s and he is personal friends with David Duke a former Grand Wizard of the KKK., and also Don Black of stormfront.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374070268672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070302148-6</Id><Topic><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yet another Democrat victory.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374070302148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374070535314-7</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's justice for all ............... and then there's southern ' justice ' for whites if a black guy had shot a white, the verdict would be electric chair.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374070535314</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374070694832-8</Id><Title>Health Plan Cost for New Yorkers Set to Fall 50%</Title><Msg>By RONI CARYN RABIN and REED ABELSON Individuals buying health insurance on their own will see their premiums tumble next year in New York State as changes under the federal health care law take effect, Gov. Andrew M. Cuomo announced on Wednesday. State insurance regulators say they have approved rates for 2014 that are at least 50 percent lower on average than those currently available in New York. Beginning in October, individuals in New York City who now pay $1,000 a month or more for coverage will be able to shop for health insurance for as little as $308 monthly. With federal subsidies, the cost will be even lower. Supporters of the new health care law, the Affordable Care Act, credited the drop in rates to the online purchasing exchanges the law created, which they say are spurring competition among insurers that are anticipating an influx of new customers. The law requires that an exchange be started in every state. “Health insurance has suddenly become affordable in New York,” said Elisabeth Benjamin, vice president for health initiatives with the Community Service Society of New York. “It’s not bargain-basement prices, but we’re going from Bergdorf’s to Filene’s here.” “The extraordinary decline in New York’s insurance rates for individual consumers demonstrates the profound promise of the Affordable Care Act,” she added. Administration officials, long confronted by Republicans and other critics of President Obama’s signature law, were quick to add New York to the list of states that appear to be successfully carrying out the law and setting up exchanges. “We’re seeing in New York what we’ve seen in other states like California and Oregon — that competition and transparency in the marketplaces are leading to affordable and new choices for families,” said Joanne Peters, a spokeswoman for the Department of Health and Human Services.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374070694832</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:18:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074894528-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau serves a five year term. Ignoring Rich Cordray’s ambitions beyond consumer protection for a second, if the GOP had confirmed him in, say, early 2012, his post would have expired in 2017, just as President Rubio was taking office. If he decides to stick it out the full five years, he’ll be running things until mid 2018. Brian Beutler</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374074894528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:28:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374074908167-10</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear Option by............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373915048396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senate, House, Congress, OBIMBO - all the SAME #$%$ and nothing gets done and will get done! OBIMBO CARE, the first #$%$ to fail - like OBIMPOLOSI said "we have to vote on it, before we can find out what's in it"! What kind of #$%$ is that??? That's about as stupid as buying a car - pay for it - and then find out what it got in it!!! The PEOPLE finding out what's in it alright and now even the UNIONS don't like it (Obimbos voter friends) Even liberal MN voted this "health care exchange program" down and we in WI won't have and the Federal exchange program, like many other states! OBIMBO CARE - a failure! Gun law - a failure! Immigration law will be a failure! Going green (electric/solar) - a failure! Only success of this administration higher cost of living, higher unemployment, less hiring, higher health care costs' higher gasoline prices, because of above - higher food prices! More division of the country, races, gender and believes! Total disrespect by foreign countries! Reduction of defense because of military "down sizing"! Mission accomplished - all undesirables have been achieved - congratulation OBIMBO! OBIMBO will go down in history of the greatest FAILURE of a president ever!!!</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374074908167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075148334-11</Id><Topic><Title>whites should profile whites since whites are the murderer of 83% of all whites murdered</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374065720553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 08:55:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blacks should profile blacks, since blacks are the murderer of 95% of all blacks murdered! (Statistics of LA, Chicago, MPLS, Atlanta, etc.) DUH! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374075148334</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374075589115-12</Id><Topic><Title>yes, the south has changed, since 1965 LEGAL oppression ended</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374070268672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats were holding KKK banner. That's just history But Robert Byrd was KKK member and served in the Senate until his death. David Duke, doofus, was running in Democrat primaries before he unsuccessfully ran in Republican. Don't know what do you make of that.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374075589115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374076149002-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right on - and OBIMBO is going to kill Bin Laden again - single handed, so he can get much needed publicity! He should fire a missile from a drone, which has a "missile RETURN switch" on it, so we get rid of our elected by democRATS Dictator in Chief! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374076149002</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 11:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374077008112-14</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wishful thinking - manslaughter at best, some times life with parole! You must still live in the 50s??? And per your handle........behomos - we know who the homos are - you liberals just passed the "gay marriage law! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374077008112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:03:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374077374744-15</Id><Title>God save the "Queen"</Title><Msg>Britain legalizes gay marriage after Queen Elizabeth II gives approval Source: Associated Press London — Britain on Wednesday legalized gay marriage after Queen Elizabeth II gave her royal stamp of approval, clearing the way for the first same-sex weddings next summer. Lawmakers cheered as House of Commons Speaker John Bercow said royal assent had been given — one day after the bill to legalize same-sex marriage in England and Wales cleared Parliament. The queen’s approval was a formality and is the last step necessary for a bill to become law. The law enables gay couples to get married in both civil and religious ceremonies in England and Wales, although the Church of England is barred from conducting same-sex unions. It also will allow couples who had previously entered into civil partnerships — which carry similar rights and responsibilities to marriage — to convert their relationships to marriage.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374077374744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:09:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374077655227-16</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear Option by............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373915048396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, You're not happy in America, so you should go back to Germany where you came from. But Germany would refuse to take you back, then where would you go? rodent, Du bist ein alter Esel, der nicht weiss was er will.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1374077655227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:14:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374079542804-17</Id><Topic><Title>Nuclear Option by............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373915048396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 15:04:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am happy here in WI, St. Croix County and don't miss CA - thank you! Why go back to a country that follows the foot steps of America - matter of fact OBIMBO is taking it as a socialist/communist model??? When Angela goes - so will be Germany, just a matter of time! Only the "Kingdom of Bavaria" and Austria is still a bright spot. Maybe communist Gerhard Schroeder could join OBIMBOS government? ROWDY Look up Winzer Stube, Hudson, WI - that's where we are going to be tonite with friends - Schweins Haxe and of course conversation in Bayrisch!</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374079542804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374080123740-18</Id><Title>Bachmann, Palin &amp; Cruz</Title><Msg>I have always regarded Bachmann and Palin in the same vein as one might when passing the scene of an accident caused by the jerk that just cut you off, flipped you off while doing it, and proceeded to weave in and out at a ridiculously high speed. It's a mixed feeling: a well-deserved crash-and-burn coupled with undeserved collateral damage. The only difference is that both Bachmann and Palin can dust themselves off and do it again every day with zero lessons learned - a truly awe-inspiring sense of self-importance. Good riddance to Bachmann. I don't know if she'll lay low while serving out her term and working out a deal with Fox. If she does, it will not only minimize the damage she inflicts; she'll no longer be outshining the hurtful, incoherent ramblings of the remaining nutjobs. I'm looking at you, Senator Cruz - you're far from the only one, but boy, you drive like a freaking maniac.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1374080123740</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 12:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080504345-19</Id><Topic><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy are you grasping at straws. Next you will be talking about how well his golf game is going.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374080504345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374080849483-20</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Since you are a Log Cabin gerbil, you like the gay marriage law, dont you? Yes, You do!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1374080849483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:07:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081848732-21</Id><Topic><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you have how many instances to prove your point about "southern justice"? See, 1st World War initiated in Sarajevo. Are you saying 3rd (next odd number) will start in Sarajevo too? Your point is that when white kills black, self defense cannot be applied. So, don't bother to use your gun when young black thug in Oakland or Chicago is trying to trash your brain. Never mind. You don't have much of it. So, wouldn't be a big loss.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374081848732</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:24:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374081952847-22</Id><Topic><Title>yes, the south has changed, since 1965 LEGAL oppression ended</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374070268672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 10:11:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you liars always tell the same lie. Yes SOUTHERN RACISTS , known as DIXIECRATS were dems... until 1965 when, they switched to the republican party as unrepentant and blatant racists: hence you have Trent Lott and his protégé "you Lie" Joe Wilson.... advocates of flying the stars and bars, and campn#####head Perry in Texas, and Ron and Rand paul the darlings of the KKK and stormfront. (and don't forget that Byrd renounced his past and racism. Compare that to Perry in Texas pumping the stars and bars, to florida flying the biggest stars and bars, and to the recent scandal that a close Rand Paul aid uses the online name of "avenger of the south" and writes in support of John Wilkes Booth.... and of course Rand has denounced the civil rights legislation and is like daddy a racist.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374081952847</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 13:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374084994531-23</Id><Title>ETFC Is A "Takeover Target" In MY Opinion @ Around $18.50</Title><Msg>John Paulson is talking right now the business channel. It just so happens that I too bought both of his top picks Sprint &amp; LEAP Wireless before they went up. I just took out a long call option position (the $14 strike) recently in ETFC.</Msg><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1374084994531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374086349716-24</Id><Topic><Title>Another bogus GOP scandal</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373998441340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, go back under your rock! you're becoming a chain poster - nothing else to do?</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1374086349716</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:39:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374087093869-25</Id><Title>RCON</Title><Msg>RCON breakout tomorrow morning</Msg><Username>savvyblood</Username><Timestamp>1374087093869</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374088515219-26</Id><Topic><Title>Another bogus GOP scandal</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373998441340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Learning from OBIMBO - campaigning!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374088515219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:15:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374088674183-27</Id><Title>Top Conservative Activist Enthusiastically Endorses Government-Run Health Care</Title><Msg>"A top conservative leader endorsed a government-run health care program similar to single-payer during an appearance on CSPAN’s Washington Journal on Sunday morning, telling a caller that TRICARE — the Department of Defense’s health care program for more than 9 million active duty uniformed personnel and their dependents — works even better than the Affordable Care Act. Dean Clancy, the Vice President of Public Policy at Freedom Works, an organization that vehemently opposes President Obama’s health care law and advocates for eliminating most government regulations in the health care system, admitted that the government program is “fairly popular” with military members: CALLER: Good morning. I have looked at all the insurance companies all over the world and the governmental plans all over the world and it comes back to one item that sticks out that would work for everybody, employers, retired people, people who have a small business, people who have low insurance and high insurance. That is TRICARE. TRICARE is what would lower everything and increase everything as far as services and there is not a doctor who doesn’t know about TRICARE. CLANCY: TRICARE is an employer provided insurance for Pentagon employees and their families. I think it is fairly popular with them. It may have some problems, but in general it works better than Obamacare is likely to do. Employer provided insurance works pretty well, in fact Congress has the best employer provided insurance in the country, it’s the gold standard. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374088674183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:17:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374089877278-28</Id><Title>A subpoena for "Wingnut Chuck "</Title><Msg>Report: Grand Jury Involved In California Probe Of $11 Million Dark Money Donation ERIC LACH 3:30 PM EDT, WEDNESDAY JULY 17, 2013 A California grand jury is now involved in the probe of a multi-million dollar dark money donation made in the state last year, The Daily Beast reported on Wednesday. California's attorney general and its campaign finance watchdog, the Fair Political Practices Commission (FPPC), have been investigating whether an $11 million contribution to a California group, the Small Business Action Committee, broke state disclosure laws. In early November, the FPPC forced the dark money group that made the donation, the Arizona-based Americans for Responsible Leadership, to disclose that the money had actually come from the conservative non-profit Americans for Job Security. A third group, The Center to Protect Patient Rights (CPPR), was also involved in the transition. (CPPR is a non-profit helmed by Sean Noble, a former congressional aide who has been tied to the movement of millions of dollars between political non-profits.) Two people familiar with the probe, speaking on condition of anonymity, told The Daily Beast that a grand jury is now part of the investigation. In addition, a person familiar with the probe told the website that either Charles Schwab, the chairman of the Charles Schwab Corporation, or an entity affiliated with Schwab has received a subpoena in connection with the probe. “The convening of a state grand jury is as serious a step in a state investigation as a federal grand jury is in a federal probe,” white-collar attorney Stan Brand told The Daily Beast. “It’s not a foregone conclusion that someone will be charged, but it indicates a heightened level of prosecutorial interest.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374089877278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374093470485-29</Id><Topic><Title>Top Conservative Activist Enthusiastically Endorses Government-Run Health Care</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374088674183</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 15:17:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all know that Congress has the best, including their dependents! The next level of "Gold Standard" are the Unions and their dependents! Large companies, like IBM, 3M Cargill, IPG etc. had excellent health care plans for their employees and dependents - till OBIMPOLSI &amp; OBIMBO screwed it up and now the the employees of those companies get a "Health care reimbursement account", pay higher premiums for less services or fend for them self's and the retirees got flat DUMPED!!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374093470485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:37:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374094142483-30</Id><Title>Survey: 74% of Small Businesses.............</Title><Msg>will fire, workers or cut hours under the OBIMBO CARE law, OR hire more part time employees instead! Those people will NOT be able to afford to pay for a "Exchange Health care plan" with their small pay checks - so they will pay a fine and go to the emergency room when needed! Some will work 3 jobs, some will go on "assistance" and some will file BK - Nice Job OBIMBORAMA! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374094142483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374094563974-31</Id><Title>Are Conservatives Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Msg>Are Conservatives Really This Ignorant About Racism? Krauthammer: For all those that want to make this into a racial incident, and example of racial prejudice, answer this, where was the racial taint in those hours and hours of that trial, where was the bias and what parts of the trial were not fair because the victim was African American? The "racial taint", as he puts it, was in the actions of George Zimmerman. My #$%$ God, he profiled him, followed him, instigated a confrontation and then killed him. The heated reaction all across America is related to the decades of racial abuse African Americans have suffered throughout American history. Prosecutors tried a bad case and didn't put in many things that might have helped, but when there really aren't any witnesses to the event, it was a hard case to make. Also, by looking at crime and prison data, you see that blacks are more likely to be convicted of crimes than whites. Krauthammer and his cronies refuse to understand why the NY Daily News and others are relating this crime to past hate crimes. Because it's related to racism!</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374094563974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:56:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>17</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374095551426-32</Id><Title>white people committed twice the number of crimes that blacks did: fbi statisitics show</Title><Msg>(this just goes to show that if a crime was committed it was FAR MORE LIKELY that a white person did it, even if the white wasn't wearing a hoody or had been hated in the south for generations) ◾Nearly 70 percent (69.7) of all adults arrested in 2009 were white, 27.8 percent were black, and 2.5 percent were of other races. ◾White individuals were more often arrested for violent crimes than individuals of any other race, accounting for 58.7 percent of those arrests. ◾The percentages of adult white and black arrestees for murder were similar, with 49.6 percent being white, and 48.4 percent being black. ◾Black juveniles accounted for 51.6 percent of juvenile arrests for violent crimes. ◾For property crime, white juveniles accounted for 63.9 percent of juvenile arrestees. ◾Of juvenile arrestees charged with driving under the influence, most were white (92.0 percent). ◾White juveniles accounted for 76.7 percent of juveniles arrested for arson in 2009. Crime in the United States U.S. Department of Justice — Federal Bureau of Investigation September 2010</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374095551426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:12:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374096473408-33</Id><Title>Are Liberals Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Msg>Liberals are friggin' Gerbil Stuffing Racists..All of them!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374096473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:27:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374097198778-34</Id><Topic><Title>white people committed twice the number of crimes that blacks did: fbi statisitics show</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374095551426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:12:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your stats are interesting save that you forgot that whites make up about 50% of the population and blacks not already under court custodianship make up barely 14%. So, if Black Juveniles make up 51.6% of all violent crimes, then it isn't that they're just as likely as whites to commit a violent crime, it's that they're alittle over three TIMES as likely to commit a violent crime. I supposed the FBI could have expressed their arrests in terms of non-incarcerated members of each group, but that'd make the numbers look even WORSE. And I'm understating the number of people considered anglo's because folks like me, with even alittle "something else" added in aren't considered "white" by the census anymore, but of "mixed race".</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374097198778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:39:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374099990821-35</Id><Title>Fubar defined</Title><Msg>From the "Bigot list" at Racism 101: The Teacher- This bigot is perhaps the most dangerous to the weak minded. The Teacher is a person who spews “Facts” but each and every fact will actually be something they heard or something they’ve conjured up in their own mind. You see an influx of this sort of thing around time when people are trying to get money for college. They’ll talk of who get’s scholarships and be 100% factually incorrect. Often, they’ll even make up percentages that never seem to be linked or backed up in any way. These people are dangerous to those that don’t do their own research, those that don’t ask questions and those that believe anything they are told. Unfortunately, those that are most likely to be susceptible to “The Teacher” are also those most likely to become “The Teacher.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374099990821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100233733-36</Id><Topic><Title>Fubar defined</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374099990821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"There is More Police Attention Payed Toward Black People Because they Commit More Crimes I hear this quite often. It never fails that when it’s proven that the police have targeted Black people, someone always pipes up with this line. Let’s see for ourselves. (Source) First things first, do the police really treat Black people differently? Stopped drivers who were searched by police (Table 14) WHITE: 2002- 3.5% 2005- 3.6% 2008- 3.9% Stopped drivers who were searched by police (Table 14) BLACK: 2002- 10.2% 2005- 9.5% 2008- 12.3% Quite the difference, don’t you think? Black people are searched 3 to 4 times more frequently. Let me repeat that for the hard of hearing, BLACK PEOPLE ARE SEARCHED THREE TO FOUR TIMES MORE FREQUENTLY. Contact with police in which force was used. In this case, we are looking at force being used by the police, toward the resident. (Table 18) Force used toward white residence: 2002- 1.1% 2005- 1.2% 2008- 1.2% Force used toward Black residence: 2002- 3.5% 2005- 4.3% 2008- 3.4% What we see here is that police are consistently using force THREE TIMES as often on Black residence. Hey, I know what you’re thinking. Maybe the Black people deserved it. That is what this is all about, right? Maybe Black people are in fact, committing more crimes and this is just a numbers game. Except, there are numbers for that too. Where to start? How about with who has the most police contact. Just so we’re clear, “Contact” is not calling the police for help. It is either being stopped while driving, being apprehended or in some other form being held by the police.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374100233733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100304008-37</Id><Topic><Title>Fubar defined</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374099990821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Contact with the police (Table 5) WHITE: 2002- 22.1% 2005- 20.3% 2008- 17.89% Contact with police (Table 5) BLACK: 2002- 19.3% 2005- 16.5% 2008- 14.2% Remember, these are percentages not the total number of people in contact. The question here is, if white people are committing more crime or at the very least, have a higher “Contact” rate, why are Black people painted as the criminals? We’ve got a ways to go so I’ll let you think on that while I get to the next part. The thing about the above stats is that they are an average of the total number of “Contacts” people had with the police. When we go a little deeper, well…you racists might want to stop reading now. (FYI-Police “Contacts" were broken up into face-to-face and without face-to-face contact. Without, would have meant being questioned over the phone or ticketed through the mail.) Residents with face-to-face contact (Table 6) WHITE: 2002- 76.7% 2005- 75.7% 2008- 74.9% Residents with face-to-face contact (Table 6) BLACK: 2002- 11.0% 2005- 9.7% 2008- 9.5% I think that can go without any real commentary, yes?</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374100304008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:31:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374100363003-38</Id><Topic><Title>Fubar defined</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374099990821</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Enforcement action taken during traffic stops (Table 13). This one was pretty interesting as well. Those ticketed, issued a written warning and even allowed to proceed with no enforcement were all fairly similar in numbers. The two that were not similar were very telling. Arrested: white- 2.4% Black- 4.7% Given a verbal warning: white- 11.2% Black- 6.0% Okay so Black people commit less…well, let me word this properly. Black people have less “Contact” with the police but consistently receive more force, more traffic stops and more searches. Even WITH all the “Extra” traps that Black people have to deal with, our rates are STILL lower. Yet, we are the criminals? We are the animals? I won’t point out that the errors report shows that Black people are FIVE TIMES more likely to have that force be unwarranted. Yep, that is ON RECORD. I also won’t point out that the searches Black people are so prone to, have an alarmingly high rate of…oh what’s that word? Unlawful search. Without permission and with zero findings. Interesting stuff. Statistics are fun. No, not fun…heartbreaking. "</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374100363003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 18:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374102058054-39</Id><Title>etfc</Title><Msg>Why do people on this board talk about other subjects than Etrade? Do you not know what board you are on. It looks like Etrade has gone up a lot in the past couple months. There might be a lot to talk about. Please do not destroy this board with other subject.</Msg><Username>clay.rogne</Username><Timestamp>1374102058054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:00:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374102249827-40</Id><Topic><Title>etfc</Title><Username>clay.rogne</Username><Timestamp>1374102058054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Put them on ignore which over time will help, make sure you are logged in when reading the board as they won't filter. In terms of ETFC I can't imagine how we won't break through to 15 soon</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1374102249827</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374102337865-41</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Is A "Takeover Target" In MY Opinion @ Around $18.50</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1374084994531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which news chanel? I would like to see the discussion. I was long Sprint as well, good times.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1374102337865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:05:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374104161702-42</Id><Title>Not a winning position!!</Title><Msg>Virginia Gubernatorial Candidate Campaigns On Effort To Restore Ban On Oral Sex By Josh Israel on Jul 17, 2013 at 12:15 pm In an unusual move, Virginia Attorney General Ken Cuccinelli II (R), his party’s nominee for governor, launched a new campaign website Wednesday highlighting his efforts to reinstate Virginia’s unconstitutional Crimes Against Nature law. The rule, which makes felons out of even consenting married couples who engage in oral or anal sex in the privacy of their own homes, was struck down by federal courts after Cuccinelli blocked efforts to bring it in line with the Supreme Court’s 2003 Lawrence v. Texas ruling.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374104161702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374105123673-43</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Is A "Takeover Target" In MY Opinion @ Around $18.50</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1374084994531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great news...$18.5 is right around where I bought in a few years ago.......thanks Motley Fool...Fooled me.</Msg><Username>alaska_the_greatland</Username><Timestamp>1374105123673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:52:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374105240400-44</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Is A "Takeover Target" In MY Opinion @ Around $18.50</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1374084994531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL ! It's been a' target 'for the last 15 years. Go pump somewhere else.</Msg><Username>reefbeveler</Username><Timestamp>1374105240400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:54:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374105377491-45</Id><Topic><Title>Are Liberals Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374096473408</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 17:27:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound like your gerbil has been trapped for a long time, and died sideways.</Msg><Username>gerbilbilliedamoron</Username><Timestamp>1374105377491</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374106039057-46</Id><Topic><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OB-GYNs Slam North Carolina’s Proposed Abortion Restrictions: ‘Get Out Of Our Exam Rooms’ By Tara Culp-Ressler on Jul 17, 2013 at 3:55 pm The two leading groups of women’s health experts in North Carolina have officially come out against the proposed abortion restrictions currently moving through the GOP-controlled legislature. Republicans in the state have attached the abortion measures to an unrelated bill about motorcycle safety in an attempt to push them through. But the two coalitions of doctors — the North Carolina Obstetrical and Gynecological Society (NCOGS) and the North Carolina Section of The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (NC ACOG) — point out that the legislation represents a sweeping overreach into their day-to-day work. In a new statement, the OB-GYNs tell North Carolina politicians to “get out of our exam rooms,” pointing out that unnecessary restrictions on abortion interfere with the doctor-patient relationship. North Carolina’s proposed restrictions would impose burdensome regulations on abortion clinics and restrict access to medication abortion. “Scientific evidence should be central to the legislature’s deliberations on any women’s health care policy, especially when the measures would severely restrict access to necessary women’s health care and related lawful medical services,” the two groups’ statement reads. “Passage of these bills, which are not based on science, will have a detrimental effect on the health of women in North Carolina. We strongly urge lawmakers to reject these measures.” As state-level abortion restrictions have gotten increasingly more extreme, women’s health experts have weighed in to warn about the potentially disastrous effects of coming between a woman and her doctor. The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists also issued a formal statement in opposition to Texas’ harsh abortion restrictions, which won final approval this past Saturday.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374106039057</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374107518446-47</Id><Title>Liberals invading your uterus</Title><Msg>After Gerbil Stuffing, they have fun with Partial Birth Abortions. Liberals are Sick Racist Murderers..All of them!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374107518446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374108518802-48</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC Is A "Takeover Target" In MY Opinion @ Around $18.50</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1374084994531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 14:16:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who the ^#^# would do anything based on motley fool?</Msg><Username>call_your_mommee</Username><Timestamp>1374108518802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374108949111-49</Id><Title>GOP admits assault on democracy</Title><Msg>Top Pennsylvania Republican Admits Voter ID Helped Suppress Obama Voters By Igor Volsky on Jul 17, 2013 at 9:43 am Last year, Pennsylvania Republican House Leader Mike Turzai (R-PA) admitted that voter identification efforts were designed to suppress Democratic votes, telling a Republican Steering Committee meeting that Voter ID “is gonna allow Governor Romney to win the state of Pennsylvania, done.” Romney ended up losing the state, but Republicans still believe that they successfully kept Democrats from supporting President Obama. As Pennsylvania’s GOP Chairman Rob Gleason told Pennsylvania Cable Network earlier this week, the party “cut Obama by 5 percent” in 2012 and “probably Voter ID had helped a bit in that.” The constitutionality of law is now being challenged before the state Supreme Court, where statistician Bernard Siskin testified on Monday that the measure would disenfranchise hundreds of thousands of registered voters, disproportionately affecting “Democrats and members of minority groups.” “By his calculations, Democrats are three times as likely as Republicans and minorities are about twice as likely as whites to lack a valid ID,” the Huffington Post’s Saki Knafo reported. In December, Republican strategist Scott Tranter acknowledged that “a lot of us are campaign professionals and we want to do everything we can to help our sides. Sometimes we think that’s voter ID, sometimes we think that’s longer lines, whatever it may be.” The Romney campaign’s Wisconsin co-chair, state Sen. Alberta Darling (R), also suggested that the Massachusetts governor would have won Wisconsin but for the fact that the state’s voter ID law was declared unconstitutional by a state court. Although the laws’ supporters claim that they are necessary to combat in-person voter fraud, a voter is more likely to be struck by lightning than to commit fraud. One study found that 0.0002 percent of votes are the product of such fraud.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374108949111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:55:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374110053564-50</Id><Topic><Title>Are Conservatives Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374094563974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are one tortured soul obsessed with the color of peoples skin.... Lets clear this up once and for all. What would YOU have done (if you were armed) and the larger Martin blind sided you with a punch, knocked you to the ground, and was straddled over you while punching and smashing your head repeatedly into the concrete. Forget what got you to this point, answer the questioned.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374110053564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374112293265-51</Id><Topic><Title>etfc</Title><Username>clay.rogne</Username><Timestamp>1374102058054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 19:00:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how do you think they will do with this qtr earnings?</Msg><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1374112293265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 21:51:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374113588400-52</Id><Topic><Title>GOP admits assault on democracy</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374108949111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Top GOP Senator Says Voting Rights Act Should Be Held Hostage To Protect Voter ID By Ian Millhiser on Jul 17, 2013 at 1:59 pm At a Senate Judiciary Committee hearing regarding how to reinstate provisions of the Voting Rights Act that were recently struck down by the Supreme Court, a top Republican senator indicated that the price of restoring the Act will be creating a special protection for certain state laws that could prevent thousands of minority citizens from casting a ballot. In his opening statement at the hearing, Sen. Chuck Grassley (R-IA) said that any legislative fix to the Supreme Court’s decision “should not threaten common-sense measures to ensure the integrity of voting, such as constitutional voter identification laws.” This statement builds upon a prior statement Grassley made shortly after the Supreme Court’s decision. In June, Grassley said that, while he is “open to looking at ways to address the issues addressed in the court’s decision,” he also believed that the Justice Department misused the Voting Rights Act when it blocked voter ID laws. His comment today, which occurred in the context of a list of limits he believes Congress must be cognizant of if it reinstates the Act, is his strongest statement to date indicating that he believes the new law must contain a carve out ensuring that voter ID laws will not be blocked, no matter how severe their impact on minority voters. In reality, voter ID laws are anything but common sense. Although Grassley claims that they are necessary to preserve voter “integrity” — i.e. to prevent people from showing up at the polls and pretending to be someone else — in-person voter fraud is virtually non-existent. Indeed, one study found that just 0.0023 percent of votes are the product of such fraud. Thus, a person is more likely to be struck by lightning than to commit fraud at the polls.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374113588400</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 22:13:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374118016820-53</Id><Topic><Title>GOP admits assault on democracy</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374108949111</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:55:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Federal Judge Rules Against Ohio Secretary Of State’s Voter Suppression Rule By Josh Israel on Jul 17, 2013 at 5:00 pm Ohio Secretary of State Jon Husted (R) A federal judge made an earlier ruling permanent last week, ensuring that valid voters who cast their vote at the correct polling place shall have their votes counted, even if they are directed to the wrong precinct location due to poll-worker error. Last year, two organizations filed suit against Ohio Secretary of State Jon Husted (R) after he attempted to block the counting of provision ballots cast voters who vote in the wrong place within a polling place (often “right church,” but “wrong pew” voters) — even though they were incorrectly sent there by poll workers. A federal appeals court ruled against Husted in October, holding that such a practice violated the U.S. Constitution. U.S. District Judge Algenon L. Marbley issued an injunction preventing Ohio from discarding those votes in November’s election. Now, Marbley has made his 2012 injunction permanent. While this ruling is only a small victory for the right to vote, 1,800 people fell into this category in the mid-cycle 2011 election alone. Thanks to this ruling, Husted will not be able to throw out their ballots.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374118016820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:26:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374118754924-54</Id><Topic><Title>Are Conservatives Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374094563974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ignorance and bigotry IS the conservative mind.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1374118754924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374118819501-55</Id><Topic><Title>Liberals invading your uterus</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1374107518446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 20:31:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good to know you have a uterus. Explains a lot !</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1374118819501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374119001290-56</Id><Topic><Title>Are Conservatives Really This Ignorant About Racism?</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374094563974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 16:56:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone wearing hoodie was sitting on top of Zimmerman beating his head against concrete. If it wasn't Travon, why Trayvon got shot? If it's all about race and it's so obvious, why prosecution decided to drop the race charge? Because prosecution itself was racist? FBI interrogated dozens to dig into race case, but not a single evidence of racism came out. Are you saying they should just make it up? What a heck? Any white just must be a racist! Are you white by chance? Than you're racist.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374119001290</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-17 23:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>