<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371397519347-1</Id><Title>The End of the Republican Party</Title><Msg>Angry old whites cannot reproduce. According to a new Census Bureau report, 12,000 more white Americans died than were born between July 1, 2011 and July 1, 2012. As our James Hamblin notes, white deaths haven’t exceeded white births in at least a century. The Caucasian population only expanded thanks to 188,384 immigrants. So there’s still no net decline in white population. But now we gotta bring in ringers. Why do you think republicans are the face of Viagra ? LMAO !</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371397519347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407160749-2</Id><Topic><Title>The End of the Republican Party</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371397519347</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 11:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It ain't that we can't reproduce it's that most are smart enough to have kids within their means rather than spitting out a litter and asking the government to pay the tab.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371407160749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407222077-3</Id><Topic><Title>time to heed Ike's warning of the military industrial complex? Mitt just ran on increasing the defense budget</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371057195067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-12 13:13:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>me thinks there is a LibTard who doesn't understand the elections were LAST year.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371407222077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371407881301-4</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Ousts Ahmadinejad !</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371324299715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has NOTHING to do with Obama. It has EVERYtHING to do with Iranian's who have discovered that the autocratic regime their parents ushered into power has served its purpose and must be discarded toward a new modernism. Don't by ANY means think that this means Iran will become secular, as that would be a pipe dream at best, as the BULK of the population, despite their desire for less theocratic control, CONTINUE to be religiously conservative. Further if Syria falls expect Iran to react "badly". There are 115 Million Shi'ite's and far far more Sunni Muslims, and if they start wiping out Shi'ite's in Syria, even the odd sect in Syria, well, Iran will fear they may not stop there. Meanwhile Saudi Arabia is playing its cards so close to its chest its hard to tell what it'll do if it decides the US aid to the rebels is insufficient. At this point they could drive a division of M1 tanks across Iraq to Syria, and the Iraq's couldn't do a think to stop them. The only thing that would put a halt to it is a lack of logistics, and if Iraq keeps letting Iranian mercenaries into Syria over their airspace, expect to potentially find Saudi F-15's shooting them down.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371407881301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371408251689-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Ousts Ahmadinejad !</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1371324299715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-15 15:24:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iran could test detonate a nuclear weapon this Monday and by Friday we MIGHT have an administration reaction that's consistent. Probably stunned disbelief. They shouldn't since the person who taught me the most about computers, Dr. Muhammed Sanati, is an Iranian software magnate now, and he KNOWS how to write code. I can write a program that would simulate the interactions of the components of a nuclear warhead, and I have NO doubt that he can also. Since the Iranians would want the best they'll want former Sinasoft employees or others taught by the caliber of Dr. Sanati. Expect Iran's first test detonation of a uranium bomb to be completely successful. The entire thing will be modeled in software before they ever build a single component. Since I only gave up my program when G.W.Bush made writing such software illegal ( I encrypted the source and buried it until the government grows a clue that writing software, whatever its function, and mine was a serious physics simulator, should not be illegal just because it COULD be used for some nefarious purpose ). I imagine that if the Iraqi's started about the first time I realized it was possible (12MFlops on a single computer, and a small distributed processing server farm) they should have finished about five years ago.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371408251689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 14:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371426912762-6</Id><Title>Cheney Says NSA Monitoring Could Have Prevented 9/11</Title><Msg>Only thing is - I still don't know who is responsible for 9/11</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1371426912762</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 19:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371427513925-7</Id><Title>Read what Cheney said on FauxNews</Title><Msg>By Arlette Saenz @ArletteSaenz Follow on Twitter Jun 16, 2013 4:58pm (Image Credit: Fox News Sunday, Fred Watkins/AP Photo) Former Vice President #$%$ Cheney defended the National Security Agency’s surveillance programs today, saying that had they been in effect over a decade ago, the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks might have been prevented. “Now, as everybody has been associated with the program said if we had this before 9/11, when there were two terrorists in San Diego, two hijackers able to use that program, that capability against the target, we might have been able to prevent 9/11,” Cheney said on “FOX News Sunday.” “If we had been able to read their mail and intercept those communications and pick up from the calls overseas the numbers here that they were using in the United States, we would then probably have been able to thwart that attack.” Cheney’s defense of the programs, which he advocated for following the attacks on 9/11, come shortly after top U.S. intelligence officials said the information obtained from the NSA surveillance program thwarted potential terrorist plots in the U.S. and over 20 other countries. Cheney described Edward Snowden, the NSA contractor who leaked details about the agency’s surveillance programs, as a “traitor” and said this incident is one of the worst security breaches in U.S. history. “I think he’s a traitor. I think he has committed crimes in effect by violating agreements, given the position he had. He was a contractor employee, but he obviously had been granted top secret clearance,” Cheney said. “I think it’s one of the worst occasions in my memory of somebody with access to classified information doing enormous damage to the national security interests of the United States.” Though he sided with the current administration’s execution of the electronic monitoring, Cheney still criticized President Obama.</Msg><Username>hunterspoint</Username><Timestamp>1371427513925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-16 20:05:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>