<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361427239946-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama suppoted sequester?</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361382597065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 12:49:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong. Obama was talking about alternative to compromise solution. Some defense cuts were already discussed and proposed at the time. Yeah, political tool to make more demons in the future because he didn't and doesn't want to cut anything except defense. No one puts forward proposition that never intended happen. Obama did, it was deliberate. Now little man demonizing sequestration. Does anyone remember he actually wanted it?.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1361427239946</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 01:13:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361460579831-2</Id><Topic><Title>Etrade system is down!</Title><Username>vincentyss</Username><Timestamp>1361457015038</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 09:30:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no problems with my account</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1361460579831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:29:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361466974165-3</Id><Topic><Title>It's insulting</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1361461255707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get a life, who cares</Msg><Username>ajbkfx</Username><Timestamp>1361466974165</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:16:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361468746769-4</Id><Topic><Title>It's insulting</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1361461255707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 10:40:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does any of this have to do with a failing economy. BTW</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361468746769</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:45:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361469432309-5</Id><Title>Uh Oh!</Title><Msg>Put that along side of Walmarts report that sales for February are a disaster, high gas prices, payroll tax increases, healthcare cost rising, stagnant wages, companies cost cutting, etc., and you have a recipe for a slowing economy...golf anyone! Weekly Jobless Claims Rise More Than Expected The number of Americans filing new claims for unemployment benefits rose more than expected last week, but still remained at levels consistent with a steady improvement in labor market conditions. Initial claims for state unemployment benefits increased 20,000 to a seasonally adjusted 362,000, the Labor Department said on Thursday. The prior week's claims figure was revised to show 1,000 more applications received than previously reported. Economists polled by Reuters had expected first-time applications to rise to 355,000. The increase in claims last week pushed them toward the upper end of their range for this year.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361469432309</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 12:57:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475060363-6</Id><Topic><Title>Subject</Title><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1361410394670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:33:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to have selective memory syndrome...remember the press pounding the storyline that Bush and Cheney were oilman in bed with Halburton...you need to get on the memory patch.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361475060363</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:31:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475510970-7</Id><Topic><Title>I still couldn't use etrade, donot understand why it takes so long to fix a said technical problem.</Title><Username>vincentyss</Username><Timestamp>1361470625702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 13:17:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Easier said than done?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361475510970</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:38:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361475852904-8</Id><Topic><Title>Subject</Title><Username>briguy260</Username><Timestamp>1361410394670</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 20:33:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biguy already said he don't buy no gas.. He take the train. BTW what you been doing Biguy? They fire you yet? Imagine the pump price if a barrel goes for $150 again wif all the dollar devaluing the Bernank does.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1361475852904</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 14:44:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361478980670-9</Id><Title>Goldman embroled in another scam</Title><Msg>**Goldman had informed the SEC "it does not have direct access to information about the beneficial owner or owners behind any particular transaction or position" in the account** If you trust these jews, then pigs can fly. Goldman private wealth client holds suspect Heinz account (Reuters) - A Goldman Sachs (GS) private wealth client is the holder of the Swiss account at the center of an investigation into insider trading in H.J. Heinz Co (HNZ) options, regulators said in a court filing late Wednesday. The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission filed a lawsuit against unknown traders last week, alleging they used a Goldman account in Zurich to buy an unusual amount of Heinz options the day before the ketchup maker agreed to sell itself for $23 billion. In an SEC application to freeze the defendants' assets, dated February 15 but filed with the court Wednesday, staff attorney David Brown said the commission had been told by Goldman that "the account holder is a Goldman Sachs Private Wealth client in Switzerland." In another application also dated February 15 and filed Wednesday, Brown's colleague Megan Bergstrom said Goldman had informed the SEC "it does not have direct access to information about the beneficial owner or owners behind any particular transaction or position" in the account.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361478980670</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 15:36:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361484483824-10</Id><Topic><Title>Look Ma! A Crackhead!</Title><Username>delucks354</Username><Timestamp>1361197035590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-18 09:17:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1. What presidential candidate thought we had 57 states? A: George Washington B: William Henry Harrison C: Barack (Berry) Obama D: H.W. Bush bonus qustion: 2. who voted for that candidate knowing he thought we had 57 states? A: conservatives B: liberals C: socialist D: B and C ANSWERS: 1. C 2. D</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361484483824</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1361484694644-11</Id><Title>More Uh Oh</Title><Msg>MANUFACTURING SLOWING News on the manufacturing sector, which has supported the economy's recovery from the 2007-09 recession, was downbeat. The Philadelphia Fed's business activity index dropped to minus 12.5 in February, the lowest level since June. The index, which measures factory activity in the mid-Atlantic region, had fallen to minus 5.8 in January. A reading below zero indicates contraction in the region's manufacturing sector. The survey covers factories in eastern Pennsylvania, southern New Jersey and Delaware. Another report from financial data firm Markit that tries to gauge overall national factory activity showed manufacturing growth slowed in February but remained near a nine-month peak.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1361484694644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 17:11:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1361489926435-12</Id><Topic><Title>BO knows EVERYTHING!!!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1361488409372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:13:29 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Imagine That!... A Lapdog will lick the hand that Feeds it!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1361489926435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-21 18:38:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>