<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360336237098-1</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$- IN DEPTH ETFC Analyst Report #$%$-</Title><Username>paulward735</Username><Timestamp>1360008343521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:05:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great info.</Msg><Username>ruben.parker</Username><Timestamp>1360336237098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 10:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360338201827-2</Id><Topic><Title>ETFC lays off 200 people in last 90 days</Title><Username>vetfrc</Username><Timestamp>1360280043711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 18:34:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These firings should have been done..... 4 CEO's ago 3 Less than stellar baby super bowl ads Long before darts crashed to 120k per month</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1360338201827</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 10:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360341264664-3</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outrage</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360099675021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many more "bodies" have been lost in Afghanistan during Obamas frst four years in office than both of Bush's terms. I do however agree with dropping a J-dam from a drone on Anyone whom wages war against this country and joins the enemy , American or not. These knuckleheads need to be killed on the battlefield since it is now against the law to interrogate them properly.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1360341264664</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 11:34:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360353612239-4</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outrage</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360099675021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-05 16:27:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Rightwinnuts hate Obama's success** It is diffecult to hate something that has never transpired. BTW, were you one of the lefties that had a nervious breakdown when you found out about waterboarding, if so, how to you feel about blowing up Americans without due process?</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360353612239</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 15:00:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360356785393-5</Id><Title>Why is the prez wearing yellow panties?</Title><Msg>They were white this morning!!</Msg><Username>president_sissypants</Username><Timestamp>1360356785393</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 15:53:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360358345014-6</Id><Topic><Title>Toyota Sells More Prius Than GM Sells</Title><Username>youbabydaddy</Username><Timestamp>1360189115376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-06 17:18:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Amoung GM bond holders...LOL</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360358345014</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:19:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360359998024-7</Id><Title>Jesse Jr. facing 5 years in the big house</Title><Msg>The apple doesn't fall far from the tree. BTW, wasen't Jesse Jr. also implacated in the selling of the community organizers senate seat along with the governor...that's two high profile Chicagoans that took a fall for Obama. Jesse Jackson Jr. Reaches Plea Deal, Could Face Five Years in Prison CHICAGO -- Former Illinois congressman Jesse Jackson Jr. has reached a plea agreement in connection to a federal probe into whether or not the troubled lawmaker misused campaign funds. Earlier this month Jackson pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit wire fraud, mail fraud, and making false statements, sources close to the investigation told ABC's Chicago station WLS. Jackson could now face up to five years in jail, a decision that will ultimately be made by a federal judge. The former congressman signed the plea deal on Feb. 1 in the nation's capital. .</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360359998024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:46:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360361020232-8</Id><Title>Obamacare snackdown by Dr. Benjamin @ prayer breakfast</Title><Msg>He better look out for a IRS audit for having the audacity to speak ill(pun intended) of the Presidents take over of the healthcare industry and the ensuing misery for all. **Now they have some control over their own health care** Dr. Benjamin Carson Addresses National Prayer Breakfast, Criticizes Obamacare Famed Baltimore neurosurgeon Dr. Benjamin Carson addressed the National Prayer Breakfast on Thursday morning on healthcare. Dr. Carson often criticized Obamacare and government intrusion in healthcare while President Obama sat in the audience. Dr. Carson encouraged a program where newborn babies are given health savings account as an alternative to Obamacare. DR. CARSON: Here's my solution: When a person is born, give him a birth certificate, an electronic medical record, and a health savings account to which money can be contributed -- pretax -- from the time you're born 'til the time you die. When you die, you can pass it on to your family members, so that when you're 85 years old and you got six diseases, you're not trying to spend up everything. You're happy to pass it on and there's nobody talking about death panels. Number one. And also, for the people who were indigent who don't have any money we can make contributions to their HSA each month because we already have this huge pot of money. Instead of sending it to some bureaucracy, let's put it in their HSAs. Now they have some control over their own health care.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360361020232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 17:03:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360361740351-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare snackdown by Dr. Benjamin @ prayer breakfast</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360361020232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 17:03:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bad time to get on the king's bad side since he just granted himself power to fire people... errr I mean hellfire folks who disagree wif his directives..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1360361740351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 17:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360363654666-10</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$- IN DEPTH ETFC Analyst Report #$%$-</Title><Username>paulward735</Username><Timestamp>1360008343521</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-04 15:05:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank u for this information.</Msg><Username>dixon_mateo</Username><Timestamp>1360363654666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 17:47:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360366527059-11</Id><Topic><Title>Jesse Jr. facing 5 years in the big house</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360359998024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 16:46:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should have never imported them from Africa.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1360366527059</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 18:35:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360366771765-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare snackdown by Dr. Benjamin @ prayer breakfast</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360361020232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 17:03:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I notice that anyone who does not kiss the ring of the empty suit on this board is automatically the reciepient of childess name calling, even more so if he is a accomplished blackman not on the white liberal plantation...sad commentary from the left.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360366771765</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 18:39:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360369817042-13</Id><Title>Look at all the weapons the G-men are carrying in Ca.</Title><Msg>I have not seen that much firepower since last week when they were going in after one senile old coot in Alabama. There is one bad guy, but they look like could take on the Mexican army! No one is going to tell us to only protect our families a little. You think we are cowards like Obama? Speaking for myself, I have no training, I am a bad shot and I get shaky under stress. God forbid some person or maybe many comes to hurt my family. They will be facing 15 rounds and I reserve the right to use as many as it takes. If the bad guys think 15 is too many, they had better die fast. HAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>lkjjkleipuieulop</Username><Timestamp>1360369817042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-08 19:30:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>