<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372134444977-1</Id><Topic><Title>IRS gins up som edocuments to try to save itself</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372128006803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:40:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pelvis, both parties are to blame - pelvis, you too need to get your head out of the sand.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1372134444977</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:27:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372134616787-2</Id><Topic><Title>IRS gins up som edocuments to try to save itself</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372128006803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:40:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>carry on soldier</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1372134616787</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372135957940-3</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First, ridiculing the NSA is funny, particularly now, but always has been ever since they were formed. Second, the picture you see in the newspapers was NOT the Trayvon Martin that Zimmerman saw, instead he saw a two large fists fly repeatedly into his face, and when he collapsed to the ground a 6' tall 180lb figure grabbed him and started bashing in his head. Now, let's play "justifiable force". Does this rise to the occasion? How much closer to unconsciousness (and loss of control of his weapon) would he have to go, and once he was unconscious how would he know Martin's next move wouldn't be to slit his throat. You see, most statues on the reasonable application of force ALWAYS consider it reasonable when you fire AFTER being engaged by someone else in a violent physical attack. You're on the ground you're going to do EVERYTHING to insure that you don't go to the morgue in a body bag instead of to the hospital in an ambulance, or better yet home relatively unhurt. Fact is the person who initiates the engagement by engaging in unlawful violence is ALWAYS the one at fault unless . . . well, I can't think of any unless's. Martin COULD have been a skinny 14 year old, and if he'd whipped Zimmerman down like that Zimmerman could have done the same thing, although he's lose so many man point's he have to go to court in a dress.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1372135957940</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 00:52:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372166673282-4</Id><Title>Don't feel bad, Barry</Title><Msg>The world treated Jimmy Carter like a doormat, too. . . . . . . You spineless coward. Maybe if you bus some of your ACORN and SEIU broads to the Russian embassy they will give in.</Msg><Username>obchelli_the_pussy</Username><Timestamp>1372166673282</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 09:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372169763942-5</Id><Topic><Title>I see 2 scenarios here</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371930864242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-22 15:54:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As mentioned by Thirboa, ETFC must stop disappointing. Every time we "Think" things should be going well, they pull out some unknown charge or write-off. When those actions stop then investors can feel more secure holding ETFC.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1372169763942</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372171510313-6</Id><Title>GOP assault on minorities</Title><Msg>Voting Rights Act Provision Struck Down by U.S. High Court By Greg Stohr - Jun 25, 2013 7:19 AM PT A divided U.S. Supreme Court threw out a core part of the 1965 Voting Rights Act, rolling back a landmark law that opened the polls to millions of southern blacks. The justices, voting 5-4, effectively invalidated the law’s requirement that officials in much of the country get federal approval before changing their election rules. The majority said Congress’s formula for determining which states were covered was outdated. It left open the possibility that Congress could enact a new formula. The ruling marks the boldest step yet by the conservative majority under Chief Justice John Roberts to cut back the legal protections that have benefited racial minorities since the civil rights era in the 1960s. The decision blocks a tool the Justice Department has used to halt thousands of state and local voting changes, including identification laws in Texas and South Carolina last year, as discriminatory.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171510313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372172314534-7</Id><Topic><Title>If Zimmerman wanted to kill the punk</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372126839016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:20:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he had a bump on his head. NO broken nose. You listen too much to Faux Lies.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372172314534</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:58:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372172697719-8</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Zimmer was the typical gun nut coward. He got his courage from his gun. He ignored the police dispatcher and went looking for a fight. A skinny little kid fought back. Gun nut coward was shocked. Zimmer will get pregnant in prison.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372172697719</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:04:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372173767638-9</Id><Title>Please tell me none of you guys</Title><Msg>Was so stupid as to sell under $12 today? Apparently there ARE people out there that don't trade with their brains.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1372173767638</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372176435341-10</Id><Topic><Title>If Zimmerman wanted to kill the punk</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372126839016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:20:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't know what you're watching. But you are well uninformed. A show trial is all you want. No details of the case really matter. It's white guy who killed a black. With the GUN!!! Like typical citizens of banana republic. Good grief. What are you doing to this country!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1372176435341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:07:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372178885494-11</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another typical tuff talking white liberal from his/her high perch above the fray. Maybe they can call our poster as a witness, he/she seems to know what happened that night.... BTW, isn't Zimmerman of Hispanic heritage, then that would make our poster under their definition, dare I say....a "racist".</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372178885494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 12:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372180407263-12</Id><Topic><Title>IRS gins up som edocuments to try to save itself</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372128006803</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:40:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Among the many left-wing groups with tax-exempt status are: -- ACORN (now renamed as other organizations, but all still tax-exempt), "community organizers" who engage in profanity-laced protests at private homes, dump garbage in front of public buildings and disrupt bankers' dinners in order to get more people on welfare in order to destroy the capitalist system and incite revolution; -- Occupy Wall Street, which -- in its first month alone -- was responsible for more than a dozen sexual assaults; at least half a dozen deaths by overdose, suicide or murder; and millions of dollars in property damage; -- Media Matters for America, a media "watchdog" group that has never noticed one iota of pro-Obama bias in the media; -- Moveon.org, which ran ads comparing Bush to Hitler under its 501(c)(4) arm; -- The Center for American Progress, an auxiliary of the Democratic National Committee funded by George Soros and staffed by former Clinton and Obama aides to promote the Democratic agenda; -- The Tides Foundation, which funnels money to communist and terrorist-supporting organizations; -- The Ford Foundation, which has never found a criminal law that isn't "racist."</Msg><Username>anthony_weenner</Username><Timestamp>1372180407263</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372182326142-13</Id><Title>Etfc trading with the brokers today...</Title><Msg>up just a bit and banks are way up. Nice trick.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1372182326142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:45:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372182674765-14</Id><Title>So much for the re-set button</Title><Msg>This is what happens when you play to much golf. The man was never Presidential material, the tuff guys in the world get it, even if the left and the adoring media doesn't. ...Jimmy "I'll never lie to you" Carters second term at play here. Putin says Snowden at Russian airport, signals no extradition Russian President Vladimir Putin said on Tuesday former U.S. spy agency contractor Edward Snowden was still in the transit area of Moscow's Sheremetyevo airport, was free to leave and should do so as soon as possible. Putin told a news conference during a visit to Finland that he hoped the affair would not affect relations with Washington, which wants Russia to send him to the United States, but indicated Moscow would not hand him over. "We can only hand over foreign citizens to countries with which we have an appropriate international agreement on the extradition of criminals," Putin said, adding that Snowden has committed no crime in Russia.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372182674765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:51:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372182754137-15</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I represent the sane crowd who believes any lawful weapons holder and those who just have to scrape by on what's laying around at the time have the right to defend themselves from a vicious physical attack by another purpose. If the fight goes on after the first person hits the ground, and you go on kicking him, hitting him, whatever . . . if he responds with deadly force, it's on YOU. Suicide by being a vicious idiot who that day happened to run into someone with a weapon, and the defense can't call his buddies to find out who else he beat down or display his "wanna be gangsta" Facebook page despite the prosecution characterizing Zimmerman as a "wanna be cop". Seem like a fair trial to you? Florida passed special legislation to let here-say evidence in from beyond the grave, let's see them apply that law in THIS case. Or better yet lets leave race, motive, and everything else out, and just go by the ME's report, then tell me how someone who's only offensive action was to pull a trigger that fired a shot that ENDED the assault got beat to heck after, how did one poster put it, he "attacked Martin". Please note this is an impossible construct since once Martin was dead there was no one left to beat the heck out of Zimmerman.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1372182754137</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185634220-16</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on minorities</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171510313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ginsburg's dissent also rattled off these eight examples of race-based voter discrimination in recent history: ◾"In 1995, Mississippi sought to reenact a dual voter registration system, 'which was initially enacted in 1892 to disenfranchise Black voters,' and for that reason was struck down by a federal court in 1987." ◾"Following the 2000 Census, the City of Albany, Georgia, proposed a redistricting plan that DOJ found to be 'designed with the purpose to limit and retrogress the increased black voting strength…in the city as a whole.'" ◾"In 2001, the mayor and all-white five-member Board of Aldermen of Kilmichael, Mississippi, abruptly canceled the town's election after 'an unprecedented number' of AfricanAmerican candidates announced they were running for office. DOJ required an election, and the town elected its first black mayor and three black aldermen." ◾"In 2006, the court found that Texas' attempt to redraw a congressional district to reduce the strength of Latino voters bore 'the mark of intentional discrimination that could give rise to an equal protection violation,' and ordered the district redrawn in compliance with the VRA…In response, Texas sought to undermine this Court's order by curtailing early voting in the district, but was blocked by an action to enforce the §5 pre-clearance requirement." ◾"In 2003, after African-Americans won a majority of the seats on the school board for the first time in history, Charleston County, South Carolina, proposed an at-large voting mechanism for the board. The proposal, made without consulting any of the African-American members of the school board, was found to be an 'exact replica' of an earlier voting scheme that, a federal court had determined, violated the VRA…DOJ invoked §5 to block the proposal."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372185634220</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:40:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185782995-17</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on minorities</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171510313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>◾"In 1993, the City of Millen, Georgia, proposed to delay the election in a majority-black district by two years, leaving that district without representation on the city council while the neighboring majority white district would have three representatives…DOJ blocked the proposal. The county then sought to move a polling place from a predominantly black neighborhood in the city to an inaccessible location in a predominantly white neighborhood outside city limits." ◾"In 2004, Waller County, Texas, threatened to prosecute two black students after they announced their intention to run for office. The county then attempted to reduce the avail ability of early voting in that election at polling places near a historically black university." ◾"In 1990, Dallas County, Alabama, whose county seat is the City of Selma, sought to purge its voter rolls of many black voters. DOJ rejected the purge as discriminatory, noting that it would have disqualified many citizens from voting 'simply because they failed to pick up or return a voter update form, when there was no valid requirement that they do so.'"</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372185782995</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372185898955-18</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, let's play out this scenario: I have a party and one of my visitors arrive. walks towards my house. For no reason some #$%$ confronts him, throws baseless, crazy accusations around and tries to .... what .... chase him away? Imprison him??? The dude is all in his face with threats and screams............. My friend, scared shirtless, first tries to go around him but when still confronted and grabbed by arm and shirt pushes him to the side simply trying to get away from this crazy maniac at which point that crazy dude shoots him...... wouldn't that be almost precisely how this played out?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1372185898955</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 14:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372190487323-19</Id><Topic><Title>Etfc trading with the brokers today...</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1372182326142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:45:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Up 4 pennies. Just fugly......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1372190487323</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:01:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372192637834-20</Id><Topic><Title>So much for the re-set button</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372182674765</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 13:51:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KGB AGENT versus STUPID Community organizer - no change! Once KGB - always KGB; once STUPID - always stupid - no change!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1372192637834</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:37:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372193061707-21</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on minorities</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171510313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After SCOTUS Decision, President Obama Vows ‘To End Voting Discrimination’ Last edited Tue Jun 25, 2013, President Barack Obama said Tuesday that while he's "deeply disappointed" with the Supreme Court's decision to gut the historic Voting Rights Act, but vowed that the ruling will not "represent the end of our efforts to end voting discrimination." "I am deeply disappointed with the Supreme Court’s decision today. For nearly 50 years, the Voting Rights Act – enacted and repeatedly renewed by wide bipartisan majorities in Congress – has helped secure the right to vote for millions of Americans," Obama said in a statement. "Today’s decision invalidating one of its core provisions upsets decades of well-established practices that help make sure voting is fair, especially in places where voting discrimination has been historically prevalent." With Chief Justice John Roberts writing for the majority, the court struck down a centerpiece of the landmark 1965 law applied to determine which states and localities — all with a history of racial discrimination — must first clear any changes to their voting laws with the Justice Department or a federal court. "As a nation, we’ve made a great deal of progress towards guaranteeing every American the right to vote. But, as the Supreme Court recognized, voting discrimination still exists," Obama continued in the statement. "And while today’s decision is a setback, it doesn’t represent the end of our efforts to end voting discrimination. I am calling on Congress to pass legislation to ensure every American has equal access to the polls. My Administration will continue to do everything in its power to ensure a fair and equal voting process."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372193061707</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372193703130-22</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you listen to the dispatcher tape, Zimmer was in full hate mode before he got out of his car. He was using every racist slur, and had no idea who the person was. Just the color. Zimmer wanted a confrontation. He wasn't going to wait for justice, he wanted to dispense his own version.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372193703130</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 16:55:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372194812107-23</Id><Topic><Title>Interesting NSA surveillance twist</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1371821926742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-21 09:38:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope, not even close. Not even remotely close. Myth : Martin was a guest in the neighborhood. Fact : Martin was cutting THROUGH the neighborhood to avoid going around it (ostensibly). The word for that, usually, is trespassing. Admittedly misdemeanor trespass, but all the same. 2nd, there was no witness as to a verbal confrontation of any duration. No audible words were spoken after the disengagement and Zimmerman started to return to his vehicle . . . we know this because the witness said someone ran past her window. Given where her window was relative to the attack it could only have been Martin running at Zimmerman towards Zimmerman's vehicle. If it had been Martin running at Zimmerman the body would have been on the OTHER side of the house. Further she saw a "failing of limbs" which was quite probably the initial punches "then someone fell down" would be Zimmerman on the ground and then the shot . . . which she didn't see (by which time Martin was on top Zimmerman playing bouncy ball with his skull). Even if it didn't happen exactly that way the OBJECTIVE evidence points to more than reasonable doubt, it almost points to a directed acquittal, any questions about the state of someone's mind being forever unanswerable.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1372194812107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372195252692-24</Id><Topic><Title>GOP assault on minorities</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372171510313</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 10:45:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All the above - excellent and about time to stop (reverse) discrimination against WHITES and ALL legal citizens!!! Voter ID with a color photo should be mandatory, just like when I had to show my Medicare, Insurance Card and Drivers License to receive services at the Hudson Medical Center - same at health Partners in MN for specialist services!!! And when the Marathon in Duluth, MN was held this month, participants had to show a passport or color photo ID, then whats wrong with showing proof when voting - the most important task, where proven fraud is committed by the left wing, minorities, illegals, unions and students! (Unions, Students and Black Panthers are the proven violators of fraud and intimidation) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1372195252692</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:20:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372195901700-25</Id><Title>Obama still wants to be Rosa Parks?</Title><Msg>fack him!</Msg><Username>alien_frikin_abduction</Username><Timestamp>1372195901700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372196740575-26</Id><Topic><Title>Obama still wants to be Rosa Parks?</Title><Username>alien_frikin_abduction</Username><Timestamp>1372195901700</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:31:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep - and another welcome distraction from the "Russian Dilemma" going right back onto his CAMPAIGN TRAIL! Doesn't he know that he can't run anymore - Oh he is drumming up votes for his cronies!!! Holder and him are singing the same song - must be a liberal black problem??? And who gives a #$%$ about global warming - obviously NOT the Russians, Chinese and other Asian Countries - forgot Iran and N-Korea will "help him right OUT"!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1372196740575</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372197167794-27</Id><Topic><Title>If Zimmerman wanted to kill the punk</Title><Username>josh_p_levine</Username><Timestamp>1372126839016</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-06-24 22:20:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Little black, skinny kid???? 1. A doper 2. Suspended from school 3. Muscular, tattooed Football player 4. Hiding under a hoodie and quit showing his 12 year of his age photo! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1372197167794</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 17:52:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372202612413-28</Id><Title>Zimmerman is a Racist Hero</Title><Msg>He played out the right wing fantasy.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372202612413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 19:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1372213380020-29</Id><Title>Bambam the incredible shrinking man</Title><Msg>43% approval rating -- and nose diving. Wif scandalrama only in FIRST inning! He's lost the trust of the American people. People laugh at him and no one believes anything he says anymore. Did anyone see the sweaty embarrassment in Germany? How about his Georgetown meltdown?</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1372213380020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372217152896-30</Id><Topic><Title>Bambam the incredible shrinking man</Title><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1372213380020</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 22:23:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayerhoneybunch, Who's scandal sheet have you been reading? Charles Krauthammer???</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1372217152896</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1372219050106-31</Id><Topic><Title>Zimmerman is a Racist Hero</Title><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372202612413</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 19:23:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are several on this board who are jealous of Zimmerman.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1372219050106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-06-25 23:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>