<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-06"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362546307964-1</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle, going to the dogs!</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362438582283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 18:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you mo rons wonder why you lost .........</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1362546307964</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:05:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362546394362-2</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are making moving targets and baseless assumptions. The reason insurance costs keep going up isn't because providers are greedy capitalists. Remember, all insurance providers in the state of MA are non profit while their premiums are just as high if not higher than anywhere else in the country. So, Obamacare already failed one promise to make insurance affordable and it's not going to happen in the future. As per your claim that "Obamacare is huge win for these people". May look attractive. But not at all when program actually take place. Obamacare is going to create another Medicare replica. But Medicare when created at least in following few decades was sustained by Medicare tax. It isn’t self sustained today and much worse prospects for the future. Regular family insurance coverage is going to cost $20K. Not my number, I didn’t make it up! The sources this government is trying to collect are vague and not going to supply nearly as much to give an adequate coverage for over 40 million new users. There will be millions more when small business will simply drop giving medical benefits. So where are the funds for Obamacare? GAO gave us an estimate that Obamacare will add another $6T($600B a year) to national debt in the next decade. If that’s the case, the end result will be total government collapse because there will be no idiots willing to lend us money. Talking about AA+ ratings today? It is going to be A- soon enough. Over $1T in deficit (borrowed money) one day won’t be possible to borrow. Or… Or we start to print money to offset the deficit. Your choice. And $1T we don’t produce is not a drop in the bucket. It is more than the cost of huge program like Medicare. One day gone! We are having Obamacare. So, enjoy the lunacy. I don’t have to convince you, you are going to experience it no matter what I say. I’d rather be proven wrong because it is going to hit EVERYONE. I see a house of cards and nothing prevents it from falling.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362546394362</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:06:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362546745342-3</Id><Title>GOP Loses Hugo</Title><Msg>The GOP's back door man is gone. Guess they have to stick with Castro. All the same party.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1362546745342</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:12:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362546863676-4</Id><Topic><Title>SUCK Me JB....JUST SUCK Me!....</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362536076040</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 21:14:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you missed yer last Log Cabin meeting.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1362546863676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:14:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362547501627-5</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are no baseless assumptions, I have seen, and read how insurance handles people with chronic illnesses. I understand why medical bills are the number one cause of bankruptcies and the scenario I just gave is a reason. There is also the simple concept of how insurance works. The greater the risk, the higher the fees. So, please, again, since I noticed you avoided the very simple question....""At what cost do you think insurers will price health insurance to the chronically ill elderly?" And try and stay on topic, the original discussion was the pubs trying to get rid of Medicare.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362547501627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:25:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362547903948-6</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tried to link a source but my comment was deleted. But you can easily find this if you care to back up your comments with facts. The effective tax rate for the top earners is close to 24%. Double that and you are at 48%. Add in state, property and purchases and you might get to 60% Not 100%, not even your lowered 90%, but 60(70% tops).</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362547903948</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:31:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362549245989-7</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well. your FOX news once again failed you... "“According to GAO, under a realistic set of assumptions, the health care law will increase the deficit by…roughly $6.2 trillion over the next 75 years.”" Note the 75 years NOT 10 like you posted. BUT WAIT, that is not the end, EVEN THAT ESTIMATE IS THE WORSE CASE SCENARIO... AGAIN, THIS IS THE WORSE CASE SCENARIO. What the GOA BELIEVES is going to happen is “The primary deficit declined 1.5 percentage points as a share of GDP over the 75-year period in this (GAO’s Baseline Extended) simulation.” Educate yourself, between your bad math, your apple and oranges logic, and now , your trust in republican news sites to get your news you come off as a simpleton.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362549245989</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 00:54:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362556712520-8</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"At what cost do you think insurers will price health insurance to the chronically ill elderly?" Elderly? Don’t they have Medicare? Why do they have to buy insurance? Medical insurance is not a welfare program. It is protection against catastrophic costs. Anyone responsible has to hold it at any time. Chronically ill pay premiums just like everyone else including perfectly healthy members. There is no difference. Premiums are dictated by actual costs of services and operation expenses. Did I tell you that many insurance providers including very large ones are non profit? Did I tell you their premiums are as high other for profit? So stop painting insurance providers as evil capitalists. For profit insurers operate on very small margins, that’s what keeps them competitive. Bankruptcy caused by medical bills? You either holding insurance which takes care of medical bills, or you pay your medical bills without insurance. What's the case? Are you saying you can go on vacations, buy a house, expensive new cars, enjoy all kinds of luxuries all your life but when health issues causing to hurt your valet someone else has to pay the bills? Who? Government help is needed only for those who absolutely can't afford neither insurance coverage, nor paying medical bills. By no means for those who neglected necessity of holding health coverage at all times. If your friends don't fall into any of those categories, may be they have to learn about Medicaid? For low income earners. And it was available long, long before Obamacare.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362556712520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 02:58:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362566690815-9</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you talking about? Medicare? Seriously try and keep up. The discussion is that pubs want to END medicare and start a voucher program. A voucher program, where at 65 when you retire and leave your company plan (after paying ALL YOUR LIFE), you are forced into the open market and have to buy and individual plan. BUT YOU ARE 65 YEARS OLD, and the insurance model will place you as a high risk for chronic illness and price your policy accordingly. Then you turn 68 and get ill, and when you get home from the hosp[ital and see your NEW rate at 69. you cry. GET IT???? Wow that last post was pathetic.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362566690815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 05:44:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362577138784-10</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are many ways of fixing medicare here is one: first I propose raising the Medicare eligibility age every year starting in 2014 by two months until it reaches 67 in 2025. Second, I will propose reforming the complex Medicare benefit structure, which is wasteful, misunderstood by nearly all Medicare enrollees and prone to over-utilization and fraud. We can fix these long-standing problems by implementing a single, combined Part A and Part B deductible, requiring a co-pay on all Medicare services and adding a maximum out-of-pocket benefit that will give seniors peace of mind by promising them they will not have to pay more than a set amount of their health-care costs annually. Third, it is time to reform the premium structure. When Medicare was designed, the premiums paid by beneficiaries supported 50 percent of the program. Today they pay only 25 percent of total costs. This results in an enormous drain on our federal budget and is one of the leading drivers of our annual deficits. I will propose that we raise the premiums for all new enrollees in Part B (doctor’s services) and Part D (prescriptions) starting in 2014 to 35 percent of program costs. Asking Americans to pay more won’t be popular, but doing nothing and allowing Medicare to go bust won’t be popular either. Fourth, we need to reform the way Medigap policies work. Many studies have found that Medicare enrollees who have supplemental coverage use as much as 25 percent more services than those with only traditional Medicare coverage. The result of this increase in utilization is a higher overall bill for taxpayers, not the holders of these policies. Fifth, we cannot keep Medicare working for seniors by only reducing benefits or making adjustments to the premium structure. We also need to raise more revenue. I will propose that higher-income Americans pay an additional 1 percent of every dollar they earn over $250,000 to help save the program. How Medicare can be saved By Joe Lieberman,June 09, 201</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362577138784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 08:38:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362581806174-11</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle, going to the dogs!</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362438582283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 18:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry, I have only one thing to say to your comment: WOOF WOOF</Msg><Username>sailorbum_94536</Username><Timestamp>1362581806174</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:56:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362581889919-12</Id><Topic><Title>Michelle, going to the dogs!</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362438582283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 18:09:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reason we lost was we didn't promise and give everything away to the lazy leeches across the country. We expect people to work for what they get.</Msg><Username>sailorbum_94536</Username><Timestamp>1362581889919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 09:58:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362583614614-13</Id><Topic><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362532227182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Dow Average Surpasses Record High as Market Opens" For FOUR YEARS the GOP stooges here have been predicting disaster and yearning for a return of the "Golden Age of Bush".</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362583614614</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:26:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362584829893-14</Id><Title>Costco back in the forefront of minimum wage debate</Title><Msg>Source: Puget Sound Business Journal Costco Wholesale Corp. President and CEO Craig Jelinek is putting his name and company in the forefront of the latest drive to increase the federal minimum wage. Jelinek was prominently quoted in a press release issued Tuesday by the national advocacy group Business for a Fair Minimum Wage. In his statement, Jelinek said Costco’s starting pay is $11.50 an hour in the United States. “Instead of minimizing wages, we know it’s a lot more profitable in the long term to minimize employee turnover and maximize employee productivity, commitment and loyalty,” Jelinek’s statement said.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362584829893</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:47:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362585120072-15</Id><Title>Imagine if they criminalize abortion</Title><Msg>Panicked Texas Republicans May Throw $100 Million Back At Women's Health (Jezebel) Oops! Remember that time that Texas lawmakers cut $73 million of family planning funding and thought that wouldn't have an effect on the overall birth rate in the Lone Star state? As it turns out, proving fewer alternatives to having babies means... that there will be more donut holes. I mean, paper clips. Wait, no, I mean babies. More babies. The Health and Human Services commission is now projecting that over 20,000 unplanned births are on the horizon for women in poverty on Medicaid, at a $237 million cost to taxpayers. Although the Texas Women's Health Program admittedly boasts an entertainingly tacky old-school Sweet Valley High-cover-style logo, Republican lawmakers have finally decided that its inadequacies will cost them more than the benefits of "defrauding the abortion industry."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362585120072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:52:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362585459715-16</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of top 1% are not making their money on Wall Street(from capital gains). They are taxed 36%(old rate). Including state and other taxes, they do pay above 50% in total. For $35K min wage they will have to pay 1.5 of their current rate. That will make them pay 90% to federal only! Now include other taxes and you leave them with nothing. For the rest: 60% federal and above 70%. total. . Not for a year or 2. Minimum wage is not introduced for short term. It is permanent. Don't understand absurdity? Ask those who proposed it on this MB.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362585459715</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:57:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362585466099-17</Id><Title>DART is higher than last Q.</Title><Msg>Loan deliquencies are improving as well.</Msg><Username>muyjk1</Username><Timestamp>1362585466099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362585557695-18</Id><Topic><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362532227182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buenos Aires Herald Tribune As the world echoes the news about the death of Venezuelan leader Hugo Chávez, the president of the Islamic Republic of Iran Mahmoud Ahmadinejad has expressed his country’s deepest condolences to the South American government and people and stated that Chávez fell martyr to a “suspicious” illness according to ANSA news agency. In that sense, Ahmadinejad followed the statements by Venezuelan Vice President Nicolás Maduro who hours before Chávez’s death affirmed that someday there will be “scientific proof” that the socialist leader was infected with cancer by “imperialist enemies”.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362585557695</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:59:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362587235104-19</Id><Title>Ney rats out former GOP co-conspirators</Title><Msg>"For a man who says he has found inner peace through meditation and study under the Dalai Lama, former Rep. Bob Ney of Ohio has an awful lot of anger. The once-powerful House chairman, who was forced out of office by scandal in 2006 and spent 11 months in federal prison, now has given powerful voice to that anger in a memoir coming out this week. The book’s 377 pages are packed with insider criticisms of some of Washington’s biggest names of the past two decades. The targets for the longtime GOP officeholder are almost all fellow Republicans, including current House Speaker John Boehner; former Attorney General Alberto Gonzales; the assistant attorney general who prosecuted him; Republican strategist Karl Rove; former President George W. Bush; former Vice President #$%$ Cheney; former House Majority Leader Tom DeLay; and Sen. John McCain. Surprisingly, Ney praises the federal judge who sentenced him, and he exhibits more sadness than anger toward super-lobbyist Jack Abramoff, the man responsible for his downfall. In the book, Sideswiped: Lessons Learned Courtesy of the Hit Men of Capitol Hill, Ney does not shield himself from criticism. He writes a lot about his out-of-control drinking but insists he is not blaming his problems on alcoholism. He proudly notes he has not had a drink since Sept. 13, 2006, 30 days before he pleaded guilty to one charge of making false statements and one charge of “honest services fraud” for accepting gifts, trips, meals, and drinks from Abramoff. Before the book, Ney had talked extensively about his situation only once, in a 2010 interview with National Journal Daily. In that interview, he joked that before overcoming his anger, “I could have computerized my resentment list.” In some ways, this book is that list.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362587235104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:27:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362587293223-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ney rats out former GOP co-conspirators</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362587235104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:27:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ney’s most dramatic accusations are against his fellow Ohioan John Boehner, the man he once saw as his biggest rival to someday being speaker. He describes Boehner as “a bit lazy” and “a man who was all about winning and money. He was a chain-smoking, relentless wine drinker who was more interested in the high life--golf, women, cigarettes, fun, and alcohol.” He said Boehner “spent almost all of his time on fundraising, not policy.” He “golfed, drank constantly, and took the easy way legislatively.” Ney recalled Boehner handing out checks on the House floor and said his ties with a tobacco company were so tight that lawmakers could get free cigarettes from Boehner’s office. His golfing, Ney said, was “nonstop” and “paid for by lobbyists.” Ney wrote: “If the Justice Department were ever to make John produce receipts for his addiction to golf just for the years from 1995 to 2004, he would be hard-pressed to comply. John got away with more than any other Member on the Hill.” The most inflammatory accusation against Boehner in the book is Ney’s contention that he ended his reelection campaign after winning the primary in 2006 only after Boehner, then the majority leader, summoned the cash-strapped and embattled congressman to his office and told him if he quit the race, Boehner would take care of him. “If you resign the next day, I will personally guarantee you a job comparable to what you are making, and raise legal defense money for you that should bury all this Justice Department problem for you,” Boehner said, according to Ney. He said he pressed Boehner, repeating the terms and getting assurance that the offer was “ironclad.” When Ney called back the next day to accept the deal, he wrote that he again repeated the terms to Boehner, who agreed. “Because of Boehner’s promise, I stepped aside,” he wrote. But Ney said Boehner did not keep his word. “I had been lied to and ditched,” Ney said."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362587293223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:28:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362588922533-21</Id><Title>Obama Brings DOW to New Highs</Title><Msg>It's just the beginning. America will be flush with success very soon.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1362588922533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 11:55:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362589921387-22</Id><Topic><Title>DART is higher than last Q.</Title><Username>muyjk1</Username><Timestamp>1362585466099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 10:57:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is that why the stock is down?? check amtd and schw. etrade caters to short sellers. heck they are on the bod.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362589921387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:12:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362589932210-23</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep trying, this number is easy to calculate and has been done, the effective tax rate for the top earners is around 24%. There is no need to post any more imaginary, made up numbers. You seem to not undertand a) a progressive tax rate, and b) most do make long term cap gains or dividends that bring their average down. So please stop. You are like some who keeps yelling water freezes at 50 degrees.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362589932210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:12:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362590018121-24</Id><Topic><Title>gop wants those 56 and younger to pay for a medicare they wont get, typical gop 2 tier solution.</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362522561812</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 17:29:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and silence.....</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1362590018121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 12:13:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362595828117-25</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- the larger income you generate, the closer it gets to 36%, (at $600K it is already almost there). On $194,175 and above income it is $52,531.00 + 36%. - in my last post I was talking explicitely about those who don't live on capital gains. They will be taxed at 100%. Did you ignore that on purpose? Majority of 1% oncome earners live on capital gains? Proof? Or you are just saying?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362595828117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 13:50:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362599409520-26</Id><Title>What Ben gives, he taketh away</Title><Msg>I guess trickle down QE ain't worken so good for the folks in the middle. Yet the Rich folks(thanks to Ben's, Barry's) policies are eating balinis with caviar, and sour cream along with their $1000 bottles of vintage estate wines on their Gulfstream jets...how's it feel to be left back on the tarmac...Suckers! Study Shows More Americans Are Raiding 401(k) Accounts To Pay Bills A new national study shows that too many of us are cashing out 401(k) accounts to pay bills. If that retirement account is calling your name, a financial expert advises you to stop listening. When the bills pile up and money is tight, many people turn to their 401(k) accounts to help ease the bind. Downingtown, Pa. CPA Jacquelyn Basso says it’s not a good idea to raid your retirement; you’re getting money now that you’ll need to live on when you’re older.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362599409520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:50:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362601455632-27</Id><Title>Got Snapple?</Title><Msg>BAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHA!</Msg><Username>traitor_queen_pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1362601455632</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362602174713-28</Id><Title>Anytime you think Obama told the truth, you just are not paying attention</Title><Msg>H. Swanson, assistant sergeant at arms for operations and the manager of cleaning technicians, said 27 people are employed on the night cleaning shift and 16 people on a day shift; a majority of the cleaning takes place at night. There is a differential for the overnight shift, so the night janitors earn an average of $51,644 a year and the day janitors earn an average of $49,481. And the overtime pay? It averaged $304 per employee in fiscal year 2012 and $388 per employee thus far in the current fiscal year. “Cleaning technicians do not earn what I would consider to be a great deal of overtime pay,” Swanson said. In other words, overtime amounts to only pittance of the overall pay — about $6.50 a week on top of wages of $1,000 a week. That’s much different from Carney’s claim of having to “depend on that overtime to make ends meet.”</Msg><Username>traitor_queen_pelosi</Username><Timestamp>1362602174713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:36:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362602376261-29</Id><Title>Almost $11</Title><Msg>yippie!!! amtd is over 20 schw =17.5. what a dog.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362602376261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:39:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362605598588-30</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong. Not 48%. In the end it is going to be 24 x 1.5 = 60% effective rate. Add other taxes and it will get easy over 70%. Now go find a single period in the US history when effective tax rate on top 1% was anywhere close to that. Even at the time when highest tax rate was 93% effective tax rate was what? 51. Those rates didn't last more than 5 years. Minimun wage is permanent. Did I mention that already? Did I say I agree this is absurd? But this absurd idea of $35K min wage is not mine. Lunatics on your side like it. Supposedly would help economy.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362605598588</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362606050014-31</Id><Topic><Title>Almost $11</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362602376261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:39:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most recent S/I is over 20 million. That is the highest I have seen in many years. The VP of Marketing and the baby's daddy is gone as of March 5th. The rats are finally jumping off the sinking ship. Hedge fund playground and piggy bank. Nice work from the BOD who is watching out for the shareholders.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1362606050014</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:40:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607305802-32</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Lies are Propagated by the Media</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1362606251393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This excuse of a president has only a few things he is great in: He is a lazy big talker showman, a campaigner, a big spender, liar and divider! Any CEO enforces a budget to be passed, a short, intermediate and long term forecast! This community organizer can't do any of it and that's why this "COMPANY" is going broke!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362607305802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:01:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362607695641-33</Id><Topic><Title>Almost $11</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362602376261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 15:39:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hedge fund bich boy you got that right. i'm glad their not belly up but this company do sux</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362607695641</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 17:08:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362615603567-34</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Lies are Propagated by the Media</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1362606251393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where did you get that? "Congress has failed to adopt a final budget only four times in the past 35 years — for fiscal years 1999, 2003, 2005 and 2007 — according to a recent Congressional Research Service report. "- POLITICO.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362615603567</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 19:20:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362616836692-35</Id><Topic><Title>Congressional Lies are Propagated by the Media</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1362606251393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 16:44:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- The House passed the budgets to the Senate where it was blocked. House didn't sit on its hands while Senate did exactly that. - The president proposed, promoted and threaten to veto any attempt to remove sequestration as alternative solution to budget cuts. Obama's owns idea 100%. GOP agreed with it in order to have at least some solution to cut spending. - Congress has failed to adopt a final budget only four times in the past 35 years.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362616836692</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 19:40:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362622708637-36</Id><Topic><Title>Who "owns " the Sequester?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362621874151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:04:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The boy who cried wolf? I don't think the boy who cried wolf looked half as pathetic as your boy does.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362622708637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:18:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362623592875-37</Id><Topic><Title>Who "owns " the Sequester?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362621874151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:04:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Old frozenface is the key here. We caint afford ever again to let her yeast infected rottencrotch straddle the speaker chair.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362623592875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:33:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362624782870-38</Id><Topic><Title>What Ben gives, he taketh away</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362599409520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 14:50:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Except for 8 years of Reagan, George W Bush. And JFK: "The stated goal of the tax cuts were to raise personal incomes, increase consumption, and increase capital investments. Evidence shows that these goals were met to some degree by the tax cut.[4] Unemployment fell from 5.2% in 1964 to 4.5% in 1965, and fell to 3.8% in 1966.[4][5] Initial estimates predicted a loss of revenue as a result of the tax cuts, however, tax revenue increased in 1964 and 1965". Clinton raised taxes(not by much), but coupled that with huge spending cuts. Let's wait and see how raising tax on top 1% will help to boost the economy. I am not holding my breath..</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362624782870</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:53:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362625547528-39</Id><Topic><Title>Who "owns " the Sequester?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362621874151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:04:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>November 2011: “Already some in Congress are trying to undo these automatic spending cuts. My message to them is simple: No,” Mr. Obama said from the White House briefing room Monday evening. “I will veto any effort to get rid of those automatic spending cuts to domestic and defense spending.” “There will be no easy off ramps on this one."</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362625547528</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:05:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362626498392-40</Id><Topic><Title>Who "owns " the Sequester?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362621874151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 21:04:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We put forth the design of the sequestration". - Gene Sperling.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362626498392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 22:21:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362632076407-41</Id><Topic><Title>Hooray! $35K min wage income!!!</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362455379887</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-04 22:49:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>24%+24% x 1.5 = 60% EFFECTIVE RATE. Add other taxes, it is going easy above 70%. Go to historical data and check if it was ever that high. Now. Did you ever hear about raising minimum wage as temporary policy? So far it was always permanent. change. So, 60% effective rate must be permanent too. On progressive scale it has to be well above 90%. As prohibitive as at is to generate wealth it is clear path to obliterate 1% in the short term. You expressed yourself clearly it would be a good short term policy. Why not long term, if it is so wonderful? This absurd idea was proposed by your loony left on this MB. Just entertaining idiocy.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362632076407</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-06 23:54:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>