<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374304430121-1</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC Anchor Asks 'Has Ken Cuccinelli Ever Had Oral Sex?'</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374253485418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:04:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In a related note: Kosher lube puts oral sex on the menu for Orthodox Jews Rabbis have certified a range of lubricants as kosher. Is this the first rabbinically approved innovation to help oral sex? Wet's kosher lubricants have been approved by the Rabbinical Council of California Rabbis have rarely generated so much excitement. At least not in the bedroom. For the first time, Orthodox Jews can buy sexual lubricants that have been declared kosher. The US-made Wet range of lubes now has eight lines that have been given a religious stamp of approval, including its "Ecstasy" product. This means that rabbis from the Rabbinical Council of California have inspected Wet's 52,000 sq ft production plant and researched the origins of every ingredient to check none comes from items prohibited by kosher rules. As with many great innovations, the lubricant resulted from personal motivation. Sean Smith, president of Trigg Laboratories, which produces Wet, converted to Judaism after marrying a Jewish-Israeli woman. But what's the need for a kosher lubricant? Orthodox Jews spread all sorts of cosmetics over their bodies without checking they are kosher. From soaps to exfoliators, moisturisers to medical ointments, observant Jews can use whatever is sold on the mainstream market without checking its origins. Kosher laws don't apply to products for external use. In fact, according to guidelines by the respected kashrut certifier Star-K: "one may even apply non-kosher ingredients to one's lips, eg lipstick, lip balm." The bottom line is that kosher certification is only relevant to Jews who swallow a product. Really, it's only necessary for the God-fearing who intentionally swallow it – but some strict observers go further and buy kosher products if there is a risk of accidentally swallowing them.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374304430121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 03:13:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374304451368-2</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC Anchor Asks 'Has Ken Cuccinelli Ever Had Oral Sex?'</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374253485418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 13:04:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So although Orthodox Jews haven't been waiting for the rabbinic nod before using lubes, they have been limited in what they could do with them. For hundreds of years the Jewish religious establishment has been divided on whether oral sex is allowed as part of a bedroom repertoire; it's still pretty taboo for public discourse – and the rabbis who have approved the lubes haven't spelled out whom their certification will benefit. But among Orthodox Jews the significance is clear – 14 years after Rabbi Shmuley Boteach struck a blow for openness by publishing his hit book Kosher Sex this is the first rabbinic innovation to help kosher oral sex. In eight flavours.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1374304451368</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 03:14:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374328282808-3</Id><Topic><Title>BO should keep his mouth shut.... We don't need his opinion of this horrible incident</Title><Username>vst01</Username><Timestamp>1374283575642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 21:26:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and your opinion is as worthless as #$%$ on a Nun.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374328282808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 09:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374329695915-4</Id><Topic><Title>BO should keep his mouth shut.... We don't need his opinion of this horrible incident</Title><Username>vst01</Username><Timestamp>1374283575642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 21:26:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and what was the gop's plan to fix Detroit? considering that Michigan has been run almost exclusively by the gop for decades .currently gop governor and gop super majority of both houses of state congress. The Michigan Senate has been controlled by the Republicans since 1983 and the house has been gop for all but 5 of the last 23 years. Michigan has had a gop governor for 15 of the last 23 years. What's the gop plan to deal with foreign competition, and better technology that requires fewer employees ? no doubt YOUR idea involves starvation wages and no benefits to the even fewer workers required to maintain high profits and high ceo pay?</Msg><Username>hydroponicoctopus</Username><Timestamp>1374329695915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 10:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374330929162-5</Id><Topic><Title>BO should keep his mouth shut.... We don't need his opinion of this horrible incident</Title><Username>vst01</Username><Timestamp>1374283575642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 21:26:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt's plan was to let it go bankrupt. But save the wealthy.</Msg><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1374330929162</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 10:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374333713928-6</Id><Topic><Title>Question for are armchair liberal</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374173161504</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 14:46:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suicide? He wouldn't have the guts or know how - he would probably get a ROPE and try to SHOOT himself! He rather would jump a "Zimmerman" and get shot to become a hero! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374333713928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374334224926-7</Id><Title>GOP bloodsuckers</Title><Msg>Sorry, Britain: Bain Capital Now Owns the Majority of Your Blood Plasma Supply "Is there no limit to what and how this coalition government will privatise?” exclaimed former UK Health Minister Mitt Romney's private equity company Bain Capital is in the news again, this time for buying the majority of United Kingdom's entire blood plasma supply. The Department of Health has sold the state-owned Plasma Reources UK (PRUK) to Bain Capital for £230 million. According to The Independent, the government "overlooked" perhaps better-qualified purchasers like healthcare/pharma firms and "at least one blood plasma specialist" before making the sale, raising calls for concern. While the deal is said to safeguard British jobs (more than 1,200 people at the two plasma supplier and collector companies in question), it is raising concerns about the seemingly limitless opportunities for privatization. PRUK had been dedicated to using low contamination risk populations, and critics fear the privatization of blood plasma could prompt profit-incentivized shortcuts and a contamination of blood supply. PURK, the UK plasma supplier, makes about $110Em in sales annually and provides the majority of the National Health Service hospital plasma supply. Employees at DCI Biologicals in the US collect plasma from American donors, and send it to the Bio Products Laboratory (BPL) in England. BPL separates the samples into clotting factors -- blood proteins -- and sends them back to NHS hospitals for the treatment of "immune deficiencies, neurological diseases, and haemophilia," The Independent said. Former Health Minister Lord Owen wrote to Prime Minister David Cameron earlier this year and urged him to stop the sale. “The world plasma supply line has been in the past contaminated and I fear it will almost certainly continue to be contaminated,” he wrote. Owens told The Independent, “It’s hard to conceive of a worse outcome .</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374334224926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374335422635-8</Id><Topic><Title>Blinghazi! , a real scandal</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374269603189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 17:33:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bami - I can see by the "thumbs down" who's ship is sinking! Of course you got help from OBIMBO - did you see the stuttering IDIOT trying to make excuses for his RACIST pre concluded statement!!! Can't take back what you accused Zimmerman of - then you got more help from RACIST Al Sharpton, "fat cow's" Shemu, Bob Beckel, Juan, Lamont.............etc. on FOX! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374335422635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:50:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374335595406-9</Id><Title>Hate crime victim</Title><Msg>"Alan Turing, the Enigma codebreaker who took his own life after being convicted of gross indecency under anti-homosexuality legislation, is to be given a posthumous pardon. The government signalled on Friday that it is prepared to support a backbench bill that would pardon Turing, who died from cyanide poisoning at the age of 41 in 1954 after he was subjected to "chemical castration". Lord Ahmad of Wimbledon, a government whip, told peers that the government would table the third reading of the Alan Turing (statutory pardon) bill at the end of October if no amendments are made. "If nobody tables an amendment to this bill, its supporters can be assured that it will have speedy passage to the House of Commons," Ahmad said. The announcement marks a change of heart by the government, which declined last year to grant pardons to the 49,000 gay men, now dead, who were convicted under the 1885 Criminal Law Amendment Act. They include Oscar Wilde." Luckily for Western civilization he was caught and persecuted for being gay AFTER his monumental contribution to the war effort.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374335595406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374335744536-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama never helped Trayvon</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1374263249646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 15:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1up, 10 DOWN - dems_lose! OUT with dems_win - the BOARD IDIOT!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374335744536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 11:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374336568920-11</Id><Topic><Title>Blinghazi! , a real scandal</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374269603189</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-19 17:33:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Are you so dumb as not to know that the thumbs down were given by Republicans in this board.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1374336568920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 12:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374339297073-12</Id><Topic><Title>Southern States are Biggest Drain on Health Care</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374205166921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 23:39:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lackof..........I also had an opportunity to visit a still in the hills of TN, a black friend who's family lives in Knoxville in a luxurious home and I stayed with in an upscale mostly black neighborhood took me there. Greeted with shotgun carrying "old timers", it was quite an experience - and the delivery system - right into the mail boxes - shine goes in, money comes out and the "Sheriff isn't watching"! I tasted some and it reminded me of home made Everclear from Fargo, ND! I am glad that I am just an "Old Bavarian Beer Drinker"! Bami must be watching all the Mayberry - how would he know about it??? I traveled every state including AK, HI and a lot of the rest of the world and had the opportunity also to deal for 7 years with Indian tribes/reservations to promote manufacturing plants on reservations for my company's tax credits! From the FL swamp Indians (known for their great chief Osceola) to ND Turtle Mountain Chippewa (Chief Belcourt) to the Nez Perce (remember chief Joseph - I'll fight no more forever!) Sitting Bull was a UNITER - OBIMBO is a DIVIDER! I also stumbled around in the Walla Walla -Thunder creek area, OR where my hobby collecting "rocks" - Thundereggs in this case sent me! I could write a book about America and it's "young culture"! Now TN has their first legal moonshine - "Ole Smoky Tennessee Moonshine"! Glad you liked the "Kings" experiance! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374339297073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 12:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374342783867-13</Id><Topic><Title>Southern States are Biggest Drain on Health Care</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374205166921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-18 23:39:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Now, we know why you're so nutty - the moonshine did it to you!!!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1374342783867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:53:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374343125152-14</Id><Title>THIS JUST IN...................</Title><Msg>A judge has ruled the bankruptcy of the city of Detroit unconstitutional and it will not go forward.</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1374343125152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374346842566-15</Id><Topic><Title>THIS JUST IN...................</Title><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1374343125152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 13:58:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suppose they can pay in slaves . . . afterall the ONE exception to the 13th Amendment is "except when such servitude is part of the sentence of a court." So, they could simultaneously solve their prison population problem, revitalize Detroit's auto industry by providing a cheap source of labor, and #$%$ off every other municipality that wishes they'd thought of it first. Nawwww . . . it's legal, but Eric Holder would have a freaking stroke.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374346842566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 15:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374352371680-16</Id><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Msg>This is the outcome when you elect a community agitator instead of a leader. Truth be told this man has all the negatives of both Nixon and Carter. The incompetence of the Carter administration and the corruption of the Nixon Administration. The one guarantee Obama can claim as his own is that he is a petty political race hustler....congratulations Mr. President! **Here is a guarantee that I've made. If you have insurance that you like, then you will be able to keep that insurance. If you've got a doctor that you like, you will be able to keep your doctor** HHS Admits, Despite President’s Guarantee, You May Not Be Able To Keep Your Doctor Under Obamacare As Obamacare was being pushed through Congress in 2010, the Obama administration and its allies were unequivocal in two claims: If you like your doctor and you like your current health care plan, you can keep them both. HHS Secretary Kathleen Sibelius and then-House speaker Nancy Pelosi backed the president fully in this regard. The White House even went so far as to post a "Health Insurance Reform Reality Check" on its website, where "Linda Douglass of the White House Office of Health Reform debunks the myth that reform will force you out of your current insurance plan or force you to change doctors." President Obama upped the ante, putting the promise in the form of a "guarantee": THE PRESIDENT: Here is a guarantee that I've made. If you have insurance that you like, then you will be able to keep that insurance. If you've got a doctor that you like, you will be able to keep your doctor. Nobody is trying to change what works in the system. We are trying to change what doesn't work in the system.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374354117352-17</Id><Title>GOP admits assault on democracy</Title><Msg>Virginia Republican Chairman Admits Voter ID Laws Hurt Obama July 19, 2013 GOP Official Admits Voter ID Law Hurt Obama Pennsylvania GOP Chairman Rob Gleason admitted on PCN that the state's voter ID law limited President Obama's margin of victory in last year's presidential election. Said Gleason: "Yeah, I think a little bit. We probably had a better election. Think about this, we cut Obama by five percent, which was big. A lot of people lost sight of that. He won, he beat McCain by 10 percent, he only beat Romney by five percent. I think that probably voter ID helped a bit in that."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354117352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:01:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374354849473-18</Id><Title>The costs of sabotaging Obamacare</Title><Msg>It turns out that being a good corporate citizen is as important to selling pizzas as the thinness of the crust or the quality of the cheese. If you don’t believe it, just ask Papa John CEO, John Schnatter. As covered—and criticized—in this column in great detail, Mr. Schnatter decided to mix his politics with his pepperoni when suggesting that he would be cutting the work hours for Papa John employees in order to bring them below the 30 hour per week threshold that would require Schnatter to provide his employees with healthcare benefits. It turns out, the pizza eating public did not approve. Indeed, so serious was the reaction that Schnatter was forced to publish an op-ed piece where he sought to convince us that he never really intended to cut back worker hours but had simply been speculating on what he might do in response to the legislation. According to YouGov BrandIndex, a leading marketing survey that measures brand perception in the marketplace (called “Buzz”), Papa John’s had good reason for concern as the pizza chain’s brand identity has plummeted from a high of 32 on election day, to a remarkably low score of 4 among adults who have eaten at causal dining restaurants during the past month. Ouch. Papa John is not alone in his anti-Obamacare misery. Fast food server, Applebee’s, possessed a healthy Buzz score of 35 before Zane Terkel, CEO of one of the company’s largest franchisees, appeared on television to complain about the law and to announce that he would not be building more restaurants or hiring any more workers in response to his objections to Obamacare. Applebee’s “pre-Terkel” Buzz score of 35 now sits at a pathetic 5. I don’t imagine Mr. Terkel will be getting many Christmas cards this year from other Applebee’s franchise owners.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354849473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374354943419-19</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IT appears you and faux news are spreading lies and nonsense. Faux spouts off the lie, but they do not cite HHS, they say go to a fricken blog on the weekly standard and they give a dead link. jeez. So you spout off bs without even showing a quote from HHS to back up your bs. and it is BS, stupid whiny righty BS. Here is why what you say is just stupid: FYI the ACA is based on private for profit free market insurance. As has ALWAYS been the case, insurance has a network of providers, docs in the network cost less, you pay more for docs out of the network. that has always been the case, ALWAYS. So previously, you could not keep a doc not in the insurance network (or pay more). If your company changed plans, the same might apply, your doc might not be on the new plans list of providers. get it? that's the way it always was and i think that is the way it is now. You can always keep your doc, but if out of network you pay more same as before.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374354943419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374354955177-20</Id><Topic><Title>The costs of sabotaging Obamacare</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354849473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:14:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>While these corporate complainers have sought to explain away the hit they are experiencing at the hands of the public’s perception, one such company is facing the music straight on. Darden Restaurants, Inc.— owner of Olive Garden, Red Lobster and LongHorn Steakhouse—has lowered its profit projections for the quarter ending November 25th, acknowledging that its bad numbers are the result of poorly performing promotions, Superstorm Sandy and…wait for it…the poor publicity it engendered by its decision to test out a plan to cut back on healthcare costs by putting more workers on part-time schedules. Check out these rather epic declines: Hopefully, other businesses seeking to avoid their responsibilities under the healthcare law—such as Walmart who intends to cut back employee hours in the effort to push workers onto Medicaid rolls rather than take responsibility for their employees’ health care—will get the message. "</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354955177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374356414769-21</Id><Title>Even low paid workers can afford health insurance with the ACA</Title><Msg>No longer is the USA the only modern nation where low earning service sector employees can't get health insurance. It seemed the USA was the only nation where cooks and waitresses can't get health insurance. A pizza cook in Canada has health insurance but the one in the USA does not. no longer, thanks to the ACA now a young min wage person in LA will be able to buy the silver plan for $34 a month. •Preliminary premiums appear to be affordable even for young men. For example, in Los Angeles - the county with the largest number of uninsured Americans in the nation - the lowest cost silver plan in 2014 for a 25-year-old individual costs $174 per month without a tax credit, $34 per month for an individual whose income is $17,235, and a catastrophic plan can be purchased for $117 per month for an individual. July 18, 2013 New report finds competition lowers premiums by nearly 20 percent in the Health Insurance Marketplace</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374356414769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374365849515-22</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've tried three times to post the URL and Yahoo has blocked it each time. It's on the White House web site, then a slash, then "realitycheck/3" then a slash then hit return. Let's see if it lets that through, or get an explanation from Yahoo on why the government web sites aren't on their "white" list.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374365849515</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 20:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374366129587-23</Id><Topic><Title>BO cought in another lie</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374352371680</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 16:32:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, and SkyWaltzer, this makes you the, how did you put it . . . the one spreading lies, nonsense, or, most likely ignorance. I remembered the quote as soon as I saw it. In fact all you have to do is use a FRAGMENT of the quote, and google, and it takes you RIGHT to the WhiteHouse website offering a transcript of the speech, an MP4 of the speech . . . What part of all that are you going to call lies and nonsense? Like the employer mandate that was, by law, supposed to start next year? No reason it can't be done, except the mass firings and cutting of hours that would result would cost the Democratic party not only further seats in the House, but most likely loose them the Senate as well. Obamacare is what happens when you vote a poorly written draft document into law without bothering to read it first.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374366129587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 20:22:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374366265009-24</Id><Topic><Title>The costs of sabotaging Obamacare</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374354849473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:14:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They got the message. Don't make any announcements . . . just DO it. Kinda the way Obamacare was passed in the first place.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374366265009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 20:24:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374366460100-25</Id><Topic><Title>Even low paid workers can afford health insurance with the ACA</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1374356414769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 17:40:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very very true, everyone should be able to afford it . . . . assuming of course they bother to fill out the paperwork. Now I wonder how many people will find themselves unable to fill out the paperwork and as a result won't have insurance by the end of next year? I'm betting it will be a SUBSTANTIAL percentage of the people who, as you guessed, don't currently have insurance. We need to get mobile assistance vans into the poor working class neighborhoods to help those people know how to get their vouchers and file for insurance or the government speak in the rules, etc, is going to drive them straight away. Particularly the illegal aliens, who have no reason to fear fines since their identities are "mutable".</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1374366460100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 20:27:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374375988643-26</Id><Title>For the next 184 weeks</Title><Msg>BO will be POTUS and the GOP tools will whine and lie about it!!!</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1374375988643</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-20 23:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>