<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364569205208-1</Id><Title>Back in the news</Title><Msg>Thursday March 28 2013 FREDERIC J. FROMMER Associated Press= WASHINGTON (AP) — A federal judge refused on Thursday to dismiss a Federal Election Commission lawsuit that accuses former Sen. Larry Craig of misusing $217,000 in campaign funds for his legal defense after his arrest in a 2007 airport bathroom sex sting. Craig had argued that the airport bathroom trip fell under his official duties as senator because he was traveling between Idaho and Washington for work, and therefore the legal fees could be paid for with campaign money. But U.S. District Court Judge Amy Berman Jackson rejected that argument. She wrote in her ruling that the charge against Craig didn't relate "to his conduct as a legislator, but only actions undertaken in the privacy and anonymity of a restroom stall." Jackson set a scheduling conference in the case for April 26. The Idaho Republican was arrested by an undercover police officer at the Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport. The officer said Craig tapped his feet and signaled under a stall divider that he wanted sex. Craig pleaded guilty to disorderly conduct and paid a fine. After his arrest later became public, Craig tried unsuccessfully to reverse his conviction.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364569205208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364569620115-2</Id><Title>Another NRA 'genius"</Title><Msg>TOM KLUDT 9:40 AM EDT, FRIDAY MARCH 29, 2013 A prominent Utah gun lobbyist fell victim to a robbery earlier this week when his AR-15 was stolen from his vehicle, the Salt Lake City Tribune reported. Clark Aposhian, chairman of the Utah Shooting Sports Council, said his car was locked and parked outside his home on Wednesday, with his weapon secured in a case in the backseat. By Thursday morning, the AR-15 was nowhere to be found. Investigators still have no leads on the missing weapon.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364569620115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364569986531-3</Id><Topic><Title>Another NRA 'genius"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364569620115</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:07:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Man Charged with Hunting Deer in a Walmart Parking Lot By Melissa LockerMarch 29, 2013 Arcangelo Bianco Jr. wasn’t at Walmart to hunt for bargains. Instead, the Pennsylvania man has been charged with hunting deer in the parking lot of the super store, the Indiana Gazette reports this week. Bianco allegedly spotted the 10-point white-tailed deer while running errands on Nov. 26, 2012 in Blairsville, Pa., which is 30 miles east of Pittsburgh. He leaped from his truck, chased the deer and fired several rounds from a handgun at it while still in the Walmart parking lot, eventually bagging the buck nearby. Reasonably concerned, Walmart shoppers called 911 to report a man with a gun running through the parking lot. Now Bianco has been charged with reckless endangerment and five other hunting-related charges, including hunting without a license, for his alleged acts. Evidence against Bianco includes surveillance footage and the deer that was seized from the processor where Bianco left it. “Obviously, we can’t have someone running through a Walmart parking lot shooting at a deer,” Jack Lucas, the wildlife conservation officer who investigated the incident, told the Indiana Gazette. “One stray bullet, as we all know, could have wrecked someone’s life,” said Patrick Dougherty, the Indiana County District Attorney. “So, I think we’re very lucky no one was hurt.” Bianco faces a preliminary hearing May 1.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364569986531</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364571376456-4</Id><Title>Simpson gets one right</Title><Msg>By Nick Wing Posted: 03/29/2013 Former Sen. Alan Simpson (R-Wyo.) has never shied away from turning his trademark brand of colorful rhetoric on his own party, and on Thursday he did so again, in a scathing examination of the Republican approach on social issues. In an interview published in the Los Angeles Times, Simpson, who has weighed in prominently on fiscal issues in recent years, blasted the trend of old, white Republican males feeling compelled to legislate on abortion. " a hideous thing. It's terrible," Simpson said of the medical procedure. "But it's a deeply intimate and personal thing. ... Men legislators shouldn't even vote on it." Simpson also called out what he saw as a "homophobic strain in our party," and accused members of the GOP of following a social agenda that was inconsistent with their broader political ideology.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364571376456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364571690210-5</Id><Title>Freiberg and Petrilli.......</Title><Msg>Took home 10.7 million and 2.5 million last year in total comp. Boy, that was money well spent.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364571690210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364590907453-6</Id><Topic><Title>A triumph Mr.Obama, a triumph</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364500051784</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 15:47:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets review the Democratic clowns shall we...Al Gore, John Kerry, Hilary Clinton, Joe(you'al)Biden, Nancy Pelosi, and the clown with biggest nose and shoes in the center ring, the one and only, Barrack Obama. I think you clowns on the left are getting ahead of your selves. You still have Obamacare to sink your prospects for 2014...stay tuned.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364590907453</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364591212866-7</Id><Topic><Title>the way some whine about health insurance</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364413123301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 15:38:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey wise guy, why are you responding if we are on Ignore. BTW, you always know when you have bested a liberal, they always revert to name calling.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364591212866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364591822597-8</Id><Title>California is insolvent</Title><Msg>And this is after Jerry(moonbeam)Brown put through his tax increase and the dopes in this state voted to raise taxes on themselves. At some point these fools in this state will realize that they have been hoodwinked by the Democratic party, or again maybe not...look at Europe. State auditor: California's net worth at negative $127.2 billion If California's state government was a business, it would be a candidate for insolvency with a negative net worth of $127.2 billion, according to an annual financial report issued by State Auditor Elaine Howle and the Bureau of State Audits. The report, which covers the fiscal year ending June 30, 2012, says that the state's negative status -- all of its assets minus all of its liabilities -- increased that year, largely because it spent more than it received in revenue. During the 2011-12 fiscal year, the state's general fund spent $1.7 billion more than it received in revenues and wound up with an accumulated deficit of just under $23 billion from several years of red ink. Gov. Jerry Brown has referred to that and other budget gaps, mostly money owed to schools, as a "wall of debt" totaling more than $30 billion.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364591822597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364597818499-9</Id><Topic><Title>California is insolvent</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364591822597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not insolvent. It's incontinent. Because of negative, resource wasting do nothings like you. All you do is sit on the computer and whine like hormonal old woman.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1364597818499</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364599874443-10</Id><Topic><Title>California is insolvent</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364591822597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California taxed rich people so they've now got less of them. California gave entitlements to the lazy poor and now got more of them. Only thing left is a Bambam bailout. He'll have to confiscate money from more fiscally responsible states to cover Cali's bad behavior. It's Bambam to the rescue wif taxpayer money from responsible states who have no say in how Cali spends their confiscated funds.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364599874443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 19:31:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364600334711-11</Id><Topic><Title>California is insolvent</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1364591822597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:17:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People go to California to get rich. And they do. Then, after California helps them get wealthy, they leave to save taxes. Cal is the #1 state in the nation. It's a world power of it's own. Thank god we don't have whiners like you who wait til California leads you to the next big wonder. We Cal goes, you little states follow. Even with taxes.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1364600334711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 19:38:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364602993821-12</Id><Title>Top Republican Warns Of French People Illegally Crossing Mexican Border In South Texas</Title><Msg>By Igor Volsky During an appearance on a local radio station Thursday morning, Texas Senator John Cornyn (R) claimed that people from all over the world are now entering the country illegally through Texas and insisted that any Congressional effort to reform the immigration system must invest in border security. “You gotta stop the flow of people coming across and my friends and your friends Edd who have places in South Texas tell me, as a matter a fact a guy told me last night, he said we’ve got people coming across our place speaking Chinese, French and basically all of the languages in the world, coming through and across our southern border,” Cornyn said during an interview on KSEV. While lawmakers agree that border security should be part of any comprehensive immigration reform package, the U.S. border is more secure than ever before. Border crossings are at 40-year low — falling to their lowest level since the Nixon administration — and net undocumented migration is at or below zero. Border agents patrol every single mile of the border every day and the vast majority of the border already meets one of Homeland Security’s highest standards of security. “People are willing to try to weigh in and try to improve our broken immigration system,” Cornyn conceded. “What we have now is a defacto amnesty when we have 11 or 12 million folks living here who have come in without going through the proper channels.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364602993821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364603417842-13</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Voter ID push found racist</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364245743675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans Introduce Legislation To Discriminate Against Non-English Speakers By Scott Keyes on Mar 29, 2013 at 1:30 pm Left: Sen. Jim Inhofe (R-OK). Right: Rep. Steve King (R-IA) Republicans are continuing their minority outreach efforts this month by introducing a bill outlawing Spanish and other non-English languages from being used in federal documents. Rep. Steve King (R-IA), most recently in the headlines after attacking President Obama’s young daughters for going on vacation, introduced the English Language Unity Act in the House earlier this month, along with Sen. Jim Inhofe (R-OK) in the Senate. As King notes on his website, the bill would require “all official functions of the United States to be conducted in English.” Federal and state governments print thousands of documents every year, many of which are translated into other languages besides English. One major impact King’s bill could have is to stop the decades-long practice of printing non-English ballots in areas where there’s a significant non-English language group. Indeed, Section 203 of the Voting Rights Act of 1965 currently requires local jurisdictions with a substantial number of non-English speakers to allow them to vote in other languages.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364603417842</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364604325150-14</Id><Title>The 28th Amendment</Title><Msg>Congress shall make no law that applies to the citizens of the United States that does not apply equally to the Senators or Representatives, and Congress shall make no law that applies to the Senators or Representatives that does not apply equally to the citizens of the United States. ``````````````````````````````````````````````````````````````` Seems dumbocare aint good enough for Bambam, the Congress and their families.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364604325150</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364610744313-15</Id><Title>faux news a "media colostomy bag"</Title><Msg>Jim Carrey has some harsh words for Fox News. Carrey released a statement on Friday blasting the conservative news network as "a media colostomy bag ..................I thought he was being kind, I would have said they ARE sh it.</Msg><Username>hardwaregurufromtheheartland</Username><Timestamp>1364610744313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364612853445-16</Id><Topic><Title>Shame on Republicans</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1364529368891</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 23:56:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like the wingnutz gun lovers here are in full support of their straw buyers. It's obvious from their posts that they wouldn't qualify for a gun license.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1364612853445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364615658515-17</Id><Title>Ben Carson - well that was a short campaign...</Title><Msg>done and done before it started.</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1364615658515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:54:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>