<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-25"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364185258330-1</Id><Title>The Republican Party’s Ratings Now Stand at a 20-Year Low</Title><Msg>Remember when Speaker John Boehner lamented that President Obama wanted to shove the Republican Party to the “dustbin of history”? Turns out, it’s not Obama who’s killing the GOP; it’s more of a suicide. For those who pay attention, this should come as no surprise, but rather a “what took so long” response. Yes, America is on to the GOP. The Republican Party’s ratings now stand at a 20-year low. Andrew Kohut, founding director and former president of the Pew Research Center and president of the Gallup Organization from 1979 to 1989, is a polling expert, so when he writes a column titled “The numbers prove it: The GOP is estranged from America”, it means something. Writing in the Washington Post, Kohut compares the radical image problem of today’s GOP with that of the Democratic Party of the 1960s and early 1970s.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364185258330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:20:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364193127068-2</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT! Breaking News from da Bear ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1364100894182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The news should be read opposite way. Citadel's leaving is a signal that Etrade would be sold, not that Etrade has less chance of being sold because Citadel would no longer pressure for a sale. Schw or amtd won't want to deal with a hedge fund which controls the majority stake of Etrade.</Msg><Username>etfc2013</Username><Timestamp>1364193127068</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 02:32:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364193184666-3</Id><Topic><Title>Feds Spend $2.7M to Study Drunk Lesbians</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363811176110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ever hear of the 'bridge to nowhere'?</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1364193184666</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 02:33:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364218138431-4</Id><Title>gop, please kill the Reagan stimulus of the V-22 Osprey, we are broke as Boehner says</Title><Msg>in 1986 the they said this aircraft program would cost $2.5 billion........ well so far it has cost about $30 billion and another $30 billion is needed.........</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364218138431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364219362724-5</Id><Topic><Title>gop, please kill the Reagan stimulus of the V-22 Osprey, we are broke as Boehner says</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364218138431</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 09:28:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Osprey has been a boondoggle since it began. It has killed more test pilots and wasted more time and money. It is a lesson that just throwing more money at a project doesn't mean it will be a success. Cut bait and start over Washington.</Msg><Username>long_short_007</Username><Timestamp>1364219362724</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 09:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364220029195-6</Id><Title>Obama and the Demunists have been in office for five years plus</Title><Msg>They have not done a single thing right. Obama, Reid, Pelosi are all bought and paid for. If i bought and paid for Harry Reid, he would be sporting some major welts. HAHAHAHAHAH!!</Msg><Username>cowboysamsuxballs</Username><Timestamp>1364220029195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364221833609-7</Id><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Msg>what next closing down officers clubs? or the hundreds of military golf courses around the world? The Army alone has 50.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364224291607-8</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Closing 149 airport towers and releasing thousands of criminals on the streets is better solution? What about not sending fighter jets and tanks to Egypt? How painful this is going to be?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364224291607</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:11:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364225224738-9</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>small airports towers are just welfare for the rich who own their on planes so screw them! Boehner is right, we are certainly too broke for that..... you lie about criminals being released...... and moron, Israel gets 20 times the aid that Egypt does per capita.. and Egypt never murdered US servicemen, attacked US facilities and US ships or committed acts of espionage against the USA, nor is it in violation of UN resolutions and international law...... do you suppose that when the gop threw its debt ceiling tantrum and then agreed to the sequester that programs and people would not suffer and why are you whining about the spending cuts at all? You are all for them.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225224738</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364225916675-10</Id><Title>charge for meals in the military! How about that Mr. Boehner?</Title><Msg>we are too broke to pay the high pay AND room and board. At least require personnel to pay for their meals. After all, before the "all volunteer" military E-1 recruits were paid about $500 a month (today's money), now they start at $1500 a month. making them pay for meals will really help keeping the billionaire's tax rates low, and is in keeping with other gop ideas to cut grannies on social security and disabled veterans to, you know, reduce the deficit. (and besides, you all hate the very idea of a "standing army" so let's cut back on this kind of socialism.)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225916675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364228289617-11</Id><Topic><Title>charge for meals in the military! How about that Mr. Boehner?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225916675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What has this to do with ETFC?..., besides, junior enlisted have always had their pay reduced when provided a meal card. More senior military enlisted may or may not be required to dine on base in a military dining facility. Keep your politics on the political blog pages.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364228289617</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:18:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364228897770-12</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MWR NAF (NonAppropriated Funds) golf courses are 100% paid for by the Civilian or Military people that use them, NOT the tax payer. At least when you go on a political rant get your facts right, but please do it on the political blogs not here.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364228897770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 12:28:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364230996827-13</Id><Topic><Title>charge for meals in the military! How about that Mr. Boehner?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225916675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>take a hike rejsuda and take your demands with you, and obviously YOU never served. else you would not lie about enlisted having to pay for a meal. I never saw that, and never even heard of a "meal card", jees, you simply show up at the mess hall and eat.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364230996827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364231310509-14</Id><Title>Al Gore Cancels Another AGW Rally Due to Snow</Title><Msg>What a big, fat dummy!!!</Msg><Username>nofatchixplease</Username><Timestamp>1364231310509</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364232359204-15</Id><Topic><Title>Thinking that Ken Griffin sold his stake.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1363984336143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I forgot time does move slower for you Elvis. Kenny Boy loves money above all else, even Milkshakes.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364232359204</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:25:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364232807755-16</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>5. Military golf. Of course, generals and admirals aren’t the only ones who get to enjoy some of perks of being in the U.S. armed forces. Although lower-ranking service members don’t get private jets and personal chefs, U.S. taxpayers still spend billions of dollars a year to pay for luxuries that are out of reach for the ordinary American. The Pentagon, for example, runs a staggering 234 golf courses around the world, at a cost that is undisclosed. According to one retired lieutenant colonel in the Air Force, who also just happens to be the senior writer at Travel Golf, the very best military golf course in the U.S. is the Air Force Academy’s Eisenhower Blue Course in Colorado Springs, Colo. He writes, “This stunning 7,000-plus yard layout shares the same foothills terrain as does the legendary Broadmoor,...” (The Department of Defense did come under fire a number of decades ago when it was discovered that the toilet seats at this course cost $400 a pop.)And the number of golf courses is often undercounted, with controversial courses in Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, and Mosul, Iraq, often left off the lists, which makes assessing the total costs difficult.Yet some courses rack up staggering expenses as they become far more than mere stretches of grass. “The U.S. Army paid $71,614 [in 2004] to the Arizona Golf Resort — located in sunny Riyadh, Saudi Arabia,… The resort actually boasts an entire entertainment complex, complete with a water-slide-enhanced megapool, gym, bowling alley, horse stables, roller hockey rink, arcade, amphitheater, restaurant, and even a cappuccino bar — not to mention the golf course and a driving range.”DoD’s Sungnam golf course in the Republic ofKorea, meanwhile, is reportedly valued at $26 million.For non-golfers, the military also maintains a ski lodge and resort in the Bavarian Alps which opened in 2004 and cost $80 million " from "7 absurd ways the military wastes taxpayer dollars "</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364232807755</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364233707111-17</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are 100% full of shizer, mr, resjuda, you are a total phony. the fact is MOST money for the army MWR fund is APPROPRIATED tax dollars (60% for 2009) and don't miss my post below for other details of military golf at the tax payers expense (and skiing too)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364233707111</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364234044869-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Republican Party’s Ratings Now Stand at a 20-Year Low</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364185258330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:20:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leave off "foknews" and just be what you are, a JUNKIE! IDIOT - you got it backwards - Republican Party gaining!!! OBIMBO at an ALL time low and losing popularity in his OWN party. (lost 10 points in the latest poll) Besides him blowing our tax payer money left and right, he must have instructed Biden to do the same - over 1 MILLION on his last 2-day trip! Take off your liberal, rose colored glasses and see the REAL WORLD!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364234044869</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:54:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364234169117-19</Id><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Msg>2. The generals’ flotillas. Former Defense Secretary Robert Gates appointed Arnold Punaro, a retired major general in the Marines, to head an independent review of the Pentagon’s budget. Here’s the caution he came up with: “We don’t want the Department of Defense to become a benefits agency that occasionally kills a terrorist.” So, just how good are these benefits? For the top brass, not bad at all. According to a Washington Post investigation, each top commander has his own C-40 jet, complete with beds on board. Many have chefs who deserve their own four-star restaurants. The generals’ personal staff include drivers, security guards, secretaries and people to shine their shoes and iron their uniforms. When traveling, they can be accompanied by police motorcades that stretch for blocks. When entertaining, string quartets are available at a snap of the fingers. A New York Times analysis showed that simply the staff provided to top generals and admirals can top $1 million — per general. That’s not even including their own salaries — which are relatively modest due to congressional legislation — and the free housing, which has been described as “palatial.” On Capitol Hill, these cadres of assistants are called the generals’ “flotillas.” In Petraeus’ case, he didn’t want to give up the perks of being a four-star general in the Army, even after he left the armed forces to be director of the CIA. He apparently trained his assistants to pass him water bottles at timed intervals on his now-infamous 6-minute mile runs. He also liked “fresh, sliced pineapple” before going to bed. 7 absurd ways the military wastes taxpayer dollars If you thought the Petraeus scandal was embarrassing, wait 'til you hear how much is spent on military golf courses</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364235466763-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Republican Party’s Ratings Now Stand at a 20-Year Low</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364185258330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:20:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How do you see the real world from the back of your cave ??? Please show us the gains in public opinion of the GOP.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1364235466763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:17:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364236495697-21</Id><Topic><Title>The Republican Party’s Ratings Now Stand at a 20-Year Low</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364185258330</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 00:20:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>...........#$%$........if you would come out from the "the back of your cave" - could read or follow the news on TV, I wouldn't have to EXPLAIN it to you!!! You are another Obimpolisi, as clueless as she pretended she know basketball! OBOMBORAMA is CRASHING!!! From Obimbocare to Gun control with "little Joe"!!! Have a nice liberal day and make sure you pay your taxes, so Obimbo can blow them! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364236495697</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364237387294-22</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Commuter planes are welfare for the rich? Tower workers are rich? Plane pilots are rich? Criminals were released, and some were already re-captured for violations. Others are still looking for trouble. 15 out of 19 9/11 hijackers where from Egypt. Dear Egyptians, please be good to us! Here is the money!!!!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364237387294</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 14:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364241378407-23</Id><Topic><Title>charge for meals in the military! How about that Mr. Boehner?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225916675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>@luckeyskywaltzer, You're right ,after retiring after 22 years of Senior Enlisted military service, I probably have no idea what I'm talking about, yep I probably have no idea what the requirements of eating in a chow hall are. You on the other hand are a DOD military budget expert (see all your other posts for proof of your own brilliance), yep, as an ObamaZombie you have all the facts figures, and data you need.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364241378407</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:56:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364241471153-24</Id><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Msg>What do they have in common? Start with a "C" - NO - they are both BROKE (KAPUTT, PLEITE, NO MAS Dineros) Isn't that Obimpolisi country, together with the liberal Bi!@#$ of Feinstein, Baxter and the "Freedom Fighter for fruit flies" Brown??? Good luck going down the drain - maybe a big earthquake can save the state from a burden to the US Treasury??? ROWDY (Bidder - move out of that misery/state!)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364243220339-25</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pacifican you are such a liar! and big fat liar.... as a matter of fact nearly ALL the 911 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364243220339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:27:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364243421770-26</Id><Title>charge military personnel for meals, that will save billions</Title><Msg>and its only fair, just before the "all volunteer" military and e-1 started at about $500 a month (today's dollars), now they start at about $1500 a month.... so charge them for meals! I'm sure this will help keep taxes on the billionaires low! we all have to do our bit for the deficit!</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364243421770</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364243476131-27</Id><Topic><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, come see what the Democrat and Liberal Welfare and Entitlement Plantation can do for your state. Yes sir..., faster than you can say "Free College for illegal's or A Pay Raise for Government Union members" California can raise your taxes..., yes your State too can enjoy just like California, the highest Taxes in the Nation. That's right there not a Tax the Democrats won't pass, a fee they won't level, or a entitlement program they won't fund! While the upper middleclass flee to lower tax States, or business's close their doors California will find a way to increase taxes. Air ain't free ya know!</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364243476131</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364243597351-28</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why hasn't mr Boehner told the generals that the USA is 'broke' and we can't afford their personal chefs? a million bucks a year for each of the 1000 generals and admirals just for "staff"..., "each top commander has his own C-40 jet, complete with beds on board. Many have chefs who deserve their own four-star restaurants. The generals’ personal staff include drivers, security guards, secretaries and people to shine their shoes and iron their uniforms. When traveling, they can be accompanied by police motorcades that stretch for blocks. When entertaining, string quartets are available at a snap of the fingers"</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364243597351</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:33:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364243985272-29</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you think the DOD budgets1 trillion dollars for General staff goodies and perks.....? Hahahaha, (gasp) Hahahaha... (and LOL).... You hang on to that thought, it'll be a great sound bite for crazy Uncle Biden in 2016.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364243985272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:39:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364244079272-30</Id><Title>the pentagon runs 234 golf courses around the world. so mr Boehner, didn't you say the US is "broke"?</Title><Msg>"For non-golfers, the military also maintains a ski lodge and resort in the Bavarian Alps, which opened in 2004 and cost $80 million" we should sell that to help with the deficit.... we can also sell this; DoD’s Sungnam golf course in the Republic of Korea, meanwhile, is reportedly valued at $26 million." in fact, why not sell ALL the military golf courses? We are broke, you know.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244079272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364244270159-31</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep each general or admiral is entitled to a "staff" and according to A New York Times analysis that showed the staff provided to top generals and admirals can top $1 million — per general. That’s not even including their own salaries —</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244270159</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:44:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364244538146-32</Id><Topic><Title>the pentagon runs 234 golf courses around the world. so mr Boehner, didn't you say the US is "broke"?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244079272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All resorts, R&amp;R facilities and golf courses are 100% paid for by the Civilian or Military user fees from NAF.., NOT the tax payer. There is NO TAX MONEY involved, thats why it's called NAF (Non Appropriated Funds). If you are going to go on a anti-military political rant get your facts right, really... dude, stay away from the little green men that are feeding you bad data.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364244538146</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:48:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364244707848-33</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>silly, silly person, you were wrong that enlisted personnel pay for their meals, you said they do, but YOU LIE, they do not!... you were wrong that tax dollars do not pay for military golf courses, they do ...... and you are wrong about the cost of "staff" for the generals.. the NY times puts it at a million a year each for each of the near 1000 generals and admirals... and geez how many Fricken generals and admirals do we need, and you tell me the cost of the generals chef, driver, guards, c-140 on call, secretaries, motorcades and even the string quartets the can get at the snap of a finger... and that million a year does not include their salary, but it does include the guy who brought Petraeus his pineapple slices each night before bed.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244707848</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364244958900-34</Id><Topic><Title>the pentagon runs 234 golf courses around the world. so mr Boehner, didn't you say the US is "broke"?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244079272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no you are wrong and you are a simpleton... as I showed you before. for instance the army MWR fund is MOSTLY APPROPRIATED tax dollars (60% for 2009) and numbskull, just because they try and operate and maintain a golf course with user fees DOES NOT MEAN THEY SUCCEED, NOR does it mean that the golf course was not built and bought with tax dollars in the first place, you fricken moron..</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244958900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:55:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364245479651-35</Id><Title>Congressional Ethics Probe Adds to Michele Bachmann’s Political Woes</Title><Msg>by John Avlon Mar 25, 2013 11:45 AM EDT Add the Office of Congressional Ethics to the long list of probes and lawsuits that may be the only enduring legacy of Bachmann’s presidential face-plant. John Avlon exclusively reports. The Hindenburg. The Titanic. Michele Bachmann. Eighteen months ago, the Minnesota House member was considered an unlikely but undeniable Republican rising star, winning the Iowa straw poll that unofficially begins the primary season. Today, she is embroiled in a litany of legal proceedings related to her rolling disaster of a presidential campaign—including a Office of Congressional Ethics investigation into campaign improprieties that has not previously been reported. The Daily Beast has learned that federal investigators are now interviewing former Bachmann campaign staffers nationwide about alleged intentional campaign-finance violations. The investigators are working on behalf of the Office of Congressional Ethics, which probes reported improprieties by House members and their staffs and then can refer cases to the House Ethics Committee. “I have been interviewed by investigators,” says Peter Waldron, a former Bachmann staffer who’s embroiled in his own fight with his former boss, involving his allegations of pay-to-play politics and improper payments by the campaign—making him one of several members of Bachmann’s inner circle who’ve fallen out with the woman they once hoped would become commander in chief. While he was careful to avoid specifics in regard to the investigating body, Waldron said that “investigators came interviewed me and are interviewing other staff members across the country.”.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364245479651</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364245718643-36</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ok Moonbeam, google "Separate Rations" . generally single, junior enlisted military living on an installation military with a mess (chow) hall DO NOT get paid "Separate Rations of $352.27 a month", those living off the installation do. Therefore, (simple logic here) the military enlisted staff do not get the same amount of "Rations at $352.27" . If they do not have a chow (mess) card, which you DON'T if you draw separate rations pay, you have to pay out of pocket to eat at the mess hall.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364245718643</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:08:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364245743675-37</Id><Title>GOP Voter ID push found racist</Title><Msg>Voter ID laws posed big hurdle for minority youth in 2012 elections, study confirms Source: Washington University in St.Louis News At polling places across America in November 2012, Latinos and African Americans under age 30 were disproportionately asked for identification, even in states that do not have voter ID laws, according to a post-election analysis by researchers at Washington University in St. Louis and the University of Chicago. “Our study shows that voter ID laws have disproportionately severe consequences for youth of color,” says co-author Jon C. Rogowski, PhD, assistant professor of political science in Arts &amp; Sciences at Washington University. “Whether the biases are conscious or unconscious, the result of these laws is that people of color are effectively being disenfranchised. Our nation has an obligation to ensure that everyone has equal access to the voting booth.”</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364245743675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:09:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364246402441-38</Id><Topic><Title>there are nearly 1,000 generals &amp; admirals and each gets about a million a year for chefs,drivers, guards, string quartets and other "staff"</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364234169117</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 13:56:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>oh brother, as I suggested to help with the deficit, all military personnel can PAY for their meals, no matter if they live on or off base.... get it ? THEY pay and NO separate rations....jeez..... PAY for the meals, you know we ALL have to make sacrifices to help with the deficit and to keep taxes on the billionaires from going up.. AND gis would still be getting a better deal even if they paid for meals than it was before the "all volunteer" military when the E-1 started a $500 a month (todays money)....plus meals........... now the E-1 starts at $1500 a month plus meals........ so, since Mr Boenhner points out that we are broke, perhaps personnel should pay for their own meals.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364246402441</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:20:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364246614190-39</Id><Topic><Title>the pentagon runs 234 golf courses around the world. so mr Boehner, didn't you say the US is "broke"?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244079272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the military has two golf courses on Guam....jeez........ "the Pentagon lists the navy's Admiral Nimitz Golf Course in Barrigada, Guam, in its inventory of overseas courses, it seems to have skipped Andersen Air Force Base's eighteen-hole Palm Tree Golf Course, also on the island. And you'd think the Pentagon would be proud of the USAF's island links; after all, it was the runner-up, in 2002, for the title of "Guam's Most Beautiful Golf Course." Whatever the true number of the military's courses, at least some of them are distinctly sprucing up their grounds. Take the Eaglewood Golf Courses at Langley Air Force Base in Virginia. In 2004, the Pentagon paid out more than $352,000 to George Golf Design to refurbish its two courses (known as "the Raptor" and "the Eagle"). George Golf Design considerately worked on the courses one at a time, so that local duffers would not be left linkless. This was of critical importance since if both courses were out of commission, Virginia would have been left with only nine military golf facilities (navy, five; army,three; Marine Corps, one) with a total of fourteen courses. "</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364246614190</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:23:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364246748182-40</Id><Topic><Title>"we are Broke" Boehner sends the Blue Angels to the hanger</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364221833609</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 10:30:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because their operating expenses are paid by user fees (IF that is true), they're still worth millions and millions, and if sold, could help the deficit. Go, luckyskywaltzer! Show (again) the hypocracy of the GOP.</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1364246748182</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364246928309-41</Id><Topic><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cypress is a tree, Cyprus is a country. How can a tree be bankrupt?</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1364246928309</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:28:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364247596006-42</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Cyprus Economics</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363877044235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:44:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First dis-arm the public, then STEAL all their hard earned money!!! Genius!! Only 'Gerbil Stuffers' could come up with a 'Fair' Saul Alinsky plan like that!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364247596006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:39:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364247724759-43</Id><Topic><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They're bucking for a bailout from uncle bambam. Cali knows there's no hole too deep that it can't be filled wif confiscated taxpayer coin.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364247724759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:42:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364248210251-44</Id><Topic><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>California is more concerned about Transgender 'Gerbil Stuffers' getting access to the girl's locker room so some psychotic freak 40 year old Man in a dress can pull his junk out in front of a 6 year old girl. No wonder that 'F'd up State is bankrupt!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364248210251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 17:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364251940640-45</Id><Topic><Title>charge for meals in the military! How about that Mr. Boehner?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364225916675</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 11:38:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As resjuda stated, what has this to do with ETFC? if you think $1500/month is a lot these days, may be you should volunteer as an enlisted man. To get a real feel for the life, I suggest a combat arms specialty. Not sure why you've got a d_ck up your as- over $18,000 per year pay (E1) where you are either on call 24x7 or work 10+ hours per day (barracks life). $1500/30 is $50 per day (minus taxes (fed/state/local), minus insurance, and so on). What happened? Did you get your Big Chcken Dinner and can't deal with life as a loser? Yeah you get three squares in the chow hall (weekends was brunch and dinner only - even if you were standing watch) but most of us used to eat a fourth meal (out of pocket) cause you get a workout (wanted or not) almost every day. I suggest you educate yourself (math-wise and world-wise) before you spout off.</Msg><Username>long_view_2000</Username><Timestamp>1364251940640</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 18:52:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364252408121-46</Id><Topic><Title>California and Cypress!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364241471153</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 15:57:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen FUp , the island is named after the tree! Is all you can do is grammar and spelling checks? Better check your bank account - IDIOT! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364252408121</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:00:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364255412405-47</Id><Topic><Title>the pentagon runs 234 golf courses around the world. so mr Boehner, didn't you say the US is "broke"?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364244079272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 16:41:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I schooled you on military Seperate Rations and how WRONG you were there Bunky, Should I school you on MRW and NAF funding of Military Recreation facilities and demonstrate your idiocy on how that funding works too? I mean if you're that Anti-Military just say so and be done with it, you have the right to open your mouth and prove your intelligence. After all it's one of the rights the military protect for you. as it stands now, you are making a rather large fool of yourself spounting leftest propaganda. NAF funding shows up in Military budgeting because it is money controlled by the Military, but it is generated by sales and usage fees on military bases, NOT the TAX PAYER.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1364255412405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-25 19:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message></Date>