<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373256567372-1</Id><Topic><Title>Independence Day. The Big Question.</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372909709065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBL choose all Saudi's for this mission in hopes of provoking precisely the idiotic reaction you had, and to get us to throw away our close relationship with the KIngdom and its allies. You'd have played directly into Al Queda's strategic plan, just like the moron you constantly demonstrate yourself to be.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373256567372</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 00:09:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373278726369-2</Id><Title>Reports From the Front Lines of Gun-Free Chicago</Title><Msg>This year’s Independence Day celebration, for many Chicagoans a four-day respite in the land of the free, was for others an ordeal in a killing field. Violence tore through parts of the city from Wednesday night to Sunday night, with 38 separate shooting incidents. Ten men were killed and 55 other people, including two young boys, were wounded. As of June 9, the rest of the People's Paradise of Illinois has de-facto concealed carry, no permit required. The governor is in violation of a federal court order. Sheriffs and state attorneys say they will not enforce a law that was declared unconstitutional.</Msg><Username>homie_dont_join_nra</Username><Timestamp>1373278726369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:18:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373293267430-3</Id><Title>$13.30 ohhhh shorty...how I pity you</Title><Msg>dabear jumps on top of the moon</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373293267430</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:21:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373294289689-4</Id><Topic><Title>$13.30 ohhhh shorty...how I pity you</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373293267430</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:21:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>shhhhhh - shorty is trying to figure a way out. he is just now figuring out that LLF is no longer helping to push it lower.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373294289689</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373295241000-5</Id><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Msg>How Republicans Quietly Mandate Transvaginal Probes When They Think No One’s Paying Attention By Tara Culp-Ressler on Feb 7, 2013 at 1:50 pm Example of a transvaginal ultrasound procedure During the height of last year’s outcry over the GOP’s “War on Women,” transvaginal probes became one of the most recognizable symbols of the Republican Party’s overreaching anti-abortion policies. Particularly when Virginia pushed forward with a controversial measure to require all women seeking abortions to undergo a transvaginal ultrasound, women’s health advocates decried the practice as “state-sponsored rape.” Virginia legislators ultimately changed the language of their ultrasound bill to remove the mention of transvaginal probes. But stringent abortion restrictions don’t necessarily need specific “transvaginal” language to force women to undergo invasive, unnecessary medical procedures against their will. These are just a few examples of carefully-worded abortion bills that would ultimately require transvaginal probes — even though it’s not explicitly stated in the legislation:</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373295314138-6</Id><Topic><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>– MICHIGAN: Talking Points Memo first reported that Michigan’s proposed ultrasound bill, HB-4187, is a bit more nefarious than it appears to be on the surface. The legislation doesn’t mention trasvaginal probes, but it does stipulate that the mandatory ultrasounds need to use the most modern equipment available, and provide “the most visibly clear image of the gross anatomical development of the fetus and the most audible fetal heartbeat.” Donna Crane, the policy director of NARAL Pro-Choice America, explained that language will require doctors to use transvaginal probes — which provide clearer images than the non-invasive ultrasound procedure. – KENTUCKY: Women seeking abortions in Kentucky already have to undergo a state-mandated waiting period and a mandatory counseling session intended to talk them out of their decision. But SB-5, which just cleared a Senate committee on Thursday, would also require women to have an ultrasound before terminating a pregnancy. During Thursday’s committee hearing, state Sen. Paul Hornback (R) admitted something that the proponents of similar ultrasound bills in other states haven’t been as forthright about: the legislation would also require a transvaginal ultrasound for early pregnancies, since abdominal ultrasounds don’t work well before 12 weeks of pregnancy. Because the vast majority of abortions are performed during the first trimester, the vast majority of women will be subjected to a transvaginal probe.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295314138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373296233236-7</Id><Title>LLF invading your wallet</Title><Msg>he ruins longs and shorts alike</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373296233236</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373296410122-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Even though ultrasounds are not considered medically necessary procedures for first-trimester abortions, 12 states currently require women to undergo one anyway. And according to NARAL Pro-Choice America, 13 new forced ultrasound bills have been introduced in 8 states since the beginning of 2013, a number the group says is all too common for the beginning of a new legislative session. Donna Crane, NARAL’s policy director, explained to ThinkProgress that Republicans are playing “games of hide and seek” with this type of legislation. But the issue of invasive probes — as well as the fundamental issue at stake, the fact that women are forced to have an unwanted, unnecessary medical procedure simply because a legislator decided they should — has never gone away. “These bills are horrific, but they’re commonplace,” Crane said. “All they’re doing is changing the language. Virginia made a PR error in actually using a searchable word, ‘transvaginal,’ and they’re not likely to do that again. But the bills are still as severe as they ever were.”</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373296410122</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373297394127-9</Id><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Msg>A Joint Statement by Episcopal, Lutheran, Presbyterian, Roman Catholic and United Methodist Leaders As you did it to one of the least of these who are members of my family, you did it to me. Matthew 25:4 We speak as bishops and Christian leaders in North Carolina about the moral issues highlighted by the Moral Monday events. Our call to speak grows out of these words that we prayed together at our meeting on June 6: “May we be a more vivid symbol of unity to all the faithful. May the witness of our lives proclaim the Kingdom of God.” As you may know, people have been gathering on Monday evenings to offer vigilant witness on moral issues being considered by our elected state officials. We share their concern for many of the issues they are bringing forth. The Rev. Dr. Rodney Sadler of Union Seminary (Charlotte) recently summarized the effect of pending and enacted legislation especially on the poor, the aging and children. "As you read this letter, the North Carolina General Assembly is passing bills that will remove 500,000 people from the Medicaid roles leaving them without health insurance; that will remove 170,000 people from unemployment when unemployment rates remain at historically high levels; that threaten to replace the graduated state income tax with a consumption tax that will adversely impact the poorest North Carolinians who will face increased prices on basic goods; that will force college students to return to their often distant homes to vote or cost their parents their $2,500 dependency deduction…. These and many other bills will adversely impact those who can least afford it and therefore demand a fervent response from people of faith! "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373297512039-10</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Our concern about the legislative actions cited by Rev. Dr. Sadler is not an act of political partisanship. Rather it is a matter of faith with respect to our understanding of the biblical teachings and imperatives to protect the poor, respect the stranger, care for widows and children and love our neighbors (Isaiah 10:1-2, Hebrews 13:2, James 1:27, Matthew 22:39, Galatians 5:14). We recognize and respect other Christian brothers and sisters who may seek to apply these biblical teachings in different ways and through different means. We speak and act in love and through our understanding that our first citizenship is in the Kingdom of God, and we do so always as faithful citizens of the democratic process. We urge all Christians to witness to their faith in seeking justice and mercy for all. The Right Reverend Michael Bruce Curry, Bishop, Episcopal Diocese of North Carolina The Reverend Dr. Leonard Bolick, Bishop, Synod of North Carolina, Evangelical Lutheran Church in America The Reverend Ted Churn, Executive Presbyter, Presbytery of New Hope, Presbyterian Church (USA) The Most Reverend Michael F. Burbidge, Bishop, Catholic Diocese of Raleigh Bishop Hope Morgan Ward, North Carolina Conference, United Methodist Church Bishop Larry Goodpastor, Western North Carolina Conference, United Methodist Church The Right Reverend Alfred “Chip” Marble, Assisting Bishop, Episcopal Diocese of North Carolina The Reverend Anne Hodges-Copple, Bishop Suffragan-elect, Episcopal Diocese of North Carolina The Right Reverend Porter Taylor, Bishop, Episcopal Diocese of Western North Carolina</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297512039</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373298131598-11</Id><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Msg>and shorty is finding it hard to exit</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373298131598</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373299298827-12</Id><Title>Oh Lord Jesus It's A Fire</Title><Msg>shorty stuck inside. Ain't nobody got time for that.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373299298827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:01:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373301939877-13</Id><Title>dalordie cares</Title><Msg>* Loans below 10 Billion * Real estate up * Reserves are plentiful...too plentiful * Kenny out of ETFC * Long term interest rates soon to rise * Buyout still on the table...only a matter of time dalorie cares for you shorty...you have been warned. The train is leaving the station!</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373301939877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373302653982-14</Id><Title>Another deal on Jan '15 $10's</Title><Msg>Someone selling 20 @ 4.35, since the bid is close to that right now its probably a retail investor taking profits. Though I gotta admit above 4 bucks cheap is relative . . . but then I only watch the $10 2015's as those are the only contracts I have.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373302653982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373303580946-15</Id><Title>Talk to Me</Title><Msg>about etfc. why don't you politicians find another irrelevant place to chat</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1373303580946</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:13:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373305118184-16</Id><Topic><Title>Another deal on Jan '15 $10's</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373302653982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude 14 holds and only 1 buy rating? When do we hear more from the street?</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1373305118184</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:38:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373305358879-17</Id><Title>$13.40</Title><Msg>All aboard!</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373305358879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 13:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373308238468-18</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The problem with the bible is that there is a tidbit there for everyone. GOP can easily find something that "justifies" their greed , selfishness and utter lack of compassion.</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1373308238468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:30:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373308560964-19</Id><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Msg>and shorty screams</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373308560964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373309072498-20</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Translation : Wahhh Wahhhh We're not getting our free stuff! I remember the days when churches dispensed charity instead of begging for government handouts.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373309072498</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:44:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373309235101-21</Id><Topic><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The American Congress of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG), a national group of women’s health experts, has come out against the harsh abortion restrictions that Texas lawmakers are attempting to force through a second special session. In a new statement, the coalition of OB-GYNs warns that the Texas bills are “over-reaching” and “set a dangerous precedent” for medical care. “The Texas bills set a dangerous precedent of a legislature telling doctors how to practice medicine and how to care for individual patients,” the group’s Executive Vice President, Dr. Hal C. Lawrence III, said in the statement. “ACOG opposes legislative interference, and strongly believes that decisions about medical care must be based on scientific evidence and made by licensed medical professionals, not the state or federal government.” Senate Bill 1 and House Bill 2 — formerly known as SB 5 during Texas’ last special session — would criminalize abortions after 20 weeks of pregnancy and shut down the vast majority of the women’s health clinics in Texas. The proposed measures threaten to restrict access to all types of reproductive care, since many women currently receive contraceptive services and cancer screenings at the clinics that will be forced to close their doors.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373309235101</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:47:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373309289732-22</Id><Topic><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373295241000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 10:54:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ACOG’s Texas District Chair, Dr. Lisa M. Hollier, called the abortion-related proposals “a compilation of over-reaching measures” intended to police the circumstances under which women can receive reproductive care. “The bills are not based on sound science, despite our efforts to provide the legislature with the best available medical knowledge,” Hollier pointed out, warning that SB 1 and HB 2 will ultimately “erode women’s health.” This isn’t the first time the nonpartisan OB-GYN group has taken a stand against restrictive abortion laws. Last month, ACOG issued a formal statement in opposition to the mounting pile of state-level restrictions that get in between a woman and her doctor, slamming anti-abortion laws for “imposing a political agenda on medical practice.” OB-GYNs have also repeatedly reiterated their support for expanding access to emergency contraception, and expressed bewilderment that providing young women with their full range of contraceptive options has become so politically contentious. Texas voters agree with the ACOG’s assessment about the proposed legislation. A recent poll found the 80 percent of Texans want their lawmakers to stop focusing on abortion restrictions in their special sessions. After successfully staging a “people’s filibuster” to help block the abortion restrictions last week, over 5,000 activists flooded the state capitol again on Monday to continue opposing the bills.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373309289732</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 14:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373310597385-23</Id><Title>GOP invading your uterus</Title><Msg>and shorty can't get out</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373310597385</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:09:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373311078244-24</Id><Topic><Title>Oh Lord Jesus It's A Fire</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373299298827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:01:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ place to hedge or I'd think of buying some short term PUTs. Never like it when it hits a resistance point in between two strikes.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373311078244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312053656-25</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The bible is just like Las Vegas !</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373312053656</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:34:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312148678-26</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I remember the days when churches dispensed charity instead of begging for government handouts." Now they hold Bingo tournaments and hide the profits.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373312148678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312239839-27</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If I recall Jesus ask for people to help the least unfortunate among us, he didn't reach in to their pockets to accomplish it. Many churches depend on the steady flow of collections from people on assistance to keep them going. Have to take them with a grain of salt for they have their own agenda. Welfare and all its subsidiaries have hurt more folks that it ever helped by entrapping them in a cycle of dependence...today you have more people on food assistance then in the work force, case in point.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373312239839</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373312653378-28</Id><Topic><Title>Independence Day. The Big Question.</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1372909709065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 23:48:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**and 5000 troops sent to the wrong country** And in your ultimate wisdom what country would you have punished for the 9-11 attacks. Some dopes on this thread actually think Saudi Arabia. I don't believe the master mind of 9-11 was hold up there and protected by the Taliban. If you recall Billy Clinton didn't send cruise missiles in to Saudi Arabia to destroy milk factories.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373312653378</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:44:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313417071-29</Id><Topic><Title>Religious leaders scold the GOP</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373297394127</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 11:29:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If I recall Jesus ask for people to help the least unfortunate among us" You embarrass the meaning of education once again. The "least unfortunate" would mean the most wealthy. Your opinion means nothing if it comes from ignorance. ( however, your party has always been supporting the "least unfortunate" )</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373313417071</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 15:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373313860483-30</Id><Topic><Title>Another deal on Jan '15 $10's</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373302653982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earnings in a week. That's when we hear more. Frankly I'm rather surprised its gone up this fast in this short a time.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373313860483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314723841-31</Id><Topic><Title>Another deal on Jan '15 $10's</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373302653982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The decision becomes do we hold the stock into earnings considering the run up?</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1373314723841</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373314756778-32</Id><Topic><Title>Another deal on Jan '15 $10's</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373302653982</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 12:57:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm happy with the 150 Jan'15 $5 calls that I picked up about a month and a half ago. The time premium was much much smaller than the $10s.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1373314756778</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 16:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324614837-33</Id><Topic><Title>Spank her for Jesus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372647412722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is there a same sex version?</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1373324614837</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373324636390-34</Id><Topic><Title>Spank her for Jesus</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1372647412722</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-30 22:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just checking, mind you.</Msg><Username>muchomacho42</Username><Timestamp>1373324636390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373325224646-35</Id><Title>Does This Stock Pay A Dividend?</Title><Msg>my broker says only invest in dividend paying stocks. serious answers only please.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373325224646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373325982782-36</Id><Topic><Title>Does This Stock Pay A Dividend?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373325224646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only to the investors that post pictures as they are leaving investor conventions in Vegas!....</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373325982782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373331250347-37</Id><Title>ETard, $1.34, big whoop</Title><Msg>Those of us who know this stock, that's the reality. Still a penny stock.</Msg><Username>thirboa</Username><Timestamp>1373331250347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373335746406-38</Id><Topic><Title>ETard, $1.34, big whoop</Title><Username>thirboa</Username><Timestamp>1373331250347</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yea its bad but at least not in pinks or bk. it has been doing better though.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1373335746406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 22:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>