<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-24"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364100894182-1</Id><Title>ALERT! Breaking News from da Bear ...learn more...</Title><Msg>Da Bear just learned that Kenny Boy is exitiing stage right for selfish reasons, he wants more money. He agreed to depart da BOD so that E-Tub could be sold off. E-Tub will soon be sold. AMTD will enter da first bid, BUT, Chucky may bid now that Kenny's gonners. I hear that they-and they know who they are-will offer up $15/share in stock. Da onlyest details to be worked out is how much Da E-Tub BTO's get when they get kicked out. E-Tub said bye byes to da poison pill last year. C Yaz - Da Bear Cares [CGDGE] ( Hey Pilgrims, Yinz don't have to believe this, BUT, if it realy does happen, please don't turn me into to da SEC, just consider it a lucky guess, okay? Oh, BTW, I'm buying 5,000 shares Monday. My current position is ZERO. )</Msg><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1364100894182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:54:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364134390844-2</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT! Breaking News from da Bear ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1364100894182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bear is long...wow...never thought I would see those words</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1364134390844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 10:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364138751127-3</Id><Topic><Title>ALERT! Breaking News from da Bear ...learn more...</Title><Username>legofthebear</Username><Timestamp>1364100894182</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 00:54:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long, or does he want us to buy why he sells short? Why would Kenny sell at $11, if he just allowed the BOD to sell at $15? He may not agree but would still make a lot more money. It does not seem logical.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1364138751127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 11:25:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364157206219-4</Id><Topic><Title>Feds Spend $2.7M to Study Drunk Lesbians</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363811176110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidder is bitter because a drunk Lez came onto him. She was confused by his man boobs.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1364157206219</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 16:33:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364172754769-5</Id><Topic><Title>Thinking that Ken Griffin sold his stake.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1363984336143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I firmly believe that Griffin ET stock has already been sold in big blocks. I do think when the next good news comes out on ET, the stock will go to 12.50 or 13.00 per share.</Msg><Username>jimdeuces</Username><Timestamp>1364172754769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 20:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364174519345-6</Id><Title>DeMarquise Elkins: not an NRA member</Title><Msg>Where was Joltin Joe Biden and his shotgun?</Msg><Username>homie_dont_join_nra</Username><Timestamp>1364174519345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 21:21:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364183840695-7</Id><Title>Minimum Wage Earners Would Need To Work Over 100 Hours A Week To Pay The Rent.</Title><Msg>By Matt Murray | March 24, 2013 Lately between the state and national battles on raising the minimum wage, people everywhere are talking about the potential impacts of the change. The people on the right, want you to believe that raising the minimum wage will cost jobs. This is completely untrue. In fact according to a recent study done by the Center for Economic and Policy Research they found that “The weight of that evidence points to little or no employment response to modest increases in the minimum wage.” This does not mean that a few smaller companies would not have to make some staffing adjustments if the wage was increased. The truth is that most of these companies are already paying employees above minimum wage. In fact over 66% of minimum wage earners work for major corporations (I.E Wal-Mart and McDonalds) not small businesses.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364183840695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-24 23:57:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>