<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364018099180-1</Id><Topic><Title>Thinking that Ken Griffin sold his stake.....</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1363984336143</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-22 16:32:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The general market appears to go higher. AMTD and SCHW have no sign to go down. Relatively, ETFC could not go down much. Looking at the chart, there is a real chance it will break up towards $13.5. The $12 is a hurdle that could be overcome soon. Regarding Citadel's dump, this time he killed 150 contracts of my $12 calls for March, which I paid $5 and $8 cents, respectively. At the last surge, I was thinking whether I should sell at 3 cents, when bid 3 and ask 5 cents. I should have shorted 12,000 shares of ETFC at that time. This time I reloaded the $12 calls for April, July, and won't be fooled again.</Msg><Username>etfc2013</Username><Timestamp>1364018099180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 01:54:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364033748399-2</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbo Cyprus Economics</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363877044235</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 10:44:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geeh 'Gerbil Stuffing' Penquins can run our Economy better than that Stupid, 'Saul Alinsky' Dumbo!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364033748399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 06:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364047498857-3</Id><Title>sequester to trim some welfare for the rich</Title><Msg>FAA To Close 149 Air Traffic Towers Because Of Budget Cuts Under orders to trim hundreds of millions of dollars from its budget, the Federal Aviation Administration on Friday released a final list of 149 air traffic control towers that it will close at small airports around the country starting early next month. (could this be as painful to the civil aviation crowd as when some of the the well heeled lost their maids and dressage horse care takers due to crack downs on illegal immigrants?)</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364047498857</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 10:04:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364048067152-4</Id><Title>W's war economics: Go shopping, go to disney world, here is some cash, now shoo &amp; don't ask any questions</Title><Msg>(by 2008 some of the bill came due though and W was now saying "Unless money is loosened up the sucker could go down") How the US public was defrauded by the hidden cost of the Iraq war George Bush sold the war as quick and cheap; it was long and costly. Even now, the US is paying billions to private contractors When the US invaded Iraq in March 2003, the Bush administration estimated that it would cost $50-60bn to overthrow Saddam Hussein and establish a functioning government. This estimate was catastrophically wrong: the war in Iraq has cost $823.2bn between 2003 and 2011. Some estimates suggesting that it may eventually cost as much as $3.7tn when factoring in the long-term costs of caring for the wounded and the families of those killed. The most striking fact about the cost of the war in Iraq has been the extent to which it has been kept "off the books" of the government's ledgers and hidden from the American people.......The dirty little secret of the Iraq war – .....– was that the American people would only support a war to get rid of Saddam Hussein if they could be assured that they would pay almost nothing for it. The most obvious way in which the true cost of this war was kept hidden was with the use of supplemental appropriations to fund the occupation. By one estimate, 70% of the costs of wars in Iraq and Afghanistan between 2003 and 2008 were funded with supplemental or emergency appropriations approved outside the Pentagon's annual budget. These appropriations allowed the Bush administration to shield the Pentagon's budget from the cuts otherwise needed to finance the war,..With the Iraq war treated as an "off the books" expense, the Pentagon was allowed to keep spending on high-end military equipment and cutting-edge technology. In fiscal terms, it was as if the messy wars in Afghanistan and Iraq were never happening.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364048067152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 10:14:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364055157264-5</Id><Title>Daily Caller's Credibility Wanes Under Defamation Accusations</Title><Msg>"Is another conservative news site turning into a tabloid? Allegations of sexual misconduct by Senator Robert Menendez (D-N.J.) emerged in November on the Daily Caller, but a defamation scandal that surfaced this week could permanently decimate the news site’s credibility. Most politicos remember Tucker Carlson as the former co-host of CNN’s Crossfire, the now-defunct political news program once characterized as “partisan hackery” by comedian Jon Stewart. Two months after Stewart’s appearance on the show, CNN declined to renew Carlson’s contract. Following a brief stint at MSNBC, he was hired as a part-time pundit on Fox News whilst launching the Daily Caller. Wherever he travels, Carlson is a disruptive presence, openly criticizing Democrats and Republicans alike, a testament to his strong libertarian conservative bias. Even so, Carlson has long sought to remove sex scandals from the mainstream news, criticizing the coverage of David Vitter’s misconduct on his MSNBC show in 2007. This portrait did a U-turn yesterday, however, when Carlson’s site was accused of paying prostitutes to lie about sexual misconduct at the hand of Senator Menendez. As new details surface, the Daily Caller may begin to self-destruct. In the meantime, Carlson will welcome the surge of attention."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364055157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 12:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364058372398-6</Id><Topic><Title>Daily Caller's Credibility Wanes Under Defamation Accusations</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364055157264</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 12:12:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dirtbag bob is out of the senate by the end of the year. He's just lucky he don't have a couple boys named lyle and erik who think the senator deserves to be 'menendezed' `````````````````````````` Politico noted, "Melgen and his family donated nearly $1 million to Menendez's campaigns and related committees." Unmentioned was the fact that Menendez has used this money in part to spread his own influence in the Democratic caucus by donating to a number of colleagues including, among others, Kay Hagan ($10,000), Mark Begich ($10,000), Mark Pryor ($12,500), Al Franken ($10,000), Tim Johnson ($10,000), Jeanne Shaheen ($7,500) and Mary Landrieu ($5,000).</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364058372398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 13:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364063690338-7</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Healthcare is for Gerbil Stuffers</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1363873846298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-21 09:50:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Paging Dr. Feeh-Gut..we have 'Gerbil Stuffing' issue on the Pink Ward..Emergency Assistance needed now</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364063690338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 14:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364077179895-8</Id><Topic><Title>No Chemicals Used in Syria</Title><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1363805821793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 14:57:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pull that friggin' dead Gerbil out of your BUTT!! Don't be too sure about your (Butt) 'Crack' reporting! You are relying on 'Al Jazeera'?? You are the very, very definintion of a 'USEFULL IDIOT" Saul Alinsky, Hillary and Dumbo are soo proud of your incredible STUPIDITY!! News is just hitting DRUDGE right now.. Oh yeah, stay with Al GORE-zeera!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1364077179895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 18:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364089424397-9</Id><Title>GOP IN YOUR BEDROOM</Title><Msg>BOSS IN YOUR BEDROOM: Sens. Fischer (R-NE), Cruz (R-TX), Johanns (R-NE), and Enzi (R-WY) introduced an amendment to put your boss in your bedroom by allowing them to deny you birth control coverage based on their beliefs, not yours. This is just one of numerous anti-Obamacare amendments offered by Republicans. Incidentally, the law turns three tomorrow. 42 GOP senators and 2 Democrats voted for this amendment.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364089424397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 21:43:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364091143524-10</Id><Topic><Title>GOP IN YOUR BEDROOM</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1364089424397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 21:43:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read carefully. They never prohibit birf control. However they won't lose any sleep when libs forget to suit up before they take the dirt road home.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364091143524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 22:12:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364092099018-11</Id><Title>While Wingnutz Obsess over Obama's Kenyan Heritage .......</Title><Msg>The Bushes Before the Bush family was the very picture of all-American do-gooderism, they were aiding the #$%$s during World War II, according to The Guardian. George W. Bush's grandfather, Senator Prescott Bush, directed the Union Banking Corporation, whose assets were seized under the Trading with the Enemy Act in 1942. The Guardian reports that UBC represented the U.S. interests of Fritz Thyssen, a steel and coal baron who funded Adolf Hitler's campaign in the 1930s. Though Senator Bush never confessed #$%$ sympathies, the Guardian investigation appeared to prove Bush was well-aware of UBC's activities with the #$%$s.</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1364092099018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 22:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364096686589-12</Id><Topic><Title>Feds Spend $2.7M to Study Drunk Lesbians</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1363811176110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 16:26:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go ahead and pick on Jesus, I rather step on the rotten fruit of the earth</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1364096686589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-23 23:44:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>