<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362754114233-1</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>breitbart progagandists and liars.......Okeefe never appeared in an acorn office dressed in anything but business attire. The outlandish pimp costumes were staged and shown by breitbart andwas a complete lie as is much coming from fox and breibart.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362754114233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 09:48:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362754818933-2</Id><Topic><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362532227182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very nice jobs number despite all the GOP obstructionism.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362754818933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:00:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362757687079-3</Id><Title>Unemployment Hits 4 Yr Low ! Stocks hit record Highs !</Title><Msg>Obama firing on all cylinders !!!!!!!</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362757687079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362757710885-4</Id><Title>GA expedites arming the mentally "troubled"</Title><Msg>Source: Yahoo ATLANTA (AP) -- While some states push to tighten gun control laws after the Connecticut school massacre, lawmakers in gun-friendly Georgia want to ease rules preventing some mentally ill people from getting licenses to carry firearms. Legislators in Georgia's House voted 117-56 on Thursday to allow people who have voluntarily sought inpatient treatment for mental illness or substance abuse to get licenses. The same bill would force officials to check on whether applicants have received involuntary treatment in the past five years before issuing licenses. Georgia also may change its laws to allow people to carry guns in churches, bars and on college campuses, contrary to what's happening elsewhere in the United States. Judges in Georgia now have discretion over whether to grant a license to carry a weapon to anyone who has received inpatient treatment at a mental hospital or substance abuse treatment center in the last five years, whether it's voluntary or not.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757710885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362757957456-5</Id><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Msg>The Surprising Brain Differences Between Democrats and Republicans First, in the American Journal of Political Science, a team of researchers including Peter Hatemi of Penn State University and Rose McDermott of Brown University studied the relationship between our deep-seated tendencies to experience fear—tendencies that vary from person to person, partly for reasons that seem rooted in our genes—and our political beliefs. What they found is that people who have more fearful disposition also tend to be more politically conservative, and less tolerant of immigrants and people of races different from their own. As McDermott carefully emphasizes, that does not mean that every conservative has a high fear disposition. "It's not that conservative people are more fearful, it's that fearful people are more conservative," as she puts it.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362758471490-6</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's proven that conservatives have more nightmares. Fear is based on ignorance. And fear, is 90% of Hannity's show.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362758471490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 11:01:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362758717911-7</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is why there will never be another Repub President. Pubs know they have to appeal to minorities. And they hate minorities.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362758717911</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 11:05:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362767226051-8</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm afraid you libs are dooshbeags.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362767226051</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 13:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362767451221-9</Id><Title>AP: Chavez Wasted His Money on Healthcare When He Could Have Built Gigantic Skyscrapers</Title><Msg>By Jim Naureckas One of the more bizarre takes on Venezuelan President Hugo Chavez's death comes from Associated Press business reporter Pamela Sampson (3/5/13): Chavez invested Venezuela's oil wealth into social programs including state-run food markets, cash benefits for poor families, free health clinics and education programs. But those gains were meager compared with the spectacular construction projects that oil riches spurred in glittering Middle Eastern cities, including the world's tallest building in Dubai and plans for branches of the Louvre and Guggenheim museums in Abu Dhabi. That's right: Chavez squandered his nation's oil money on healthcare, education and nutrition when he could have been building the world's tallest building or his own branch of the Louvre. What kind of monster has priorities like that? In case you're curious about what kind of results this kooky agenda had, here's a chart (NACLA, 10/8/12) based on World Bank poverty stats–showing the proportion of Venezuelans living on less than $2 a day falling from 35 percent to 13 percent over three years. (For comparison purposes, there's a similar stat for Brazil, which made substantial but less dramatic progress against poverty over the same time period.) Of course, during this time, the number of Venezuelans living in the world's tallest building went from 0 percent to 0 percent, while the number of copies of the Mona Lisa remained flat, at none. So you have to say that Chavez's presidency was overall pretty disappointing–at least by AP's standards.</Msg><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362767451221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 13:30:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362769186822-10</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Vera contacted the police to report "possible human smuggling," unaware that he had been duped. Vera claims he lost his job as a result of O'Keefe's deception after the conservative's video of their encounter was posted on a Breitbart website." ACORN fired its employee for doing the right thing, notifying police about possible human smuggling? Even if ACORN made an original mistake by firing Mr Vera, it could have been corrected almost immediately by contacting police department about alleged phone call. Can you believe ACORN didn't lift a finger to correct the mistake? They didn't reward him? Didn't give him promotion? Just kept Vera suffering from injustice done by evil right wing conspirator? And we learn about this injustice 3 years later! Got to be joking!!!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362769186822</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 13:59:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362769326812-11</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayerhomo, Conservatism is on the losing end in this country, Europe, and many other parts of the world. Poor slayer, What will you do when this board shuts down?</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1362769326812</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:02:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362769648054-12</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Ms. Clinton would say, "what difference does that make"? Like he wasn't explicit enough explaining what he allegedly was trying to do? A bunch of community organizers apparently bought the trick well with business costume.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362769648054</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:07:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362769746921-13</Id><Topic><Title>Unemployment Hits 4 Yr Low ! Stocks hit record Highs !</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1362757687079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correct - he is firing employees on all cylinders! (Last week alone over 4000 in the Twin Cities, which has a unemployment rate of only 6.2%!!) Stocks (Wall Street) never go hand in hand with the Economy (Main Street), is that new to you??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362769746921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:09:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362770278921-14</Id><Topic><Title>GA expedites arming the mentally "troubled"</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757710885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:48:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beloved Obimbo better stay away from this state for another "Photo-Op, better send "Uncle Joe", so he can blame it on him! His last Photo-Op in Chicago didn't go well either! (One shot right after his speech by gang bangers - not mentally troubled!) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362770278921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:17:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362771861249-15</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually, the jail bird was thrown out of the acorn offices , they called the police on him in several.Oddly enough he didn't report that...... his video was a paid for hack piece, heavily edited , and the pimp outfit was staged, but shown on fox and brietbart to imply that is how he was dressed..... However he did manage to get an employee to say something stupid..... to bad he wasn't interviewing catholic priests , you know with the pimp outfit and all. People like you must judge the catholic chrurch rotten to the core because many of its priests have raped children and so many of its officials had covered up the raped , thus ensuring they went on.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362771861249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:44:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362772152114-16</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perfect! This explains why the Somalis, Asians and Blacks hate and shoot each others groups!!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362772152114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362772200440-17</Id><Title>catholic church was quick to fire a priest who spoke out for ordaining women as priests</Title><Msg>the idea of women priests was a problem for them and they acted quickly to fire the priest...... but decades of priests raping children went on and on and was covered up.. and considered more of a pr problem or what ever. BUFFALO, NY (WKBW) - Controversy seems to follow Roy Bourgeois wherever he goes, and he does not seem to mind. After publicly coming out in support of women's ordination in the Catholic Church, the former priest was fired, excommunicated and laicized. "</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362772200440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:50:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362772432734-18</Id><Topic><Title>Conservatism driven by fear</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362757957456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 10:52:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow - that beats Pierce Morgan with a fear factor of 200%!!! (I love to watch him rumbling and bumbling on gun control - clueless!!!) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362772432734</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362773161969-19</Id><Topic><Title>catholic church was quick to fire a priest who spoke out for ordaining women as priests</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362772200440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, love women priest, they can take the altar boys right to the back room, like the school teachers and ore-deam them! The first female cardinal shall be named Lucrezia Borgia!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362773161969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:06:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362776076193-20</Id><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Msg>(CNN) -- The U.S. government on Thursday notified 60,000 federal workers responsible for securing borders and facilitating trade that they will face furloughs due to government-wide spending cuts. Customs and Border Protection said it expects furloughs and other austerity will cause delays at ports of entry, including international arrivals at airports, and reduce the number of border patrol officers on duty at any one time. David Aguilar, the agency's deputy commissioner, said it must cut about $754 million by September 30, the end of the fiscal year. Rancher: Mexican border isn't secure Locals: Arizona border is not secure Reality of U.S. border security Forced cuts are 'a win for nobody' It aims to reach that goal through agency-wide furloughs, a hiring freeze, and reducing or eliminating overtime, compensatory time, travel and training. Other agencies are taking similar action due to spending cuts that took effect last week across the government, called sequestration. Customs spokeswoman Jenny Burke said in a statement that the agency "continues to evaluate further impacts of sequestration" on its operations. "Even with these cuts though, individuals apprehended illegally crossing the southwest border will still be processed as usual," she said. The agency said furloughs will begin in mid-April. Reductions in Border Patrol overtime will begin April 7 and furloughs will start around the middle of that month. Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano said on Monday that she expects customs wait times to increase to 150 to 200 percent of normal. "I don't mean to scare, I mean to inform. If you're traveling, get to the airport earlier than you otherwise would. There's only so much we can do with personnel," Napolitano said. The union representing some 24,000 agency employees predicted the cuts will "undercut" national security and lead to a loss of revenue. Customs collects more money for the federal government than any agency other than the Internal Revenue Service, said the National Treasury Employees Union. "There is no escaping the reality that sequestration is having serious effects on the traveling public and on vital commerce," said Colleen M. Kelley, the union's president.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362776441573-21</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other MANDATED cuts: n Mar 2, 2013 at 11:03 am With Congress unable to reach a deal to avert the indiscriminate spending cuts put in place in the Budget Control Act of 2011, President Obama on Friday signed an order authorizing the government to begin canceling $85 billion from federal accounts for this fiscal year. As Obama said during a press conference yesterday, “This is not going to be a apocalypse, I think as some people have said. It’s just dumb. And it’s going to hurt. It’s going to hurt individual people and it’s going to hurt the economy overall.” In a 83-page letter to House Speaker John Boehner (R-OH), the Office of Management and Budget details the specific reductions each government program will face. Here are the dumbest and most painful cuts: Health care $20 million cut from the Maternal, Infant, and Early Childhood Home Visiting Programs $10 million cut from the World Trade Center Health Program Fund $168 million cut from Substance Abuse and Mental Health Services Administration $75 million cut from the Aging and Disability Services Programs Housing $199 million cut from public housing $96 million cut from Homeless Assistance Grants $17 million cut from Housing Opportunities for Persons with AIDS $19 million cut from Housing for the Elderly $175 million cut from Low Income Home Energy Assistance Disaster and Emergency $928 million cut from FEMA’s disaster relief money $6 million cut from Emergency Food and Shelter $70 million cut from the Agricultural Disaster Relief Fund at USDA $61 million cut from the Hazardous Substance Superfund at EPA $125 million cut from the Wildland Fire Management $53 million cut from Salaries and Expenses at the Food Safety and Inspection Service Obamacare $13 million cut from the Consumer Operated and Oriented Plan Program (Co-ops) $57 million cut from the Health Care Fraud and Abuse Control $51 million cut from the Prevention and Public Health Fund $27 million cut from the State Grants and Demonstrations $44 million cut from the Affordable Insurance Exchange Grants program Education $633 million cut from the Department of Education’s Special Education programs $184 million cut from Rehabilitation Services and Disability Research $71 million cut from administration at the Office of Federal Student Aid $116 million cut from Higher Education $86 million cut from Student Financial Assistance Immigration $512 million cut from Customs and Border Protection $17 million cut from Automation Modernization, Customs and Border Protection $20 million cut from Border Security Fencing, Infrastructure, and Technology Security $79 million cut from Embassy Security, Construction, and Maintenance $604 million cut from National Nuclear Security Administration $232 million cut from the Federal Aviation Administration $394 million cut from Defense Environmental Cleanup</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776441573</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:00:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362776914755-22</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We might as well lay off the boarder workers JB... They are not allowed to do their jobs anyway....</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362776914755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:08:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362776993039-23</Id><Topic><Title>DART up Housing up Employment up</Title><Username>muyjk1</Username><Timestamp>1362677057963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 12:24:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>etfc Down. whats left to say??</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1362776993039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:09:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362777600804-24</Id><Title>Hello Obimbo!!!</Title><Msg>If you really want to go down in History as an achiever - abolish the "DAY LITES SAVING TIME"!!! Lots of cost savings there, including increase in health! We don't us WAX CANDLES any more just like you said "we don't have muskets any more and have ships now that can go under water"!!! WOW - what an observation!!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362777600804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:20:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362778005870-25</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Republicans, who refused to raise any additional revenue to avoid the budget cuts, have described the reductions as “modest” a “homerun” and something that “needs to happen” in order to “get this economy rolling again.” The latest projections from the Congressional Budget Office show that the nation’s deficits have shrunk by trillions of dollars, and the debt is close to being stabilized as a percentage of the economy. Meanwhile, budget cuts have already reduced spending by $1.5 trillion and even with the revenue included in the fiscal cliff deal, the ratio of cuts to revenue stands at an unbalanced 3 to 1. "</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362778005870</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:26:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362778608607-26</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep - it's like trout fishing up here - catch and release!!! (Or you get a fine for NOT releasing) ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362778608607</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:36:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362778746551-27</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About 85% of GOOD cuts - maybe the undesirables leave the country and the freeloaders go back to where they came from! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362778746551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:39:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362779737367-28</Id><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Msg>View profile South Dakota Law Will Allow Guns in Classrooms Source: NYT Gov. Dennis Daugaard of South Dakota on Friday signed into law a bill that would allow teachers to carry guns in the classroom. While some other states have provisions in their gun laws that make it possible for teachers to be armed, South Dakota is believed to be the first state to pass a law that specifically allows teachers to carry firearms. About two dozen states have proposed similar bills since the shootings in December at Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown, Conn., but all of them have stalled. Supporters say that the measure signed by Mr. Daugaard, a Republican, is important in a rural state like South Dakota, where some schools are many miles away from emergency responders.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362780075528-29</Id><Topic><Title>DART up Housing up Employment up</Title><Username>muyjk1</Username><Timestamp>1362677057963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 12:24:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Downgraded today from Outperform to Underperform. In addition the following: Gone out the door.... Steve Freiberg CEO Greg Framke COO Nick Utton V.P. Marketing Frank Petrilli Chairman of the Board</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1362780075528</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 17:01:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362781983074-30</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O.K. JB... A guy walks into Your classroom with a Gun and starts to shoot people....What do You do? Ask him to Pretty Please STOP? Or would You rather reach in your Purse and grab Your gun and Return Fire to ELIMINATE the Threat????</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362781983074</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 17:33:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362782512445-31</Id><Topic><Title>AP: Chavez Wasted His Money on Healthcare When He Could Have Built Gigantic Skyscrapers</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1362767451221</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 13:30:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the World stood quiet as JB Prayed at the Alter of Hugo!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362782512445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 17:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362782814557-32</Id><Title>HEY JB!....I'm Sorry I Insinuated That You Would Carry a Purse...</Title><Msg>We All know You would reach down into your Millitary Boot to grab your gun!....</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362782814557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 17:46:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362783825605-33</Id><Topic><Title>catholic church was quick to fire a priest who spoke out for ordaining women as priests</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362772200440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look out Boy Scouts, the LGBT community is looking for a new host.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362783825605</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 18:03:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362784014483-34</Id><Topic><Title>Sequesters have consequences</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362776076193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 15:54:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you this stupid, or just a fib teller. There is no cuts period...only cuts to spending increases...were are going broke...get it!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362784014483</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 18:06:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362784252652-35</Id><Title>New email tax to support post office</Title><Msg>That's like taxing automobiles to keep the buggy whip business going...only Democrats would think of something this inane. Berkeley Councilman Proposes Email Tax To Fund Postal Service A Berkeley city councilman has suggested that a tax on email may be wise way to help fund the United States Postal Service, according to the blog Berkeleyside. District 8 Supervisor Gordon Wozniak, who represents an area that includes the Claremont Hotel and the eastern end of the UC Berkeley campus, made the comments Tuesday as city officials moved to halt the sale of a Post Office building on Allston Way due to a decline in business. “There should be something like a bit tax. I mean a bit tax could be a cent per-gigabit and they would still make, probably, billions of dollars a year…And there should be, also, a very tiny tax on email,” Wozniak said at Tuesday’s</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1362784252652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 18:10:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362788821601-36</Id><Title>Just in!</Title><Msg>SD, the first state to pass a law to allow teachers to carry firearms in class rooms after the CT School Shooting! Wait till Uncle Joe and Pierce Morgan hears about that!!! Well, Obimbo started pushing that whole gun issue at the wrong end - now he is getting it! Just watching a standoff with police on Dowling in N-Minneapolis, this is going on since 11;00 this morning! 3 blocks down a triple shooting last nite in a known gang/biker after hours club, neighbors complaining about drinking, loud music and gun shots - whats done about it - nothing - last nite police had to respond after 2 are dead. Police is too busy running back ground checks on law abiding citizens! If you like to buy anything you want, including weapons, that's the place to go - no back ground checks required and no gun show either!! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1362788821601</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:27:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362788858717-37</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Arizona Daily Star Legislation that would allow Arizona teachers, staff and administrators to carry a gun on campus confuses taking action with making a meaningful change. The bill, pushed by Attorney General Tom Horne and Rep. David Stevens of Sierra Vista, would allow school district governing boards to designate employees who would have access to a gun that is kept in a secure firearm locker at the school. Should something terrible happen, like a shooter coming onto campus, these employees - who have had 24 hours of weapons training on an active shooter scenario, "mental conditioning on the use of deadly force, marksmanship and judgmental shooting" - could get the campus gun and respond. Horne and Stevens, both Republicans, point out that the decision would be voluntary. Local governing boards would decide. This is an attempt at school safety on the cheap. As Andrew Morrill, president of the Arizona Education Association, pointed out in a report from Capitol Media Services, "What I hear is passing the buck on training until we get it down to an affordable model," he said. This legislation lets people feel as if the community is doing something to keep schools safe. In light of the horrors of the Newtown, Columbine and Virginia Tech gun murders, everyone wants to do something, anything to keep children safe. But arming teachers and school personnel won't do it. School resource officers - police officers who worked from schools - used to be common in Tucson districts. But budget cuts eliminated most, if not all, positions. The trained police officers were better used in the community, was the thinking. Arming teachers, or other school workers, isn't a replacement for properly trained peace officers on campus. Horne's response that at least with this "if a bad guy gets in and starts shooting, there's somebody there to stop them." Unless that person is shot first."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362788858717</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:27:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362788997338-38</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A similar unrealistic thinking says that school shootings happen because schools are "gun-free zones" and that's why shooters choose them. In a logical world, maybe that would make sense. But the mind of a person bent on homicide isn't motivated by common sense - the decision in most mass murder cases is to commit suicide in the most spectacularly awful way possible. The shooter typically plans to die, at his own hand or those of police, and to take as many people as possible with him. Knowing that someone on campus might have a gun, or access to a gun, won't stop a person bent on attaining the twisted glory they believe will come to them once they've showed the world what they're capable of doing. It's not about rational motivation, although actions leading up to the murders may appear thoughtful and planned. Stopping gun violence and improving community and school safety can't be a make-do effort. This bill, HB 2656, is just that. It offers the comfort of "doing something" while requiring only three workdays of training. Our efforts should be on preventing attacks from happening in the first place."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362788997338</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:29:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362789180735-39</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surprise! Some ACORN employees did what they had to? Oh! And all others fell victims of O'Keefe's deception. Right. ACORN Obama apparatchicks can do no wrong. O'Keefe didn't go far enough to prove it. But that would end with those "victims" behind bars. So, they paid a low price: had to change the chair in other useless office. What an evil man this O'Keefe is, he dared to check if ACORN employee didn't cooperate with human traffickers.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362789180735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:33:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362790436540-40</Id><Topic><Title>catholic church was quick to fire a priest who spoke out for ordaining women as priests</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362772200440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 14:50:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>biddermoon, There are homosexual clubs among Catholic priests, as well as within the Vatican. However, pedophile priests are criminals. It is well known that 50% of seminarians are gay.</Msg><Username>union_dude25</Username><Timestamp>1362790436540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 19:53:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362792330551-41</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's like trying to stop You from posting from 32 different I.D.'s... It just Can't be Done!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1362792330551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:25:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362792570836-42</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"One recent study in the Journal of Police Crisis Negotiations found that the introduction of police officers in schools helps lower overall violence and gang problems. At the same time, the study found that schools with armed guards tend to experience more violent crime than those without. "The evidence about more guns suggests that more guns lead to more problems," said Aaron Kupchik, associate professor of sociology and criminal justice at the University of Delaware and author of the 2010 book "Homeroom Security: School Discipline in an Age of Fear." "More guns in schools is particularly problematic," he added. SEE ALSO: U.S. Guns by the Numbers Kupchik has studied school security since the 1990s and says that school administrators have borrowed techniques from the criminal justice system to deal with violence and behavioral problems with school-age children, techniques such as metal detectors, surveillance cameras and zero-tolerance policies with violent behavior or drug use. The irony is that crime in schools has declined just as it has in the rest of the country, Kupchik said. "The nationwide drop in school crime is following crime rates generally," Kupchik said. "It may or may not have anything to do with policies they have implemented."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362792570836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:29:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362792661666-43</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still, at least one administrator says the placement of armed guards is working to deter bad behavior. Michael Queen, president of the Harrison County Board of Education in West Virginia, says he's seen drug use and behavioral problems decrease in the seven years since the district started hiring local police full-time inside five of the county's 24 schools. "It's absolutely an undeniable fact that when we put armed police officers in our high schools, drugs in schools went dramatically down and violence with fights went down dramatically," Queen said. Officers' pay is split between the school district and the local municipality. They also conduct anti-drug, anti-bullying and anti-gang classes inside schools. He'd like to increase their presence to all middle schools as well as elementary schools. While Queen believes arming teachers is a mistake, he does want to see more security measures such as double-doors and reinforced glass to prevent a would-be shooter from entering the schools. "We know we have to do something," he said. One advocate says that the discussion of arming schools is a distraction from the more important issue of controlling access to powerful weapons. Arming teachers "is not a preventive strategy; it is a reactive strategy," said Ladd Everitt, spokesman for the Coalition to Stop Gun Violence, a non-profit advocacy group. "Once you have a homicidal maniac who has stockpiled weapons legally, you've failed from a public policy perspective." The fact that we are talking about armed guards and armed teachers, and talking about putting kids in the middle of shootouts is insane," he added. Everitt noted that armed guards didn't deter killers at Columbine High School or Virginia Tech."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362792661666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:31:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362792933707-44</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He'll craphis pants then fling hispoo.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1362792933707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:35:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362793241053-45</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"It’s important to keep in mind that while mass shootings are extremely rare, violence impacts the lives of young people every day. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention report that each day, an average of 13 people between the ages of 10 and 24 are victims of homicide in the U.S., making homicide the third leading cause of death among youth and young adults; it is the leading cause of death among African American youth. Yet very little of this violence occurs on school grounds. Children spend more than a third of their waking hours on campus, but less than 2% of youth homicides occur at school. One of the reasons why there are so few homicides at school is because these places are largely successful at keeping guns off the premises. Adult supervision and, in very high-risk schools, metal detectors have proven to be effective deterrents. While there are no specific data regarding having armed adults in schools, an analysis of U.S. mortality data found that people with guns in the home are at greater risk than those without guns in the home of dying from a homicide there. There is no reason to think schools would be any different: the more guns there are, the more opportunities there are to use them."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362793241053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:40:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362793904437-46</Id><Topic><Title>James O'Keefe To Pay $100K Settlement To Former ACORN Employee</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362704807800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 20:06:47 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad o'keefe didn't use his pimp routine on the catholic church, huh. there is some real evil there. and it was covered up all the way to the top.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362793904437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 20:51:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362794741646-47</Id><Title>tax dollars went to gop "faith based" community organizers..where was O'keefe &amp; his pimp costume?</Title><Msg>how much tax money went to the employees of churches, many of whom are , well, as is well known sex predators?................."President Bush punched a dangerous hole in the wall between church and state earlier this month by signing an executive order that eases the way for religious groups to receive federal funds to run social services programs. The president's unilateral order, which wrongly cut Congress out of the loop, lets faith-based organizations use tax dollars to win converts and gives them a green light to discriminate in employment. It should be struck down by the courts. The Bush administration's faith-based initiative has long been high on the wish list of religious conservatives. "</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362794741646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362795317782-48</Id><Topic><Title>tax dollars went to gop "faith based" community organizers..where was O'keefe &amp; his pimp costume?</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362794741646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:05:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>for all their electoral histrionics, Republicans have aligned themselves with ACORN in the past. Indeed, in addition to the McCain photo, there is a host of examples of prominent McCain surrogates attending ACORN events, signing ACORN legislation, or complimenting the group's efforts. Florida Gov. Charlie Crist, for example, partnered with ACORN in March 2008 for a "Homeownership Promotes The Economy" taskforce. More recently, Crist declared that -- contrary to GOP outrage -- he was not upset with the group's voter registration efforts in his state. The New York Times reported that ACORN supported a law signed by Governor Crist, which "changed the rules last year to restore the voting rights of about 112,000 former convicts." In July 2005, meanwhile, another Republican governor, Rick Perry of Texas, signed ACORN's Lending Law Reform Bill that changed the state's homelending practices. In June 2007, Minnesota Governor and McCain VP short-lister Tim Pawlenty signed a similar bill -- drafted by ACORN -- that helped homeowners get fairer deals on their mortgages. "The legislation was drafted according to recommendations made by a predatory lending study group established by Swanson prior to the legislative session," wrote the Northwestern Financial Review. "The study group contained representatives from the banking industry and the mortgage brokers association, as well as consumer advocates from organizations such as Illegal Aid and ACORN." As Governor of Massachusetts, Mitt Romney signed an anti-predatory lending bill that ACORN supported. In February 2006, Connecticut Senator Joe Lieberman met with the ACORN Katrina Survivors Association. And back in July 2005, New York City mayor Michael Bloomberg actually got a kiss from ACORN's state leader, according to the publication City Limits, during an announcement that the city would protect or create 65,000 affordable units in a new housing proposal. ....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362795317782</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:15:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362795492458-49</Id><Title>will there ever be another republican president?</Title><Msg>will there ever be another republican president? . it seems that the gop hates about everyone but the rich. The gop knows they need to overcome their racism, misogyny, homophobia and so forth, but they are so full of hate and dogma that it might be an impossible task for them. Republicans should get back to their roots: The Square Deal was President Theodore Roosevelt's domestic program formed upon three basic ideas: conservation of natural resources, control of corporations, and consumer protection. Thus, it aimed at helping middle class citizens and involved attacking plutocracy and bad trusts while at the same time protecting business from the most extreme demands of organized labor. ... Roosevelt was a Republican who believed in government action to mitigate social evils, and as president denounced “the representatives of predatory wealth” as guilty of “all forms of iniquity from the oppression of wage workers to defrauding the public.”[2] Booker T. Washington, the most important black leader of the day, was the first African American to be invited to dinner, on October 16, 1901, at the White House, where he discussed politics and racism with Roosevelt.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1362795492458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:18:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362796450813-50</Id><Topic><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362532227182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chavez wasn't worth assassinating. For all his bombastic talk and all his damage to the economy of Venezuela, as far as State is concerned that's fine as long as he keeps selling us the oil. Defense says he isn't a threat unless working with an alliance of Central and South American Governments, of which its a group, albeit a weak group, of three right now, also, none of them threats together or separately. Basically he was entertainment.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1362796450813</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:34:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362796891629-51</Id><Topic><Title>BO the Conqueror</Title><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362532227182</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 20:10:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The legal reason is hardly a secret. Obama is most likely simply having his courts declare such people "outlaw". Once a declaration of outlawry is used then that person has NO legal protections whatever, and can be killed by anyone, on sight. or for that matter anything else they want to do with them. The reasoning is quite solid and our Supreme Court has also upheld declarations of Outlawry to be Constitutional when certain circumstances are met. All you have to do to avoid dying is submit yourself to the nearest US law enforcement personnel . . . carefully. Then you stand trial for the charges which were the basis of the original declaration. If the cops at the station house don't decide its too much paperwork and just drag you out back and shoot you. Hint, come in early in the morning when they've had sleep, after their coffee and doughnuts, you might live to see the declaration lifted.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1362796891629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 21:41:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1362799129445-52</Id><Title>Fewer gun deaths in states with most gun laws, study finds</Title><Msg>By Bill Briggs, NBC News contributor States with a heavier dose of firearm laws tend to have the lowest rates of gun deaths, according to a study released Wednesday by Boston-based researchers who argue their findings show "there is a role" in America for more rigid gun-control legislation. "It seems pretty clear: If you want to know which of the states have the lowest gun-mortality rates just look for those with the greatest number of gun laws," said Dr. Eric W. Fleegler of Boston Children's Hospital who, with colleagues, analyzed firearm-related deaths reported to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention from 2007 through 2010. By scoring individual states simply by the sheer volume of gun laws they have on the books, the researchers noted that in states with the highest number of firearms measures, their rate of gun deaths is collectively 42 percent lower when compared to states that have passed the fewest number of gun rules. The study was published online in the journal JAMA Internal Medicine. Advertise | AdChoices As proof, Fleegler pointed to the firearm-fatality rates in law-laden states such as Massachusetts (where there were 3.4 gun deaths per 100,000 individuals), New Jersey (4.9 per 100,000) and Connecticut (5.1 per 100,000). In states with sparser firearms laws, researchers reported that gun-mortality rates were higher: Louisiana (18.0 per 100,000), Alaska (17.5 per 100,000) and Arizona (13.6 per 100,000)."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362799129445</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 22:18:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362799230570-53</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you want to make maximum damage, you don't give it to a chance. Shooters do want something spectacular. But they know that they have one and only opportunity to make it happen. To try it in the place where people can be armed is stupid. No need for high IQ to realize that. All of the recent mass murderers had higher than average IQ. Colorado shooter showed up in 2 other theaters prior to the one which he eventually targeted. Other 2 didn't prohibit concealed weapons.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1362799230570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 22:20:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362801891421-54</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do Armed Civilians Stop Mass Shooters? Actually, No. Five cases commonly cited as a rationale for arming Americans don't stand up to scrutiny. —By Mark Follman | Wed Dec. 19, 2012 In the wake of the unthinkable massacre in Newtown, Connecticut, pro-gun ideologues are once again calling for ordinary citizens to arm themselves as a solution to mass shootings. If only the principal at Sandy Hook Elementary School had possessed a M-4 assault rifle she could've stopped the killer, they say. This latest twist on a long-running argument isn't just absurd on its face; there is no evidence to support it. As I reported recently in our in-depth investigation, not one of 62 mass shootings in the United States over the last 30 years has been stopped this way. More broadly, attempts by armed civilians to intervene in shooting rampages are rare—and are successful even more rarely. (Two people who tried it in recent years were gravely wounded or killed.) And law enforcement overwhelmingly hates the idea of armed citizens getting involved. Those pesky facts haven't stopped the "arm America more!" crowd from pressing the argument with alleged examples of successful armed interventions. The problem is, the few examples they keep using—in which they depict plain old folks acting heroically and with definitive results—fall apart under scrutiny. Here are five cases commonly cited and why they don't work:</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362801891421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362802016645-55</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appalachian School of Law shooting in Grundy, Virginia Gun rights die-hards frequently credit the end of a rampage at the law school in 2002 to armed "students" who intervened. They conveniently ignore that those students also happened to be current and former law enforcement officers, and that the killer, according to police investigators, was out of ammunition by the time they got to him. Middle school dance shooting in Edinboro, Pennsylvania An ambiguous case from 1998, in which the shooter may well have already been done shooting: After killing a teacher and wounding three others, the 14-year-old perpetrator left the dance venue. The owner of the venue followed him outside with a shotgun, confronting and subduing him in a nearby field until police arrived. The Atlantic's Jeffrey Goldberg, who himself recently argued for more guns as an answer to gun violence, told me this week that one police source he talked to about this case said that it was "not clear at all" whether the kid had intended to do any further shooting after he'd left the building.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362802016645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:06:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362802087980-56</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>High school shooting in Pearl, Mississippi Another case, from 1997, in which the shooting was apparently already over: After killing two and wounding seven inside Pearl High School, the 16-year-old perpetrator left the building and went outside near the parking lot. The assistant principal—who was also a member of the Army Reserve—ran out to his own vehicle, grabbed a handgun he kept there, and then approached the shooter, subduing him at gunpoint until authorities arrived. New Life Church shooting in Colorado Springs, Colorado In 2007 a gunman killed two people and wounded three others before being shot himself; the pro-gun crowd likes to refer to the woman who took him out in the parking lot as a "church member." Never mind that she was a security officer for the church and a former cop, and that the church had put its security team on high alert earlier that day due to another church shooting nearby. Bar shooting in Winnemucca, Nevada In 2008, a gunman who killed two and wounded two others was taken out by another patron in the bar, who was carrying with a valid permit. But this was no regular Joe with a concealed handgun: The vigilante, who was not charged after authorities determined he'd committed a justifiable homicide, was a US Marine.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362802087980</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:08:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1362802209666-57</Id><Topic><Title>How droolers solve problems</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1362779737367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 16:55:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what about cases in which citizens try to use their guns and things go terribly wrong? There are at least two examples of ill-fated attempts that you won't see mentioned by those arguing for your kid's teacher to start stashing a loaded Glock in her classroom: Shopping mall shooting in Tacoma, Washington As a rampage unfolded in 2005, a civilian with a concealed-carry permit named Brendan McKown confronted the assailant with his handgun. The shooter pumped several bullets into McKown, wounding six people before eventually surrendering to police after a hostage standoff. A comatose McKown eventually recovered after weeks in the hospital. Courthouse shooting in Tyler, Texas In 2005, a civilian named Mark Wilson, who was a firearms instructor, fired his licensed handgun at a man on a rampage at the county courthouse. Wilson was shot dead by the body-armored assailant, who wielded an AK-47. Such actions in chaotic situations don't just put the well-intentioned citizen at risk, of course. According to Robert McMenomy, an assistant special agent in charge in the San Francisco division of the FBI, they increase the danger for innocent bystanders. (Exhibit A: the gun-wielding guy who came really close to shooting an innocent person as the Tucson massacre unfolded.) They also make it more difficult for law enforcement officers to do their jobs. "In a scenario like that," McMenomy told me recently, "they wouldn't know who was good or who was bad, and it would divert them from the real threat."</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1362802209666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-08 23:10:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>