<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373344821387-1</Id><Topic><Title>Does This Stock Pay A Dividend?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373325224646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dunno. You should Call EF Hutton. They'd know.</Msg><Username>fritz_schnabel</Username><Timestamp>1373344821387</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 00:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373371592595-2</Id><Topic><Title>Does This Stock Pay A Dividend?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373325224646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you know i was there in my best business suit. i smuggled in two spuds as usual. stupid yahoo won't let me post a pic from the conference.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373371592595</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 08:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373371675623-3</Id><Topic><Title>Does This Stock Pay A Dividend?</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373325224646</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 19:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you know anything about EF Hutton? I call and call and call - but nobody answers. plus i don't get statements in the mail like before.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373371675623</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 08:07:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373374103341-4</Id><Topic><Title>Reports From the Front Lines of Gun-Free Chicago</Title><Username>homie_dont_join_nra</Username><Timestamp>1373278726369</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-08 06:18:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is this the place obama came from,, no wonder he's some messed up.</Msg><Username>ajbkfx</Username><Timestamp>1373374103341</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 08:48:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373376928353-5</Id><Title>$13.50</Title><Msg>Something must be up...stock keeps rising</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373376928353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:35:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373379748320-6</Id><Topic><Title>$13.50</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373376928353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:35:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she wants to go higher because LLF isn't busy shorting the schllt out of it.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373379748320</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:22:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373379892709-7</Id><Title>Rush Agrees w/ Me about Fox Snooze</Title><Msg>he's sayin what I've been sayin for a decade ............ "You need to stop watching these people, because they're not going to change," he said. "Your blood pressure is going to suffer if you keep watching these people. I mean, they're designed to get you ticked off. They're designed to make you question your sanity. You're going to watch these people [and] you're going to say, 'how in the world can we have such idiotic people?' And you're going think maybe they're not and you're crazy." He's sayin only idiots watch this idiotic show. We have quite a few idiots on this board. Hehe</Msg><Username>lonelyxprezfromcrawford</Username><Timestamp>1373379892709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:24:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373380030125-8</Id><Title>Rush Agrees w/ Me about Fox Snooze</Title><Msg>LLF has shorty by the short hairs</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373380030125</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373380400448-9</Id><Title>LLF says - Mahalo</Title><Msg>he sends his best regards to shorty</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373380400448</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373381968857-10</Id><Title>LTS in full blown breakout mode NOW</Title><Msg>prosper</Msg><Username>colbatana</Username><Timestamp>1373381968857</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 10:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373382897365-11</Id><Title>Hele mei hoohiwahiwa</Title><Msg>Come celebrate with Little Lord Fauntleroy at his island retreat.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373382897365</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 11:14:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373384027532-12</Id><Topic><Title>$13.50</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373376928353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:35:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactly.</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373384027532</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 11:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373384224465-13</Id><Title>Took out stops...</Title><Msg>Now we go higher</Msg><Username>strade1107</Username><Timestamp>1373384224465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 11:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373389535897-14</Id><Title>3d "up" day on almost 3 month rise from $10.</Title><Msg>So, where are the shorts given that short interest is only down a wee bit (as of 6/14) compared to the month previous? Why maintain a short position and brag about how rich you're going to get "when the stock falls" even though you've been averaging up your costs from $10? This has legs until earnings notwithstanding at least ONE attempt to shake out loose hands. But do you REALLY want to hold a short position through earnings without buying some nice CALLs?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373389535897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373390267247-15</Id><Topic><Title>$13.50</Title><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373376928353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 09:35:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't hurt that interest rates are up and default rates are down while DARTS keep rising.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373390267247</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373391865525-16</Id><Title>Voter suppression panned by conservative jurist</Title><Msg>" Jul 8, 2013 at 12:00 pm If a leading conservative scholar and former judge were now on the Supreme Court instead of Chief Justice Roberts or Justice Alito, it is likely that the Voting Right Act would remain intact. Judge Michael McConnell was a leading conservative law professor at the time President George W. Bush named him to the United States Court of Appeals for the Tenth Circuit in 2002 (he’s since left the bench to return to the legal academy at Stanford Law School). McConnell was also widely viewed as a possible Supreme Court nominee during the Bush Administration. In an interview with NPR’s Nina Totenberg, McConnell has harsh words for the five conservative justices’ recent decision neutering much of the Voting Rights Act — labeling the reasoning that drove that decision “made up.” Although the conservatives’ decision in Shelby County v. Holder never actually identifies the legal standard of review that led them to strike down the heart of America’s voting rights law, the opinion rests in large part on the fact that the Voting Rights Act applies some of its requirements “only to some States,” in what the Court labels as a “dramatic departure from the principle that all States enjoy equal sovereignty.” As McConnell explains, however, “[t]here’s no requirement in the Constitution to treat all states the same,” adding that “[i]t might be an attractive principle, but it doesn’t seem to be in the Constitution.” Judge McConnell is, of course, correct. The Fifteenth Amendment provides that “[t]he right of citizens of the United States to vote shall not be denied or abridged by the United States or by any State on account of race, color, or previous condition of servitude,” and it gives Congress “power to enforce this article by appropriate legislation.” One searches the Constitution in vain for language forbidding the Voting Rights Act application of some of its strongest medicine to jurisdictions judged to have the worst record of voter suppression."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373391865525</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:44:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373392352553-17</Id><Title>Another GOP lied exposed</Title><Msg>"For years, South Carolina Republicans have complained about the names of dead voters being used to cast ballots in a broad voter fraud scheme. Now that a recent report by the State Law Enforcement Division has blown up those claims, unable to find a single example of a "zombie voter" committing fraud, one Democrat is demanding that Gov. Nikki Haley (R) apologize for her party's "bogus" crusade. In a statement released Monday, House Democratic Leader Todd Rutherford accused Haley and other Republicans of deliberately and deceptively pushing false claims for political gain. "Now we have the proof that shows that the accusations of voter fraud were completely without merit," said Rutherford. "And once again, South Carolina's taxpayers have to foot the bill for the millions of dollars unnecessarily spent as a result of Governor Haley and her colleagues' incompetence and blind-ideology." Rutherford went on to call for Haley and Republicans to "acknowledge that they were being dishonest about voter fraud" and to "apologize to the public."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373392352553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373394618642-18</Id><Topic><Title>Another GOP lied exposed</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373392352553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is this related to E Trade? If you are looking for dead voters going for the Dems, look no further than his hometown of Chicago.</Msg><Username>klass1klown2</Username><Timestamp>1373394618642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 14:30:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373394634852-19</Id><Title>Another GOP lied exposed</Title><Msg>aloha shorty</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373394634852</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 14:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373400960960-20</Id><Topic><Title>Another GOP lied exposed</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373392352553</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:52:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blah, blah, blah! yawn, yawn, yawn!</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1373400960960</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 16:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373404472689-21</Id><Title>BO the conqueror</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — The White House said Monday that the federal budget deficit for the current fiscal year will shrink to $759 billion. That’s more than $200 billion less than the administration predicted just three months ago. The new figures reflect additional revenues generated by the improving economy and take into account automatic, across-the-board spending cuts that the White House had hoped to avert. The White House projected that economic growth would be slightly slower in the coming years than it forecast in April. The report said the automatic spending cuts that kicked in during March will slow down economic growth this year from the 2.6 percent increase it forecast for the fourth quarter of this year to a 2.4 percent increase. But the White House sees a slightly rosier jobs picture. It projects that unemployment will average 7 percent next year and reach 6.8 percent in the final quarter of 2014. That’s an improvement over the 7.2 percent unemployment it forecast in April as an average for 2014.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373404472689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:14:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373405345919-22</Id><Title>BO the conqueror</Title><Msg>no easy outs for shorty this time</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373405345919</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:29:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373406117270-23</Id><Topic><Title>3d "up" day on almost 3 month rise from $10.</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373389535897</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 13:05:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound bitter shortie... Your wife says hi - she will be back when she says she will be back.</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373406117270</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:41:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373406773102-24</Id><Title>A Poem</Title><Msg>Posted on Jul 9, 2013 Public debate over SB-1, the controversial piece of legislation that would ban abortion after 20 weeks of pregnancy and close most of the clinics that perform the procedure in Texas, heated up in Austin on Monday as hundreds of supporters and opponents testified at the Capitol during the legislature’s second consecutive special session. One of those who spoke was Katie Heim, an abortion activist who shared her opinion in a highly unorthodox fashion: through poetry. Here’s the transcript of Heim’s poem “If My Vagina Was a Gun.” You can listen to her “performing” it in front of the Texas lawmakers in the audio clip below. If my vagina was a gun, you would stand for its rights, You would ride on buses and fight all the fights. If my vagina was a gun, you would treat it with care, You wouldn’t spill all its secrets because, well, why go there. If my vagina was a gun, you’d say what it holds is private From cold dead hands we could pry, you surely would riot. If my vagina was a gun, its rights would all be protected, no matter the body count or the children affected. If my vagina was a gun, I could bypass security, concealed carry laws would ensure I’d have impunity. If my vagina was a gun, I wouldn’t have to beg you, I could hunt this great land and do all the things men do. But my vagina is not a gun, it is a mightier thing, With a voice that rings true making lawmakers’ ears ring. Vaginas are not delicate, they are muscular and magic, So stop messing with mine, with legislation that’s tragic. My vagina’s here to demand from the source, Listen to the voices of thousands or feel their full force.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373406773102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:52:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373407256508-25</Id><Title>A Poem</Title><Msg>Poor shortie - posting nonsense to dull the pain.</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1373407256508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 18:00:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373417108654-26</Id><Topic><Title>Crackers hiding behind kids</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1372698451713</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-01 13:07:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's funny how you don't even try to hide your multiple I.D.'s anymore...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373417108654</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 20:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373419183428-27</Id><Topic><Title>A Poem</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373406773102</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 17:52:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vagina vincit Omnia. #$%$--y conquers all.</Msg><Username>sant3899</Username><Timestamp>1373419183428</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-09 21:19:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>