<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-31"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364704787928-1</Id><Topic><Title>MN REJECTS Fed. Exchang!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1364677777694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 17:09:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uhh, Obama is hoping the states set up their own echanges, what are you talking about?</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1364704787928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 00:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364704950192-2</Id><Topic><Title>Home prices market vs replacement price</Title><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1364657457964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 11:30:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have no clue what you are trying to say here. Are you actualy implying that a substantial portion of the market, the homes can not be made ready to be livable for less than the market value of the home. LMFAO</Msg><Username>sec_fordummies</Username><Timestamp>1364704950192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 00:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364736920080-3</Id><Title>will congressman Issa covene all male male to invstgate Pope washing women's feet</Title><Msg>he convened one to investigate papal views on other parts of women. Pope's foot-wash a final straw for traditionalists By NICOLE WINFIELD | Associated</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364736920080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 09:35:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364742390473-4</Id><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen'</Title><Msg>Walmart, one of the richest corporations in the world, refuses to pay its employees a livable wage or provide any form of decent healthcare, increasing reliance on government assistance, and the need for a social safety net. by Paddy Ryan At over $446 billion per year, Walmart is the third highest revenue grossing corporation in the world. Walmart earns over $15 billion per year in pure profit and pays its executives handsomely. In 2011, Walmart CEO Mike Duke – already a millionaire a dozen times over – received an $18.1 million compensation package. The Walton family controlling over 48 percent of the corporation through stock ownership does even better. Together, members of the Walton family are worth in excess of $102 billion – which makes them one of the richest families in the world. What is shameful is that CEO Mike Duke makes more money in one hour, than his employees earn in an entire year. Yet, Walmart – which employs millions of people in its stores, distribution centers, and warehouses – continues to abuse its employees and refuses to pay them a livable wage. The company has frequently been charged with wage theft claims by workers who point to the most common forms of wage theft: the refusal to pay proper overtime, the refusal to honor the minimum wage, and illegal paycheck deductions. Meanwhile, Walmart routinely blocks any attempt by workers to organize, using anti-union propaganda and scare tactics, firing employees without just cause, failing to provide any form of decent healthcare coverage or a livable wage. To make matters worse, these abusive Walmart policies have increased employee reliance on government assistance and the need for a government funded social safety net. In fact, Walmart has become the number one driver behind the growing use of food stamps in the United States with "as many as 80 percent of workers in Wal-Mart stores using food stamps."</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364742390473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364743008625-5</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364742390473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wal-Mart's poverty wages force employees to rely on $2.66 billion in government help every year, or about $420,000 per store. In state after state, Wal-Mart employees are the top recipients of Medicaid. As many as 80 percent of workers in Wal-Mart stores use food stamps. Walmart's employees receive $2.66 billion in government help every year, or about $420,000 per store. They are also the top recipients of Medicaid in numerous states. Why does this occur? Walmart fails to provide a livable wage and decent healthcare benefits, costing U.S. taxpayers an annual average of $1.02 billion in healthcare costs. This direct public subsidy is being given to offset the failures of an international corporate giant who shouldn’t be shifting part of its labor costs onto the American taxpayers. Wal-Mart workers’ reliance on public assistance due to substandard wages and benefits has become a form of indirect public subsidy to the company. In effect, Wal-Mart is shifting part of its labor costs onto the public. Recently, Walmart workers have been speaking out against the abuses they face because of excessive corporate greed. For the first time in Walmart's 50 year history, workers at multiple stores are striking. Last week, over 70 Walmart workers in Los Angeles decided to walk off the job.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364743008625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 11:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364747238308-6</Id><Topic><Title>Profit Share Hits Post-War High and the Post Doesn't Notice</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364648194891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 08:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(the rich get richer and everyone else poorer) DECREASE in corporate taxes since Reagan amount to a "$5.0 trillion tax on the nation's workers" . "the rise in after-tax corporate profits since the Reagan era can be seen as equivalent to a $5.0 trillion tax on the nation's workers" profit share of corporate income is now 25.6 percent, highest since 1951 however, the AFTER TAX is share of 19.2 percent, is the highest since 1930 ! In other words corporatations are making more now AFTER taxes than any time since 1930.... and the " rise in after-tax corporate profits since the Reagan era can be seen as equivalent to a $5.0 trillion tax on the nation's workers" quotes from Dean Baker Phd economics</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364747238308</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 12:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364748959001-7</Id><Topic><Title>Profit Share Hits Post-War High and the Post Doesn't Notice</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364648194891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 08:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Lies, damned lies, and statistics" is a phrase describing the persuasive power of numbers, particularly the use of statistics to bolster weak arguments. And in this instance they're propagated by stooges for the country destroying left to buy votes and confiscate taxpayer funds. Fact!</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364748959001</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 12:55:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364749805432-8</Id><Topic><Title>Profit Share Hits Post-War High and the Post Doesn't Notice</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364648194891</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 08:56:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the fact is that people like you hate facts. For instance it is a fact that human beings did not "walk with dinosaurs" as many of your persuasion insist. Another fact is that corporations now make far more after tax profits after taxes than in many decades, and ntm the fact that ceos pay themselves about 350 times their avg worker's salary, up from around 50 times only 30 years ago... and they also pay lower tax rates than then.. all part and parcel of the rich getting richer and everyone else getting poorer, or a s warren buffet put it: “There’s class warfare, but it’s my class, the rich class, that’s making war, and winning.” As Richard Thaler, a professor of economics at the University of Chicago, wrote in a recent New York Times op-ed: “The question comes down to whether we want a society in which the rich take an ever-increasing share of the pie, or prefer to return to conditions that allow all classes to anticipate an increasing standard of living..............</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364749805432</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:10:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364749942128-9</Id><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Msg>There is nothing there that is worth having your family brutally attacked on the street. Thank you, Obama. Thank you Lyndon Johnson. The welfare state is turning our cities into 3rd world holes.</Msg><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364750147693-10</Id><Topic><Title>Arkansas residents evacuate as Exxon-Mobil tar sands pipeline ruptures</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364700891787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-30 23:34:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People living near fracking sites can actually put a match to their water tap, ............. and it lights up. Now that Republican progress. Light your cigarette with your tap.</Msg><Username>borderxingbeaner</Username><Timestamp>1364750147693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:15:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364750257923-11</Id><Topic><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>'Community Organizers' were quick to blame white European millionaires for multiple attacks on the former tourist attraction Gold Coast.</Msg><Username>homie_dont_join_nra</Username><Timestamp>1364750257923</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364751245093-12</Id><Topic><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Maroon, check the FACTS !!!!! The 10 most violent states in America are ALL RED STATES !!!!!!! http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2011/04/13/10-most-violent-states_n_848317.html#s263628&amp;title=1_Louisiana</Msg><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1364751245093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364752106175-13</Id><Title>stay away from Dallas</Title><Msg>prosecutor and wife murdered in home..... maybe some connection to murder of an assistant da in jan or the murder of a warden in colo.....</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364752106175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:48:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364752156779-14</Id><Topic><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean the states with the most REPORTED violence. People in some areas of southern Michigan don't even bother calling the police anymore. All they do is show up 30 minutes late, take a statement, search your house, and leave if they can't arrest you. Same with New York, LA, Miami, Atlanta (unfortunately) and quite a few other urban hellholes, most of which are located in BLUE states. When a crime's committed no one seen NOTHIN. We get ALITTLE of that in Texas, but we have even more lax enforcement of immigration rules than even California, and folks know the Texas police aren't going to deport you for reporting a crime unless you're also a criminal. They don't have any interest in that since folks living across the border can just get frequent crossers cards and come and go across the border as they please or, in some parts of rural Texas, just cross the border at will. Texas views immigrants as an asset, not a liability. And this state has ALWAYS been part Mexican anyway. Disrespect for Rule of Law in Red states has not, in general, eroded to the degree it has in Blue states where the prisons are so crowded a revolving door policy has become the only sustainable policy.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364752156779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364752202818-15</Id><Title>stay away from the south?</Title><Msg>who can forget that the racists bombed churches, murdered children and legally oppressed minorities until 1965.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364752202818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364752605192-16</Id><Topic><Title>stay away from Dallas</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364752106175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DALLAS IS where classy whites spit on Lady Bird Johnson "It became known as the “Lady Bird Spitting Incident”.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364752605192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364752936784-17</Id><Title>Conservative Judge speaks out</Title><Msg>A conservative case for an assault weapons ban Op-Ed If we can't draw a sensible line on guns, we may as well call the American experiment in democracy a failure. December 20, 2012|By Larry Alan Burns Last month, I sentenced Jared Lee Loughner to seven consecutive life terms plus 140 years in federal prison for his shooting rampage in Tucson. That tragedy left six people dead, more than twice that number injured and a community shaken to its core. Loughner deserved his punishment. But during the sentencing, I also questioned the social utility of high-capacity magazines like the one that fed his Glock. And I lamented the expiration of the federal assault weapons ban in 2004, which prohibited the manufacture and importation of certain particularly deadly guns, as well as magazines that can hold more than 10 rounds of ammunition. The ban wasn't all that stringent — if you already owned a banned gun or high-capacity magazine you could keep it, and you could sell it to someone else — but at least it was something And it says something that half of the nation's deadliest shootings occurred after the ban expired, including the massacre at Sandy Hook Elementary in Newtown, Conn. It also says something that it has not even been two years since Loughner's rampage, and already six mass shootings have been deadlier.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364752936784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364753042503-18</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Judge speaks out</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364752936784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not a social scientist, and I know that very smart ones are divided on what to do about gun violence. But reasonable, good-faith debates have boundaries, and in the debate about guns, a high-capacity magazine has always seemed to me beyond them. Bystanders got to Loughner and subdued him only after he emptied one 31-round magazine and was trying to load another. Adam Lanza, the Newtown shooter, chose as his primary weapon a semiautomatic rifle with 30-round magazines. And we don't even bother to call the 100-rounder that James Holmes is accused of emptying in an Aurora, Colo., movie theater a magazine — it is a drum. How is this not an argument for regulating the number of rounds a gun can fire? I get it. Someone bent on mass murder who has only a 10-round magazine or revolvers at his disposal probably is not going to abandon his plan and instead try to talk his problems out. But we might be able to take the "mass" out of "mass shooting," or at least make the perpetrator's job a bit harder.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364753042503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:04:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364753122054-19</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Judge speaks out</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364752936784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To guarantee that there would never be another Tucson or Sandy Hook, we would probably have to make it a capital offense to so much as look at a gun. And that would create serious 2nd Amendment, 8th Amendment and logistical problems. So what's the alternative? Bring back the assault weapons ban, and bring it back with some teeth this time. Ban the manufacture, importation, sale, transfer and possession of both assault weapons and high-capacity magazines. Don't let people who already have them keep them. Don't let ones that have already been manufactured stay on the market. I don't care whether it's called gun control or a gun ban. I'm for it. I say all of this as a gun owner. I say it as a conservative who was appointed to the federal bench by a Republican president. I say it as someone who prefers Fox News to MSNBC, and National Review Online to the Daily Kos. I say it as someone who thinks the Supreme Court got it right in District of Columbia vs. Heller, when it held that the 2nd Amendment gives us the right to possess guns for self-defense. (That's why I have mine.) I say it as someone who, generally speaking, is not a big fan of the regulatory state.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364753122054</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364754800605-20</Id><Topic><Title>stay away from Dallas</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1364752106175</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:48:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah one of those home invasion murders some idiot here recently said that "rarely" happen. It's potentially connected with the Aryan Brotherhood movement in Texas Prisons. There was a previous homicide of an officer of the court in that same area, shot in the parking lot of his office building (a courthouse). I don't see any connection to the Colorado case which involved a DIFFERENT Prison gang, whose name I don't remember off the top of my head (it's actually a series of three numbers with some odd significance). All that's different is that instead of Preaching Hate the Aryan Arsewipes have couched there message as "protection" and flagged what they consider "unfair prosecutions of White People" for their attention. Almost always in cases where the system was abused to obtain a conviction. (That I got from someone who is was recently IN prison). I guess that makes them related in a way, but it's not the same gang, it's two different white "protection" groups acting on the same change in policy. They decided that sentences in these states have been jacked so high for many crimes that they're effectively at war with law enforcement.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364754800605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364756239418-21</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Judge speaks out</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364752936784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If they can't kill a bunch of people at the same time with a gun, then they'll just use a bomb instead. If you look around the internet you can find plans for anything up to primitive atomic weapons (assuming you can get a bunch of weird materials). I bought one of those 100rd Beta-C Mags for my HK53, though, and it really IS a bit much for anything but combat. Loading it is even MORE a pain in the rear than a regular 30round mag, and it's ALOT harder to maintain properly (required special oil free lubricants, in fact just putting it in an over-lubricated rifle can cause it to malfunction). Frankly the only reason I got it was that regular HK33/53 magazines were HORRIBLY expensive anyway (I only have a handful for both my 53 and 33, certainly not enough for a single regular infantry load out). If I had my druthers I'd always rather use the mag that was designed to work with the weapon, or at least adapted well to it. I don't want a banana clip hanging down from my Ruger 10/22, it just looks dumb, on the other hand my FS2000 NEEDS 30 round mags in order to be able to easily load and remove them, no matter how many rounds are actually IN the magazine. 30 round and 40 round mags for my M1A are just too cumbersome to believe, so I mostly use 10 round mags to hunt with, and 20 round mags for service rifle competition practice. It all depends on the way the individual firearm was designed. Note I DID get some 30rd extended mags for my FNH FiveseveN, but that was because it gave me another 2" length of grip and help balance the pistol when the suppressor was attached. I want to see if the thing really IS effective out to 300 meters when I get the chance. So far its only seen the 50 yard pistol range. Something about only allowing rifles on the rifle range no matter how far I think I can shoot the little thing.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364756239418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:57:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364756395505-22</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative Judge speaks out</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1364752936784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah like hauling away all the bodies of the idiots that try to enforce it, who must be themselves at the moment of enforcement in violation of the law themselves, raising equal protections clause issues. We the people under the law do not consider ourselves "equally protected" if those resource allocated to police departments cannot also be allocated to us as citizens. Period.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1364756395505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 14:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364757984293-23</Id><Topic><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A friend and coworker took his family for a weekend in Chicago. He is black, an educated professional and a family man. They saw clusters of urban yutes hanging around. They witnessed a guy on a bicycle riding on the street. Without warning, a yute punched the #$%$ out of the man on the bicycle, right in the face.</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1364757984293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 15:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364759212653-24</Id><Topic><Title>Stay away from Chicago.</Title><Username>illinois_failed_welfare_state</Username><Timestamp>1364749942128</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 13:12:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chicago: 2 dead, 20 wounded in weekend gun violence in gangland Chi-raq...Chi-raq ranked dead last in Federal Gun Law enforcement in 2012.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1364759212653</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 15:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364771448985-25</Id><Topic><Title>Freiberg and Petrilli.......</Title><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1364571690210</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:41:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The new guy in charge is slashing employees and non-essential projects. Expect to see related charges in quarterly announcements. The question is, will the market applaud those efforts, or react badly to them?</Msg><Username>gambler099</Username><Timestamp>1364771448985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 19:10:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364771612604-26</Id><Topic><Title>10 YEARS AGO, We Were At $42.10 Per Share...</Title><Username>rogerdonna_1988</Username><Timestamp>1363798724868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-20 12:58:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and that was before the reverse 10:1 split, so it was the equivalent of $421.00</Msg><Username>gambler099</Username><Timestamp>1364771612604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 19:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364774350656-27</Id><Title>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country</Title><Msg>Posted: 03/31/2013 1:36 pm EDT A former adviser of Ronald Reagan has some choice words for George W. Bush. David Stockman, Reagan’s budget director from 1981 to 1985, slammed Bush and his former boss in an op-ed in The New York Times Sunday. Stockman argued in the piece that Reagan’s view on the deficit “created a template for the Republicans’ utter abandonment of the balanced-budget policies of Calvin Coolidge.” “(Reagan’s deficit policies) allowed George W. Bush to dive into the deep end, bankrupting the nation through two misbegotten and unfinanced wars, a giant expansion of Medicare and a tax-cutting spree for the wealthy that turned K Street lobbyists into the de facto office of national tax policy,” Stockman wrote.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364774350656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 19:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364774442613-28</Id><Topic><Title>David Stockman, Ex-Reagan Budget Director: George W. Bush's Policies Bankrupt The Country</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364774350656</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 19:59:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stockman, also a former Republican congressman from Michigan, resigned from Reagan’s administration in 1985 in protest over deficit spending. Bush and Reagan aren’t Stockman’s only targets in the piece; he attacks lawmakers, Federal Reserve and Treasury officials and Wall Street for a combination of easy money and deficit expanding policies that he argues will lead to another Wall Street bubble explosion in the near future. Stockman may have a point when it comes to Bush’s policies, at least. The cost of the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan combined with the Bush-era tax cuts for the wealthy will account for nearly half of the debt the U.S. will owe by 2019, according to a February analysis from the Center on Budget Policy and Priorities, a left-leaning think tank. Bush isn’t the only Republican leader to draw Stockman’s ire in recent months, though. During the 2012 presidential election, Stockman called Republican candidate Mitt Romney “a master financial speculator who bought, sold, flipped, and stripped businesses.” He also attacked Vice Presidential Candidate Paul Ryan’s budget, arguing that it was “devoid of credible math or hard policy choices.”</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364774442613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 20:00:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364785156428-29</Id><Topic><Title>Walmart: America's real 'Welfare Queen'</Title><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1364742390473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 11:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>COSTCO pays their people a minimum of $20/ hour. And offers great healthcare. And they STILL beat Walmart prices !!!!!!!!!!! Liberals rule again.</Msg><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1364785156428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-31 22:59:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>