<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-20"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371703089876-1</Id><Title>Minuteman founder charged</Title><Msg>By David Schwartz PHOENIX | Wed Jun 19, 2013 10:49pm EDT (Reuters) - The co-founder of the Minutemen civilian border patrol group that for several years watched for unauthorized immigrants crossing to Arizona from Mexico, was arrested on Wednesday on suspicion of molesting three young girls. Chris Simcox, 52, who co-founded the Minuteman Civil Defense Corps in 2005, was booked into a Maricopa County jail in connection with the molestation of three girls under the age of 10, said Sergeant Tommy Thompson, a Phoenix police spokesman. Detectives with the department's Family Investigations Bureau developed "probable cause" that Simcox had sexual conduct with the girls during the past several months, Thompson said. No other details were immediately available. Simcox has denied the allegations to police. It was not known if he had an attorney. He faces two counts each of child molestation and sexual conduct with a minor, and one count of attempted child molestation. A former kindergarten teacher from California, Simcox co-founded the border watch group to highlight what he said was the government's failure to secure the porous southwest border with Mexico. Its force of housewives, office workers and veterans sat in lawn chairs in southern Arizona, spotting suspected migrants whom they reported to the U.S. Border Patrol, until the group disbanded in 2010. The U.S. Senate is debating comprehensive immigration reform that aims to tighten security on the border with Mexico while offering millions of illegal immigrants living in the United States a path to citizenship.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371703089876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 00:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371705285998-2</Id><Title>Ain't that ironic!</Title><Msg>NSA Whistleblower Russ Tice Alleges NSA Wiretapped Barack Obama as Senate Candidate</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371705285998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 01:14:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371705581960-3</Id><Topic><Title>Beck: "I wish I could take back everything I said"</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1370638711767</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-06-07 16:58:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>slayerhoneydarling, To see Beck's show on tv you have to pay for it.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1371705581960</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 01:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371731315920-4</Id><Title>so when will Snowden denounce China's aggressive surveillance, hacking &amp; espionage programs?</Title><Msg>why hasn't Snowden denounced China's aggressive surveillance, hacking &amp; espionage programs? . Hey snowden: "there are some two million Chinese spies working with the communist state’s security apparatus".... will you please whine about how unethical that is to them while you are there?......... ".... communiist Party officials do not want to make a big deal out of Snowden, lest it encourage debate about the government's own aggressive domestic programs. "but many attacks originating in China are believed to come from special cyber units belonging to the Chinese military. A recent report by Mandiant, a northern Virginia cybersecurity firm, identified a Chinese military detachment known as Unit 61398 as one of the “most prolific” hacking groups in the world. The military link suggests China considers economic dominance a matter of national defense, raising the stakes for any western firms it targets..................... there are some two million Chinese spies working with the communist state’s security apparatus. The regime has countless agencies engaged in intelligence gathering, including the Ministry of State Security; various military intelligence agencies; multiple industrial, political, and economic espionage departments; and more. Hiding behind “diplomatic immunity” and using blackmail, bribery, special privileges, strategic “business” partnerships, cyber attacks, and a wide array of other methods, China’s spies have been extremely successful in their efforts.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1371731315920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371731632487-5</Id><Topic><Title>ETRADE</Title><Username>finch.kathy</Username><Timestamp>1371662863785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 13:27:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no they play the same game.. if you traded with them you'd know.. I see it all the time on my own trades.. I hope they rot!</Msg><Username>finch.kathy</Username><Timestamp>1371731632487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 08:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371738976839-6</Id><Topic><Title>Good News on a Bad day!</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1371692677526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least we're not cratering despite the entirely stink week. People are starting to look for hidden value, and eTrade had that in spades once real estate started coming back. Now it's hanging quite tough and I shed my hedge at a slight loss as I don't see another massive dip in our future. One earnings and guidance are posted (though I expect them to be conservative) we should be good to go in another year, speculators aside.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371738976839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 10:36:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371739393101-7</Id><Topic><Title>Good News on a Bad day!</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1371692677526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I keep pointing to how negative the street is on the stock with only 1 buy rating and a dozen holds. They spent years reducing the loan book by 70%, the street will start to look at the company in a more favorable light. I was surprised to see they are still in the S&amp;P, thought they would have gotten the boot years ago.</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371739393101</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 10:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371742873455-8</Id><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Msg>just sayin</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371743832237-9</Id><Topic><Title>Good News on a Bad day!</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1371692677526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-06-19 21:44:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They pulled a reverse split to stay listed. It kept the stock price reasonable for the exchange and though it had obvious negative connotations (and still does) it probably made for easier bookkeeping and a less volatile stock. On the down side it also meant they had to prove they could eat whatever losses were coming and still remain a viable business. I thought they had a shot at it so I started buying. It's taken awhile but I think they're just about to hit a point where ever a comparatively mild decrease in defaults will make a significant difference based on the governments current weird formula for provisioning. Once unencumbered the business itself should be very profitable and significantly more valuable than its current market cap suggests.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371743832237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:57:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371746638424-10</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody is selling them to them....Just sayin</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1371746638424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:43:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371746719116-11</Id><Title>Market down 200, ETFC up</Title><Msg>Funny scenes</Msg><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371746719116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371746767739-12</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so did Little Lord Fauntleroy exited - and we've surpassed his dump price in short order. what say you?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1371746767739</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371747789153-13</Id><Title>Options writers trying to screw folks again . . .</Title><Msg>So they have an artificially low bid on the Jan '15 $10 CALLS, top their bid by just alittle and you could end up with those cheap contracts. Right now the spread is 3.15/3.5 last 3.25 . . . a 3.2 limit order might work if someone decides to take quick profits. I'd do it myself but all my operating capital is invested, mostly in eTrade equity and LEAPs.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371747789153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371748463487-14</Id><Topic><Title>Minuteman founder charged</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371703089876</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 00:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>these right wing gun #$%$ are all perverts. We need to take their guns away.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1371748463487</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:14:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371750024755-15</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you think he covered and ran?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371750024755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371750260278-16</Id><Topic><Title>Market down 200, ETFC up</Title><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371746719116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry, it will be down by the end of the day.</Msg><Username>gedownonit24me</Username><Timestamp>1371750260278</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:44:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371750447380-17</Id><Topic><Title>Market down 200, ETFC up</Title><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371746719116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt it, it's shown upward movement at a slow but steady pace all week. The market makers might hammer it tomorrow to make the $12 calls worthless.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371750447380</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:47:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371752520907-18</Id><Topic><Title>Market down 200, ETFC up</Title><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371746719116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>discount brokers get a pretty large percentage of their profits due to short term interest rates....and those rates are now going up! talking heads have been talking about this for a couple of days now and it is starting to reflect in the stock prices of the discounters.</Msg><Username>jjovaz</Username><Timestamp>1371752520907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:22:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371752736396-19</Id><Topic><Title>Options writers trying to screw folks again . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371747789153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now they're getting REALLY greedy with a bid of 3.2 and an ask of 3.7 How much of a spread do these options writers think they can get away with? A spread of over 10% is just plain silly.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371752736396</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:25:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371752819931-20</Id><Topic><Title>Market down 200, ETFC up</Title><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371746719116</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah I'm looking to maybe trim margin in the future because of it. however that'll add to their daily trade average :-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371752819931</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 14:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371755565216-21</Id><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Msg>Thanks to my ETFC position, my portfolio is doing significantly better than the market (although still net down).</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371755933104-22</Id><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Msg>Health Care Plans Under Obamacare Will Cost Even Less Than Expected By Sy Mukherjee A new analysis of health care premiums proposed under the Affordable Care Act concludes that health plans will cost even less than originally expected. That’s likely because the insurance marketplaces will encourage more competition between insurers. Avalere Health looked at insurers&#146; proposed rates for Obamacare’s statewide insurance marketplaces in nine different states, and found that premiums for a 40 year old non-smoker on a mid-level health plan will cost anywhere from a low of $205 (in one Oregon region) to a high of $413 (in one Vermont region). That high-end price is actually lower than what the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) predicted the average mid-level plan cost would be in 2016. Avalere’s report comes with some important caveats: the analysis is limited to 2014 premiums, whereas CBO’s projections deal with 2016 rates. Critics may argue that insurers are offering deceptively low rates to attract consumers in the health law’s first year of implementation, but plan on jacking those charges up once they have a larger customer base. But insurers wouldn’t necessarily be able to do that under Obamacare, since the law subjects any premium hike over 10 percent by insurers selling plans on a marketplace to review. Furthermore, sicker Americans are expected to take advantage of the law’s protections before healthier and younger Americans enter the individual insurance market, meaning that future rate increases could be mitigated by a less costly pool.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371755953848-23</Id><Title>Its odd</Title><Msg>this thing is showing strength last few days.</Msg><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1371755953848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371756181171-24</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brokerages do better with volatility and the expectations of long term rates going up is good for brokerages.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1371756181171</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:23:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371756433105-25</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you look at ETFC's history over the past 5 years, it normally went down GREATER than the broader market on these downdraft days. The action today suggests a major change in sentiment and trend.</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371756433105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:27:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371757109103-26</Id><Title>Catching up to the market</Title><Msg>I think ETFC is hanging because of one big order yet to be filled. It will catch up the the drop before weekend.</Msg><Username>daytradejoe</Username><Timestamp>1371757109103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758224708-27</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371758224708</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371758247701-28</Id><Title>Some New Money Moving In Today</Title><Msg>on above average volume plus look at the volume on SCHW and AMTD - some rotations going on?</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1371758247701</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:57:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758283540-29</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>or put another way, a stock in a profitable company selling for 40% of book value might as well be theft if you're confident in their financials.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371758283540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:58:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758398284-30</Id><Topic><Title>Options writers trying to screw folks again . . .</Title><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371747789153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 13:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone got 20 Jan'15 $10 LEAPS for 3.4 each, just a dime above market makers bid . . . any of you get those 20 cheap contracts?</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371758398284</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:59:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758472144-31</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is investors' flight to quality. Just think a dime here a dime there and before you know it the stock will be back to $600.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1371758472144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758803898-32</Id><Topic><Title>Who knew that ETFC could be a safe haven stock on a major down draft?</Title><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371755565216</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:12:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm thinking that's just a tad more than a trifle optimistic :-) Though it'd be darn nice.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371758803898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:06:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371758882243-33</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You could say that about every stock and option couldn't you. Someone is right and someone is wrong but that was a decent amount of volume in those calls all at premium prices.</Msg><Username>traderbbc</Username><Timestamp>1371758882243</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:08:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371759404260-34</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i think LLF ran his own hedging schemes (as reported in the WSJ) and he used his monster share of common stock as a ballast to control the price. he also had his inside information as a board member and a syndicate of short hedge fund cronies. now he's gone</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1371759404260</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371760609339-35</Id><Title>Love the price action today, up on a crazy down day.</Title><Msg>Once everyone realizes that higher interest rates are actually good news we are going to head towards 20 very quickly.</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1371760609339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371760716711-36</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>$2 BILLION needed to establish, operate Fed. Healthcare exchanges, plus the OBIMBO PLAN won't be able to be implemented in Oct. 2013!!! States are pulling out out of the program including LIBERAL MN!!! Insurance companies will most likely NOT support their programs in LIBERAL CA and no longer underwriting insurance policies!!! Wonder where they going to get insurance - except for the illegals??? ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1371760716711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:38:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371760970404-37</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well at least he left behind a gold mine for people. I couldn't believe it when it was actually trading under $8 for alittle while. I took profits on those temporary positions, but those profits bought me a big pile of LEAPS to hold onto until they go long term. I also have a lump of stock, which I sometimes trade in and out bits of it, the other already being long term . . . Besides, I'm not even close to worrying about long term versus short term my gains have been so pathetic. I've taken like 3500 in realized short term and 500 in realized long term gains net of losses, but I still have unrealized losses on my books that are holding me down. But when I am ready to sell the shares I expect that sale will make me grateful for holding long term rather than repeated short term cycling. If I liquidate the LEAPS and long term position in Jan '15 that alone would generate enough gains that it would push me into a tax bracket that actually required I pay taxes. That would PROFOUNDLY suck. My brokerage account started as a mad money account, and has now grown large enough its actually something to pay attention to more closely than I have in the past.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371760970404</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371761040640-38</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Elvis, Pelvis.....I will say the 18mil shorts are in some trouble right now. When you don't get a chance to cover on a 350 point down day, you have to think hmmm....that and a really good metrics report on Wednesday.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1371761040640</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:44:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371761256195-39</Id><Title>Only green On My Screen</Title><Msg>only stock up today out of about 30 ... Good sign for things to come for e-trade?</Msg><Username>topline1</Username><Timestamp>1371761256195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371761294369-40</Id><Topic><Title>Its odd</Title><Username>buythisdog</Username><Timestamp>1371755953848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:19:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you looked at the bond market carnage? Rates are rising......fast. That has been a death nail for schw, amtd, and etfc.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1371761294369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371761331993-41</Id><Title>Just in!</Title><Msg>Germany - the OBIMBORAMA is not just falling apart here, but also overseas! The speech in Berlin by the anointed one drew a whopping 4500 people versus at his election/campaign speech off over 200000!!! The German SPD (Socialistische Partei Deutschland) has dropped to a follow ship of 20% from 50%!!! OBIMBO the "Leader from behind" is perceived as a week, clueless and a NOT to be trusted mistake!!! OBIMBORAMA will fall apart, already dropping like a rock in the polls! Black Senator from LA just switched from DemocRAT to Republican after he could take no longer the broken, empty promises and lies of OBIMBO - more to follow!!! Take that to the bank - junkie! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1371761331993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:48:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371761454307-42</Id><Topic><Title>Love the price action today, up on a crazy down day.</Title><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1371760609339</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats only 2 bucks pre split, crazy!</Msg><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371761454307</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:50:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371761697755-43</Id><Title>ETFC setting up for a nice pop</Title><Msg>when the markets rebound. imo</Msg><Username>time_s_now</Username><Timestamp>1371761697755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:54:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371761782021-44</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>any SINGLE premium hike over 10%. Does that mean it's limited to 9.9% a year, or 9.9% a quarter, or 9.9% a month, or could they hike rates on a daily basis? All that and more has yet to be written into law. Obamacare was a draft document in unfinished form filled with contradictions, that still has to be legislated into some form of sanity before any of this is even worth discussing. Parts of it are functioning, true, at least the parts that collect money, but other parts have proven to be utterly unworkable, like the insurance for the uninsurable plan that was cancelled 6 months after they started taking applications because they'd already overcommitted their budget by 100%. Theoretically that plan was supposed to run indefinitely. The President has, if nothing else, learned a great deal about the differences between a theoretical ideal universe and the one we live in.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371761782021</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371762012589-45</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lett'em Burn Lett'em Burn! Anyone who shorts a stock of a profitable company trading at near half its book value is, absent other considerations, an idiot. Shorting a stock is one of the few ways on Wall Street to incur theoretically infinite losses.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371762012589</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:00:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371762258711-46</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1371761331993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:48:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Be specific, the dude who switched parties had 1. Switched parties before and 2. Is a STATE Senator, not a national one, hence more of a pop than a bang. 3. If anyone starts to think this is going to start a wave of party conversion among african american's living particularly in the south, they're insane. No matter how religious or conservative they may be, they vote the bloc.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371762258711</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371762397905-47</Id><Topic><Title>Only green On My Screen</Title><Username>topline1</Username><Timestamp>1371761256195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only the only green in my portfolio, but the only green on my company watch list. Scary scary day!! At one point there were NO gainers listed for the DOW % Gainers category in the Research section, though % Losers were WELL represented.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1371762397905</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371763003584-48</Id><Topic><Title>Only green On My Screen</Title><Username>topline1</Username><Timestamp>1371761256195</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:47:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey clgl - I sold most of it around $11.80 and scrambled to get back in with some this morning - not much to lose, but lots to gain if one of the BIG ones decides it's time to buy ETFC, especially now since they become a very stable company! Looks like we are getting your TX heat now after being in the 60s, about 20F below normal and the heater kicking in over night! No transition, ju8st from one extreme to the other! Still holding ING and adding to URZ on the bottom! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1371763003584</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371764654240-49</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OK, its been profitable for 1 whole quarter. Last year was a loss. I will tell who shorts stocks like this, big players and not retail. It is an easy target with no dividend (shorts have to pay the divy) and 5 ceos in the past 3 years. Some might overstay there welcome and that has yet to be seen. Food for thought....If you took a short position here when Freiberg was hired you would still be in the money by about 20%.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1371764654240</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 17:44:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371766909549-50</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nitpicking and obfuscation won't hide the BIG truths about Obamacare: 71 Million Kids &amp; Adults With Private Insurance Have Received No-Cost Preventive Care. “HHS estimates that, as a result of the ACA, 71 million children and adults with private insurance, and 34 million Medicare beneficiaries have received no-cost preventive care. Enhanced federal matching funds in Medicaid are available to states providing all USPSTF-recommended preventive benefits without cost-sharing, but, to date, few states have made the changes required to gain the higher match rate.” “Health Reform-The Affordable Care Act Three Years Post-Enactment,” Kaiser Family Foundation, March 2013.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371766909549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 18:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371768007274-51</Id><Topic><Title>Ain't that ironic!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371705285998</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 01:14:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A rally held by Bloomberg's Mayors Against Illegal Guns stirred up at least one crazed gun nut enough to get himself arrested in Concord, New Hampshire yesterday. Daniel Musso literally got in the face of speaker John Mantin, and later found himself on the wrong side of the law, apparently his second amendment rights superceding the first amendment. At one point after mentioning his deceased daugher, a victim of shooting violence, Mantin asked him to show a little respect, to which Russo responded, “if you had your speech in your mind, you wouldn’t have to read all this propaganda #$%$ in front of you.” New Hampshire has come under increased scrutiny from Bloomberg's group for the pussilanimous vote against expanded background checks by Senator Kelly Ayotte. via WMUR CONCORD, N.H. —Police used an electronic stun gun to subdue a Brentwood man Tuesday night at a gun control rally in Concord. Police use an electronic stun gun to subdue a Brentwood man at a gun control rally in Concord. A News 9 camera was on the scene when officers took 52-year-old Daniel Musso to the ground shortly after he interrupted a speech in favor of expanded background checks for people purchasing guns.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371768007274</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 18:40:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371768475000-52</Id><Topic><Title>They are buying the Oct $13 calls today</Title><Username>pokerpro8222</Username><Timestamp>1371742873455</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 11:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you think he is sitting at home listening to Lynyrd Skynyrd?</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371768475000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 18:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371770570417-53</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Discrimination By Insurance Companies For Children With Pre-Existing Conditions Was Banned. “Coverage exclusions for children with pre-existing conditions were prohibited as of September 23, 2010. Insurers are no longer permitted to deny coverage to children due to their health status, or exclude coverage for pre-existing conditions. Protections for adults will take effect in 2014. In addition, lifetime limits on coverage in private insurance have been eliminated and annual limits are being phased out.” “Health Reform-The Affordable Care Act Three Years Post-Enactment,” Kaiser Family Foundation, March 2013.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371770570417</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371771189869-54</Id><Title>up another 1/2 % after hours?</Title><Msg>is that a misprint?</Msg><Username>gorakrishna</Username><Timestamp>1371771189869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371771531469-55</Id><Title>The search for GOP moderates</Title><Msg>National Review has found several dozen moderate Republicans fighting back against their party's right-wing lurch: The Tuesday Group, a moderate-Republican caucus long ignored within the House GOP, is quietly starting to fight back against the conference’s right turn. In fact, it's so quiet that you basically can't hear them at all. Apparently, there are supposed be 30 or 40 members of The Tuesday Group, but the National Review must have a pretty weird definition of "fight back" because you'd never know it from the evidence they provide. Their first example is of Rep. Steve Womack from Arkansas complaining to Eric Cantor about how the Heritage Foundation is attacking some Republicans for being insufficiently pure. And their second example is of Rep. Charlie Dent from Pennsylvania, who publicly criticized Republicans for holding this week's abortion ban vote. If this is what counts as moderates fighting back ... then the GOP is every bit as nutty as we think it is. In the case of Womack, he was complaining about an external group—nothing inside the House Republican Conference. And in the case of Dent, he did complain about the vote, and he did vote against it—but he was one of only six Republicans to do so, and some of those six voted no because they opposed the rape exception. So much for 30 to 40 members, right? And that leads me to my favorite line from the article: One GOP aide explained to me, “I wish the Tuesday Group were more active. It would help fight the caricature that we are all a bunch of right-wing nutjobs.” Except there's a reason it's not more active. It's because they are a bunch of right-wing nutjobs.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371771531469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1371771699383-56</Id><Title>I'll Praise Ya While I Kiil Ya!....</Title><Msg>You can't make this stuff up!... The Atlanta Journal-Constitution An Atlanta bishop and well known gospel singer was arrested Wednesday afternoon for allegedly taking a gun to Hartsfield-Jackson International Airport. Bishop William Henry Murphy III was carrying a 9 mm handgun in his carry-on luggage, according to the warrant by the Clayton County Police Department. A Transportation Security Administration official allegedly discovered the weapon during an X-ray screening. Murphy does have a license to carry permit, the warrant states. Murphy is the bishop of The dReam Center Church. He also is a prominent gospel singer. His song “Praise is What I Do” has more than 4.5 million views on YouTube. According to the church’s Facebook page, Murphy had just been consecrated from pastor to bishop on Monday. Murphy was charged with misdemeanor possession of a weapon in an unauthorized area. He appeared in court Thursday, where the judge set his bond at $2,500. He could face civil penalties of up to $7,500, according to Channel 2 Action News.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1371771699383</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371772184003-57</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stop with the 'insurance for the uninsurable' like it is some major flaw. it was simply meant as a bridge until the exchanges were up and running in 2014. wow, massive failure, no not really.</Msg><Username>iizconfused</Username><Timestamp>1371772184003</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371772493312-58</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Consumers Received $1.1 Billion in Rebates From Their Insurance Companies. “Insurance companies that don’t spend at least 80 percent of its customers’ premium dollars on health care are required to provide rebates to policy holders. In 2012, the first year this rule was implemented, 12.8 million consumers received $1.1 billion in rebates.” "Health Reform in Action," , accessed 6/5/13.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371772493312</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 19:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371772915447-59</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Foxjunkie has to be the biggest koolaid drinker on the planet... I will bet you he won't be signing up anytime soon.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1371772915447</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371773361842-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3.1 Million More Young Adults Have Health Insurance Through Their Parent’s Plan. "Under the law, most young adults who can’t get coverage through their jobs can stay on their parents’ plans until age 26.” "Health Reform in Action," accessed 6/5/13.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371773361842</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 20:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371785716656-61</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare- news just keeps getting better!!</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371755933104</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 15:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seniors Have Saved More Than $6.1 Billion on Their Prescription Drugs Since 2010 "Seniors who hit the gap in Medicare’s prescription drug coverage, often called the ‘donut hole’ now receive 50 percent discounts on covered brand name drugs. The new health reform law will provide additional savings each year until the coverage gap is closed in 2020.” "Health Reform in Action," accessed 6/5/13.</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1371785716656</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1371785933969-62</Id><Topic><Title>Just in!</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1371761331993</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 16:48:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Again, you display your ignorance. Obama's speech in Berlin was attended by invited guests only. All of the guests were screened and had their backgrounds checked. In regard to the black Democrat who became a Republican I can only say, LA is a progressive bastion and he will not be missed. Turncoats never last very long. rodent, Obama is not dropping like a rock in the polls. He lost less than 2 percentage points and I'm positive he will regain them shortly. Rassmussen poll is always wrong - on purpose.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1371785933969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-06-20 23:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>