<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-15"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360934441707-1</Id><Title>Former customer's evaluation of ETFC</Title><Msg>As a former customer of E-TRADE for the last year, here are my comments and observations: I. Platform strength and ease-of-use.........B+ II. Customer Support..................................A III. Financial Stability..................................C-- (Not clear to me that the mess created from mortgage backed securities has been completely resolved) IV. The rippling effect from executive changes, force reduction and the resulting instability within the firm........C--</Msg><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1360934441707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 08:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360942950877-2</Id><Topic><Title>Former customer's evaluation of ETFC</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1360934441707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 08:20:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mortgage crisis OVER, If Platform B+, CUSTOMER SUPPORT A!!!! and new customers rising, volume up, and selling WAY below book it's a STRONG BUY! Did you notice Merrill Lynch started coverage yesterday with underperform and the stock was up 12 cents and up another penny today. If Merrill can't get the stock down for ONE DAY what's that tell you!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1360942950877</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 10:42:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360943346873-3</Id><Title>Merrill starts ETFC with UNDERPerform STOCK GOES UP!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Merrill Lynch started ETFC with underperform and the stock goes up another 12 cents yesterday and another couple of cents today! I guess I can quote Gordon, " their analysts don't know preferred stock from live stock." Volume up, customers up, housing crisis over, platform and customer service great, great takeover candidate, and selling at way under book vs over 2X for peers, this new merrill analyst should find a new career he'll never make it in this business. When it gets bought out and he still has a sell, he'll say I don't consider takeover value, just rate the fundaments. Unfortunately for him THEY TURNED POSITIVE MONTHS AGO!!!!!!</Msg><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1360943346873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 10:49:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360946144284-4</Id><Topic><Title>Classless act</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1360944515456</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:08:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does the ASPCA know???? We have to see this. Where is the link, ajole? ROFLMAO!!!</Msg><Username>obama_2012_bankrupt_2013</Username><Timestamp>1360946144284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360946488699-5</Id><Title>HAHA I knew jbmaria was lying!</Title><Msg>There are some things even a fake panda will do. No matter how drunk you get him. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHHA!!!!!!</Msg><Username>obama_2012_bankrupt_2013</Username><Timestamp>1360946488699</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:41:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360946533690-6</Id><Topic><Title>Former customer's evaluation of ETFC</Title><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1360934441707</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 08:20:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Far superior to Scottrade by a mile. I give it 50/50 chance that ETFC will be bought out for $20.00 ps.</Msg><Username>mayor3004</Username><Timestamp>1360946533690</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:42:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360954900244-7</Id><Topic><Title>E*TRADE have blocked my account and took my money fore more than TWO WEEKS</Title><Username>tamthi_2005</Username><Timestamp>1360947150002</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 11:52:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe you got caught day trading without enough money in your account.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360954900244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:01:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360955521102-8</Id><Title>Michelle Antoinette, and Berry party on Valentine's Day</Title><Msg>Just saying...Middle Class Warrior Obama’s $900 Valentine’s Day Dinner President Obama took First Lady Michelle out for dinner Thursday night to the restaurant Minibar, possibly the most exclusive joint in Washington. It’s almost impossible to get a reservation – the place seats 12. The dining room includes an open kitchen where you gaze in awe as famed chef Jose Andres cooks you dinner as if you were in his home. “Each bite is an experience to be savored, pondered, and sometimes puzzled over,” asserts the website for the restaurant. Which is nice, since each bite probably costs about $10. That is, the price for tasting approximately 20 small dishes is $225, not including tax and tip, while wine pairings will set you back $75, $120, or $200. If we assume a mid-range $120 for wine, the total comes to $345 per person, or $690 for two. Add in Washington’s 10 percent restaurant dining tax and a 20 percent tip and we’re at $910.80 for dinner. Surprisingly, the Obamas did not go out for any $900 dinners during the presidential campaign.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360955521102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:12:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360955537978-9</Id><Title>We'll Be Going To APRIL 1999 Highs Here. Here's Why:</Title><Msg>E*TRADE Financial Will Become The BIGGEST Bank In The World In My Opinion. Price Today? $11.28 Bye.</Msg><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1360955537978</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:12:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360956358100-10</Id><Title>TPG-Axon held over 6 million etrade shares...</Title><Msg>as of 9/20/12. Sold out all shares in Q4. Fickle bunch those hedge funds.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1360956358100</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:25:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360956590577-11</Id><Topic><Title>What's the Point of the Second Amendment?</Title><Username>stock_trader_00l</Username><Timestamp>1360956082448</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:21:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How silly!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956590577</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:29:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1360956895070-12</Id><Title>Obama's preschool scam</Title><Msg>What this is, is another pay back to the teachers unions for all the exstorsion money thay gave to the Democratic party. Besides we can't afford it! Definition Of A Liberal Is To Take Failed Program And 'Double Down And Make It Universal' KRAUTHAMMER: I find this amazing. First of all, just hearing him say every first grader in America has to be prepared for a high-tech economy, that is a bit early, I think. The other part of this is here we are with $16 trillion in debt, a trillion dollars a year of deficits. We have created already, with under Obama, the biggest entitlement in 50 years. And now he wants to create a new entitlement for preschool for every 4-year-old in the country. The worst part of this, this isn't just any new entitlement. This is an entitlement in an area where we know the $7 billion a year that we spend on Head Start doesn't make any difference after the third grade. There is a study that HHS has done that showed that. So it's failure and yet he wants to double down and to make it universal. That's probably a definition of a liberal.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956895070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:34:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360962353708-13</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's preschool scam</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956895070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:34:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The indoctrination process has been thoroughly studied by the left and it concluded early brainwashing leads to greater success in mindfunking the future entitlement libtarts. NTM the huge kissback Brak is giving his beloved teacher Union.</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1360962353708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360963423660-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's preschool scam</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956895070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:34:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**Heckman told the Wall Street Journal that high-quality programs might appear to be expensive, but those expenses “are not high in terms of the opportunity costs of not doing the programs.”** Oh, like the war on poverty. This is the same old tired argument the left uses to justify useless spending programs disquised as a pay back to the public unions...try to be a little less obvious next time.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360963423660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:23:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360964081190-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's preschool scam</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956895070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:34:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why start at 4 year olds, why not 6 months old...Stalin would be proud of commrade Obama....and you wonder why the founding fathers put in the second amendment.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360964081190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:34:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360965539410-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's preschool scam</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1360956895070</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 14:34:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I raised my own kids...3 of them, out of My own pocket. You did Not help pay for Any of it. Why do I Have to help pay for Daycare of all those that Won't pay for there Own?...</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1360965539410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 16:58:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360971455701-17</Id><Topic><Title>The California Rambo is Going Out in a Blaze!...</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1360705133670</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-02-12 16:38:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Life is just flying along...</Msg><Username>eagles03711</Username><Timestamp>1360971455701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 18:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1360987253173-18</Id><Topic><Title>I thought this was a ETFC board, cut the freakin political #$%$ and post etfc info only!</Title><Username>equityman2002</Username><Timestamp>1360898690144</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-14 22:24:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spend a few minute each time you come here clicking "Ignore" on the political people, the board clears up pretty fast. Also I report abuse with the obvious stockcharts spam. Annoying morons they all are. Long and strong on E*Trade, we need to keep letting the story play out...</Msg><Username>mr_brightside_xy</Username><Timestamp>1360987253173</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-02-15 23:00:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>