<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366352076282-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama nominee admits unemployment numbers are bogus.</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366310551463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:42:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was nothing educational in reeducation camps. How old are you? 12? Know how to Google? Putting yourself in educated category? Quite premature. When jumping in the middle of discussion, try to read the point being made, at least. That helps too.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366352076282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 02:14:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366374616708-2</Id><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Msg>The media does not want to have American people #$%$ at Islamist terrorism.... so they called them Russian.</Msg><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366377962225-3</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you ok with calling the 100 or so USA abortion clinic bombings and murders of 8 in abortion attacks, Christian terrorism? why is it religious zealots are such killers?</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366377962225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 09:26:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366380076846-4</Id><Title>One man surrounded. By an army!</Title><Msg>Where are the liberals asking why they 'need' so many high-capacity weapons? We saw it in California when one deranged ex-cop was surrounded. In Alabama, when one deranged nut was in a bunker. The government does not show up with a .38 or a shotgun. They bring lots of serious weapons and high-capacity magazines. Even though they know it is one guy who will end up perforated like a screen door. Then they ask us why we 'need' to defend our family from possible multiple intruders.</Msg><Username>president_schittstain</Username><Timestamp>1366380076846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:01:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366380805495-5</Id><Topic><Title>Timothy McVeigh 'Al Queda' connection. Nazis are LIBERALS</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366145577464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:52:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't our president hanging around with terrorists like Bill Ayers and questionable figures like Rashid Khalidi? Didn't the left defend this guy with this "guilt by association" nonsense? "Tell me who your friends are, and I will tell you who you are." Who is Ron Paul anyway? The guy who collected few percentage points in Republican primaries?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366380805495</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:13:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366381151524-6</Id><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Msg>Mccain's bombing target was a civilian electric generating station..... run by, you know, civilians... engineers, electricians, technicians, mechanics, front office secretaries..... it was intendened as a terror bombing of the civilian populace, period.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366382740810-7</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By the same token, Clinton was terrorist. He ordered to bomb an aspirin factory in Sudan. Is Harry Truman a terrorist too?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366382740810</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366382848775-8</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is reaching a bit - don't you think ducky?</Msg><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366382848775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:47:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383295380-9</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny you can't see the difference. Do you really think those two Chechen cared exactly who they targeted? Women, children, elders, black, whites, gay, straight, rich, poor, Muslims, Jews, Christians? How many Muslims were buried under WTC rubles? "Crazy rightwing bigots, who hate the government and listen to the fat liars beck and Limbaugh, wait and see, this smells like crack pot rightie hate violence." What happened to your prediction? Now, don't you feel lucky that you were not greeting those marathon runners at the finish line?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366383295380</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383480841-10</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess in your book some terror bombing of civilian targets is special. Mccain just following orders. Like Lt Cally, who never was never jailed for his attacks on civilians. Point being, some are quick to blame one religion....the one THEY hate.......just as they are quick to denounce terrorism.... even while perpetrating terrorism in illegal invasions and occupations........</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366383480841</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366383736382-11</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there you go , McVeigh's cowardly bombing or the lunatic cowardly Christian bombings and murder of doctors, nurses and others in women's health clinics.... are special to you, not as bad as the ones done by the lunatic islamists, right.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366383736382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366384550721-12</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did you miss it that japan declared war on the United States of America? seems to me that self defense is always a justification to fight. Vietnam was not a threat to the USA..... the USA has suffered from its post WW2 murder and meddling.... we paid a terrible price for our murder and meddling in Nam.... and we have paid a terrible price for our murder an meddling in the Mideast... the sooner we leave there the better, same as in se asia.... same as france left their murder and meddling ........ the soon we clear out the better......... but I suppose you think we were right to murder and meddle in nam and the Mideast same as france.......and you are ok with OUR terrorism there........</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366384550721</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366384916592-13</Id><Topic><Title>All these write-off the last 2 qtrs</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366318534568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 16:55:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That question was downgraded by 4 people. Most likely all shorts!</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366384916592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366385188042-14</Id><Topic><Title>just remember etfc never fails to dissappoint</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1366306772388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:39:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dead weight? Just about everyone is gone! CEO, Bank President, VP of Marketing, and COO, and numerous BOD's The new guys will get all the credit but must admit the old guys put in a very good effort cleaning up Mitch's mess. Now the new guys will get all the credit. Personally, will be happy to see this company back on its feet. I am a long satisfied customer and a shareholder.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1366385188042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:26:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366386166597-15</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never said I justify any murder. You're jumping to your own conclusions that fits your narrative. I pointed out that there is difference between someone who gets morally ill watching endless butchering of innocent babies and decides do "justice", and those indiscriminate cold blooded murderers. "Crazy rightwing bigots, who hate the government and listen to the fat liars beck and Limbaugh, wait and see, this smells like crack pot rightie hate violence." If that's not the words of true hate, I don't know what hate is. None of the people you mentioned appealed for murder. But aren't you jumping out of you own skin to make them murderers? That's your narrative. And it's sick.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366386166597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 11:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366387305043-16</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They came here under Bush's nose. All these sleeper cells who are radicalizing youths casually walked across the mexico border after 9/11 and Bush did nothing. We are paying for all of Bush's vacations and golf. He still holds the all time record for vacation days away from his job.</Msg><Username>borderxingbeaner</Username><Timestamp>1366387305043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:01:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366388793209-17</Id><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG) ....... Break out to begin. Don't miss it !!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Don't miss it !!!!!!!</Msg><Username>ubrg_1</Username><Timestamp>1366388793209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366391175873-18</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The youngest one was like 7 years old when Bush gave him his special permission to become a part of American dream. Bush apparently missed jihadist look on his face and forgot to check his terrorist connections, his drawings which showed lots of bomb explosions. Now Obama had whole 4.5 years to prevent the plot. But he never gets the blame. After all, "Osama is dead, Al Quaeda is on the run'. Nothing to worry about!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366391175873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366392271549-19</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was just curious why do you call McCain terrorist, not Lyndon Johnson and JFK? So what about Mr. Clinton bombing civilian sites in Baghdad and aspirin factory in Sudan? What about Obama killing children with drones? Why McCain is the worst terrorist? Didn't he suffer enough in rotten, smelly cells with all his limbs twisted for his terrorist "sins"?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366392271549</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:24:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366392599386-20</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are the one making some kind of distinction between coward and crazy man McVeigh blowing up people, and these two cowards and crazy people and "islamists" blowing up people......and Christian cowards and crazy people blowing up people,......and you do know that cowardly bombs often kill the innocent right?..... These are all acts of cowardly criminal terrorism, you take the cake with your special case for terrorism you approve of and justify.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366392599386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366393233928-21</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(make all the additional points you want to, but I don't see much real difference US bombing of civilians in Nam for our insane reasons or others throwing bombs at us for their insane reasons) Principle IV states: "The fact that a person acted pursuant to order of his Government or of a superior does not relieve him from responsibility under international law, provided a moral choice was in fact possible to him". This principle could be paraphrased as follows: "It is not an acceptable excuse to say 'I was just following my superior's orders'". Previous to the time of the Nuremberg Trials, this excuse was known in common parlance as "Superior Orders". After the prominent, high profile event of the Nuremberg Trials, that excuse is now referred to by many as "Nuremberg Defense". In recent times, a third term, "lawful orders" has become common parlance for some people. All three terms are in use today, and they all have slightly different nuances of meaning, depending on the context in which they are used. Nuremberg principles</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366393233928</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 13:40:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366394589742-22</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You made your point. JFK, Lyndon Johnson, Bill Clinton are terrorist too. Oh! I forgot. Barack Obama dropped few drones on the houses with innocent children in Pakistan.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366394589742</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366394744185-23</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are a good german. and as usual you are OK with the terrorism you like. Bush is a war criminal, same as LBJ......as you point out.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366394744185</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366395352241-24</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great!!! It took quite an effort to pull out from you that LBJ had something to do with Vietnam. Now, say after me: "Clinton and Barack Obama are terrorists as well!"</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366395352241</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:15:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366396989049-25</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only because you are thick headed. I have consistently told you that our decades of murder and meddling in SE Asia and the Mideast were criminal and have cost us dearly. You fools charged in and did another Nam in Iraq and Afghanistan... and if we hadn't been murdering and meddling in the Mideast for decades 911 would have never occurred. And as ususal you are pathetic and a liar to not label Nixon the same , since he invaded Cambodia and Laos and escalated the bombing of civilians in Nam... and don't forget both bushes for their oil wars in the mideast</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366396989049</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 14:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366399592996-26</Id><Title>The far left and bombings</Title><Msg>These type of America haters feel that we need to get bombed so we understand how it feels...with these folks everything always boils down to moral equivalency. Pointing to John McCain's military service as some equivalency to these recent bombings proves the point. Add to that the far lefts new paradigm of "moral relativism", where their is no moral judgment made under any circumstances. How can you have a conversation with some one that is unable to distinquise between good and evil. All that will come of it is a severe headache.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366399592996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:26:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366401009459-27</Id><Topic><Title>Universal Bioenergy Inc. (UBRG) ....... Break out to begin. Don't miss it !!!!!!!</Title><Username>ubrg_1</Username><Timestamp>1366388793209</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 12:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pump and dump Spam.</Msg><Username>resjuda</Username><Timestamp>1366401009459</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366401113029-28</Id><Title>April Expiration</Title><Msg>April expirations putting a wall against gains today</Msg><Username>gonoi2000</Username><Timestamp>1366401113029</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366403276705-29</Id><Title>Provision Outlook for 2013</Title><Msg>Audette comes out and give a range of 50-70 million per quarter for 2013. The first quarter was 43 plus 13 for the settlement or 56 million total for Q1. The next 3 quarters range is 50-70? Nice job working the analyst crowd. Home prices going up is simply not helping this turd.......</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1366403276705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:27:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366403392394-30</Id><Topic><Title>April Expiration</Title><Username>gonoi2000</Username><Timestamp>1366401113029</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 15:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not really. That would be the shorts putting a wall on this thing. 3 upgrades today most from sell or underperform to hold or neutral but still, not a great gain. Shorts never get burned with this stock, they always get a smooth exit if needed.</Msg><Username>billwilliselkins</Username><Timestamp>1366403392394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 16:29:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366405389303-31</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you see no difference between self defense and just plain murder? In other words japan attacked the USA and we defended ourselves..... Vietnam nor Iraq nor Afghanistan never attacked the USA.... just the other way around actually, we were over there murdering and meddling in their countries....and btw. oliver stone is not the first to get the history of USA militarism right.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366405389303</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366405699109-32</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>same as Nixon, Reagan, bush 1 and bush 2.......except Clinton and Obama killed no where near the hundreds of thousands of civilians killed by Nixon's b-52s and the Reagan/bush/bush decades of murder and meddling in the Mideast.....</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366405699109</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 17:08:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366416954622-33</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And BOTH of you guys seem to forget that the laws of armed combat allow a certain degree of collateral damage if the target involved is of strategic or operational value and would normally be considered a valid target (like a power plant, or an aspirin factory that by its nature could be rapidly converted to making anything else requiring simple chemical processes). Civilians are not totally off limits, you just don't go out of your way to kill them. That's the biggest difference between a terrorist and a soldier, aside from a lack of uniforms (though there are so many uniforms now there might as well not be any), the terrorist goes out of his way to avoid hard targets and hit soft ones, while the soldier does it the other way around. Thus while one of our B1B's might roll in on a terrorist encampment and disgorge 12 tons of bombs, those same terrorists would plant half a dozen suicide bombers in a market crowded with holiday worshippers and end up killing more people total. The hard target EXPECTS the airstrike, the soft target expects to be left in peace.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366416954622</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:15:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366417297753-34</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wankerbill is 100% right (Yes, I'm as shocked as you are), the abortion bombers and shooters are terrorists as well, attempting to influence public policy through fear and intimidation and striking at civilians with lethal force. They're every bit as much terrorists as the radical Islamists and for almost exactly the same reason, a belief structure that demands conduct contrary to what is universally accepted and which impacts the freedoms of others.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366417297753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:21:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366417469039-35</Id><Topic><Title>just remember etfc never fails to dissappoint</Title><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1366306772388</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 13:39:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then they'll get their credit when their options vest if they do their jobs right. Meanwhile that should be the only kind of bonus that they can expect. Tie in executive compensation to shareholder wealth growth and while there are issues of temptation to fudge the books, careful auditing produces a more responsive board and executive structure.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366417469039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:24:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366417835621-36</Id><Topic><Title>"Guns Save Lives" ?!</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366310901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe it was the Good Doctor Sigmund Freud who once said, "A fear of weapons is a sign of #$%$ sexual and emotional maturity."</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366417835621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:30:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366419464026-37</Id><Topic><Title>"Guns Save Lives" ?!</Title><Username>crown_11111</Username><Timestamp>1366310901728</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:48:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can depend on these maroons to miss the point every time.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366419464026</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 20:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366419708918-38</Id><Title>Obama gets the Bad Guy</Title><Msg>Big O promised to bring em to justice. He delivers. Got bin Laden ?</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366419708918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 21:01:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366421448279-39</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gets the Bad Guy</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366419708918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 21:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had to declare marshal law on half a state full of pantspeeing libtarts and postpone a sox game..</Msg><Username>slayer98_l</Username><Timestamp>1366421448279</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 21:30:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366426530804-40</Id><Title>30,000 deaths in USA per year, no big deal to gop. (but they charged off to iraq)</Title><Msg>americans have killed about a million Americans with guns in the 30 plus years since Reagan helped saddam in the 80s...............and the gop was 100% for charging off to invade Iraq......but 100% against doing anything about a million Americans killed in gun violence........wow.... no money in that...huh? just the opposite, the money is in gun sales.</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366426530804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366427573227-41</Id><Topic><Title>Obama gets the Bad Guy</Title><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366419708918</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 21:01:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which means you give him credit for getting the job done. That's big of you.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366427573227</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 23:12:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366427794033-42</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell us. If you're making a statement by killing innocent people .................. How is picking your target morally different than picking any target ? Will you have to wait for Rush to get your answer ?</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366427794033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 23:16:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366428165974-43</Id><Topic><Title>The Children of Newtown are Ashamed of Republicans</Title><Username>anotherwingnutloser</Username><Timestamp>1366256949714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-04-17 23:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Ohhhhh, wait, they don't use assault rifles with magazines on deer." One thing I can tell you for certain. Right wing gun nutzos like to take an assault weapon, and reduce a live deer to bite sizes, any chance they get. It's their substitute for sex.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366428165974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 23:22:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>