<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373690736258-1</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right. Zimmerman didn't get fast enough to his car. He was walking toward his car, not running like gazelle. This is why Martin sitting on top and beating his head against concrete is 100% his, Zimmerman's fault. Next time, when some punk on drugs starts beating the hell out of you, make sure you don't resist. Let him finish his job of making beef steak out of you. Or otherwise, you can end up behind bars till the end of your life. So, if you are white, and the punk is black, you better pick up the lesser of 2 evils. Getting permanent brain injury may not be that bad vs sitting in prison cell until almost retirement age. Interesting dilemma.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1373690736258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 00:45:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373693506453-2</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"All the evidence you need — all the evidence the cops needed — is right there in the interrogation they did with him three days after the shooting. The only thing more shocking than what Zimmerman says in the clip, which was released on the internet one year ago, is how little it has impressed the bloviating jerks who dominate the coverage of this trial. Why did he follow Martin, a police officer asks. “These assholes, they always get away,” Zimmerman answers. The officer asks, “What’s behind that?” “These people who victimize the neighborhood,” Zimmerman answers. In Zimmerman’s angry mind, without trial or jury, even after he killed him and learned he was a 17-year-old who was legitimately staying in the complex, Martin was an asshole victimizing the neighborhood. The officer gets a little defensive at this point. “There was an arrest a week ago,” he points out, though it is also a gentle reminder that Zimmerman’s fear might be a tad misplaced. He continues, skeptically. "How was he running?" Zimmerman describes it and the officer says, “Sounds like he was running to get away... you jumped out of car to see which way he was running? That’s not fear … it’s going to be a problem.” Then Zimmerman whispers something. “What is that you whispered?” the officer asks. “Fucking what?” “Punks,” Zimmerman says.</Msg><Username>q4dike</Username><Timestamp>1373693506453</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 01:31:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373696150822-3</Id><Topic><Title>Option Question for Board Members.</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1373599111607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 23:18:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Similarly I bought Jan '15 $10 calls, and they're trading approximately with the stock with some narrowing of the premium due to them going FURTHER into the money. The deeper into the money the less the time premium matters, and the less leverage you get . . . it's a tradeoff.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373696150822</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 02:15:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373720326289-4</Id><Topic><Title>Option Question for Board Members.</Title><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1373599111607</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-11 23:18:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you Gora and Fubar. That was very helpful. I started to use options because I was getting margin calls at the worst times. Now with Options I keep less margin (bad for E-Trade) and can hold thru the downdrafts. I look back in hindsight and realize I would have avoided my most financial disaster using options. I held a large position in a company that went Bankrupt. If I held the same position in options I would have only lost the option costs of around 10%. Live and learn I guess. I also learned from this past downturn that I should not be afraid to trade options. Since they are leveraged you can lose a lot very fast as well. This insightful on topic discussion got 6 thumbs down. Go figure on this political board.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1373720326289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 08:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373723630770-5</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Shorty: Kenny ain't gonna hurt no woman. But he's gonna hurt you.</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373662869042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 17:01:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>real bad.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373723630770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373723923180-6</Id><Title>Hey Shorty: Increases In Home Values</Title><Msg>happening all over.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373723923180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:58:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373723973157-7</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Shorty: Increases In Home Values</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373723923180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i know one home in hawaii that is definitely going up in value.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373723973157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373726997222-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hey Shorty: Increases In Home Values</Title><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1373723923180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 09:58:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you President Obama. 2014 will be a great year. Obama will be handing a strong economy over to Hillary. Pubs will continue to whine and bleat, and invent scandals that don't exist.</Msg><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373726997222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 10:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373731581892-9</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remind me please, what was the reason for Trayvon#$%$ Zimmerman's head against concrete? If Trayvon was running from someone, he would run up to his house where he would be 100% safe, and go on with his life like everyone else. Instead he stopped, spent several minutes on the phone with his girl friend, after that confronted Zimmerman with punch in the nose. He was moving away from his home, not toward safety, but to confront Zimmerman. Was that Zimmerman's fault? Trayvon had nothing on his body pointing out that he was even touched. Always pick up a part of the story you want, like other details are insignificant. Is that how our justice system supposed to work these days?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1373731581892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373733573433-10</Id><Topic><Title>Snowden Voted Republican</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373677729205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-07-12 21:08:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Failure is the only thing republicans understand. And traitors. Traitors like biddermon want to short America.</Msg><Username>methuserlaw</Username><Timestamp>1373733573433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 12:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373738812208-11</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It looks like the right wing now is now willing to stand for any murderer. If a killer says he's not guilty, wingnutz will agree. And if the murderer kills a black child, he's a hero.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373738812208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373740809595-12</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Can't find more stereotypical response? Sorry. I was just trying to help raising your IQ. You resist.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1373740809595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 14:40:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373744028221-13</Id><Title>My neighborhood has a Neighborhood Watch</Title><Msg>What they do is watch. If they see something suspicious, we are not shy. We don't say, "I do not want that stranger to think I am nosy." We go get a good look and ask him where they are going. If the stranger was thinking about committing a crime, they know that someone is watching and can identify him. We don't apologize for keeping our neighborhood safe. That is for pansies.</Msg><Username>ismith251</Username><Timestamp>1373744028221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 15:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373747336263-14</Id><Title>Screaming republicans on Fox news are a drag says gop rep</Title><Msg>GOP Rep: Republicans Have to Stop Screaming on Fox News Rep. Adam Kinzinger (R-IL): “When you try to talk to the American people, and try to bring our vision, that Reagan vision of a ‘shining city on a hill,’ but you’re doing it screaming on Fox News Channel all the time, screaming and yelling on all these cable news channels and being angry, you’re not drawing Americans to your vision. Instead, what you’re doing is showing anger,”</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1373747336263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373747483617-15</Id><Title>Martin would be alive if Neighborhood Watch had been followed</Title><Msg>"It should be emphasized to members that they do not possess police powers and they shall not carry weapons or pursue vehicles," the manual states. "Members should never confront suspicious persons who could be armed and dangerous." USAonWatch</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1373747483617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:31:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373748169984-16</Id><Topic><Title>Martin would be alive if Neighborhood Watch had been followed</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1373747483617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:31:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>National Sheriffs' Association forgot to make the most important rule. If you live in white neighborhood, find some black people for Neighborhood Watch, you are not supposed to be white for that. Big NO-NO! So, good luck watching!</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1373748169984</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373748327899-17</Id><Topic><Title>Americans should kiss Obama's feet for..</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372876741382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**May all the crackhead who belittle his good name... Die** It's nice to see all the tolerance coming from the far left. I notice since Obama's poll numbers are tanking you boys are even getting more dopy and desperate in trying to make a silk purse out of a sow's ear...I am sure you thought OJ was innocent, that would be consistent with your train of thought. Do yourself a favor and go outside and get some fresh air.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373748327899</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 16:45:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373755495705-18</Id><Topic><Title>Americans should kiss Obama's feet for..</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372876741382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And more than doubled the national debt, and more than tripled the average annual deficit. A "recovery" achieved by borrowing isn't a recovery, it's called digging yourself deeper into debt. But hey, as long as those sucker countries out there don't know that the Federal Reserve is actually a corporation hired by the government to circulate a "reserve" currency and that this company can go bankrupt at any time without ill effect on the government, they'll keep buying Federal Reserve debt . . . Until of course the Federal Reserve can't pay the vig and they go under. Then we just hire another company, even if the government has to create it, to circulate our NEXT "reserve" currency. Probably one currency per state in the Union.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373755495705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:44:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373755562205-19</Id><Topic><Title>Americans should kiss Obama's feet for..</Title><Username>indie103_ca</Username><Timestamp>1372876741382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-07-03 14:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yepper, preferably in a pit under a very large boulder.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373755562205</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:46:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373755698008-20</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think buying the Judge was enough. So far her rulings alone have been enough for an appeals court to grant a new trial, thereby kicking the bucket down the road for the next judge to deal with and hopefully relieving racial tensions simply by sacrificing the life of that "white hispanic" on the alter of black denial. By the time he's finally acquitted on appeal they'll have moved on to something else to deny.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373755698008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373755937448-21</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's how the entire liberal subculture works today . . . ignore the facts, go with what "feels right". Unfortunately most liberals have all the moral compass of a house cat. You can point out their errors consistently, and like most house cats, they believe their primary error was getting caught.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373755937448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:52:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373756125390-22</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trayvon . . . NOT a child, at his age I'd already joined the military. I also could have wiped the floor with that overweight slug Zimmerman without a great deal of effort. But I was still in High School, and even without getting suspended for fighting and doing drugs and even without the skipping cl#$%$ to get some Purple Drank with my homies, I certainly wouldn't have considered jumping some clown and beating the hell out of him for hurting my feelings to be appropriate. Unless maybe the guy was a "crazy #$%$ cracker", which of course makes EVERYTHING different.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373756125390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 18:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373761568608-23</Id><Topic><Title>Zimerman says the thug was beating hm up</Title><Username>dumb_as_an_ashtray</Username><Timestamp>1372964922569</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-07-04 15:08:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Yahoo will actually allow me to post this URL under their new rules . . . http://news.yahoo.com/not-guilty-beyond-reasonable-doubt-070000611.html You who think Zimmerman guilty would do well to read it and try to answer ANY of the questions posed as to the physical evidence supporting in its entirety Zimmerman's story. I grew up in a law enforcement household, and before I was 15 I understood that NO ONE can improvise a false story that absolutely matches the physical evidence when interrogated at the scene. There are almost ALWAYS serious inconsistencies that cause them to begin to re-build their story again and again until the entire thing unravels. Now if you DELAY the interrogation then they might be able to pull something together, but something like this, with an on scene and later interrogation that while narrated in slightly different words matched the previous interrogation completely in every factual manner . . . Frankly Zimmerman doesn't strike me as being nearly that clever, or the kind of a person who'd have the guts to LET someone get in close and repeatedly beat him just to justify a shooting.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1373761568608</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 20:26:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373768696715-24</Id><Title>Not GUILTY!!!!!!</Title><Msg>JB....WILL BE Protesting!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373768696715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373770051683-25</Id><Topic><Title>Not GUILTY!!!!!!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373768696715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>convicted of manslaughter!</Msg><Username>bypartisan305</Username><Timestamp>1373770051683</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:47:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373770321378-26</Id><Topic><Title>Not GUILTY!!!!!!</Title><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373768696715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:24:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As Usual.... All you got is LIES!!!!!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373770321378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 22:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373772546232-27</Id><Title>Al Sharpton.........</Title><Msg>.....stick it up your black racist A$$$ with your precluded slander verdict on Zimmerman! Latest score from ancient Rome: Lyons 12 - Christians NOTHING! Latest score from Florida: Concealed carries 12 - Hoodies NOTHING! OBIMBO needs to apologize for his precluded RACIST statement after the shooting! Jessie Jackson was smart enough to realize his racist statements and reversed course - he was smart enough to predict the out come! ANY uproar, riots, etc. by black activists, especially by black panthers should be met with fire power by authorities!!! THE LAW IS THE LAW!!! ROWDY (Cheers erupted in the WI bar we were in, just about to finish a beer after our great North Shore Trip to Duluth, MN!)</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1373772546232</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 23:29:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373773695630-28</Id><Title>HEY JB!....Wassa Matter?....</Title><Msg>Are you consulting your "Sources" on how to React?... Well let me Tell you how We are going to react... WE are going to be Armed and Ready for ANY and ALL of the Racial Incitements that You and your "Sources" can stir Up! BRING it ON you confused social misfit!....WE are Ready for you!</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1373773695630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-07-13 23:48:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>