<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-08"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365394469861-1</Id><Topic><Title>Sensitivity Training...............</Title><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365183589422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-05 13:39:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rodent, Do you know how absolute crazy you are? Please get help because you are mentally ill.</Msg><Username>dems_win</Username><Timestamp>1365394469861</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 00:14:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365407107350-2</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kofi Annan who authorized to shred thousands of documents to cover up for corrupted oil-for-food program? Yeah. Starving Iraqis to death to give some dirty money to handful of countries. UN and Kofi was right in the middle of it. Annan who resigned in disgrace? That one said Iraq invasion was illegal? Oh! That gives it a lot of credibility! Thanks.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365407107350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 03:45:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365409316941-3</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Mom Threatened by Dumbo</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365362544522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:22:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"And I don’t appreciate everybody going to bed and going to sleep and not taking care of the guys that they put in harm’s way, one of them being my son". That would be Commander in Chief she is talking about? Doesn't she know he really deserved some rest from campaigning? You know, he had to go to Vegas the next day for money! Who is this woman to have an opinion anyway?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365409316941</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 04:21:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365432168852-4</Id><Title>7 CEOs in 5 years</Title><Msg>all very overpaid failures........the wonders of public companies in America. Whether they succeed or fail, the execs all come out winners.</Msg><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1365432168852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:42:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365435068600-5</Id><Topic><Title>7 CEOs in 5 years</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1365432168852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never understood this...strange...it seems like a scam "in my opinion"...this and many other companies...good ol boy network where everyone gets a piece of the action...really all you need is a 500K level executive who may not even be in the industry and hires 300K executives who are experts in the industry who helps him/her out. I dislike Obama policies / liberal policies but there needs to be a major overhaul on how "public" not private companies operate...</Msg><Username>roblordie</Username><Timestamp>1365435068600</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 11:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365436347994-6</Id><Topic><Title>7 CEOs in 5 years</Title><Username>cjclink3</Username><Timestamp>1365432168852</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 10:42:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>exactly they just keep skimming the profits with the so called management they keep shuffling around. I wonder who gets the payola? IMHO keep from showing any real profit</Msg><Username>roadtoad25</Username><Timestamp>1365436347994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 11:52:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365440495703-7</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Mom Threatened by Dumbo</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365362544522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:22:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ignored. Oh, I think you meant "you're" -- talk about dumbo.</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1365440495703</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 13:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365440548206-8</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs Cave on Illegal Immigration !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365389247344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, they're selling their principles for votes.</Msg><Username>mybmw49</Username><Timestamp>1365440548206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 13:02:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365441948339-9</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs Cave on Illegal Immigration !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365389247344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, some, as in most of those from Texas, actually LIKE some illegal immigration, as long as it's challenging enough that we filter out the losers. Those who manage to make it across despite all we can do to keep them out are worth having, as long as we DO make an effort, of course, to keep them out. It's only the Wilsonian Democrats in Arizona that have a hard on for illegal immigration, and those people in mostly non-immigrant states who think "they" have to "pick up the tab", and never mind that most safety net programs are state funded and administered, and that they also "pick up the discount" at the grocery when they buy fresh farm produce and other goods largely harvested by migrant workers, many of whom "lack proper documentation". The most telling sign of Obama's failure was when the Mexicans started sneaking BACK south across the border DESPITE a drug war going on.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365441948339</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 13:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365445121605-10</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you and bush are both liars and have the same brain power it seems, all you do is "brain fart" and lie....Gen Zinni, mid east expert and frm commandant of the Marine Corps called W's Iraq invasion a "brain fart"......the .Pope called it illegal and immoral and so did the UN... and still no matter all YOUR lies and brainfarting, the liar bush LIED big time as I have shown and as everyone knows.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365445121605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 14:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365446713511-11</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs Cave on Illegal Immigration !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365389247344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>clgl............sounds like you got yourtself a nice spread in TX??? The only time I spent in TX was when I got an assignment at then Biggs Air Field, Ft. Bliss (El Paso) with our NATO Squad - F104Gs and later as I worked for a large company I retired from in 1996, flying all over the country/world! I also flew into Dallas, San Antonio, Houston and also Austin, where we have a huge Center now, the company with many other like IBM etc. decided to leave MN because of taxes, even so we had a excellent work force here! Good trading, ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1365446713511</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 14:45:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365452053663-12</Id><Topic><Title>Repubs Cave on Illegal Immigration !</Title><Username>radionazi4morons</Username><Timestamp>1365389247344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 22:47:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's a starter spot. I bought it when I liquidated most of my stocks in mid 2007 along with some other non-stock investments. It's got a tenant on a 1 acre subdivision for now, but that's good because she keeps an eye on the rest of the land, and I armed her so she could run off intruders. I served at Bliss from 80 to 82 and learned to appreciate Texas quite a bit. When I was working at MIT I had a job offer to join a startup here, so I took it and left my secure Institute position for the uncertain world of private industry. Then my MS got bad enough I couldn't work under any reasonable circumstances anymore so I had to give it up. If I'd stayed at MIT I'd probably be on their long term disability program instead of SSDI, as my former employers bothered with no such policies.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1365452053663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:14:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365453168748-13</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>- George W Bush and Pope had frank discussions about Iraq. Pope John Paul never called war in Iraq illegal, despite his opposition to invasion. The word illegal doesn't have meaning in religious terms. - General Zinni is one among many Middle East experts. Why don't you refer to Gen. Tommy Franks? Because he has different opinion? All that though has nothing to do with your point about "Bush lied". The quote you give was from June 14, 2003 WH press briefing with reporters. It wasn't official WH statement. To say that inspectors were not allowed in, couple months after whole world saw the spectacle of them running around Iraq for several months is ludicrous. You can't lie about something everyone knows as a fact. Instead of looking for clarification of what has been said the left wing press immediately calls Bush a liar, disregarding all previous official WH statements that led to invasion. So, this quote is used to feed people with no shred of brain to absorb without proper digestion. It is sick to watch how people's reputation is being destroyed with utter disregard to any previous records, just based on few words, most of the time taken out of context. And you are a perfect player in this game. A parrot.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365453168748</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365453521465-14</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vatican Strongly Opposes Iraq War Published March 12, 2003 Associated Press VATICAN CITY – Pope John Paul II and top Vatican officials are unleashing a barrage of condemnations of a possible U.S. military strike on Iraq, calling it immoral, risky and a "crime against peace." The unwavering stance has made the pope one of the most visible opponents of war in current circumstances, and a rallying point for peace groups and politicians who seize on his words counseling against war.</Msg><Username>delucks345</Username><Timestamp>1365453521465</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:38:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365454397574-15</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The quote you give was from June 14, 2003 WH press briefing with reporters. It wasn't official WH statement." What? A WH press briefing IS an official statement.</Msg><Username>iizconfused</Username><Timestamp>1365454397574</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 16:53:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365455722452-16</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what I am saying. You are easily spoon fed. A perfect target for Obama statists. They strive on public illiteracy. Hey! How long does it take to learn what official statement is?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1365455722452</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 17:15:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365456495892-17</Id><Topic><Title>One of the biggest, deadliest of W's Iraq lies:</Title><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365255128831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-06 09:32:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you ever see the Pope recant the Vatican statement that W's Iraq war is immoral. Nope....and illegal too as per the UN......and a "brainfart" per Gen Zinni, Mideast expert and frm commandant of the Marine Corps. Next you will be saying W did find the wmd behind the curtains in his office where he looked, and if he looked really hard he would have found the N. Korean wmd too.... and the heads up memo he said he ignored , the one entitled "bin laden determined to strike the USA". On August 6, 2001, the Bush administration received a President’s Daily Brief entitled “Bin Laden Determined to Strike U.S.” Here’s how the Bush administration reacted, according to the 9/11 Commission report: [President Bush] did not recall discussing the August 6 report with the Attorney General or whether Rice had done so.[p. 260] We have found no indication of any further discussion before September 11 among the President and his top advisers of the possibility of a threat of an al Qaeda attack in the United States. DCI Tenet visited President Bush in Crawford, Texas, on August 17 and participated in the PDB briefings of the President between August 31 (after the President had returned to Washington) and September 10. But Tenet does not recall any discussions with the President of the domestic threat during this period. [p. 262] Rice acknowledged that the 9/11 Commission report is the authoratative source on this debate: “I think this is not a very fruitful discussion. We’ve been through it. The 9/11 commission has turned over every rock and we know exactly what they said.”</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365456495892</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 17:28:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365457340444-18</Id><Title>Iraq invasion was illegal and immoral</Title><Msg>W and crew went to the UN to get legal authorization for war but never got it. Hence the invasion was illegal. And is was immoral because their was no threat to the USA from Iraq, it was not a matter of self-defense, it was just plain w and crew trumping up a crock of lies. The UN said the invasion is illegal, only the security council can authorize war. the Vatican said the invasion was illegal and immoral. Gen Zinni, mid east expert, and fmr commandant of the marine corps called it a "brain fart". W was just another vain glorious lout like lt col custer who also charged out the gate like a fool and got a lot of people killed for nothing.</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365457340444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 17:42:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365458166606-19</Id><Title>Gerbil invasion is illegal and immoral</Title><Msg>You Pink Bath House scrubbers in a Dress should realize that!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365458166606</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 17:56:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365458243898-20</Id><Title>John Paul II vehemently opposed the IraW's iraq invasion</Title><Msg>John Paul II &amp; the Iraq War John Paul II was very vocal about the Iraq war and seriously condemned it. There were some Conservative Catholics residing in America who tried to reason with John Paul 2 that the invasion of Iraq was not an immoral act but a sensible idea. However, no amount of justification could convince him otherwise. He vehemently opposed the Iraq war and even appealed to the President of the US, George W. Bush to avoid taking such a step. on the 13th of January, 2003 .......Paul II upheld the view that the United Nations should take the route of diplomacy to solve the concerned international conflict and opting for war means violating the international code of law. In another such address on the 16th of March, 2003, the Pope further commented on the Iraq scenario. He stressed on the importance of working for peace with responsibility and maintained that all alternatives have still not been considered.... Unfortunately, two days later, the Iraq war started on the 18th of March, 2003. John Paul ii continued to oppose it..... A Rift Over Iraq Between President and Pope The Vatican and the White House have disagreed over the war In March 2003, just hours after the first American cruise missiles slammed into Baghdad, the Vatican proclaimed the nascent conflict a "defeat for reason and for the gospel." It was a war, said papal confidant Cardinal Roberto Tucci, that was "beyond all legality and all international legitimacy." Strong words coming from the clerical leaders of some 1.5 billion Roman Catholics and indicative of the rift that still dogs relations between the president and the pope</Msg><Username>luckyskywaltzer</Username><Timestamp>1365458243898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 17:57:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1365458434827-21</Id><Title>Saddam bought the UN. (Corrupto#$%$)</Title><Msg>Blood for Oil scam done by that stupid evil Koffi Anan and the UN. Billioons spent on Bribes So sick!!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365458434827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 18:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1365458534494-22</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi Mom Threatened by Dumbo</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365362544522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-04-07 15:22:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jail Dumbo now!</Msg><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1365458534494</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-04-08 18:02:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>