<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-02-03"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359902085613-1</Id><Topic><Title>-= =- Major ETFC Pre Promotion Report (LEAKED!!!!) -= =-</Title><Username>fosterjoseph487</Username><Timestamp>1359407914135</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-01-28 16:18:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I subscribed. Good report.</Msg><Username>craigsmith345</Username><Timestamp>1359902085613</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 09:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359904265638-2</Id><Title>Was Jessie Ventura in Texas?...</Title><Msg>GLEN ROSE, Texas (AP) — Former Navy SEAL and "American Sniper" author Chris Kyle was fatally shot along with another man Saturday on a Texas gun range, a sheriff told local newspapers. Erath County Sheriff Tommy Bryant said Kyle, 38, and a second man were found dead at Rough Creek Lodge's shooting range west of Glen Rose, according to the Fort Worth Star-Telegram and Stephenville Empire-Tribune. Glen Rose is about 50 miles southwest of Fort Worth. Bryant did not immediately return phone calls to The Associated Press seeking comment late Saturday and early Sunday. A woman who answered the phone at the lodge where the shooting occurred declined comment and referred calls to the sheriff's office. Investigators did not immediately release the name of the second victim, according to the newspapers. Witnesses told sheriff's investigators that a gunman opened fire on the men around 3:30 p.m. Saturday, then fled in a pickup truck belonging to one of the victims, according to the Star-Telegram. The newspapers said a 25-year-old man was later taken into custody in Lancaster, southeast of Dallas, and that charges were expected. Lancaster police did not immediately return calls for comment. The motive for the shooting was unclear. Kyle wrote the best-selling book, "American Sniper: The Autobiography of the Most Lethal Sniper in U.S. Military History," detailing his 150-plus kills of insurgents from 1999 to 2009. Kyle was sued by former Minnesota Gov. Jesse Ventura over a portion of the book that claims Kyle punched Ventura in a 2006 bar fight over unpatriotic remarks. Ventura says the punch never happened and that the claim by Kyle defamed him. Kyle had asked that Ventura's claims of invasion of privacy and "unjust enrichment" be dismissed, saying there was no legal basis for them. But a federal judge said the lawsuit should proceed. Both sides were told to be ready for trial by Aug. 1.</Msg><Username>lackofzzzzzz</Username><Timestamp>1359904265638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 10:11:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1359912515752-3</Id><Title>engineered inflation and cap gaisn tax increase makes stocks generational loser</Title><Msg>Lets say you buy a stock for $1000. You picked well and the share price appreciates 7% a year, for seven years. HOME RUN in today's economic environment. Your shares are now worth $1,606. You sell the shares and pay capital gains tax on the gain plus Obama's health tax. Now you have $1,364. Inflation runs 3.5% a year, and due to insane printing of worthless paper money infaltion may roar during the next seven years but we will ignore that, so the buying power of that $1,242 in current buying power adjusting for capital gains tax and government designed 3.5% inflation is really $1,071. After brokers fees you have less money in seven years than when you started. And that is if you are a great stock picker and win big, nobody reading this is. Because of Obama's tax regime and Obama's wild printing of new paper it is physically impossible to make a real return in the stock market using idealized assumptions, on a real risk adjusted basis anybody with any money in the stock market is totally screwed. The combination of a high capital gains tax applied to fictional, and government engineered, nominal inflationary gains is the biggest theft of wealth in all time. Bonds are much, much worse in the current tax and print environment, every bond of every type is nothing but a certificate of confiscation. There is no place to hide and this train is on the track</Msg><Username>durdoc2000</Username><Timestamp>1359912515752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 12:28:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1359925828919-4</Id><Topic><Title>engineered inflation and cap gaisn tax increase makes stocks generational loser</Title><Username>durdoc2000</Username><Timestamp>1359912515752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 12:28:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure there is a way to make money on this train wreck, just buy a small farm and enjoy the fruits of ur own trees..</Msg><Username>rkmtt</Username><Timestamp>1359925828919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-02-03 16:10:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>