<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-07-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373987233914-1</Id><Title>Free OJ</Title><Msg>I understand that Holder is looking into if he can file a civil rights charge because the Las Vegas jury and prosecutor were racist, thus clearing the path for a new trial for the double murderer. This injustice can not stand!</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373987233914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:07:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373990235861-2</Id><Title>GOP policing uteri</Title><Msg>Tue Jul 16, 2013, 09:29 AM USA/ET - Edit history (1) The party of fiscal responsibility is hard at work policing uteri in North Dakota: North Dakota already has spent more than $52,000 defending the 2011 state law, according to records obtained by The Associated Press. Records show that Dr. Donna Harrison, the president the American Association of Pro-Life Obstetricians and Gynecologists, has billed the state more than $49,000 to act as an expert witness. In his ruling Monday, Corwin was highly critical of Harrison, saying her “opinions lack scientific support , tend to be based on unsubstantiated concerns and are generally at odds with solid medical evidence.” The AAPLOG is all for trans-vaginal ultrasound, against insurance paying for contraception, and against Plan B. They think abortions cause breast cancer, cerebral palsy and a host of other ills, and they think the jury is out on whether having an IUD or taking the pill is committing abortion. I’d suggest checking their find a physician page to make sure your or your family member’s OB/GYN isn’t a cult member. More from the ND article: N.D. judge: 2011 abortion law unconstitutional A 2011 North Dakota law that outlaws one of two drugs used in nonsurgical abortions violates the state and U.S. constitutions, a state judge ruled Monday. After a three-day trial in April, East Central Judge Wickham Corwin said he'd rule in favor of the state's sole abortion clinic, calling the 2011 state law "simply wrongheaded." Corwin officially ruled on the case Monday. One abortion clinic for the whole state, and the state government is using public money (to pay unethical doctors to lie) to try to shut it down.</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1373990235861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 11:57:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373995397805-3</Id><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Msg>This is the reason nobody with any intellectual integrity buys this phony outage about the Zimmerman trial. The wholesale violence being perpetrated against blacks by other blacks is an American tragedy...and where are the race hustlers? No rides on Air force One for the parents of these children, nothing in it for the left. to profit from politically or financially. And what is the response from the White African at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue...another round of golf. Four Children Gunned Down in Chicago During Zimmerman Trial In the 20-day period of the George Zimmerman trial, four minors, three teens and a five-year-old boy were gunned down in Chicago.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1373998441340-4</Id><Title>Another bogus GOP scandal</Title><Msg>"There is no evidence President Obama used the Internal Revenue Service to target his political enemies, according to Sen. Roy Blunt (R-Mo.), a member of the GOP's Senate leadership team. "Presidents have always been very careful about maintaining the appearance of keeping hands off the IRS," Blunt told The New York Times."</Msg><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373998441340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1373998637475-5</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they take care their own.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1373998637475</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374003888981-6</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't forget the "The wholesale violence being perpetrated against " whites by other whites......... of all white murder victims, 83% were murdered by white people....... which goes to show you that if you are white and worried about getting murdered you should profile whites, since they are most likely to murder you.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374003888981</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>14</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374004297515-7</Id><Topic><Title>Another bogus GOP scandal</Title><Username>foknewsjunkie</Username><Timestamp>1373998441340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 14:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OBIMBO is a lying piece of #$%$! ROWDY</Msg><Username>rowdyrodent_1995</Username><Timestamp>1374004297515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374004605636-8</Id><Title>where is the outrage: most murder victims are killed by a family or friend or acquaintance, &amp; whites ARE MOSTLY murdered by WHITES</Title><Msg>the racists here are so moronic, really. It is a fact that of all white murder victims, 83% were murdered by white people. so, you white racists who worry about getting murdered ARE profiling WHITES, right? You know, the ones FAR more likely to murder you.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374004605636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374005136907-9</Id><Topic><Title>where is the outrage: most murder victims are killed by a family or friend or acquaintance, &amp; whites ARE MOSTLY murdered by WHITES</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374004605636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said anything about profiling? I don't understand the point you seem to be trying to make.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374005136907</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374005189106-10</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>**which goes to show you that if you are white and worried about getting murdered you should profile white** Typical liberal response, pointing to other bad behavior to justify this behavior. I think we can agree that it is safer in white districts, right? Lets check the facts, shall we... 1.The incarceration rate in state or federal prison or jail for men was 1,384 per 100,000 residents, for women 134 per 100,000 residents. The rate for white men was 736 per 100,000, for black men 4,789 per 100,000, for Hispanic men 1,862 per 100,000. The rate for white women was 94 per 100,000, for black women 358 per 100,000, and for Hispanic women 152 per 100,000. 2.Of the 249,400 state prison inmates serving time for offenses at yearend 2004, 112,500 (45.1%) were black, 51,800 (20.8%) were Hispanic, and 65,900 (26.4%) were white.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374005189106</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:06:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374005724508-11</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can spout off all you want and it doesn't change the fact that a white is far more likely to be murdered by a white person. Sorry, but that is just a fact. 83% of murdered whites were murdered by a white person. fbi Expanded Homicide Data Table 6 Murder Race and Sex of Victim by Race and Sex of Offender, 2009 [Single victim/single offender] White victims 3,518 Race of offender white 2963 black 454</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374005724508</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374005943176-12</Id><Topic><Title>where is the outrage: most murder victims are killed by a family or friend or acquaintance, &amp; whites ARE MOSTLY murdered by WHITES</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374004605636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>c'mon........ the racists here go to great lengths to prove they are justified in profiling blacks for self defense purposes........... but they are, of course, irrational as over 80% of white murder victims were murdered by whites.......</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374005943176</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:19:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>13</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374006406762-13</Id><Topic><Title>where is the outrage: most murder victims are killed by a family or friend or acquaintance, &amp; whites ARE MOSTLY murdered by WHITES</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374004605636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wasn't profiling but it sure seems that is your intent. You sure are sounding racists.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374006406762</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374006740374-14</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who attached who? Are you kidding me.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374006740374</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:32:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374007381529-15</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trayvon over reacted to being questioned and Zimmerman overreacted by shooting someone over punches. I seriously doubt Zimmerman would be dead if he was not carrying his gun. If trained properly, he could have at least shot him in the leg. I think that would have deterred anymore advances.</Msg><Username>gar4one</Username><Timestamp>1374007381529</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:43:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374008215549-16</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Trayvon over reacted to being questioned" I agree and the over reaction was to punch some one asking the questions, I belive this response started at the home with his parents. As to doubting Zimmerman would be dead if not carrying his gun, I don't get to that without going back to being hit in the face and having the attacker on top of me. Shoot the attacker in the leg, I only see that if the attacker was not on top of me, but he was. Conculsion for myself is Tryvon had some real hate in his heart to attack over being question, and this started at home with the parents.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374008215549</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 16:56:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374009623642-17</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>being a child, one can't fault trayvon for realized he was being stalked by a person who would not any question had he not been carrying a concealed weapon. Too bad trayvon wasn't packing 9mm, then could have safely told Zimmerman to fk off. Zimmerman had no right at all to ask any question of travon, period. neighborhood watches are not supposed to do ANYTHING but call the police, and they are NOT supposed to carry weapons.</Msg><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374009623642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 17:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>15</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374010006386-18</Id><Topic><Title>where is the outrage: most murder victims are killed by a family or friend or acquaintance, &amp; whites ARE MOSTLY murdered by WHITES</Title><Username>manceridermunce</Username><Timestamp>1374004605636</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 15:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and 99 percent of blacks are killed by blacks.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1374010006386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 17:26:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374010983027-19</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can see we are far apart and this is the case across the country. You sound very hatefull as well. To even suggest if Trayon had gun a full gun fight should have happen, maybe if he did nothing would had happen and maybe he would not have attacked. It is because of this attitude you show I carry, my wife carry's, my two sons carry and my daughter carry's. All have good jobs, pay our tax's. And by the way I was just taking a very late night walk and I was ask by a neighbor watch as to who I was, I told him and never hit him for asking.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374010983027</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 17:43:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374011787709-20</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen, you are spinning the fact that % wise blacks kill at a disproportionately rates to whites. Statistically you are on the wrong side of the argument. It is much safer to be hanging with white folks, which I am sure you do... which "may" show your momma didn't raise no fool.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374011787709</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 17:56:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374013071983-21</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You will give yourself a headache trying to reason with these folks. They see everything through the prism of race and economic injustice, though the suffer from neither.</Msg><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374013071983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 18:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374018283582-22</Id><Topic><Title>WAAAAA ! WAAAAAAAA ! I attacked Him .............</Title><Username>slayerhomo98_1</Username><Timestamp>1373775992478</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-07-14 00:26:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"You're making assumptions about facts not in evidence" Your only evidence is the killer's testimony The same killer who attacked police and was accused of domestic violence. Nice guy.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374018283582</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 19:44:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374018397701-23</Id><Title>When a White Guy Kills a Black Guy</Title><Msg>The only evidence necessary is the killer's testimony. When a black woman fires a warning shot, she gets 20 years. Florida southern justice still rules.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374018397701</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 19:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374018775494-24</Id><Topic><Title>Where is the outradge</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1373995397805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 13:23:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's your beloved government which is profiling, unlucky. Al Sharpton(House), Eric Holder(Justice Department), and president himself. Among all the cases whites vs whites, blacks vs blacks, blacks vs whites, whites vs blacks, our government for no good reason nor even authority unlawfully interferes into single case where black kid was shot by Hispanic who looks white. And you call those who stands against this injustice a racist. It doesn't matter to you that the case has no merit. You make Zimmerman to be white supremacist, he is not. Move on to another case, doofus.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374018775494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 19:52:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374019724580-25</Id><Title>When a black woman fires a shot</Title><Msg>And her target is lucky to escape the bullet, he files a lawsuit. Now there is a jury to decide if it was warning shot or women simply missed the target. What a hell these liberals have against Florida? Didn't Floridians help to elect black president last year?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374019724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:08:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374021610681-26</Id><Topic><Title>When a black woman fires a shot</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374019724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only the smart Floridians. There's still plenty of backwoods red necks who would eat Log Cabin Pubs like you for lunch.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374021610681</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374021808295-27</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"If the neighborhood watch guy asks you questions you DO NOT punch him in the nose" Was Zimmer wearing a badge ? No. Did he identify himself ? Only the killer knows. Do YOU cower and grovel in the street when some stranger confronts you ? Likely, yes.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374021808295</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:43:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374022372619-28</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidder's headache never leaves.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374022372619</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:52:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374022522971-29</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're either a jewelry dealer, live in Somalia, or are very paranoid.</Msg><Username>mitt_wit</Username><Timestamp>1374022522971</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:55:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374022851843-30</Id><Title>Bo the Conqueror</Title><Msg>The Senate has voted to end a two-year Republican blockade that was preventing Richard Cordray from winning confirmation as director of the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau. The job was originally for Elizabeth Warren, GOP obstruction forced her out so she's now a Senator. Nice work GOP, now you get both of them!!!</Msg><Username>junglebobmaria</Username><Timestamp>1374022851843</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 21:00:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>12</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374029068217-31</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No I,m an American and your are a nit wit like your state.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374029068217</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374029507814-32</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you shoot a guy in self defense that is trying to beat you possibly kill you, yes.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374029507814</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 22:51:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374030195418-33</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Adding a few letters to someone's identity shows who your are, and you are the moron.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374030195418</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374030289571-34</Id><Topic><Title>When a black woman fires a shot</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374019724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just trashed the whole state of Florida because jurors dared to judge the way you don't like. Case like Trayvon's could be decided same way in the state like California. Means only there are reasonable people everywhere. Not drones like you.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374030289571</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:04:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374030483096-35</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are probobly some punk who never did anything but wipe is own as- and never had to anyting but that. To much into yourself to procreate.</Msg><Username>iride2up</Username><Timestamp>1374030483096</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:08:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374030889340-36</Id><Topic><Title>Trayvon Martin made mistakes too, mistakes that ultimately cost him his life!</Title><Username>hotmanforahotwoman</Username><Timestamp>1373926173329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-07-15 18:09:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sir, sound like you would prefer to grovel and say ' Yassa "</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374030889340</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:14:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374031309545-37</Id><Topic><Title>When a black woman fires a shot</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374019724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sure, just like you agreed with the OJ jury.</Msg><Username>biddermoron_ca</Username><Timestamp>1374031309545</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:21:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1374032016909-38</Id><Title>Fox news Panel Said Manslaughter Was Justified</Title><Msg>Unlike the wingnuts here, I actually listen to 5 different conservative TV/ Radio shows. On Hannity tonight, he had a hand selected panel of lawyers, about 20. And the majority said it should have been manslaughter.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1374032016909</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1374032820528-39</Id><Topic><Title>When a black woman fires a shot</Title><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374019724580</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 20:08:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>? Where did you get that one? Trying hard to prove all you capable of is to put labels on anyone who has an opposite point of view? I was only asking about your outrage in OJ's case. What do ya think about state of CA after OJ's decision? Aren't those Californians stupid? In general, big time.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1374032820528</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-07-16 23:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>