<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-04-20"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366437916974-1</Id><Topic><Title>30,000 deaths in USA per year, no big deal to gop. (but they charged off to iraq)</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366426530804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Had a bad day today? There were no white supremacists involved in Boston massacre, and you wanted them there so badly! Same old suspects instead. Your jihadist friends. Yeah. They just wouldn't stop murdering the innocent. So now to make them not to look that bad you equate them to McCain. Why McCain? Maybe every single one who served in Vietnam deserved to be called terrorist? John F Kerry, for example? Oh, yes. He shot an innocent Vietnamese boy. Didn't have to. And. Got a Purple Heart for this "heroic" act. Anyways, you sick creep, there was a relatively good day today. One jihadist dead and another apprehended. I hope after he gives all his liaisons, he gets a bullet right between his eyes and goes to hell. People in Boston were waving American flags today. Don't remember that much patriotic celebrations after Christian abortionist killer got arrested. For you sick boy, they are all the same. Oh! Those guns. Get off this horse, doofus. This horsie is dead. can't you see? Your Democrat controlled Senate stopped gun control bill. Another blow for Obama. You forgot to mention that 2/3 of those non-accidental gun deaths are suicides. Number of deaths from car accidents is 3x-4x higher than from guns. Where is Obama and his crowd doing something against those killer-cars?</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366437916974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 02:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366448564721-2</Id><Topic><Title>Timothy McVeigh 'Al Queda' connection. Nazis are LIBERALS</Title><Username>unluckyskankgerbil</Username><Timestamp>1366145577464</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-04-16 16:52:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wanted to vote for Paul in the primary but they lost my freaking ballot request form. Not that it would have mattered as Romney had already started to counter his delegate strategy, but it would have been neat to see him win at the convention on a technicality :-)</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366448564721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 05:02:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366462938816-3</Id><Topic><Title>30,000 deaths in USA per year, no big deal to gop. (but they charged off to iraq)</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366426530804</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 22:55:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are so confused. I pointed out and condemned all terrorism and you actually justified bombing abortion clinics and a civilian power plant in Hanoi ......in a war you admit was based on lies and was the fault of lbj who you condemn for it (while never mentioning Nixon who invaded Cambodia and laos and escalated the b-52 bombing of civilians,nor the fact that Vietnam was not a threat to the USA and had never attacked the usa, so killing them was just plain murder and terrorism)</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366462938816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366463964697-4</Id><Title>craziest of the rightwing terrorists? he cited cuts to his food stamps as a reason for wanting to kill all liberals</Title><Msg>Adkisson's manifesto[12] also cited the inability to find a job, and that his food stamps were being cut. “ During the interview Adkisson stated that he had targeted the church because of its liberal teachings and his belief that all liberals should be killed because they were ruining the country, and that he felt that the Democrats had tied his country's hands in the war on terror and they had ruined every institution in America with the aid of major media outlets. Adkisson made statements that because he could not get to the leaders of the liberal movement that he would then target those that had voted them into office. Adkisson stated that he had held these beliefs for about the last ten years. Knoxville Unitarian Universalist church shooting</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366463964697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:19:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366466877779-5</Id><Topic><Title>craziest of the rightwing terrorists? he cited cuts to his food stamps as a reason for wanting to kill all liberals</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366463964697</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 09:19:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know who this Adkisson guy is - but his manifesto ain't all bad. A job might have helped him out.</Msg><Username>investorelvis</Username><Timestamp>1366466877779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 10:07:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366471812244-6</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the power plant was purely civilian. In fact most bombing of N. viet..was nothing but terror bombing of the civilian populace. The N viets had about zero manufacturing and certainly the weapons they used were not manufactured there....( nor had they ever attacked the USA, certainly were not a threat to the USA , and in fact were the very same people who were our allies in ousting the Japanese and their Vichy French puppet rulers , and the very same people McCain hugged a few years ago and who have been a favored USA trading partner, Nam was a war based on lies, the whole thing was a war crime) He [ McNamara] [1968 ] bluntly admitted that there was "no basis to believe that any bombing campaign...would by itself force Ho Chi Minh's regime into submission, short, that is, of the virtual annihilation of North Vietnam and its people."[98] Robert McNamara On 31 December 1967, the Department of Defense announced that 864,000 tons of American bombs had been dropped on North Vietnam during Rolling Thunder, compared with 653,000 tons dropped during the entire Korean War and 503,000 tons in the Pacific theater during the Second World War.[108] .....PBS estimate that the 3.5 year Operation Rolling Thunder killed 182,000 civilians........................</Msg><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366471812244</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 11:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366474441345-7</Id><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Msg>Many have left the military and the State Department.</Msg><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366477596944-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Bush, most left the Military in boxes.</Msg><Username>mittins_da_wimpins</Username><Timestamp>1366477596944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 13:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485405625-9</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfit to be Commander in Chief On July 7, 2011, U.S. troop deaths from the war in Afghanistan since President Obama took office reached 1,000. That means that nearly two-thirds of the U.S. fatalities in the war in Afghanistan have occurred during the Obama administration, which has managed the war for a mere quarter of its duration. These numbers should give us pause. While the Administration has publicly conceded that there is no military solution in Afghanistan, and claimed that it supports 'Afghan-led reconciliation', its policy on the ground is marked by a refusal to establish a timetable for full military withdrawal. The Administration has even backed away from the 'substantial drawdown' of troops that was promised to begin this July, instead opting for a token drawdown that will leave about twice as many troops in the country as were there when he assumed office, with no plan for their removal. See Just Foreign Policy's press release marking this grim milestone here. We must ask ourselves how many more lives will be sacrificed before the Obama administration sets a clear end date for America's longest war.</Msg><Username>islam_needs_new_ceo_now</Username><Timestamp>1366485405625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485721920-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KABUL, Afghanistan — The killing of an American serviceman in an exchange of fire with allied Afghan soldiers pushed U.S. military deaths in the war to 2,000, a cold reminder of Obama's treachery. Huffington Post September 2012</Msg><Username>homoho_bo</Username><Timestamp>1366485721920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366485978035-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey dukky if yuo don"t like what the u s a gov.go to live in another country maybe a musslim one.</Msg><Username>vince1947</Username><Timestamp>1366485978035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 15:26:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366493953255-12</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What this whole issue comes down to is this: I believe President Obama is doing the right thing by not putting 'boots on the ground' anywhere. Once the President committs troops to places like Libya, Syria, and other places the troops will be there for some time. Some American entanglements started out as 'police actions' but developed into fullfledged wars. Americans need to forget about 'nation building' and bringing democracy to those who don't want it. If it were up to politicians like John McCain and his buddy Joe Lieberman, this country would be again involved in wars with troops on the ground, somewhere in the Middle East. I'd say, let Muslims destroy themselves, they don't want our help. To hell with the 'Arab Spring' - let them fight it and not us. It is truly sad that the United Nation lacks the power of enforcement.</Msg><Username>liberal_hollywood</Username><Timestamp>1366493953255</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:39:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494133236-13</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no such thing as a "purely civilian" power plant. Power plants operate industry which fuels the war effort, power plants are totally legitimate targets.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366494133236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494380737-14</Id><Topic><Title>Was Mccain a terrorist? He was sent to bomb civilians</Title><Username>duckywankerbill</Username><Timestamp>1366381151524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 10:19:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Further keep in mind you're attempting to apply 21st century technical standards on a war fought 50 years ago when we didn't have self guided munitions or a GPS system, and thus it was necessary to drop planeloads of bombs to destroy a target. Now if you want to talk war crime look to the fire bombing of Japanese cities prior to the A-Bomb attacks. We used a high altitude daytime strategic bomber to fly at low altitudes at night setting entire cities on fire. In fact just about the only intact cities left were the ones we picked as "example targets" for later A-Bomb attacks. Of course if the invasion of Japan had been deemed to be necessary the serviceman landing ashore would be glad for every one of those destroyed cities, as without face saving cause they would have NEVER surrendered.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366494380737</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:46:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366494657902-15</Id><Topic><Title>Obama nominee admits unemployment numbers are bogus.</Title><Username>biddermon_ca</Username><Timestamp>1366310551463</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-04-18 14:42:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, they won't, because it gives them a reason to not feel like idiots for being fooled not only once, but twice, by the same guy peddling the same lines. Fool me once, shame on you, fool me twice, shame on me . . . Fortunately where this particular matter is concerned, I'm clean. I voted against BO both times.</Msg><Username>clgl_fubar</Username><Timestamp>1366494657902</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 17:50:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366499923504-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Under Cheney/Bush many fine general officers were fired or forced into retirement because they advised against the invasion of Iraq.</Msg><Username>bami2012</Username><Timestamp>1366499923504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:18:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366501768597-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama not worth a damn</Title><Username>coward_of_benghazi</Username><Timestamp>1366474441345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 12:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Prove it. The original poster is correct. Obama is not worth a damn.</Msg><Username>contempt_4_conservative_idtios</Username><Timestamp>1366501768597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 19:49:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366506626782-18</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just because unborn doesn't have a voice to defend itself, doesn't mean they can be thrown to trash can at will. You can hold your personal view on that. But this is not a freedom of choice for way too many in this country. The notion that unborn is not human and thus can be discarded is far, far from being universally accepted. And if it will this nation completely lost its soul. It isn't Christianity or Judaism. It's simple humanity.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1366506626782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 21:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366515688318-19</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I never said I justify any murder. You're jumping to your own conclusions that fits your narrative. " And I never said you did either. I asked how the two scenarios are morally different ! You jump to ignorant, defensive conclusions. It's really difficult to have a discussion with a person who can't think for themselves.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366515688318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:41:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1366516117480-20</Id><Topic><Title>Chechen Islamist brothers were the Boston bombers</Title><Username>croxcost</Username><Timestamp>1366374616708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-04-19 08:30:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>""Crazy rightwing bigots, who hate the government and listen to the fat liars beck and Limbaugh, wait and see, this smells like crack pot rightie hate violence." That's not hate, that's reality ! There are literally thousands of right wing govt hating militias hiding in remote areas and loading up on weapons. And you know it. All the professional mercenary groups are right wing. Find me a group of liberals wearing camouflage and and assault weapons meeting in Montana and Arkansas. And every other red state.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366516117480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1366516452753-21</Id><Title>Obama Says... "Americans Refuse to be Terrorized " .........</Title><Msg>All except the Limbots who buy Rush's gold and are getting killed. The cave dwellers are easily terrorized. And are always the first to give up their freedom so they won't be scared. Liberals don't scare easily. And demand more freedom. Not less.</Msg><Username>conservativeslieandbehomos</Username><Timestamp>1366516452753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-04-20 23:54:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>