<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-21"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348200333704-1</Id><Topic><Title>Obama bragging about 4M jobs but the Stimulus was $800B what did he do with that my god those 4M jobs didnt cost 800B did it</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348200132244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>•President Obama wants to create 4 million jobs. $800B is $200,000 per job (where do I apply?}. •Illinois Governor Blagojevich has allegedly tried to sell Barrack Obama's senator seat. If you could buy a seat for $10 million, $800B could buy 80,000 US Senators. Of course, there are only 100 US Senators and they get elected every six years. So you could own all 100 Senators for 4,800 years. •The population of the United States is 306 million. $800B is $2,614 per person. (I have a family of four, that's nearly $10,500.) •Bernie Madoff's Ponzi's scheme is estimated to be $50 billion. With $800B, we could fund 16 such schemes. •From the IRS, there were about 97 million people with 2006 income tax liability. So $800B is $8,247 for every person who actually pays income taxes. •President Obama's inauguration was magical and watched around the world. At a cost of $170 million, we could do it 4,705 more times. •About 6.5 million people are receiving unemployment benefits. $800B is $123,000 each. •California's budget gap appears to be around $30 billion. $800B can fill that gap for over 25 years. •There were 850,000 home foreclosures in 2008. At the current median home sale price of $175,000, $800B could buy everyone of them more than five times over. •John Thain, the former CEO of Merrill Lynch, paid $1.2 million to remodel his office/bathroom/conference rooms. With $800B, he could remodel it 666,666 more times. •If the entire $800B were applied to the US consumber credit card debt, it would completely pay...er...well, it would pay down 85% of it.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348200333704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348202059133-2</Id><Topic><Title>Obama bragging about 4M jobs but the Stimulus was $800B what did he do with that my god those 4M jobs didnt cost 800B did it</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348200132244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get rid of O'blammah! And the Democrap Congress!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348202059133</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348202141167-3</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT REPUBS REALLY WANT TO SAY: I'm ready to give up on Romney. I wanted Huntsman or even Ron Paul.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1348148725244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vote the Party to Get rid of O'blammah! And the Democrap Congress!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1348202141167</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348205054762-4</Id><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Msg>Here are the 40 Republicans who voted to keep America’s veterans unemployed, because it is more important to oppose the president than to help the veterans. 3T in the war, but not 1B for the vets. Alexander (R-TN) Ayotte (R-NH) Barrasso (R-WY) Blunt (R-MO) Boozman (R-AR) Burr (R-NC) Chambliss (R-GA) Coats (R-IN) Coburn (R-OK) Cochran (R-MS) Corker (R-TN) Cornyn (R-TX) Crapo (R-ID) DeMint (R-SC) Enzi (R-WY) Graham (R-SC) Grassley (R-IA) Hatch (R-UT) Hoeven (R-ND) Hutchison (R-TX) Isakson (R-GA) Johanns (R-NE) Johnson (R-WI) Kyl (R-AZ) Lee (R-UT) Lugar (R-IN) McCain (R-AZ) McConnell (R-KY) Moran (R-KS) Paul (R-KY) Portman (R-OH) Risch (R-ID) Roberts (R-KS) Rubio (R-FL) Sessions (R-AL) Shelby (R-AL) Thune (R-SD) Toomey (R-PA) Vitter (R-LA) Wicker (R-MS) Mark Kirk and James Inhofe did not vote.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348207363740-5</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT REPUBS REALLY WANT TO SAY: I'm ready to give up on Romney. I wanted Huntsman or even Ron Paul.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1348148725244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 09:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"..., the earth as a sphere," Too funny, LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348207363740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 02:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348224493819-6</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been asked this on other boards, little Polish buddy, and keep running away. Where does the $1 billion funding come from? The 47% finally going to pay their 'fair share'?</Msg><Username>habanag</Username><Timestamp>1348224493819</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 06:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348225024794-7</Id><Topic><Title>'I GUESS I'M ONE OF THE LEECHES ON THE SYSTEM' Disabled Veteran Responds To Romney's 47 Percent Comments</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348224713650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 06:51:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 53% think Mr. Romney nailed it. The 47% think he's talking about someone else.</Msg><Username>habanag</Username><Timestamp>1348225024794</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 06:57:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348225957288-8</Id><Topic><Title>Obama bragging about 4M jobs but the Stimulus was $800B what did he do with that my god those 4M jobs didnt cost 800B did it</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1348200132244</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 00:02:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wasteful thinking! LoL!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1348225957288</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 07:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348227935373-9</Id><Title>Dow</Title><Msg>Best time in history to sell stocks. Stock market as we know it is over. Debt capitalism is unsustainable. Producing with dirt cheap Asian slave labor and selling into developed market where 50% of population live hand-to-mouth (e.g., USA) is failed model of capitalism. No amount of money printing can fix failed model of debt capitalism.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1348227935373</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 07:45:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348228414361-10</Id><Topic><Title>Fox poll: Obama leads in Ohio, Fla., Va.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1348161868996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" In a new poll conducted for The Hill, only 40 percent of likely voters said they felt Obama deserves a second term." The negativity is out there.</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1348228414361</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 07:53:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348228662025-11</Id><Topic><Title>Fox poll: Obama leads in Ohio, Fla., Va.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1348161868996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only 23% of people felt they could relate to mitt romney as a person; 66% felt they could relate to obama</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348228662025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 07:57:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348229208696-12</Id><Title>6 MILLION Americans to face new Obamacare TAX</Title><Msg>Thank you Mr. President for ANOTHER new tax on Americans. More hope and change folks, more hope and change.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348229208696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348229818039-13</Id><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Msg>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348229865079-14</Id><Topic><Title>6 MILLION Americans to face new Obamacare TAX</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348229208696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:06:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>isn't it too early in the morning for you to post a lie?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229865079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:17:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348230384791-15</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once AGAIN libTURDS only tell half the truth and PREY on the people. Passing the bill would violate the budget control act. Congress agreed to raise the debt ceiling, both parties agreed to follow the Budget Control Act of 2011. That Act signed into law by Obama PROHIBITS increasing the budget for specific programs including Defense, Homeland Security, and VA. Passing this bill VIOLATES the Act that EVERYONE agreed to and the President signed. Democrats are doing nothing more than playing a childish GAME for political gain in front of an election. DemoCRAPS are pathetic, LIARS, and can't be trusted. Looks like I had to put ol BOYsurfer in his place AGAIN. The WHOLE truth is out.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348230384791</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:26:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348230829522-16</Id><Title>Obama Campaign desecrates the American Flag....</Title><Msg>Has anyone looked to see the how the ARROGANT President has changed the AMerican flag and put his logo where the stars are? These people are out of control.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348230829522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:33:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348231516979-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Campaign desecrates the American Flag....</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348230829522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:33:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post hidden because you ignored this user. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH LMMFAO that whoever you are, you keep wasting your time and I can't see your CHILDISH replies. hehehehehehehe</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348231516979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:45:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348231773999-18</Id><Title>Here's what former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan wrote last night for The Wall Street Journal about Mitt Romney's presidential campaign: This week I called it incompetent, but only because I was being polite. I really meant 'rolling calamity.'</Title><Msg>thank God the wimpy Mitt has Ann to stand up and tell the GOP to stop picking on Mitt.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348231773999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:49:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348232182994-19</Id><Topic><Title>Fox poll: Obama leads in Ohio, Fla., Va.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1348161868996</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 13:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"42 million adult Americans can't read. 50 million adult Americans are limited to a 4th or 5th grade reading level or can only recognize a few printed words." Is this who "relates" to Obama? This is a major fundamental issue facing this country.These folks cannot comprehend the issues. They "relate" to Obama...so they vote for him?</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1348232182994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:56:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348232396570-20</Id><Topic><Title>Here's what former Reagan speechwriter Peggy Noonan wrote last night for The Wall Street Journal about Mitt Romney's presidential campaign: This week I called it incompetent, but only because I was being polite. I really meant 'rolling calamity.'</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348231773999</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:49:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Peggy Noonan WHO. Talk about an irrelevent NOBODY. While some are focusing on Romney telling the truth President Narcissist is changing the American flag and putting his logo on it. Interesting how O'Loser can simply do no wrong in the eyes of the pathetic media.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348232396570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348232404535-21</Id><Title>Even 12 year olds see what's wrong with Romney</Title><Msg>Dear Governor Romney, I’d like to say congratulations on winning the republican nomination. But, I wish you stayed in Massachusetts. You’re plan for America isn’t what we need, and would hurt us more than it would help. First, repealing Obama care and other health plans he’s put in place have helped families across America, including mine. I live in a middle class family, and two years ago my little sister; Kennedy was denied insurance because of her pre-existing condition. This was a huge emotional stress and financial burden on my entire family. Under Obama Care, insurance companies can no longer deny Kennedy and kids like her, the coverage they need and deserve. Because of Obama care my little sister was able to have the several surgeries she needed that helped save her life. Once the President was elected he put Obama Care into action, just like he promised and made it so that you could get insurance with pre-existing conditions. This has made a direct impact on my family. My family is with out a doubt better off now, than we were four years ago! It is to my understanding that you stated that you were going to repeal Obama Care, including the part I have mentioned, which will take away the insurance we have and need for my sister Kennedy. Why do you think she doesn’t deserve health care? Also, when you were interviewed on “Meet the Press”, you stated that you would NOT repeal this part of Obama Care, but then your campaign backpedalled and on the “Tonight show with Jay Leno”, you said that you WOULD repeal this. Also, you’re domestic plans (birth control, gay rights etc.) are horrible! Women should get to manage their own health, and if you wonder why you’re not appealing to many women voters, rethink your birth control and women’s’ rights plans. And people should be able to marry whom they want. We built this country so people could have freedom, and not have religious beliefs control them to that length. This country was in no way built on any religion, so we should not create laws that repress the American people in a religious way and hurt our most vulnerable. Sincerely, Jackson Ripley, age 12</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348232404535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348233034471-22</Id><Topic><Title>Even 12 year olds see what's wrong with Romney</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348232404535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh look, isn't that precious, libTURDS are now quoting 12 year olds. Looks like they finally found their comfort zone. LMMFAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348233034471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348233444273-23</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems Inc</Title><Username>anavth63291</Username><Timestamp>1348067113544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 11:05:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just read your article. Impressive.</Msg><Username>nadiayyd88566</Username><Timestamp>1348233444273</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:17:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348233833083-24</Id><Title>MIAMI, Fla. - President Obama today said his failure to push comprehensive immigration reform as promised ised was the biggest failure of his first term but blamed Republicans in Congress for the lack of progress.</Title><Msg>but blamed Republicans in Congress for the lack of progress. this coward blamer needs to go. mr blamey and his children followers. he would not last one day in the real world of business. leaders take the blame and move on children point fingers. I have no respect for this clown. he needs to grow up and be a man!</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348233833083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348233932190-25</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how does posting all day on a stock message board about non-sense from your gov job paid for by tax payers help american people.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348233932190</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348234455289-26</Id><Title>obama failed because GOP</Title><Msg>hahahahahahahahahah enough with this child. we need a man for a president!</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348234455289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:34:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348234969687-27</Id><Topic><Title>MIAMI, Fla. - President Obama today said his failure to push comprehensive immigration reform as promised ised was the biggest failure of his first term but blamed Republicans in Congress for the lack of progress.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348233833083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama had two years of complete control of congress but did not address immigration reform. He is now pandering (and lying) to Latinos to secure their vote.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348234969687</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348235198766-28</Id><Topic><Title>MIAMI, Fla. - President Obama today said his failure to push comprehensive immigration reform as promised ised was the biggest failure of his first term but blamed Republicans in Congress for the lack of progress.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348233833083</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he turned america into a big playground what a joke. the children are leading the parents. dopey is just an angry child. what did he think everyone would just agree with him and let him be a king. sorry dopey the real world has oppositions we set the constitution up that way for our safty from clowns like you who erode personal freedoms. fn crybaby president.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348235198766</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348235277609-29</Id><Topic><Title>obama failed because GOP</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348234455289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well he said he did...made the statement. fn idiot. go back to your mommy.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348235277609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348235417956-30</Id><Topic><Title>Even 12 year olds see what's wrong with Romney</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348232404535</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>children relating to one another how cute. a 12 year old who never had a job is telling us what we need. exactly my point. thank god that idiot cant vote until he grows up. now all we have to do is get the liberals who can vote to grow up.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348235417956</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:50:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348237110984-31</Id><Title>Tax penalty under president Barack Obama</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (AP) — Nearly 6 million Americans — significantly more than first estimated— will face a tax penalty under President Barack Obama's health overhaul for not getting insurance, congressional analysts said Wednesday. Most would be in the middle class.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348237110984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348237250785-32</Id><Topic><Title>obama failed because GOP</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348234455289</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 09:34:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry your dad did not give you attention...but i am not your dad kid. get a clue.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348237250785</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348238199245-33</Id><Title>just put the infant juniorclass-5 on ignore</Title><Msg>most likely another magoo id- Why is it so obsessed with sandusky and children petting. what a creep. everything you say it relates back to that. we know what it is thinking about 24-7.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238199245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:36:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348238212909-34</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please stay on topic. don't become another Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>oscar_dimwitty</Username><Timestamp>1348238212909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:36:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348238252651-35</Id><Topic><Title>I said a year+ ago that this election was the GOP's to lose. Obama had just enough going against him that if the GOP ran a competent, insightful individual, they would win in a landslide. Then they roll out the West wing of the nut house and expect us to respect their choices. The only credible candidate they had was Jon Huntsman and he didn't even get the time of day from the GOP. So sad.</Title><Username>oscar_dimwitty</Username><Timestamp>1347988777474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-18 13:19:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see that the Dimwitty is proven correct!</Msg><Username>oscar_dimwitty</Username><Timestamp>1348238252651</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:37:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348238280893-36</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>please do your job idiot...get back to work you cry baby spoiled brat.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238280893</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:38:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348238498135-37</Id><Title>Middle class enjoy your</Title><Msg>tax penalty under President Barack Obama...you have been mislead.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238498135</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:41:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348238639917-38</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bain Capital was about 70% successful in saving companies. Imagine all those employes are grateful they are still working. Libs want to concentrate on the 30% who weren't so fortunate. It's the political season.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348238639917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348238651832-39</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just want you to do the job we tax payers pay you for. you are such a useless human being. posting all day whining about your situation -begging others to pay your way. pathetic.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238651832</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348238763222-40</Id><Title>magoo crys about how the world is unfair</Title><Msg>all day long form its obviously useless gov job. magoo the go getter wonders why its not rich...BWAHAHHAAHAHAHAHAHAHAH what a useless turd.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238763222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348239000574-41</Id><Topic><Title>magoo crys about how the world is unfair</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238763222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:46:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It says the rich dont pay its fair share...all day on a stock message board under many ids while at its government job. Magoo YOU are the biggest tax cheat of all. stealing money from tax payers all day. you need to pay your fair share and do the job we pay you to do. magoo thinks it has the right to steal from tax payers. what a #$%$ useless POS.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239000574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:50:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348239333470-42</Id><Topic><Title>QUESTION TO Mr. ROMNEY: How does buying American companies firing American workers, cutting wages and benefits of the rest, moving manufacturing to China selling the companies and stashing $250,000,000 in Switzerland, the Bahamas and Cayman Islands to avoid paying taxes help the American people?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348229818039</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 08:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how about a government employee working for the money we pay it to do its job? get back to work tax thief! obamas kids running rampant like spoiled little out of touch brats.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239333470</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:55:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348239521124-43</Id><Title>obama said he failed</Title><Msg>because GDP...hahahahahahahahahahahahaha kick this out of touch community organizer out. poor mr obama he says GOP dont agree with him. he is the only president who has had opposition. what a child. he would never make it in the real world.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239521124</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:58:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348239526724-44</Id><Title>obama said he failed</Title><Msg>because GDP...hahahahahahahahahahahahaha kick this out of touch community organizer out. poor mr obama he says GOP dont agree with him. he is the only president who has had opposition. what a child. he would never make it in the real world.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239526724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348239702609-45</Id><Topic><Title>Tax penalty under president Barack Obama</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348237110984</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that hopey change thing is not so warm and fuzzy anymore is it. poor middle class always get hurt.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239702609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:01:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348239750789-46</Id><Topic><Title>FOX NEWS CALLS ITSELF AMERICA'S ELECTION HQ BUT NOTHING ON LATEST POLLS Even that gop hack rasmussen has o'bama in the lead</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1348239643001</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:00:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe you should accually do some work today for us tax payers magoo?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348239750789</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:02:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348240264964-47</Id><Title>Barrack Obama: "Destruction of the middle class is necessary to achieve equality". From his autobiography. FACT</Title><Msg>I guess he thought he could do that in 4 years. Not quite but he is off to a good start. The USA wont survive another 4 years of Obama.</Msg><Username>stevestunning356</Username><Timestamp>1348240264964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348240479326-48</Id><Topic><Title>Barrack Obama: "Destruction of the middle class is necessary to achieve equality". From his autobiography. FACT</Title><Username>stevestunning356</Username><Timestamp>1348240264964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:11:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>communism...it is nothing new...just new to america.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348240479326</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348240516704-49</Id><Title>now obammy has a new american flag planned ... what will this guy think of next ??</Title><Msg>Obama continued: "The National Anthem should be 'swapped' for something less parochial and less bellicose. I like the song 'I'd Like To Teach the World To Sing'. If that were our anthem, then, I might salute it. In my opinion, we should consider reinventing our National Anthem as well as 'redesign' our Flag to better offer our enemies hope and love. It's my intention, if elected, to disarm America to the level of acceptance to our Middle East Brethren. If we, as a Nation of warring people, conduct ourselves like the nations of Islam, where peace prevails - - - perhaps a state or period of mutual accord could exist between our governments ......" When I become President, I will seek a pact of agreement to end hostilities between those who have been at war or in a state of enmity, and a freedom from disquieting oppressive thoughts. We as a Nation, have placed upon the nations of Islam, an unfair injusticewhich is WHY my wife disrespects the Flag and she and I have attended several flag burning ceremonies in the past". "Of course now, I have found myself about to become the President of the United States and I have put my hatred aside. I will use my power to bring CHANGE to this Nation, and offer the people a new path. My wife and I look forward to becoming our Country's First black Family. Indeed, CHANGE is about to overwhelm the United States of America "</Msg><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1348240516704</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:15:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348240650331-50</Id><Title>obammy declares muslim world a world of peace !!!!!! ?????????</Title><Msg>where has this guy been for the last two weeks ...</Msg><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1348240650331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:17:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348240906554-51</Id><Topic><Title>just put the infant juniorclass-5 on ignore</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348238199245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 10:36:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I put him on ignore few days ago. His childishness gets extremely boring.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348240906554</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:21:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348241809642-52</Id><Title>Happy Friday</Title><Msg>"Mitt Romney said the 47 percent of people who don't pay taxes are going to vote for Obama. You know what that means? He's going to vote for Obama." --Jay Leno "Mitt Romney says that about half the country is freeloaders. And freeloaders - that includes wealthy politicians who only pay 13 percent in tax." -David Letterman "I like Mitt. Listen to this. He has alienated the young people, alienated the old people, alienated women, alienated minorities, alienated gays. I'm telling you, this takes talent." -David Letterman "Romney said he doesn't watch 'Keeping up with the Kardashians' because if Romney wants to see rich people say dumb things on camera he can watch that fundraiser video." -Jimmy Fallon</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348241809642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348242696629-53</Id><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Msg>The GOP base sees government as a burden that weighs the private sector down rather than a tool that can generate growth if used properly. Ninety-six percent of Republican voters believe that the best thing the government can do to help the economy is to cut spending and free up more money for the private sector. The Republican base is looking for someone like a 21st century Ronald Reagan, who will display his faith in the American people. The Washington Republicans are more comfortable with politicians like George W. Bush, Bob Dole, John McCain and Mitt Romney. Though the establishment has dominated the party since Reagan left the White House, the 2012 election could well be the end of the line. If Romney loses in November, the Republican base will no longer buy the electability argument for an establishment candidate. From the view of the base, the elites will have given away an eminently winnable election. Someone new, from outside of Washington, will be the party's nominee in 2016. If Romney wins and does nothing to change the status quo, the economy will falter. He will end up as the second straight one-term president, and the nation will desperately be searching for an authentic outsider in 2016. If he wins the White House, the only way for Romney to succeed will be to side with the nation's voters and throw out the club in Washington. That will be great news for the country but bad news for political insiders on both sides of the partisan aisle. COPYRIGHT 2012 SCOTT RASMUSSEN</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348242787539-54</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Friday</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348241809642</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:36:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>david letterman the wife cheater has a lot to say. he should just worry about his own morals. BTW obama paid less than my assistant in taxes last year on millions in earnings. finger pointing liberals cant live up to the standards they impose on others.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348242787539</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:53:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348242977761-55</Id><Topic><Title>obammy declares muslim world a world of peace !!!!!! ?????????</Title><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1348240650331</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:17:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>golfing and campaigning to save his job...the only one he really cares about.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348242977761</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348243679699-56</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2008 James Carville said the republican party was done for 40 years......then came 2010. LOLOLOLOLOLOL You loons are hilarious!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348243679699</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348243787281-57</Id><Title>in a communist system all are miserable</Title><Msg>misery loves company.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348243787281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244007683-58</Id><Title>Forgotten speech</Title><Msg>Ryan Vowed To Privatize Social Security And Medicare In Forgotten Speech September 20th, 2012 7:04 pm Henry Decker As the Republican presidential campaign attempts to move on from the secretly recorded video of Mitt Romney addressing a private fundraiser in Florida, an obscure recording of Paul Ryan reveals that the Republican vice presidential nominee likewise preaches a different vision when the media isn’t watching. The audio recording, recently rediscovered by Vincent Miller of America Magazine, is a speech delivered by Ryan to the objectivist Atlas Society in 2005. (It can be found on the Atlas Society’s website.) While the speech has been cited for containing Ryan’s declaration that Ayn Rand was the reason he got into public service, closer scrutiny shows that Rand is also the inspiration for Ryan’s policy decisions. “It’s so important that we go back to our roots to look at Ayn Rand’s vision, her writings, to see what our girding, under-grounding [sic] principles are,” Ryan told the Atlas Society crowd. “The fight we are in here, make no mistake about it,” he later adds, “is a fight of individualism versus collectivism.” Ryan went on to explain how he and his fellow Randians can “break the back of this collectivist philosophy that really pervades, you know, 90 percent of the thinking” in Washington. The first step is to “focus on big-ticket items,” such as Social Security. According to Ryan, Social Security is a “collectivist,” “welfare-transfer system,” that Congress can only fix by transitioning it to “an individually pre-owned, pre-funded retirement system.” In other words, by privatizing it. If Social Security is “personalized,” as Ryan put it (to knowing laughter from the audience), then “every laborer in America will not only be a laborer but a capitalist,” which will create “that many more people in America who are not going to listen to the likes of Dick Gephardt and Nancy Pelosi, Ted Kennedy, the collectivist, class warfare-breathing demagogues.” Given all of this rhetoric, it’s no surprise that Ryan has tried to put his plan into action on multiple occasions. As Talking Points Memo’s Sahil Kapur explains, in 2004 Ryan and Republican Senator John Sununu co-sponsored legislation that introduced private accounts in such a financially irresponsible way that even the Bush administration opposed it. Ryan tried to privatize Social Security again in 2010, as part of his “Roadmap for America’s Future.” As Paul Van de Water, a Social Security expert at the Center on Budget and Policy Priorities told Kapur, Ryan’s plan “would have made deep cuts in guaranteed Social Security benefits and impaired the program’s solvency by diverting a large portion of payroll taxes into private accounts that would primarily benefit high earners.” Neither measure succeeded, and Romney has not even hinted at any plan to privatize Social Security. Given that Ryan views every fight as a battle between individualism and collectivism, however, there can be little doubt that he’d still promote privatization in a Romney-Ryan administration. Ryan also targeted Medicare in his speech to the Atlas Society. His current plan — which would supplant Medicare for seniors with a voucher system — is unpopular enough as it is. In 2005, however, Ryan went even further, suggesting that the system should be entirely privatized: When you take a look at the seeds that have been planted in this Medicare law, there is a situation that we hope will materialize and we think that this law gives us a great chance of doing it – whereby Boomers are coming into retirement with an HSA that has resources in it, so that when they come to retirement they’ll pick among catastrophic plans that are private-provided from which to choose from Medicare, and they’ll have their HSAs come in underneath that. And so you’ll have a consumer-directed system not only for those who are under 65 in America but for those who are over 65 in America. That is the way to save Medicare not only from bankrupting the federal government because of its incredible growth, but also to bring this system to a defined contribution, individually driven, consumer-directed health care system. All those seeds, all those provisions are in this Medicare law, but they’re just delayed because of their enactment dates. Which makes Ryan’s mock outrage that President Obama is “raiding” the collectivist system that he’d like to do away with even more ridiculous. Throughout the 2012 campaign, pundits from both sides of the aisle have pleaded for the Romney-Ryan campaign to lay out a specific vision for the future. Ryan’s Atlas Society speech — and Romney’s stunning fundraiser remarks — help explain why they don’t do so. Those private moments expose how Romney and Ryan really view America, and it’s a vision most voters do not share.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348244007683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:13:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244204259-59</Id><Topic><Title>Forgotten speech</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348244007683</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:13:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i agree, ryan is right. SS is full of obama and billy IOUs they take our money and spend it. it wont be there anyway. i would rather keep my money thanks.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244204259</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244341743-60</Id><Title>I think there is only one liberal</Title><Msg>poster on this board...magoo and all its ids. what a loser.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244341743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244361515-61</Id><Title>100 days until TAX DOOMSDAY</Title><Msg>100 Days Until Taxmageddon Sunday will mark the start of the 100-day countdown to “Taxmageddon” – the date the largest tax hikes in the history of America will take effect. They will hit families and small businesses in three great waves on January 1, 2013: First Wave: Expiration of 2001 and 2003 Tax Relief In 2001 and 2003, the GOP Congress enacted several tax cuts for small business owners, families, and investors (later re-upped by President Obama and Democrat Congress in 2010). The following tax hikes will occur on January 1, 2013: Personal income tax rates will rise on January 1, 2013. The top income tax rate will rise from 35 to 39.6 percent (this is also the rate at which the majority of small business profits are taxed). The lowest rate will rise from 10 to 15 percent. All the rates in between will also rise. Itemized deductions and personal exemptions will again phase out, which has the same mathematical effect as higher marginal tax rates. The full list of marginal rate hikes is below: -The 10% bracket rises to a new and expanded 15% -The 25% bracket rises to 28% -The 28% bracket rises to 31% -The 33% bracket rises to 36% -The 35% bracket rises to 39.6% Higher taxes on marriage and family coming on January 1, 2013. The “marriage penalty” (narrower tax brackets for married couples) will return from the first dollar of taxable income. The child tax credit will be cut in half from $1000 to $500 per child. The standard deduction will no longer be doubled for married couples relative to the single level. Middle Class Death Tax returns on January 1, 2013. The death tax is currently 35% with an exemption of $5 million ($10 million for married couples). For those dying on or after January 1 2013, there is a 55 percent top death tax rate on estates over $1 million. A person leaving behind two homes and a retirement account could easily pass along a death tax bill to their loved ones. Higher tax rates on savers and investors on January 1, 2013. The capital gains tax will rise from 15 percent this year to 23.8 percent in 2013. The top dividends tax will rise from 15 percent this year to 43.4 percent in 2013. This is because of scheduled rate hikes plus Obamacare’s investment surtax. Second Wave: Obamacare Tax Hikes There are twenty new or higher taxes in Obamacare. Some have already gone into effect (the tanning tax, the medicine cabinet tax, the HSA withdrawal tax, W-2 health insurance reporting, and the “economic substance doctrine”). Several more will go into effect on January 1, 2013. They include: The Obamacare Medical Device Tax begins to be assessed on January 1, 2013. Medical device manufacturers employ 409,000 people in 12,000 plants across the country. This law imposes a new 2.3% excise tax on gross sales – even if the company does not earn a profit in a given year. Exempts items retailing for</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348244361515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244372624-62</Id><Title>HOW MANY DEMS will Have to Be Sodomized And Offed before</Title><Msg>Obama finally strikes back against the Libyan murderers? How weak is Obama anways?? Under Obama the U.S. has become nothing more than they bytch of the towelheadmooslims, their punching bag!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1348244372624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244534023-63</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MANY DEMS will Have to Be Sodomized And Offed before</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1348244372624</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sodomy???? Fake Junior says him and his daddy really enjoyed it!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348244534023</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244644162-64</Id><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Msg>From Yahoo news (AP): "WASHINGTON (AP) — Unemployment rates rose in more than half of U.S. states last month, the latest evidence that hiring remains tepid across the country. The Labor Department said Friday that rates increased in 26 states. They fell in 12 states and were unchanged in the other 12." Obama &amp; Co. are MASSIVE FAILURES</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244654160-65</Id><Topic><Title>100 days until TAX DOOMSDAY</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348244361515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is bad for all americans! middle class especially! to dumb to notice. love how dopey does it after elections. sneaky slime that he is.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244654160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244680140-66</Id><Topic><Title>I think there is only one liberal</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244341743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Exactimundo!!!! Guy is a real sicko!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348244680140</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244782417-67</Id><Topic><Title>I think there is only one liberal</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244341743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seriously needs to get a job.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244782417</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244809061-68</Id><Title>WHY IS OBAMA STILL DEFENDING THE TERRORIST BUTCHERS OF LIBYA?</Title><Msg>Because he is their Muslim brother! All he does is make excuses for what they did and NO retaliation for it!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244809061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244821895-69</Id><Topic><Title>yes, it’s true. At the age of 16, Ryan began receiving Social Security benefits and saved them to help him pay for college. He stopped receiving benefits when he was 18 years old.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348244633312</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, give the guy a break. He was young, and in an experimental phase. What he did was WRONG. He knows that now, and wants to keep others from making the same mistake. =/</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348244821895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244896821-70</Id><Title>DOW</Title><Msg>Mother of all flash crashes will take out stock and bond markets, starting with big bond sell off as inflation level climbs, forcing bond sales. this will cause massive interest rate spike in the face of all the Fed money printing. Declining profits due to rising input prices and slowing sales will cause massive stock sell off. This bond and stock bubble will end in a big bang, not a slow whimper.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1348244896821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:28:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244905088-71</Id><Title>Cisco down almost 1% in an UP market??????????</Title><Msg>Option boys have Cisco by the ballz. Gotta love how they can manipulate the price for expiration.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348244905088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348244927407-72</Id><Topic><Title>I think there is only one liberal</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244341743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seriously needs to get a life...all he has is the Yahoo message boards.What a creep!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348244927407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:28:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348244966714-73</Id><Title>Why is Boarder Agent Brian Terry</Title><Msg>dead and Eric Holder still in office?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348244966714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:29:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245111947-74</Id><Topic><Title>DOW</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1348244896821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as long as the fed has his endless press and fixes rates risk trades are the only ones where you can make money. no doubt things will get bad but no one will sell stocks paying divs. with all this free money corps are making a killing. If earnings peak i still think people will chase PEs higher. no where else to invest. where is your money?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348245111947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:31:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245148830-75</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES, SCOTT RASMUSSEN IS A REAL IDIOT! AGREED!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348245148830</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245169187-76</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Boarder Agent Brian Terry</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348244966714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:29:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama would rather talk about trayvon.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348245169187</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348245201396-77</Id><Title>ECYT BIG NEWS coming Next week$$$$</Title><Msg>EC145, is not only about ovarian small lung and they will get approval in EU and us but it suits, of which Merck will pay all costs, lots of big market and important threatments EC20 can be used all over the place, not sure if ECYT wants to licence, but it can Tubulysin is huge, and confident in rest of pipeline. I know BIO stock with just 20% of potential trading at market cap of $ 3bln, don't forget market cap is still low, also $200 mln in cash, but I think it will go step by step. But do not be surprised this trading 24 months from now at $100+</Msg><Username>dansonstevie</Username><Timestamp>1348245201396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245271232-78</Id><Topic><Title>I think there is only one liberal</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348244341743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is rather sad one has nothing to do but this board where no one likes it....hence the constant changing of ids. I think it just wants attention. must be very lonely.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348245271232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:34:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245326142-79</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well that is EXACTLY what the bill would do, remove the violation. I bet if the 1 Billion was to buy another 2 fighter jets repukes would spend the money before the ink in the check was dry. But not for their BELOVED troops. Because they really love their troops don't they...EVERYTIME THEY SCREW THEM. I have establish a boolshjt no-fly-zone, and your shjjjt doesn't fly here. Try again IDIOT OF THE WEEK.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348245326142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245461284-80</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most accurate pollster in 2008 and you call him an idiot. You are HILARIOUS!!!!!!! LOLOLLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL What a dork!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348245461284</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:37:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245462335-81</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like you mean RASMUSSEN is hilarious...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348245462335</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245666280-82</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY STILL CAN WIN THIS ELECTION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348175725466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody has seen JC in Missouri yet ? Time is running out.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348245666280</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348245811676-83</Id><Title>LINDSEY GRAHAM TELLS IT LIKE IT IS...</Title><Msg>LMAO ! LMAO! LMAO ! Oh my God, he describes his base with a straight face. Lindsay Graham, R-SC “The demographics race we’re losing badly,” said Sen. Lindsey O. Graham (S.C.). “We’re not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term.” --Washington Post, August 29, 2012</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348245811676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245825847-84</Id><Topic><Title>100 days until TAX DOOMSDAY</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348244361515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your right but the public isn't being told by the media what is happenning</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348245825847</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:43:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245855240-85</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which is it ? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways ! What a maroon you are! What a dolt! AHAAHA!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348245855240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245898572-86</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>carey50 is flipping out.... shoots out an inference that SCOTT RASMUSSEN is wrong, then states how accurate RASMUSSEN POLLING is !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348245898572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348245974746-87</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY STILL CAN WIN THIS ELECTION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348175725466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>: romney still can win this election if he keeps his mouth shut!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348245974746</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:46:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246033287-88</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in (CSCO)</Title><Username>bernadettetqo227</Username><Timestamp>1348171563231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:06:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>anettetts445</Username><Timestamp>1348246033287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:47:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348246310208-89</Id><Title>ANN ROMNEY TO PEGGY NOONAN (Who called Mittens campaign a disaster) "STOP IT!!! YOU TRY AND DO THIS!" Boohoohoo, I'm a spoiled country-club wife, and you are being MEAN TO MY MITTY!!! Hey, Annie, if you can't take the heat, get out of the kitchen!!</Title><Msg>ANN ROMNEY TO PEGGY NOONAN (Who called Mittens campaign a disaster) "STOP IT!!! YOU TRY AND DO THIS!" Boohoohoo, I'm a spoiled country-club wife, and you are being MEAN TO MY MITTY!!! Hey, Annie, if you can't take the heat, get out of the kitchen!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348246310208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246332524-90</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's even funnier is you loons calling Rasmussen a repub shill but when he says something you like, he comes quite the authority.Your hypocrisy is amazingly funny!!! Notice none of you commented on Carvilles " The repubs are done for 40 years"remark. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Thats one of your dem"experts "LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348246332524</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246420774-91</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY STILL CAN WIN THIS ELECTION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348175725466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why bother posting such none sense? if obama has it in the bag than why rub it in? class eludes these pieces of spam.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348246420774</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:53:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246431509-92</Id><Topic><Title>SO HOW DID THAT FAST AND FURIOUS THINGY WORK OUT FOR YOU GOPPERS ROTFLMAO!!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348245307750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:35:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2010 the CONCONs (CONgressional RepubliCONservatives/CON-men) campaigned on the theme JOBS, JOBS, JOBS. Boehner still repeats this line at least once per day, just to keep in practice, and every time he sees somebody holding a phonecam within a 50 yard radius. Then CONCONs spent the entire past two years on (i) trying to nail Holder to the wall on Fast &amp; Furious, the final incarnation of a legacy ATF program begun in 2005, well before Obama's election, and (ii) forcing rape victims to carry their assailants' offspring to term. I know all this, but then again, I read. Hope the Democrats hammer this point home over and over and over during the next ~50 days.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348246431509</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:53:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246451163-93</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So which is it ? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways ! What a maroon you are! What a dolt! AHAAHA!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348246451163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:54:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246726377-94</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY STILL CAN WIN THIS ELECTION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348175725466</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 17:15:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he can pantomime throwing money from the back of a truck !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348246726377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:58:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348246775996-95</Id><Title>Lindsay Graham, R-SC “The demographics race we’re losing badly,” said Sen. Lindsey O. Graham (S.C.). “We’re not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term.” --Washington Post, August 29, 2012</Title><Msg>C'mon gotta get those angry white guys going !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348246775996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246836927-96</Id><Topic><Title>LINDSEY GRAHAM TELLS IT LIKE IT IS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348245811676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:43:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lindsay Gayham, you go girl !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348246836927</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348246996695-97</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you saying Rasmussen is always right??? Few people are. But next time he shows Romney in the lead I'll remind you how highly you regard Rasmussen's opinion.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL You are becoming very boring....as usual ....may have to say ta ta ,dolt.......LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348246996695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348247142784-98</Id><Title>Life span drops sharply for least-educated whites</Title><Msg>Bad news for the GOP, life span of poorly educated whites is dropping and this is the core constituency of the Republican party. The population is red states is overwhelmingly poor and uneducated while blue states are populated by higher earners that are better educated. Take a look at a ranking of the states based on median household income, the bottom of the list, or poorest states, are all red or purple while the top of the list is dominated by blue states. The life expectancy for those living in blue states continues to rise while the life expectancy of those living in red states is dropping. Evolution at it's best.</Msg><Username>chi_town_gramps</Username><Timestamp>1348247142784</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348247325798-99</Id><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Msg>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways ! What maroons you are! What a bunch of dolts! AHAAHA!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348247531970-100</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go back to the original thread,doofus.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Got you on the run!!!!!!!!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL BYEBYE....I WIN!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348247531970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:12:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348247568376-101</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>get back to work. egads...magoo gets free gov money at its "job".</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348247568376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348247587397-102</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice comeback for the redneck BOYsurfer. Instead of explaining his HALF truths and LIES that I exposed, he DIVERTS away from the truth as a typical LYING libTURD. DemoCRAPS are offering up a bill that VIOLATES the agreement and are using Veterans once again to DIVIDE. HATE and DIVISION, thats all you and your ILK know. You LYING trailer trash socialists sure don't disappoint do you?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348247587397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348247837569-103</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>by winning you mean you just have to wait for the next time RASMUSSEN shows ROMNEY ahead? If that's winning, I'd hate to see your definition of losing! (loooser!)</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247837569</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348247933487-104</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>gop obstructionists want NO BILLS to be passed.... their excuse, we need a balanced budget...... but when BUSH was Pres................. GOP- doesn't care about BALANCED BUDGET! RACIST GOP!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247933487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348247988329-105</Id><Title>Birthers saying the ex-governor MITT ROMNEY could not be a U.S. citizen because his father was a citizen of Mexico. Citizenship comes "primarily" through the father, the objection said!</Title><Msg>Birthers saying the ex-governor MITT ROMNEY could not be a U.S. citizen because his father was a citizen of Mexico. Citizenship comes "primarily" through the father, the objection said!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247988329</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248019351-106</Id><Topic><Title>Squeeze play in (CSCO)</Title><Username>bernadettetqo227</Username><Timestamp>1348171563231</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-20 16:06:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like these guys, they're really good.</Msg><Username>anettetts445</Username><Timestamp>1348248019351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348248070796-107</Id><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Msg>Lame stream media going down the toilet. Gallup says Americans don't trust the mainstream media to give the truth. LMMFAO. These people aren't professional journalists anymore, they are nothing more than gutter rumor reporting children. They have RUINED their profession.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348248209673-108</Id><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust fluteman_greg to tell the truth!</Title><Msg>MAGOO AGREES!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248209673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248234374-109</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That means 40% are gullible, naive, stupid, or a combination thereof.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348248234374</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:23:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248344584-110</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust fluteman_greg to tell the truth!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248209673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:23:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New poll says 99 %of those reading Magoo's post think he is a dork.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348248344584</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:25:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248470088-111</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust fluteman_greg to tell the truth!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248209673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:23:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought 99% of repukes had magoo on ignore? I guess you're extra special stupid then, no?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248470088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:27:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248499055-112</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But he can play a mean skin flute</Msg><Username>chi_town_gramps</Username><Timestamp>1348248499055</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248564643-113</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(loooser !) Isn't that what your boyfriend said is happening to your pooper...its getting looser????</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348248564643</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:29:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348248591110-114</Id><Title>SO LINDSAY GAYHAM FORGOT TO EXPLAIN WHY THERE AREN'T ENOUGH ANGRY WHITE GUYS ?</Title><Msg>Because the repukes can't get laid !!! Natural selection is taking its course. The average Rush/Fox listener is a single/divorced white guy whose wife who makes more money than him told him to GF himself ! Bwaaaaahahahahahahahah, see pukes evolution in display before your very own eyes.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348248591110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:29:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248710301-115</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY! So which is it REPUBS? IS SCOTT RASMUSSEN WRONG ABOUT THIS, or VERY ACCURATE? you can't have it both ways !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348247325798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:08:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>personal attacks = you lost the argument MAGOO WINS AGAIN!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248710301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248845718-116</Id><Topic><Title>SCOTT RASMUSSEN says MITT ROMNEY may be the END of the LINE for the REPUBLICAN PARTY!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo10</Username><Timestamp>1348242696629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 11:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called an "admission against interest" and can be quite telling. Look it up.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348248845718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248859182-117</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Finally Americans are starting to open their eyes to the LIES and half truth spread by the left leaning liberal media. As their viewership drops, one by one they will fall. Serves them right.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248859182</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348248891452-118</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust fluteman_greg to tell the truth!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248209673</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:23:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont know the percentage who have you on ignore...would you like me to join them...then pretty soon you really will be all alone..LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348248891452</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:34:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348248990151-119</Id><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Msg>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348249090116-120</Id><Title>gop obstructionists want NO BILLS to be passed.... their excuse, we need a balanced budget...... but when BUSH was Pres................. GOP- doesn't care about BALANCED BUDGET! RACIST GOP!</Title><Msg>gop obstructionists want NO BILLS to be passed.... their excuse, we need a balanced budget...... but when BUSH was Pres................. GOP- doesn't care about BALANCED BUDGET! RACIST GOP!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348249090116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:38:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348249222859-121</Id><Title>Obama ahead of RobbedMe by 20+ percent IN MASSACHUSETTS(!)</Title><Msg>LMAO~</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348249222859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348249290491-122</Id><Topic><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cogete en burro,ben de hoe!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348249290491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:41:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348249392000-123</Id><Title>BREAKING: OBAMA JUST HIT 72% ON INTRADE.......POOR WILLARD FELL THROUGH 30 SUPPORT AND IS NOW AT A PALTRY 28%.</Title><Msg>Time to buy PUTS ?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348249392000</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348249623748-124</Id><Title>ROMNEY proud to be called the GRANDFATHER OF OBAMACARE NOW? Aw c'mon MITT, let me in on this joke!</Title><Msg>ROMNEY proud to be called the GRANDFATHER OF OBAMACARE NOW? By allnewquincymagoo7 . 0 seconds ago . Permalink Aw c'mon MITT, let me in on this joke!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348249623748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:47:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348249656702-125</Id><Topic><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senor Romney esta cogiendose a la empleada. Si ! Ann no esta feliz, oh no !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348249656702</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348249765693-126</Id><Topic><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Él está en la casa de mierda</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348249765693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348249781333-127</Id><Topic><Title>SO LINDSAY GAYHAM FORGOT TO EXPLAIN WHY THERE AREN'T ENOUGH ANGRY WHITE GUYS ?</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348248591110</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:29:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If repukes could get laid, they would be democrats ! Bwaaaaaaaaaaaahahahahahah. But now, they are more like angry Arabs, Blue balls will do that to you.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348249781333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:49:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348249831490-128</Id><Title>Cain Says He Would Have Been Better than Romney</Title><Msg>Cain Says He Would Have Been Better than Romney When Herman Cain is taking shots at you, you know it's baaaaaaaad.... Herman Cain jabbed Mitt Romney while talking to the Gainesville Sun saying that he would have been doing better if he was the Republican presidential nominee, claiming he'd probably have a "substantial lead" on President Obama at this point. Said Cain: "The reason is quite simple: I have some depth to my ideas."</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348249831490</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:50:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250085202-129</Id><Topic><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's up? Did Magoo find a Spanish dictionary?Or is he going for the Latino posters now?LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348250085202</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:54:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250179496-130</Id><Title>Look At All This Socialist Redistribution! But some of you think these rich folks need another tax cut...for some reason...</Title><Msg>Look At All This Socialist Redistribution! But some of you think these rich folks need another tax cut...for some reason... JM Ashby: According to Forbes magazine, growth in the net worth of the wealthiest Americans “far outpaced” the rest of the economy over the past year. (Reuters) – The net worth of the richest Americans grew by 13 percent in the past year to $1.7 trillion, Forbes magazine said on Wednesday, and a familiar cast populated the top of the annual list, including Bill Gates, Warren Buffett, Larry Ellison and the Koch brothers. [...] “The gap between the very rich and merely rich increased and helped drive up the average net worth of The Forbes 400 members to an all-time record $4.2 billion,” said Forbes Senior Wealth Editor Luisa Kroll. Collectively, this group’s net worth is the equivalent of one-eighth of the entire U.S. economy, which stood at $13.56 trillion in real terms according to the latest government data. But the 13 percent growth in the wealth of the richest Americans far outpaced that of the economy overall, helping widen the chasm between rich and poor. Forbes attributed the growth in net worth in part to the performance of the stock market and a recovering real estate market. I suppose Fox News is right. There is redistribution happening in this country, but isn’t going to the bottom. Some of those who the money is going too probably are members of the 47 percent who pay no federal income taxes, however.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348250179496</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250246237-131</Id><Title>REPUKES CAN'T LET THE WAR ON WOMEN GO...</Title><Msg>The American Taliban Society in action. What 'tard associates themselves with these creeps ? Oh wait I see flutie, caps, and bird brain raising their hands. Will they ever get laid ? Doubt it. WASHINGTON, DC — Literature being handed out at the Values Voter Summit on Friday attacks women for being “immodest” and extolled them to “go home and put some clothes on!” In flyers and brochures on display at Values Voters, the social conservative conference where Republican Vice Presidential nominee Paul Ryan spoke, an organization called Modesty Matters criticized women for dressing “immodestly” at church, and blamed women for causing men to stare lustfully at them. Women must “embrace MODESTY in dress and behavior,” one of the handouts read. Women dressed immodestly in church are “an insult to a holy God,” another said.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348250246237</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:57:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250269197-132</Id><Topic><Title>¿Dónde está Senor Romney? ¿Que?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348248990151</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:36:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of his new boyfriends is from Guatemala.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348250269197</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250312394-133</Id><Title>Romney to Release 2011 Tax Returns; Paid $1.9M on $13.7M</Title><Msg>........</Msg><Username>multiuse2012</Username><Timestamp>1348250312394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250328044-134</Id><Topic><Title>auntie carey says he married a guy named ben de hoe</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348250302188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Senor Butthead?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348250328044</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250599586-135</Id><Topic><Title>auntie carey says he married a guy named ben de hoe</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348250302188</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost as dumb as you posting about" INTADE" earlier isn't it.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Since I'm not little kid I chose to ignore it but you asked for it. Does your foot taste good?/LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348250599586</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:03:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250662144-136</Id><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Msg>He won't release them but is busy telling everyone he has always payed at least 13% in taxes, LOL So now we know the reason he won't release his taxes isn't because he once never paid taxes. So we know it is for an even worse reason, it is because he is a tax felon who hid his money overseas but then took the offered amnesty and paid the penalty. Gonna be interesting in the debate when someone asks him out right if he took advantage of the tax amnesty, will he confess or lie??</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250678950-137</Id><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Msg>Asked about the Fast and Furious program at the Univision forum on Thursday, President Obama falsely claimed that the program began under President George W. Bush.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250703163-138</Id><Topic><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In actuality, the Fast and Furious program was started in October 2009, nine months into the Obama presidency.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250703163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:05:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250720211-139</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to Release 2011 Tax Returns; Paid $1.9M on $13.7M</Title><Username>multiuse2012</Username><Timestamp>1348250312394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like he's paying MORE than his fair share.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348250720211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:05:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250734902-140</Id><Topic><Title>INTADE HASOBAMA @ 70% -- NOT ONE SINGLE POLL ON THE PLANET HAS MITT THE TWIT LEADING.....ROTFLMAO!!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348245533422</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:38:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump... what is an " INTADE HASOBAMA"?????????? TOOOOOOOO FUNNNNEEEEEEEE Suck that foot,JuniorLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348250734902</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250813013-141</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious when things get so bad that RobbedMe wants to change the subject BACK to his tax returns...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348250813013</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:06:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348250828168-142</Id><Title>New language?????</Title><Msg>"INTADE HASOBAMA" HILARIOUS !!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348250828168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:07:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250832355-143</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious when things get so bad that RobbedMe wants to change the subject BACK to his tax returns...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348250832355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250890211-144</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to Release 2011 Tax Returns; Paid $1.9M on $13.7M</Title><Username>multiuse2012</Username><Timestamp>1348250312394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt's selective talking about his past returns without releasing them reminds me of Nixon saying he would only release some of the tapes, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250890211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250902619-145</Id><Topic><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama lies and blames bush again hahahahahaha what a creep.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250902619</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:08:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348250935575-146</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OHHHH NO, Flutie's crying again. He is the John Bonher of the board. " I am taking my ball and playing no more. Bwwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa ! I am flutie and I hurt easy. Bwwwwwwwwwwwwwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaa"</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348250935575</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:08:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251055929-147</Id><Topic><Title>New language?????</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348250828168</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:07:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still want to play the misspelling/typo game, Junior???? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL GOTCHA, FOOL!!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348251055929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251135565-148</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I didn't expect you to understand or comprehend what the American people are thinking. Thanks for verifying your ignorance.......AGAIN. FYI, tried to buy some more CerAnt today, order wouldn't go thru. LMMFAO at the board Janitor.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348251135565</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251288333-149</Id><Topic><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348251288333</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:14:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251335794-150</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting the twit showed tax returns to McCain before McCain chose Palin. What does that tell us?</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348251335794</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:15:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251386581-151</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL yeah the lame stream media isn't fact based like FAUX LOL funny no other media has gone to court to defend their right to lie. By Mike Gaddy. On February 14, a Florida Appeals court ruled there is absolutely nothing illegal about lying, concealing or distorting information by a major press organization. The court reversed the $425,000 jury verdict in favor of journalist Jane Akre who charged she was pressured by Fox Television management and lawyers to air what she knew and documented to be false information. The ruling basically declares it is technically not against any law, rule, or regulation to deliberately lie or distort the news on a television broadcast.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348251386581</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348251452164-152</Id><Title>Ann Ronmey to other republicans "STOP IT",,"STOP IT"</Title><Msg>Mitt is always right,,,"STOP IT,,,STOP IT"</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1348251452164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:17:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251470914-153</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to Release 2011 Tax Returns; Paid $1.9M on $13.7M</Title><Username>multiuse2012</Username><Timestamp>1348250312394</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:58:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well at least he's consistent on tax rate ... nailed 13.9% AGAIN. (Prolly the ONLY thing ol' Myth is consistent on, though...)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348251470914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251483872-154</Id><Topic><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look up operation wide receiver.</Msg><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1348251483872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:18:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251492876-155</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So let me get this straight, you LIARS accused Romney of NOT paying taxes, now that he has released his 2011 numbers which show ETR of 14% and also 13% in Charity now you are claiming he hid money and is a tax felon. Do you know the difference anymore when you LIE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348251492876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:18:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251556381-156</Id><Topic><Title>ANN ROMNEY TO PEGGY NOONAN (Who called Mittens campaign a disaster) "STOP IT!!! YOU TRY AND DO THIS!" Boohoohoo, I'm a spoiled country-club wife, and you are being MEAN TO MY MITTY!!! Hey, Annie, if you can't take the heat, get out of the kitchen!!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348246310208</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:51:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt hides behind Ann's skirt, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348251556381</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348251574334-157</Id><Title>Mitt Ronmey "trust me about my taxes,,,,,Hell NO,,,SHOW YOUR TAXES !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Not for 2 years,,you tax cheater,,MITT IS UNFIT</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1348251574334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251600179-158</Id><Topic><Title>New Poll shows 60% of Americans don't trust Media to tell the truth</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348248070796</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 13:21:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Bwwwwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, I am a cry baby. While surf was architecting the fiber optic structure of the country I was laying sheet rock with my Mexican crew. Bwwwwwwwwaaaaaaaaaa. My name is Flutie and I like to whine. Bwwwwaaaaaaaaaaaaa"</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348251600179</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251641899-159</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt got an extension on 2011 taxes. So, has he FINALLY sent his tax info to the IRS like most of us did by April 15??</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348251641899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:20:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251648821-160</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You CRYBABY whiners are never happy. You WHINE about Romneys tax returns , then you WHINE when they're released. Interesting that YOU make excuses for O'Losers past records that he has paid lawyers MILLIONS to seal up and REFUSES to release. Go ahead HYPOCRITE, Splain it away.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348251648821</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:20:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251682304-161</Id><Topic><Title>lies lies lies</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348250678950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348251682304</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:21:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348251713241-162</Id><Title>Junior trying to contact " INTADE" ...no luck</Title><Msg>HILARIOUS!!!!!!!" "INTADE" LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Point out some more boo-boos by other posters,ding-a-ling. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL who is HASOBAMA???? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348251713241</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:21:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348251937112-163</Id><Topic><Title>Junior trying to contact " INTADE" ...no luck</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348251713241</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:21:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jackwagon Junior is on iggy for daily retardation.....I wouldn't know.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348251937112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348252051029-164</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're a defective, and I haven't the extra time to tutor defectives today. You'll have to ask somebody else.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348252051029</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:27:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348252292634-165</Id><Topic><Title>Lindsay Graham, R-SC “The demographics race we’re losing badly,” said Sen. Lindsey O. Graham (S.C.). “We’re not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term.” --Washington Post, August 29, 2012</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348246775996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can repukes procreate more angry white men if they can't get laid ? The last time an Oxycotin Rush follower got laid was when he bang his dead mother in a casket. And that is the absolute truth. Look it up !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348252292634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:31:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348252363975-166</Id><Title>If you want to know what a " concure"is ,ask Junior. He knows!</Title><Msg>Oh,boy JEEZ You sure stepped in it,Junior LOLOLOLOLOL Taking you off ignore has been wonderful.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL I'm laughing my fanny off at you!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348252363975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:32:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348252594276-167</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO will become the stock to follow this year.</Title><Username>markferland662</Username><Timestamp>1348079683828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-19 14:34:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Awesome</Msg><Username>nelsoneugene277</Username><Timestamp>1348252594276</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:36:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348252646974-168</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"CONCURES"??????? #$%$ is that????LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Want to keep on playing?????? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348252646974</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348253001849-169</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GW's was called operation wide receiver. Next...</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348253001849</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:43:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348253308248-170</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would Obama declare 'Executive Privilege' to cover up Bush's deal? Hum, now we need to get to the bottom of this, Brain Terry is still dead? Bring it on ---------------- you liberal Socialist Tree Hugging Pecker-woods!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348253308248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:48:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348253752805-171</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FACT started under odopy...on yahoo front page news. obama lied and now being exposed as the fraud he is. dont worry a few more of these and obama is toast. see the media wants to keep the race close so they go back and forth will mud throwing. if they keep it close they make more money on the news. watch mitt will be leading polls soon.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348253752805</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254001376-172</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brian Terry was killed on Obama's watch with guns supplied by the ATF on Obama's watch.Libs still want to blame Bush. Nobody buying that.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348254001376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:00:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348254067281-173</Id><Title>remember the media elects the president</Title><Msg>its all about spin and what they forget to mention. close races sell papers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254067281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:01:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348254072181-174</Id><Title>remember the media elects the president</Title><Msg>its all about spin and what they forget to mention. close races sell papers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254072181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254103161-175</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bwwwwwahahahah. You are right ! Let's get back to my taxes, the tape is killing me. And Lindsay Gayham saying we are running out of white angry dudes is really a shocking truth. Oh lord, instead of running for president I should have ridden Rafalca like a Pegasus all the way to Kolob !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348254103161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:01:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254189226-176</Id><Topic><Title>FAST &amp; FURIOUS: = BUSH OPERATION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348251583925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:19:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also,the Terry family holds the Obama administration responsible so what the rest of us think is not important.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348254189226</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348254217618-177</Id><Title>These numbers proposed by the Minneapolis FED should be good for Cisco</Title><Msg>Proposed numbers (from Minn. FED): 1. 5.5% target for unemployment 2. 2.25% target for inflation 3. 4 years of no rise in interest rates, if inflation target is not breached If we are going to create jobs in the USA, with major slowdowns occuring in the rest of the world, we need a private industry/ government blend (new, innovative economics) with emphases on the smart-grid, infrastructure, energy independence, housing, financial, agri-business, and advanced technology (bio, military, information, energy, etc).</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1348254217618</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254263119-178</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean like obama took every tax loop hole to pay only 20% on his taxes? the problem is not people like mitt and obama it is the tax code you idiot! get a clue. liberals think people should try to pay the highest taxes they can. fn idiot how do you even tie your shoes amazes me?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254263119</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:04:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254306102-179</Id><Topic><Title>40 REPUKES SPIT ON VETERAN's FACES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348205054762</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 01:24:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>those veterans are part of the 47%, the GOP doesn't represent them</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348254306102</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:05:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348254592572-180</Id><Title>obama paid 20% tax rate</Title><Msg>and took every tax loop hole possible, liberals should be as outraged as they are with mitt. the problem is not mitts tax rate you idiots it is the american tax code. both mitt and obama used everyone available to them...why wouldnt they you idiots. liberals shop around for the highest price. so far away from reality it hurts...see what happens when you coddle these children you make them dumb.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254592572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348254733817-181</Id><Topic><Title>obama paid 20% tax rate</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254592572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes you pinhead, that is why Obama is trying to raise taxes on himself and Romney, it's Romney who's policies would have him paying less then 1% tax</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348254733817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:12:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348255150706-182</Id><Topic><Title>obama paid 20% tax rate</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254592572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what obama "wants to do" and does are two very different things. if he really wanted that then he could have done it with majority house...right? nope what did he do extended the bush cuts he stated got us in this mess in the first place.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255150706</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:19:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348255153471-183</Id><Title>At least O-Whimpy is uniting the MOOOOOOSLIMEs</Title><Msg>DEPORT ALL FOREIGN mooooolsime students and OUT LAW ISLAM !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348255153471</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:19:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348255308319-184</Id><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Msg>the middle class. what a slap in the face.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348255318215-185</Id><Topic><Title>deadpainting has been warned by the feds to stay away from children</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348254726418</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:12:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was your daddy ever warned to stay away from your pooper??</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348255318215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348255587498-186</Id><Title>What does the ACLU and LIBS have to say about it ?</Title><Msg>Ameri-Phobia ! when will the hate stop ! Americans are so offened watching it take place all over the world ! I bet booting foreign islamic students would bring the BROS back home fall in line then...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348255587498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348255771255-187</Id><Topic><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lower ratethan what? Buzz Fruck? He only paid 13% income taxes on money he didn't work for but earned through manipulating companies, are you a #$%$ or what? Reminds me of a quote: "Hey Mitt!, you know that huge lead Obama has?... You Built That!"</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348255771255</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:29:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348255856633-188</Id><Topic><Title>obama paid 20% tax rate</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254592572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt Romney's trustee said in a campaign press release that Romney artificially inflated his own effective tax rate so it would remain above 13 percent by deferring $1.75 million in charitable deductions. Romney had previously said that none of his last decade of tax returns dipped below that 13 percent threshold. In an interview with ABC News in July, however, Romney dismissed the idea that he would ever pay more taxes than legally owed, saying if he did so he wouldn't be "qualified" to be president. Woopsie flipping again.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348255856633</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:30:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348255918563-189</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt talking about his past tax returns</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348250662144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 14:04:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when you learn how the real world works maybe you will understand...see unlike you who fills out a form on line and gets all the money back...mitts taxes have to be looked over by many tax accountants because tax code law books are bigger than the bible. it takes a while and if he misses one law he is subject to communist type punishment. the government grants this to corps with a penalty because they know how hard taxes are to do. perfectly legal.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255918563</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:31:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348256035691-190</Id><Topic><Title>obama paid 20% tax rate</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254592572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:09:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitt "flip flops" obama "evolves" hahahahahahahaha idiots.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348256035691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348256331287-191</Id><Topic><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL now that's funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348256331287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:38:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257071137-192</Id><Topic><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the reason is because the GOP blocked his bill to raise taxes on the wealthy, any other questions?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348257071137</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257543871-193</Id><Topic><Title>"Hey Mitt!, you know that huge lead Obama has?... You Built That!"</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348257515113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that's funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348257543871</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257550850-194</Id><Topic><Title>remember the media elects the president</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348254072181</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:01:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so then you already know who your next pres will be........ thanks for being honest with the board finally!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348257550850</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:59:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348257604296-195</Id><Title>Mitt now losing the old vote</Title><Msg>Will Mitt's defeat be worse then Goldwater's? If so will he run again in 2016? (CBS News) NEW ORLEANS - The audience reception for President Obama and Paul Ryan at Friday's AARP convention couldn't have differed more: Obama won cheers for discussing the health care law, while Ryan drew the most aggressively negative response he has faced as a GOP vice presidential candidate for vowing to repeal it. Obama's and Ryan's back-to-back speeches before the nation's largest senior citizens lobby also exposed just how wide the gulf is between their ideas on how to reform America's entitlement programs, as each man insinuated that the other's plan spelled certain destruction for the nation's seniors. The audience of several thousand clearly came down on Obama's side. Despite Ryan's exhortations that the president had "turned Medicare into a piggy bank for Obamacare" cutting $716 billion from provider payments - a claim that fact-checking watchdogs have judged to be largely false -- he was met with a loud round of boos and cries of "no!" as he pledged to repeal the health care reform law, which AARP as an organization supported.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348257604296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:00:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257615718-196</Id><Topic><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mitt did not work? hahahahahahah yes the only work in america is getting paid to stay home and write books about yourself. hahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348257615718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257825637-197</Id><Topic><Title>"Hey Mitt!, you know that huge lead Obama has?... You Built That!"</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348257515113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's ok ! anytime magoo can be of assistance !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348257825637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:03:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348257908623-198</Id><Title>You want to see where the real voter fraud is being committed, look at the GOP voter suppression crap.</Title><Msg>You want to see where the real voter fraud is being committed, look at the GOP voter suppression crap.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348257908623</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:05:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348257917853-199</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt Romney's trustee said in a campaign press release that Romney artificially inflated his own effective tax rate so it would remain above 13 percent by deferring $1.75 million in charitable deductions.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348256133341</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:35:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How much kick back got from the charitable organization later on?</Msg><Username>hzhou6310</Username><Timestamp>1348257917853</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:05:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348258321186-200</Id><Title>Palin would have been a better pick than this Ryan idiot. At least she could tell a believable lie. And Romney would be polling in the 45% range instead of 28%</Title><Msg>Palin would have been a better pick than this Ryan idiot. At least she could tell a believable lie. And Romney would be polling in the 45% range instead of 28% It's over REPUBS.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348258321186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348258760384-201</Id><Title>Romney: If my grandkids were gay, "I'd want them to be happy"</Title><Msg>Does that mean he supports gay marriage now? Is he flipping back?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348258760384</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:19:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348258895595-202</Id><Topic><Title>You want to see where the real voter fraud is being committed, look at the GOP voter suppression crap.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1348257908623</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:05:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>real tax payer fraud look to magoo's useless government job.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348258895595</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:21:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348259121718-203</Id><Title>ONE CHURCH ABUSES WOMEN THE OTHER LITTLE BOYS...</Title><Msg>Quite the family values you've got going in that repuke ticket !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348259121718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348259239874-204</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another Obama accomplishments</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348259239874</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348259361666-205</Id><Topic><Title>100 days until TAX DOOMSDAY</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348244361515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbuummpp</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348259361666</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348259765469-206</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like i said the only job he cares about is his. he wants the vacation time and air force one.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348259765469</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260122934-207</Id><Topic><Title>"Hey Mitt!, you know that huge lead Obama has?... You Built That!"</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348257515113</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:58:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol now that's funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348260122934</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:42:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260166570-208</Id><Topic><Title>100 days until TAX DOOMSDAY</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348244361515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:19:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>media has their own agenda. we need our schools to teach this kind of stuff. how the fed works national debt...people who look to media for a lesson are going to learn alright. the basic stuff that schools need to teach are the way our system is set up. most americans dont understand what is going on. they are giving obama credit for what ben has been doing. totally wrong. bens press causes pain later down the road but people blame the president. it is so messed up right now no one has any idea how this ends. really cant find this sort of thing in history books.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348260166570</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260233405-209</Id><Topic><Title>ONE CHURCH ABUSES WOMEN THE OTHER LITTLE BOYS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348259121718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guns don't kill, people do. NO different with with MOST religions, it's not the church it's MAN......Well unless your a muslim, then it's NORMAL to abuse Women.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260233405</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:43:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348260241686-210</Id><Title>Conservatives are stuck</Title><Msg>if they vote for Romney and he wins they will never nominate a true conservative, LOL True conservatives will vote for JOHNSON!!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348260241686</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348260357370-211</Id><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Msg>I think he's abusing the pills. NOBODY is this blatantly retarded.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260491777-212</Id><Topic><Title>ONE CHURCH ABUSES WOMEN THE OTHER LITTLE BOYS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348259121718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes bill clinton and david letterman abused women...what is your point?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348260491777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348260658261-213</Id><Title>We built that!</Title><Msg>during WWII it was corp america who converted its factories to make the stuff that won the war. not gov workers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348260658261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:50:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348260771410-214</Id><Title>When will the media acknowledge that O'Loser LIED to the American people</Title><Msg>Obama administration LIED to the AMerican people when they BLAMED the terrorist attack on a silly film instead of having a handle on foreign affairs. They didn't bother looking for the truth, instead they went into BLAME mode which is what they do best. Looks like this administration shoots first and then aims later. Oopsie...looks like an Obumbles backfire. Community organizing at its finest.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260771410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260849981-215</Id><Topic><Title>When will the media acknowledge that O'Loser LIED to the American people</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260771410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait when the polls get lopsided the media will pick the other side. close elections sell papers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348260849981</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348260930743-216</Id><Topic><Title>ONE CHURCH ABUSES WOMEN THE OTHER LITTLE BOYS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348259121718</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:25:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO ! The church IS man. And YOUR man believe in the dogma WRITTEN at his church. May I remind you Flutie that Surf's NO-BOOSHJJT-FLY-ZONE is activated and running. You are shot down...AGAIN ! Many religions have recently begun changing in an attempt to equalize the roles and responsibilities of men and women. Mormonism is one of the exceptions. The Mormon position on women has changed little since the early 1800's, when the official view was that "woman's primary place is in the home, where she is to rear children and abide by the righteous counsel of her husband" (McConkie 844). Mormonism has created an ingenious system of oppression, in which opposition towards men is tantamount to arguing with God. The Mormon religion makes no distinction between clergy and laity, at least with regard to men (Laake 9). All Mormon men are ordained as members of the "priesthood," with the absolute authority to preach the gospel, bestow blessings, prophecy, perform healings and baptisms, and generally speak for God. "Their priesthood gives them the right to advise and instruct the Saints (i.e., Mormons), and their jurisdiction extends over all things spiritual and temporal" (Snowden 134). At age twelve, boys become members of the Aaronic, or lesser priesthood, and at nineteen become eligible for the Melchezedek, or higher priesthood. Members of either priesthood are higher authorities on everything than are non-members. Women are, of course, excluded from the priesthood. This practice in effect says that a woman's prepubescent son is more qualified to advise her than she is to advise him.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348260930743</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:55:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348261172604-217</Id><Title>ANOTHER 9-11 INSIDE JOB IN THE WORKS...</Title><Msg>Reuters: Bank of America, Chase, Citi targeted by Iranian hackers. Hey, we need an excuse don't we ? If nuclear threat does not do it, the israelis will run the next inside job until it happens.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348261172604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:59:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348261333671-218</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER 9-11 INSIDE JOB IN THE WORKS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348261172604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only a libTURD bigot can mention a possible Iranian attack on American banks and somehow bring up Israel. You are what your are, eh BOYsurfer.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348261333671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:02:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348261928281-219</Id><Title>Conservative pundits told Romney he needs to get out and fight!!!</Title><Msg>So he had Ann come out and ask them to stop picking on him, LOL just to funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348261928281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:12:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348262092961-220</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ad hominems are simply an admission you are unable to refute the facts.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348262092961</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:14:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348262193098-221</Id><Topic><Title>how come obama paid a lower rate than</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1348255308319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 15:21:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he is a lot smarter? The only people dumber than Obama, are those that voted for him and repeat his lies.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348262193098</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348262361597-222</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ad hominem...... Did they teach you that in Media Matters school. How do you debate a RETARD. How do you engage with a person who posts jibberish. You post 24/7 diarrehea of the mouth, mostly repeating FAR LEFT lies or talking points. Have a nice day RETARD.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348262361597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:19:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348262916061-223</Id><Title>Hanky panky in Columbia</Title><Msg>Appears some White House people were involved in the Columbian prostitution scandal along with the Secret Service .Since most liberal men prefer other men ,we'll probably hear about W.H.staffers and young boys in Columbia. Tsk tsk tsk.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348262916061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263200865-224</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ad hominems are simply an admission you are unable to refute the facts. you respond with an ad hominem after you look it up, just to funny "Hey Mitt!, you know that huge lead Obama has?... You Built That!" By juniorsclassmate_5 . 42 minutes ago . Permalink</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348263200865</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263242482-225</Id><Topic><Title>When will the media acknowledge that O'Loser LIED to the American people</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260771410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama and his lackeys LIED from day 1, blaming a stupid film instead of being responsible and telling the truth. Maybe they were just so INEPT they really don't have a clue what is going on.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348263242482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263354689-226</Id><Topic><Title>Conservative pundits told Romney he needs to get out and fight!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348261928281</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:12:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's twit's current deferment!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1348263354689</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:35:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263463079-227</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on dumb dumb, do you have to plagiarize another poster because you're so STUPID. I was right......DUMB DUMB.... LMMFAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348263463079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:37:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263570441-228</Id><Topic><Title>When will the media acknowledge that O'Loser LIED to the American people</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260771410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:52:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever credibility Susan Rice and Jay Carney had was effectively destroyed this week.No matter your party most people realize what really happened in Libya and dont appreciate being lied to by Obama's lackeys.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348263570441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348263984122-229</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER 9-11 INSIDE JOB IN THE WORKS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348261172604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember the 5 Mosaad agents that were jumping up and down on the NJ side as the towers disintegrated ? Flutedumb, it isn't an Iranian anything. The jooos are at it again and you are being sold another war package, all wrapped in a nice white and blue bow tie and a star of david for a sticky bonnet. Go ahead sucker boy, go to you tube and search for Mossad Truck Bombs on Sept 11</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348263984122</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348264240406-230</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan I resent you beating up on flutedumb after 3PM on Fridays. You know the sheet rock crew quits early and he gets to hit the Popoff by 3:30PM. By 4PM he is splattered at the back of the trailer totally defenseless. Shame on you Ivan !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348264240406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:50:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348264396096-231</Id><Title>Looks like #$%$ Harry Reid will be PROVEN a LIAR</Title><Msg>Romney disclosed today that he will aslo release details of 20 years worth of tax returns. His average annual effective rate over the 20 years was 20.2%. Looks like alot of BIG MOUTH LIARS on this board will be MUTE over this issue in the coming days. I wonder how long it will take that LIAR Harry Reid to apologize? Chickens coming home to roost, eh libTARDS?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348264396096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:53:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348264616454-232</Id><Topic><Title>Does Dumb Dumb self medicate</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348260357370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:45:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gosh BOYsurfer, if you're going to make a feeble attempt at making fun of me maybe you should know what you're talking about. You HANG drywall, you don't lay it. I thought sure a janitor would know this. On a side note for the board LIAR, I can't get a market order filled for Cerant. You know the company you owned.......Wasssup wit dat?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348264616454</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348264900904-233</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER 9-11 INSIDE JOB IN THE WORKS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348261172604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BIGOT........You are what you are....well besides being a clown with the experience of a Janitor. Don't you have to go push a mop on Friday nights? I'm concerned.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348264900904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:01:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348264995592-234</Id><Topic><Title>Looks like #$%$ Harry Reid will be PROVEN a LIAR</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348264396096</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:53:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how mitt still won't release his tax returns, guess he doesn't want to show how he avoided taxes with illegal offshore accounts,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348264995592</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348265119327-235</Id><Title>Remember when Nixon tried to get away</Title><Msg>with releasing just some of the tapes, the ones that didn't implicate him? remember when Mitt tried to get away with releasing just part of this returns, the ones that didn't implicate him?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265119327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348265615655-236</Id><Title>Obama 317 Mitt 191</Title><Msg>latest electoral college estimates, LOL Mitt going down like Goldwater, LOL I estimate smart conservatives (what few there are) will vote Johnson and not sacrifice their principles to support Mitt a northern liberal who is going to lose anyway.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265615655</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348265897684-237</Id><Title>Romney overpaid his taxes!!!</Title><Msg>That means all that money can't go to creating jobs, guess he really doesn't want Americans to go back to work.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265897684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348266267899-238</Id><Title>Iran admits it lied</Title><Msg>just like Fox news admitted in court it lies, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348266267899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:24:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348267078593-239</Id><Title>In July the baggers told us how Obama was going down in flames</Title><Msg>now the GOPERS are all running from Mitt, LOL, they know the DNC will hold the Senate and pick up a lot of seats in the House. (everyone but the birdbrain and his other alias know this to be true) But more important, Brown is losing crossover appeal. The number of Democrats who said they were backing the Senator decreased by more than a fifth since May, even as Brown’s robust +31 popularity in the state hardly moved. And if you listen to the candidate himself, he seems worried that his interparty appeal is being compromised by the national Republican Party. Brown was quick to disavow Todd Akin’s comments on rape and even quicker to distance himself from Mitt Romney’s videotaped remarks disparaging the 47% of Americans who don’t pay federal income taxes. “I’m Scott Brown, he’s Mitt Romney. We disagree on a whole host of things,” Brown told TIME on Wednesday. “I lived in 17 houses by the time I was 18. My mom got public assistance for a short period of time. I don’t think anybody is on public assistance because they want to be.” But it isn’t just the case of one moderate Senator in a liberally inclined state. Senator Dean Heller of Nevada, locked in a tight race with Representative Shelley Berkley, similarly disavowed Romney’s worldview espoused in the video posted by Mother Jones. “I have a very different view of the world, having grown up, as I said, with a father who was an auto mechanic and a mother who was a school cook and five brothers and sisters,” Heller said. “I believe in a safety net. I believe that’s one of the responsibilities of the federal government.” Wisconsin’s Thompson was more blunt in a local TV interview. “You know, whether you’re a Democrat or Republican, if your standard bearer for the presidency is not doing well, it’s going to reflect on the down ballot,” he said. I have no idea what pushed Menino over the edge for Warren. Maybe it was always in the cards. But Republicans like Scott Brown need Democratic supporters to win. A juiced conservative base may (or may not) help Romney nationally, but ideological warfare appears to be damaging Republican prospects down ballot. And regardless of who wins the White House, control of the Senate will help determine what the next President is able to accomplish with his term.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348267078593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348267243286-240</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER 9-11 INSIDE JOB IN THE WORKS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348261172604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:59:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's dad was smart, that is why he left Sadaam in place AND in check, but the family idiot came along and said, "Old man you know jack", nothing worse than an idiot with ambition.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348267243286</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:40:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348267357035-241</Id><Title>WILLARD/OBAMA this Sunday on 60 MINUTES...</Title><Msg>Expect Willard to be another 3 points down by Monday.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348267357035</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:42:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348268742058-242</Id><Topic><Title>Romney overpaid his taxes!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265897684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:18:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What it means is YOU and Reid "LIE" in the same bed. ha ha YOU LIED, Romney told the truth.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348268742058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:05:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348269039183-243</Id><Topic><Title>In July the baggers told us how Obama was going down in flames</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348267078593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:37:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Menino was impressed with her Indian heritage, you schmuck. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348269039183</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:10:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348269176915-244</Id><Topic><Title>Romney overpaid his taxes!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265897684</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:18:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No matter what Romney reveals about his taxes,it will never satisfy the loons.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348269176915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:12:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348269359625-245</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Nixon tried to get away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265119327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember when Obama didn't release his school records?/</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348269359625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348269533253-246</Id><Topic><Title>Hanky panky in Columbia</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348262916061</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 17:28:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb.Ivan would like the name of the hotel with the young boys.LOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348269533253</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 19:18:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348272214248-247</Id><Topic><Title>### CSCO Featured on Squawk Box ###</Title><Username>culttradeers</Username><Timestamp>1347910268996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>great info</Msg><Username>besofts</Username><Timestamp>1348272214248</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 20:03:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348275338740-248</Id><Title>Origin of Left &amp; Right</Title><Msg>Ecclesiastes 10:2-3 New International Version (NIV) 2 The heart of the wise inclines to the right, but the heart of the fool to the left. 3 Even as fools walk along the road, they lack sense and show everyone how stupid they are.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348275338740</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 20:55:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348276186600-249</Id><Title>And now for a Spelling Lesson...</Title><Msg>The last four letters in American..........I Can The last four letters in Republican.......I Can The last four letters in Democrats........Rats End of lesson… test to follow November 6, 2012. Remember, November is to be set aside as rodent removal month.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348276186600</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:09:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348276446191-250</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes! the filthy freeloading Obamarat is a total leech who does nothing most of the time but screw around, but then again, we don't want the pinko to be successul, he's already totally screwed up our nation's morality and economy for decades to come!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348276446191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348276538085-251</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all of his "accomplishments" are built on total lies and exagerations--He didn't build that!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348276538085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:15:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348279149749-252</Id><Title>Ignore the polls saying Obama is going to win</Title><Msg>Republicans are getting depressed under an avalanche of polling suggesting that an Obama victory is in the offing. They, in fact, suggest no such thing! Here's why: 1. All of the polling out there uses some variant of the 2008 election turnout as its model for weighting respondents and this overstates the Democratic vote by a huge margin. In English, this means that when you do a poll you ask people if they are likely to vote. But any telephone survey always has too few blacks, Latinos, and young people and too many elderly in its sample. That's because some don't have landlines or are rarely at home or don't speak English well enough to be interviewed or don't have time to talk. Elderly are overstated because they tend to be home and to have time. So you need to increase the weight given to interviews with young people, blacks and Latinos and count those with seniors a bit less. Normally, this task is not difficult. Over the years, the black, Latino, young, and elderly proportion of the electorate has been fairly constant from election to election, except for a gradual increase in the Hispanic vote. You just need to look back at the last election to weight your polling numbers for this one. But 2008 was no ordinary election. Blacks, for example, usually cast only 11% of the vote, but, in 2008, they made up 14% of the vote. Latinos increased their share of the vote by 1.5% and college kids almost doubled their vote share. Almost all pollsters are using the 2008 turnout models in weighting their samples. Rasmussen, more accurately, uses a mixture of 2008 and 2004 turnouts in determining his sample. That's why his data usually is better for Romney. But polling indicates a widespread lack of enthusiasm among Obama's core demographic support due to high unemployment, disappointment with his policies and performance, and the lack of novelty in voting for a black candidate now that he has already served as president. If you adjust virtually any of the published polls to reflect the 2004 vote, not the 2008 vote, they show the race either tied or Romney ahead, a view much closer to reality. 2. Almost all of the published polls show Obama getting less than 50% of the vote and less than 50% job approval. A majority of the voters either support Romney or are undecided in almost every poll. But the fact is that the undecided vote always goes against the incumbent. In 1980 (the last time an incumbent Democrat was beaten), for example, the Gallup Poll of October 27th had Carter ahead by 45-39. Their survey on November 2nd showed Reagan catching up and leading by three points. In the actual voting, the Republican won by nine. The undecided vote broke sharply -- and unanimously -- for the challenger. An undecided voter has really decided not to back the incumbent. He just won't focus on the race until later in the game. So, when the published poll shows Obama ahead by, say, 48-45, he's really probably losing by 52-48! Add these two factors together and the polls that are out there are all misleading. Any professional pollster (those consultants hired by candidates not by media outlets) would publish two findings for each poll -- one using 2004 turnout modeling and the other using 2008 modeling. This would indicate just how dependent on an unusually high turnout of his base the Obama camp really is.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348279149749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348279594876-253</Id><Topic><Title>MSNBC beats Fox, Maddow beats Oreally and Hanity, Susteren beaten</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348261041923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 16:57:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must do bath salts</Msg><Username>bamapride57</Username><Timestamp>1348279594876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 22:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348280205225-254</Id><Topic><Title>Ignore the polls saying Obama is going to win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348279149749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So much liberal bias in the press that the only reliable poll will occur on Nov. 6th. Sad what this country is becoming.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1348280205225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 22:16:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348281806388-255</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Nixon tried to get away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265119327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't reason with a HYPOCRITE. You know the boys and girls on the far left, those would be the ones who are CRYING for 10 years worth of tax returns from Romney, BUT can't believe anyone could possibly want the past records of a cocaine snorting community organizer. Yea, HYPOCRITES are what they are.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348281806388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 22:43:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348281816430-256</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Nixon tried to get away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348265119327</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 18:05:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can't reason with a HYPOCRITE. You know the boys and girls on the far left, those would be the ones who are CRYING for 10 years worth of tax returns from Romney, BUT can't believe anyone could possibly want the past records of a cocaine snorting community organizer. Yea, HYPOCRITES are what they are.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348281816430</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 22:43:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348286039556-257</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT RISES IN TWENTY-SIX OF THE STATES!</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1348244644162</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:24:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't you read that Benny will print more money to lower unemployment? QE infinity only means lower US$, and higher gas and food prices. You know, those that still trade in US$! Notice gold up again? Due to US$ printing, why else?</Msg><Username>dr.market</Username><Timestamp>1348286039556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 23:53:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>