<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-12-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355030343769-1</Id><Topic><Title>M1 tanks? Now that's more like it.</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355004028302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:00:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Owning one shouldn't be a problem. Operating it in public might. Were it legal to own one, It would be most acceptable in a suitable landscape. Couldn't perform any proper training excercises in an urban neigborhoods.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355030343769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 00:19:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355030965199-2</Id><Topic><Title>M1 tanks? Now that's more like it.</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355004028302</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:00:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me a little about when I was a kid, on fourth of July. The local collectors would bring their cannons and fire them. I wonder how large a cannon you can still own?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355030965199</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 00:29:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355038793102-3</Id><Topic><Title>Former Republican presidential hopeful Rick Santorum, addressing attendees at the Values Voter Summit on Saturday, said that, “We will never have the media on our side, ever, in this country. We will never have the elite, smart people on our side.”</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1354993377575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:02:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sir are the typical nincompoop !!!</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355038793102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 02:39:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355039500985-4</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder how the dads of the 4 Americans that the Kenyan murdered feel?</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1355005464365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:24:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know but I know your dad feels really sad every time he looks at you.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355039500985</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 02:51:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355056004907-5</Id><Topic><Title>Bet dad was glad he was packing so he could keep his son safe from the bad guys</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355000152818</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 15:55:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad, we could have used a brave kid like this in Iraq.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1355056004907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 07:26:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355063523768-6</Id><Topic><Title>How some Americans start to associate a Southern accents with lack of intelligence as early as AGE FIVE</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355060667301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 08:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>junior....if you had a brain you'd take it out and play with it....</Msg><Username>floodkid2003</Username><Timestamp>1355063523768</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 09:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355063752960-7</Id><Topic><Title>I Love America</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1355038875112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 02:41:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well statede Deep!</Msg><Username>floodkid2003</Username><Timestamp>1355063752960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 09:35:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355065322630-8</Id><Topic><Title>How some Americans start to associate a Southern accents with lack of intelligence as early as AGE FIVE</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355060667301</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 08:44:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you rub it -- it grows!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355065322630</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:02:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355065611082-9</Id><Topic><Title>I wonder how the dads of the 4 Americans that the Kenyan murdered feel?</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1355005464365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 17:24:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's not a Kenyan -- he's a Keynesian. Stupid blacks think that's in Africa. BWHHHHHHHAAAAAHAHHAHHAAAA!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355065611082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:06:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355065693201-10</Id><Topic><Title>2 days total fed expenses, is all the taxes on the rich will pay for</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1354908286282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 14:24:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama voted present most of the time... when he showed up. His tenure was much like Jesse Jackson Jr.'s.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355065693201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:08:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355066172876-11</Id><Topic><Title>Former Republican presidential hopeful Rick Santorum, addressing attendees at the Values Voter Summit on Saturday, said that, “We will never have the media on our side, ever, in this country. We will never have the elite, smart people on our side.”</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1354993377575</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 14:02:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and facts and science get in the way of the "truth!" *** There are no facts in science -- laws and theories that are subject to revision. You must have attended an American high school or dropped out to become an Obama lemming. The difference between a "law" and a "theory" often confuses people. This happens, in part, because even among scientists there can be different usage of these terms. Of course, to the general public, these terms have very different meanings and connotations. I suggest that you look up the definitions of both words in any English dictionary. As used in science, laws and theories are based on tested hypotheses; both are supported by a large body of empirical data; both help unify a particular field; both are widely accepted by the vast majority (if not all) scientists within a discipline. Furthermore, both scientific laws and scientific theories could be shown to be wrong at some time if there are data to suggest so. Many scientists did not believe the god particle existed until they were proven wrong.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1355066172876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:16:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355066609659-12</Id><Title>yet another self inflicted GOP knifing</Title><Msg>JUDY WOODRUFF: We have about only 20 seconds, but one of the moves in the Senate among these conservatives was to deny the U.N. treaty on the rights of persons with disabilities. How does something like that happen? DAVID BROOKS: It's an embarrassment for the country. This was a treaty that could have given Afghan vets who have lost limbs the greater ability to go abroad and live with dignity. And to do it for black helicopter reasons, to vote against this, it is an embarrassment. MARK SHIELDS: You have heard of a profile in courage. This was a profile in cowardice. It really was, I mean, Republicans who are terrified of a primary, of a challenge on their right. And so they come up with this bogus explanation or theory about blue-helmeted U.N. soldiers coming into homeschooling parents and ripping their child away, having disembarked from the black helicopters. It's a total fabrication. And to do it as Bob Dole sat there on the Senate floor asking for their support is a travesty. GOP crazy doesn't sell well outside of the rabbit hole</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355066609659</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:23:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355067977649-13</Id><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Msg>In a bit of parliamentary squabbling common only to the United States Senate, the chamber will not be voting Thursday on President Obama’s proposal to largely shift responsibility for raising the debt ceiling from Congress to the White House. Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Ky.) proposed an immediate vote on the idea Thursday morning, as a way to highlight potential Democratic unease with the idea. This afternoon, Senate Majority Leader Harry M. Reid (D-Nev.) called that bluff, asking to proceed to immediate vote on the measure. But he asked for an up-or-down vote, allowing the Senate to skip to a final vote by which the measure could be approved on a simple 51-vote majority. McConnell countered the measure should require a 60-vote majority, as most votes do in the Senate. “What we’re talking about here is a perpetual debt ceiling grant, in effect, to the president. Matters of this level of controversy always require 60 votes,” McConnell said. Reid objected to the 60-vote threshold. “What we have here is a case of Republicans here in the Senate once again not taking yes for an answer,” Reid said. “Now the Republican leader objects to his own idea. So I guess we have a filibuster of his own bill.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355068322532-14</Id><Title>GOP still can't read polls, reality is skewed to them</Title><Msg>"At the end of the month, taxes are going to go up for everybody," Mr. Cole said. "So, let's make sure, where we can, we save as many of those tax cuts for as many people as possible and continue to fight. It's not waving a white flag to recognize political reality." Rep. Marsha Blackburn, Tennessee Republican, appearing on the same program, seemed unmoved by her House colleague's arguments. "We won the House; the American people have clearly said, 'We don't want our taxes to go up,'" she said. She brushed aside suggestions that Republicans are losing the public relations battle over the tax cuts. BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH WE DON'T NEED NO STINKING REALITY AROUND HERE!! Voters support higher taxes on the wealthy by a margin of better than 2 to 1, according to a new poll Thursday. Sixty-five percent of voters back increased taxes for Americans making more than $250,000 a year, while 31 percent oppose, according to a Quinnipiac University poll released. Democrats support that measure 84-14 percent, and independents are in favor of the tax hikes 66-31 percent. Republicans, on the other hand, oppose such tax increases 53-41 percent, the poll found.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355068322532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:52:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355069612908-15</Id><Title>why is the GOP wasting all it's political capital protecting the top 2%</Title><Msg>when they could take all that capital and use it to fight for entitlement reform? Could it be the GOP doesn't really want entitlement reform?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355069612908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 11:13:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355070118117-16</Id><Topic><Title>Do the Pukes really care?</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1355023837693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:30:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP doesn't care about keeping 2.3 million people out of poverty including 600,000 children they care about 400 people on the Forbes list</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355070118117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 11:21:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355073674677-17</Id><Topic><Title>Do the Pukes really care?</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1355023837693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:30:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>non-sequiter? You can't spell it, and you're off topic. ROFL The concept of extending unemployment benefits can be run as a standalone issue, outside the relevence of the entire budget. Liberals can't seem to focus on negotiating a few details, and would rather attempt to insult the voters with this garbage. The election is over. There is no further need to get the #$%$ on your side. ROFL</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355073674677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:21:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355074194132-18</Id><Topic><Title>why is the GOP wasting all it's political capital protecting the top 2%</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355069612908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 11:13:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good question. I asked myself that for several months. It seems that they believe that Democrats are acting like Arafat. "If Israel gives me an inch, I will use that inch to destroy Israel" They seem to be right. Obama asked to tax the rich, and wants to go over the cliff so he can tax everyone.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074194132</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:29:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355074472282-19</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now that's funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355074472282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355074689207-20</Id><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Msg>the Bush tax cuts expire? Yes, Mr. Obama. For what 8 years? The average middle class american has saved $2200 a year because of Bush tax cuts. For once, it doesn't sould like a bad idea to blame Bush. 8x2200 in the bank is $17,600 of their money that they can Blame Bush for.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355075259321-21</Id><Topic><Title>Do the Pukes really care?</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1355023837693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-12-08 22:30:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, liberals are the extreme left-wing of the Democratic Party, which is w ho r edom of special interest groups. You won because single women is growing demographic, and single white girls aren't listening to their daddies anymore.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355075259321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:47:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355075733151-22</Id><Topic><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real estate crash doubled UE. Only a #$%$ thinks that the President's policies are responsible for the entire economy. Good think we are on a stock board where our livelyhood is derived from knowing economic principles, and won't be bothered by #$%$ic drivel from upstatrs who come here to learn about it.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355075733151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:55:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355076310239-23</Id><Topic><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let Obama have everything he wants.When the country takes a dump,the libs will no longer be able to blame Bush.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1355076310239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:05:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355076637561-24</Id><Topic><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I heard the war was started to deplete stockpiles of old munitions and modernize the military. then there was that tricky issue of taking Saddam out of power and attempting to liberate the entire Middle East of crushing dictatorships. Like signing a bill to let maroons borrow money to buy houses took a long time, so did the effect of propagating democracy. Of course Clinton didn't specify "maroons and buffoons" as borrowers, but effectively broke the banks, by signing certain legislation. I remind you that this is a stock board. You should probably try your idiot tactics on a Justin Beiber fans club or "my little pony" fetish board.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355076637561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:10:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355077087110-25</Id><Topic><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was a rumor that certain trucks left Iraq and travelled to Syria. My source had sattelite images of the convoy. IDK, do we have WMD's?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355077087110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:18:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355078200403-26</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa Burglarized: $100,000 In Jewelry Stolen From California Home</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1354902256129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:44:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, yeah, he's a CONGRESSMAN actually. My bad. Now that we've addressed the corrigendum, maybe we could focus on the crucial point, which I'll now restate: RepubliCONs decided to appoint a manifest swindler and two-bit hood as their most visible public face for stage-managing their partisan witch-hunts and show-trials of the current Democratic administration. I would be willing to BET that investigators on the case felt constrained to put Issa at or near the top of the list of potential suspects when the theft was reported. Not to do so would be exceedingly BAD police work.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1355078200403</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:36:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355078374220-27</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa Burglarized: $100,000 In Jewelry Stolen From California Home</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1354902256129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:44:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe if you learn how to spell Republican, and address the question with an ounce of civility?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355078374220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:39:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355078528831-28</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa Burglarized: $100,000 In Jewelry Stolen From California Home</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1354902256129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:44:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course, I could just forget about that and ask what a donkeydewsh want to say?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355078528831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:42:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355079421088-29</Id><Topic><Title>Darrell Issa Burglarized: $100,000 In Jewelry Stolen From California Home</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1354902256129</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-12-07 12:44:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appointing a hood and swindler as their public face? How about the former cokehead and dealer who is leading the democratic party????</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1355079421088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 13:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355079622652-30</Id><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Msg>Basic civil rights. Innocent until proven giulty. Right to a trail of his peers. Right to have an attorney present during questioning. If you give up these these rights, and right a book about it, you might get convicted.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355080958980-31</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And this actually matters? Statute of limitations? I don't know. Please tell us. Possession and use are still crimes. It's a mandatory 90 days in California. Did they complete diversion?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355080958980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:22:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355081086736-32</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Board libs type faster than they think. Hard to slam republican neer-do-wells when your president admitted in his book he used and sold cocaine. Members of both parties have skeletons in their closets. Playing tit for tat gets you nowhere.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1355081086736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:24:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355081342393-33</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I imagine it's difficult for them to separate the wheat from the chaff. It seems a rather difficult task of logic and reason. One might be able to rationalize the possibility that if his neighbor deals drugs, then he should also. One should be able to reason other possibilities. That is to say, that just because one Democrat is openly gay, it doesn't mean they all are.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355081342393</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:29:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355081790229-34</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. , "it'd be "virtually impossible" for any Democrat to beat her for the Democratic nomination, former House Speaker Newt Gingrich said Sunday." Fraud is crime, fool.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355081790229</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:36:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355082282424-35</Id><Topic><Title>I Love America</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1355038875112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 02:41:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL Purrrrrrfecto! Butt really i think they get those turd encrusted digits from poking it into their neighbor's poop scoops in the next stall over. After all they is purrverted demo CRAPS as you eloquently say!!!!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1355082282424</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:44:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355082776400-36</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully The Newt includes himself in the incapable group, the arrogant fat #$%$</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355082776400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:52:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355082888365-37</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"IF HILLARY RUNS,... supported by Bill Clinton and presumably, a still relatively popular President Barack Obama, trying to win that will be truly the Super Bowl,” You left out the references to "today" and "in it's current form." I am an independent, and I know they need lots of work. Pushing the evangelicals to a minority fringe might be a good start. They have almost four years to work on it, according to an accurate reading of what Gingrich said.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355082888365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:54:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355082916447-38</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Art go drive your truck. You are not made up for this thinking stuff.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355082916447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:55:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355083041389-39</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical lib response from Junior .Trying to justify Obama's bad behavior by citing someone elses. Also,I dont believe there has ever been any proof of Bush using, only rumors. Obama admitted what he did.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1355083041389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:57:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355083227753-40</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Four years is a long time. Who had heard of Barack Obama in 2004???</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1355083227753</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:00:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355083371763-41</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe somebody can buy you a calendar? 20 years ago, Grover Norquist started to brand the GOP as the "against taxes" They are still trying to push off the old "religious hardhead" branding of the past. Maybe they will figure it out tommorow, but they don't appear to "today" and "in the current form." 4 years to ramp up for the superbowl. More than enough time.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355083371763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:02:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355083739066-42</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If junior owns a calendar, he probably doesn't know how to read it.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355083739066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:08:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355084052918-43</Id><Title>On Nov 6, 2012 - Amazing fact</Title><Msg>CSCO was at $17.35. (sdjusted for dividends) Some of here are big winners, regardless of political nonsense. Fact.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355084052918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:14:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355084508521-44</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shoot the messenger is the best you got? Ever wonder why decent americans consider your party to be an affront to society, offensive, and violent?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355084508521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:21:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355085374149-45</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>True statement. Any questions? False statements are fraudulent. Would you like to reiterate your position to clarify anything, or do you just prefer to seem like an idiot?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355085374149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:36:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355085801370-46</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems are admitting they have a weak bench. Ever hear them talk about anyone but Hillary?? What about their two term vice president ,the human gaffe machine?? Is that the best they have???</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1355085801370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:43:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355085985272-47</Id><Topic><Title>"How about the former cokehead "</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355079622652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:00:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess you have difficulty with calendars and reading. I became a computer tech in 1991, and an internet tech in 1998. I haven't driven a truck in about 25 years. I am currently a professional slacker. I trade stocks, and the market is closed until 4:00 my time, when it opens in Tokyo.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355085985272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355086046180-48</Id><Topic><Title>Funny how Kommie Lib Pigs call Syria's chem weapons WMD</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1355081846581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:37:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the real world no WMD were found in Iraq, when Saddam used Chemical weapons he was an ally of Bush Sr, Cheney and Rummy, they were supplying him weapons at the time remember?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086046180</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:47:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355086343141-49</Id><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Msg>and allowed the remaining sane GOPers to negotiate a reduction in entitlements? But Corker says insisting on that red line -- especially since President Barack Obama won re-election after campaigning on raising tax rates on the wealthy -- might not be wise. "There is a growing group of folks looking at this and realizing that we don't have a lot of cards as it relates to the tax issue before year end," Corker told "Fox News Sunday." If Republicans agree to Obama's plan to increase rates on the top 2 percent of Americans, Corker added, "the focus then shifts to entitlements and maybe it puts us in a place where we actually can do something that really saves the nation."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355086467877-50</Id><Topic><Title>Funny how Kommie Lib Pigs call Syria's chem weapons WMD</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1355081846581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:37:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Appears the commy dumbivan is trying to blame the U.S.for gassing the Iraqis. If he hates this country so much why doesn't he leave? He claims he's rich. Go live where you are happy.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1355086467877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:54:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355086499543-51</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would probably be real nice when the donkeydewshes learn that offensive language is meant to be inflammatory, and can incite violence.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355086499543</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:54:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355086688640-52</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean offensive language like If junior owns a calendar, he probably doesn't know how to read it. what are you going to do, shoot your laptop, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086688640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:58:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355086917699-53</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It would be a consideration, but "probably" isn't a certainty, and we still don't know "IF" he owns one. It would be necessary for one to logically analyse the statement to draw a conclusion. Are you trying to help?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355086917699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:01:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355087173440-54</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama can pretty much prevent any GOP bills from passing by agreeing to sign them, that makes the GOP fillibuster them</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355087173440</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:06:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355087481041-55</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Brilliant plan. Maybe he'll threaten to sign the next one, huh?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355087481041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:11:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355087715971-56</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, if you can read the article, it's fascinating. He presented the bill when the Dems flip flopped, then they flip flopped again, and he filibustered it. Politics is tough when you guys have such a hard time with making decisions. Maybe he noticed that the dems were all hungover from a night of partying?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355087715971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:15:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355088174018-57</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that how limpballs is trying to spin it in the alternate reality world? Is he still calling for Mitt to win in a landslide?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355088174018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:22:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355088426073-58</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Does limbaugh call you guys poopieheads? I am just wondering if he's fallen to your level yet.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355088426073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:27:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355089277609-59</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Should I be listening to Anderson Drooper, Rachel Madcow, or Wolf Switcher, for the gay facts?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355089277609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 16:41:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355090618200-60</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>actually it is your hero that came up with the poppiy-head label “The president was elected on the basis that he was not Romney and that Romney was a poopy-head and you should vote against Romney,” Norquist, an anti-tax crusader, said on CBS’s “This Morning.” “[Obama] won by two points, but he didn’t make the case for higher taxes and higher spending. He kind of sounded like the opposite.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355090618200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:03:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355091020325-61</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The president was elected on the basis that he was not Romney and that Romney was a poopy- head and you should vote against Romney,” Norquist said that? He just described the entire campaign, and you think he was calling names. Go back to school and learn grammar. He said in his narrative that Obama won because his party was calling Romney a poopie head. He was complaining about the quality of the debate, and the mindset of the Obama voters. He wasn't my hero, but he sure is working on it.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091020325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:10:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355091429784-62</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nobody but Norquist has used the poopyhead label so let's review. You post and claim some vague Democrat used the poopy-head label. When I point out that no DNC used the label that only Norquist used it you come back claiming he wasn't really using it. LOL by the way why the homophobic comments? Psychiatrist agree most homophobes are repressed homosexuals.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355091429784</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355091613034-63</Id><Title>"Grover Norquist invented the poopiehead comment"</Title><Msg>Sounds like the lib braintrust is working overtime. When a republican says "poopiehead," he is referring to the type of comment a little child makes when he argues in a kindergarten sandbox. Thanks for the laughs, Dumb.Ivan. You really need to work on your reading comprehension and construction. Try considering simile and metaphor once you tighten up the basic skill set.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091613034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:20:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355092118530-64</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who had heard of Barack Obama in 2004??? Probably not too many terrorists,but you can bet the farm,they know him now.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1355092118530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:28:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355092452113-65</Id><Topic><Title>GOP reaches new low, filibusters their own bill, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355067977649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 10:46:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"by the way why the homophobic comments? Psychiatrist agree most homophobes are repressed homosexuals." In what way was my comment homophobic? It's not like nobody thinks those folks are gay. They seem to focus on gay issues for gay people and put a gay spin on it. Stating the obvious is not a phobia. Should I look up the word phobia in the dictionary? Or are you saying because I called them names, it means I am scared? That would be funny, Ivan, because I was just responding to your name calling, and illustrating how effective it is. So who is scared, Ivan?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355092452113</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:34:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355093948045-66</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has been my experience that most people that use the word "retarded" are insecure,selfish and are bullies. Just like the squater in the peoples house.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1355093948045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:59:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355094490060-67</Id><Title>DEC 21....MAN WILL BE EXTERMINATED FROM EARTH JUST PROBABLY NOT ON DEC 21</Title><Msg>But sometime down the road the Human race will no longer be around..you can counrt on it!</Msg><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1355094490060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:08:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355094622642-68</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Freud called it Psychological Projection. A person who calls other people names will quite often be suffering the effects of the naming he projects upon another. Sometimes, its only a projection of a close family member or friend. In my experience, it's actually easy to determine whether someone is lacking intellect on a message board. Freuds theory often proves correct. Projection is easy to remember in children's taunts: I know you are, but what am I? I am rubber, you're glue... etc. My father taught me to "consider the source," which basically means that the opinions of fools are to be given due consideration, ie. none is due the OP.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355094622642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:10:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355095164692-69</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You need to go back to the Justin Beiber board, youngster.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355095164692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:19:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355095457352-70</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are going to tee hee people for typos you shouldn't post words like"teaillys". It just confirms what a hypocritical juvenile twit you are.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1355095457352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:24:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355095550043-71</Id><Topic><Title>Average American will be taxed $2200 after</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355074689207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 12:38:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Greg. "Most economists agree the recession was caused by the subprime mortgage crisis, which had little if anything to do with tax policies" The board pest should probably try reading a bit. Keywords " Economists" "subprime" "google" Thanks.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355095550043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:25:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355095829184-72</Id><Topic><Title>DEC 21....MAN WILL BE EXTERMINATED FROM EARTH JUST PROBABLY NOT ON DEC 21</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1355094490060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:08:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We all get exterminated,dont we?? It's usually just one at a time though when our turn comes.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1355095829184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:30:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355096348901-73</Id><Topic><Title>DEC 21....MAN WILL BE EXTERMINATED FROM EARTH JUST PROBABLY NOT ON DEC 21</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1355094490060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:08:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did some research on the topic. There's about a 3 week margin of deviation in the translation of the Julian calendar from the Mayan. The most interesting FACT is that the Mayans Predicted the movement of the heavens for thousands of years, and did not have faith in calculating further. The FACT that they didn't have confidence in futher prediction is the only "prediction" that the calendar makes. Look to the sky, and hope that future movements will be predictable. We are transversing a section of the Galaxy which has a history of causing disruption. Allegedly, the traverse caused severe flooding in the time of Noah. Maybe God lied, and will do it again?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355096348901</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:39:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355096622005-74</Id><Topic><Title>wouldn't it be nice if the retarded baggers shut up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355086343141</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 15:52:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen Junior's grades?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355096622005</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:43:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355100131654-75</Id><Topic><Title>"Grover Norquist invented the poopiehead comment"</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091613034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:20:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we take as an admission from you that it is only Norquist that is using preschool language to describe political posturing. Since you can come up with no one but Norquist who has said it. Try using logic and reason when you post, if you can overcome your retarded logic.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1355100131654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 19:42:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355100458867-76</Id><Topic><Title>"Grover Norquist invented the poopiehead comment"</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091613034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:20:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is " we" ? You and your other ids??</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1355100458867</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 19:47:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355100786833-77</Id><Topic><Title>"Grover Norquist invented the poopiehead comment"</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091613034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:20:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only poster I've seen on this board who agrees with Ivan's far out views is Junior....who is probably also one of Ivans ids.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1355100786833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 19:53:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355100887835-78</Id><Topic><Title>"Grover Norquist invented the poopiehead comment"</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355091613034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 17:20:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never said anything like that. You quoted Norquist after I commented on your low level of rhetoric. Since you seem incapable of board searches, I'll quote it for you. "Does limbaugh call you guys poopieheads? I am just wondering if he's fallen to your level yet."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355100887835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 19:54:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1355101075881-79</Id><Title>World markets up, Asia, Australia.</Title><Msg>Isn't it nice to be diversified, and not have your lips on Obamas a ss all day?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1355101075881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 19:57:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355109296237-80</Id><Topic><Title>DEC 21....MAN WILL BE EXTERMINATED FROM EARTH JUST PROBABLY NOT ON DEC 21</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1355094490060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 18:08:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No shhhjjjt !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355109296237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 22:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355109502310-81</Id><Topic><Title>GINGRICH: IF HILLARY RUNS, GOP 'INCAPABLE OF COMPETING'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1355081017974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:23:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes we are violent, we are the guys with the guns, xenophobes, anti gay, anti woman. Shut up and drive your truck Forrest, that is the limit of your capacities.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355109502310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 22:18:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355109672296-82</Id><Topic><Title>Funny how Kommie Lib Pigs call Syria's chem weapons WMD</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1355081846581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 14:37:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"YOU CAN'T HANDLE THE TRUTH" Bwwwwwwahahahahah</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355109672296</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 22:21:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1355109855243-83</Id><Topic><Title>I Love America</Title><Username>deeperharbor</Username><Timestamp>1355038875112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 02:41:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deeperswallow is like a 2 year old, going through the anal phase and playing with fecal matter. Geeeeeee, what an IDIOT ! LMAO ! LMAO ! This is why I love this board, I never get enough of the repuke idiots trying to sound smart, it is comedic material with no end.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1355109855243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-12-09 22:24:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>