<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-24"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353735265438-1</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is ANY of this a WH decision?!? Republican Petraeus himself even said this had NOTHING to do with the WH. GOP pukes are the new hippies, apparently. They would rather we tip off our Al-Qaeda enemies than let the CIA do their job. Sickening. We have a motley collection of FOX ad-sellers and their favorite demographic- armchair conspiracy theorists- pretending to be authorities. I am proud that these voices are kept on the fringe. The hijacked Republican party is dying; I hope the sane remnants of the party can take it back, but it's not looking good...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1353735265438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 00:34:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353735453344-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bush supporters better be prepared</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353715058755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So was it Yale or Wharton that teaches the kiddies to type without caps and punctuation? The liberals might be right about hiring better teachers. Oh, sorry, they just say pay them more money to teach. It's a union thingy. They teach them poorly and demand more money with fat pensions and work 8 moths a year. My mistake.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353735453344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 00:37:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353735744679-3</Id><Topic><Title>I went to my local WalMart last night</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1353671136714</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 06:45:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>100% of people with the fake name "hairyroid" are cowardly middle aged men with 15 or so good years left...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1353735744679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 00:42:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353738820251-4</Id><Topic><Title>It's different this time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353465234808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 21:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There isn't a waterboarding part to the Geneva convention, sir. There is a section which refers to the "humane treatment" of conflict VICTIMS, which stupid liberals insist refers to terrorists. There is no section which insists on the "humane treatment" of terrorists. A terrorist who has knowledge of a planned attack, could be considered an "active combattant" regardless of his captured status. Law is such a tedious field. It relies on specific text which usually turns out to be ambiguous and undefined, especially when people can't understand the definitions of specific header words such as "Victim" at the top of the protocol definition.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353738820251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:33:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353739324400-5</Id><Topic><Title>It's different this time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353465234808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 21:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only section that specifically references anything like terrorism in the Geneva Convention relates to perfidy. Perfidy is a war crime which occurs when a combattant performs military action in secret without a uniform. It is punishable by death. Ok, so they should have just killed them. Does that make you happy? Is that humane enough?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353739324400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:42:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353739957695-6</Id><Topic><Title>It's different this time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353465234808</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 21:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perfidy is the most insidious of war crimes. When combattants pose as civilians, and fire rockets from civilian locations, you get what we have here. More failures to follow the rules.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353739957695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 01:52:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353759189089-7</Id><Title>It all makes sense now</Title><Msg>Gay marriage and marijuana being legalized on the same day Leviticus 20:13 -- "if a man lays with another man he should be stoned." We've just been interpreting it wrong all these years!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353759189089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:13:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353759578116-8</Id><Title>Arafat to be Exhumed, Aids Alert</Title><Msg>Nowhere in this article does it say that DNA has shown his kid is his. Arafat was a known Tookus Cowboy. While they are at it check him for AIDS. Arafat to be exhumed next week in poison probe Investigation into former Palestinian leader's death to begin after traces of poisonous substance allegedly found on his clothes. PHOTO: REUTERS The corpse of former Palestinian leader Yasser Arafat will be exhumed next week to investigate allegations he was poisoned, a senior Palestinian official said Saturday. Arafat’s tomb in the West Bank city of Ramallah will be opened on Nov. 27, Tawfiq Tirawi, a member of the Palestinian Authority’s central committee said. Related: Experts gather to discuss Arafat exhumation Russia to join investigation into Arafat's death Arafat’s wife, Suha, had requested an autopsy to search for traces of a poisonous substance. She told Al Jazeera in July that a Swiss laboratory had detected high levels of the radioactive isotope polonium in Arafat’s clothes, which have been in storage since his death in 2004. Palestinians have accused Israel of causing Arafat’s death, though no conclusive evidence has been presented publicly. Israel denies killing him. Arafat, who founded the Palestine Liberation Organization, died in a French hospital at the age of 75. Doctors at the Percy military hospital in Clamart, France, said he suffered from a brain hemorrhage and fell into a coma before he died. He is buried below a glass tomb adjacent to the offices of his successor, Mahmoud Abbas. Polonium, which had been stirred into a cup of tea, was identified as the substance that killed Alexander Litvinenko, a former KGB agent who became a critic of the Russian government. Litvinenko died in 2006 after being poisoned in London.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353759578116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:19:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353759696850-9</Id><Topic><Title>Bush supporters better be prepared</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353715058755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't he the leader that gave us 9.11. 2 precious wars, two recessions, and the Patriot Act? Ya, that's the guy, how'd this last election work out for ya?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353759696850</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:21:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353763449969-10</Id><Topic><Title>It all makes sense now</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353759189089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:13:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Religion not only brings your IQ several pegs down, it is also a sign of immaturity. Grow up child .</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353763449969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:24:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353763565743-11</Id><Title>I FEEL GOOD THIS MORNING...REPUKES HAVE ANOTHER 4 YEARS OF MISERY.</Title><Msg>Sweet justice.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353763565743</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:26:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353764828879-12</Id><Title>IS SUSAN RICE THE WORLD BIGGEST FOOL or JUST BLACK ?</Title><Msg>Mooooolsimes want to know...??? SALTY to the google power !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353764828879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:47:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353764922420-13</Id><Topic><Title>Arafat to be Exhumed, Aids Alert</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353759578116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:19:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many are resonant with quivering lips...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353764922420</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:48:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353765236802-14</Id><Title>Hey everyone, Surferboy dumb.ivan feels good this morning ...</Title><Msg>He gets an early start yanking his crank every day...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353765236802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:53:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353765967413-15</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>those unarmed farmers were threatening Israel by checking out the farm land they own that Israel hasn't let them farm now for 5 years</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353765967413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353766252008-16</Id><Topic><Title>Arafat to be Exhumed, Aids Alert</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353759578116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:19:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course Israel murdered him, it's their way, God chose them and they are allowed to kill people 7:1 When the LORD thy God shall bring thee into the land whither thou goest to possess it, and hath cast out many nations before thee, the Hittites, and the Girgashites, and the Amorites, and the Canaanites, and the Perizzites, and the Hivites, and the Jebusites, seven nations greater and mightier than thou; 7:2 And when the LORD thy God shall deliver them before thee; thou shalt smite them, and utterly destroy them; thou shalt make no covenant with them, nor shew mercy unto them: 7:3 Neither shalt thou make marriages with them; thy daughter thou shalt not give unto his son, nor his daughter shalt thou take unto thy son. 7:4 For they will turn away thy son from following me, that they may serve other gods: so will the anger of the LORD be kindled against you, and destroy thee suddenly. 7:5 But thus shall ye deal with them; ye shall destroy their altars, and break down their images, and cut down their groves, and burn their graven images with fire. 7:6 For thou art an holy people unto the LORD thy God: the LORD thy God hath chosen thee to be a special people unto himself, above all people that are upon the face of the earth.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353766252008</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:10:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353766435278-17</Id><Title>Run, Jebby,Run! HAAHAHAHA</Title><Msg>Run, Jeb, Run! Another Bush, Another Target-Rich Presidential Campaign November 23rd, 2012 11:59 pm Joe Conason The Jeb Bush boomlet that fascinated gullible pundits — and tantalized Republicans — during the dark days of last winter’s presidential primary is undergoing a swift revival. Less than three weeks after the defeat of Mitt Romney, a candidate who proved repellent to minority voters, Republicans are said to be yearning for Jeb, who speaks fluent Spanish and whose wife is from Mexico. Perhaps after another four years’ distance, the former Florida governor will somehow overcome the bad memories (and the human, economic, and diplomatic destruction) left by his older brother George W. and restore the damaged family political brand. But according to The New York Times, which reported that Jeb is considering a presidential run, he is also considering whether he can afford the luxury of returning to politics: He “is said by friends to be weighing financial and family considerations — between so many years in office and the recession his wealth took a dip, they said, and he has been working hard to restore it…” Aside from his need to “restore” his depleted wealth, Jeb’s business dealings may well prove an insurmountable obstacle to a national candidacy, just as Romney’s business career became excess baggage for his presidential campaign. Known today only as another Bush brother, Jeb must be introduced to American voters. And among the first things they are likely to learn about him is the string of borderline business deals that built his original fortune in Florida real estate, which began three decades ago. While some aspects of the Jeb story may sound uplifting, there are certainly other episodes that will make voters’ hair stand on end. Consider his gamy relationship with Miguel Recarey, whose International Medical Centers stands accused of one of the largest Medicare swindles of all time. Before Recarey fled the country ahead of several federal indictments, Jeb had placed a call on his behalf to Health and Human Services Secretary Margaret Heckler — a Cabinet secretary serving at the pleasure of Jeb’s daddy, President George Herbert Walker Bush. Recarey paid Jeb a sweet $75,000 for that lobbying effort, which forestalled government action to stop Recarey’s skimming of millions in Medicare dollars. Although Jeb has denied that Recarey — a Mafia associate — hired him to importune Heckler, both the fugitive and the former HHS secretary have since confirmed those circumstances. After Recarey fled Miami, Jeb gradually grew rich through real estate investments, thanks to his connections with the Cuban-American community in South Florida. To show his gratitude, Jeb sought a presidential pardon from his dad for Orlando Bosch, a murderous anti-Castro militant denounced by his father’s own attorney general Richard Thornburgh as “an unreformed terrorist” responsible for the murder of dozens of innocent people. That kind of thing is acceptable among the South Florida Cubans, but may not look so good in the post-9/11 era to the rest of the country. Then there is Jeb’s career as governor, a saga that includes his vow to sign legislation that would have awarded Florida’s disputed electoral votes to his brother in November 2000, and his attempted intervention in the case of Terri Schiavo, the brain-dead woman whose husband and parents fought over whether to turn off her respirator. Interference in that sad matter by congressional leaders and other right-wing busybodies was gross exploitation of a family tragedy — and the Schiavo affair became a turning point in the 2006 Republican midterm debacle. So yes — run, Jeb, run! The fact is that almost any presidential candidate from Florida represents a full-employment program for investigative journalism — and the “smarter” Bush brother is no exception.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353766435278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:13:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353766668246-18</Id><Topic><Title>Arafat to be Exhumed, Aids Alert</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353759578116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:19:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" allowed to kill them " Is that a little like Obama#$%$ list and murdering with drones? You hypocrites on the FAR LEFT are a hoot.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353766668246</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:17:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353768131429-19</Id><Topic><Title>Run, Jebby,Run! HAAHAHAHA</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353766435278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:13:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you forget his role in the savings and loan scandle and the fact his wife was caught smuggling and the fact that all three of his children were arrested, the daughter multiple times. Yeah nominate another tax dodger GOPERS see how well that Bush name works for you, LOL Between 1981 and 1989, when George Bush finally announced that there was a Savings and Loan Crisis to the world, the Reagan/Bush administration worked to cover up Savings and Loan problems by reducing the number and depth of examinations required of S&amp;Ls as well as attacking political opponents who were sounding early alarms about the S&amp;L industry. Industry insiders were aware of significant S&amp;L problems as early 1986 that they felt would require a bailout. This information was kept from the media until after Bush had won the 1988 elections. Jeb Bush defaulted on a $4.56 million loan from Broward Federal Savings in Sunrise, Florida. After federal regulators closed the S&amp;L, the office building that Jeb used the $4.56 million to finance was reappraised by the regulators at $500,000, which Bush and his partners paid. The taxpayers had to pay back the remaining 4 million plus dollars. MOST OF us know the feeling: as you walk through Customs, you wonder whether you'll be stopped, and those holiday purchases subjected to scrutiny. Fewer of us have actually had the customs officer running his hands through our luggage, asking where all this stuff came from. And only Columba Bush went through all this and then saw the story hit the front pages of newspapers across America. But then she is the wife of the governor of Florida, and a member by marriage of one of America's most famous political families. Mrs Bush had been on a shopping trip to Paris, and she seems to have got a little carried away. She bought $19,000 (pounds 11,875) worth of clothes and jewellery, but she didn't admit it to Customs at Atlanta airport: she declared only $500. "So we asked her for receipts," said a spokesman for US Customs,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353768131429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 09:42:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353769378559-20</Id><Topic><Title>It all makes sense now</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353759189089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 07:13:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Didn't know you were a Bill Maher fan.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353769378559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:02:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353769587108-21</Id><Topic><Title>Bush supporters better be prepared</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353715058755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Obama repeal the patriot act? If liberals didn't have double standards, they wouldn't have any.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353769587108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:06:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770273356-22</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How is ANY of this a WH decision?!? Republican Petraeus himself even said this had NOTHING to do with the WH" Not according to the OP. WE aren't discussing anything Fox news said. We are discussing what the OP wrote: "The CIA asked the WH not to call Bengahzi a terrorist attack" And then what the President said in a Nationally televised debate to the American people.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353770273356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:17:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770306571-23</Id><Topic><Title>IS SUSAN RICE THE WORLD BIGGEST FOOL or JUST BLACK ?</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353764828879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:47:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not sure. What I do know is your mom likes to gobble on my meat roll.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353770306571</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:18:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353770728377-24</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So was it the WH decision to call it a terrorist attack and then perform a coverup in the debate? Or was it just Obamas decision to lie because he is most accustomed to doing it for your vote?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353770728377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353771217028-25</Id><Topic><Title>IS SUSAN RICE THE WORLD BIGGEST FOOL or JUST BLACK ?</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353764828879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:47:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder if Surf comes up with those really intelligent responses on his own or has help??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1353771217028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:33:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353771821370-26</Id><Topic><Title>Hey everyone, Surferboy dumb.ivan feels good this morning ...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353765236802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:53:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I suspect he would enjoy yanking another man's crank even more.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353771821370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:43:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353772001995-27</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A close family of 300?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353772001995</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:46:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353772130160-28</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"note the aggressor" Would that be the 300 people approaching the border fence who were warned by shots in the air?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353772130160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353772307858-29</Id><Title>His naivete is showing</Title><Msg>Obama praises Morsi one day and then the next day Morsi announces he's wants to be a dictator. Is Morsi way ahead of Obama or what??</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353772307858</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:51:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353772694938-30</Id><Title>GOP is the party of family values!!!</Title><Msg>Rep. Scott DesJarlais (R-Tenn.) won't be going away unless his constituents vote him out, he told the Knoxville News Sentinel Wednesday. Giving his first public comments since the latest report on his sordid 2000 divorce proceedings -- which revealed that he had supported two abortions for his then-wife -- the self-proclaimed staunchly anti-abortion DesJarlais suggested that he regretted his actions but didn't believe they warranted his resignation, especially after his recent reelection victory. "I am human," he told the News Sentinel. "I don't think I ever put myself out there to be somebody that was perfect. I put myself out there as somebody who wanted to serve the public." Political foes have attacked DesJarlais based on his messy divorce since his first election in 2010, when it was publicly revealed that he had once put a gun in his mouth and threatened suicide while distraught over the impending split. DesJarlais denied those reports, despite the fact that he'd once testified they were true, and won the election. HuffPost's Michael McAuliff also reported earlier this year that DesJarlais, a doctor, had pressured one of his patients to abort a pregnancy that she said was the result of their affair. The congressman has since suggested that she was not pregnant and that he suspected that all along. DesJarlais also had affairs with other patients to whom he'd prescribed pain pills, as well as intimate relationships with co-workers while serving as chief of staff at a Tennessee hospital.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353772694938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773069994-31</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is the party of family values!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353772694938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He should join the Dems. They would make him a poster boy.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353773069994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:04:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773431082-32</Id><Topic><Title>IS SUSAN RICE THE WORLD BIGGEST FOOL or JUST BLACK ?</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353764828879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 08:47:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4 more years of not being able to call a spade a spade. If you can't do the job right the first time. The second time give us the truth, Alveda King. Ms King is MLK niece and she is right. Just because your a black woman doesn't mean you are telling the truth or competent at your present job. And you certainly don't deserve a promotion to a more demanding job.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353773431082</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:10:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353773501503-33</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is the party of family values!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353772694938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should give you thumbs up for that one. It's nice to see a Democrat addressing the abortion issue in a positive way, and the GOP has no business endorsing such a candidate. Can you show us any recent endorsements to prove that this issuse is otherwise relevant to the national politcal landscape? We already know what it's like to see a liar win the election.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353773501503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:11:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353774006844-34</Id><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Msg>The 13 states of the Confederacy were Alabama, Arkansas, Florida, Georgia, Louisiana, Mississippi, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, Missouri, Kentucky, Texas and Virginia. Notice these are the poorest states in the union, they are the States that require huge federal subsidies and pay the lowest amount of taxes into the Treasury. If we can get a petition going to force them out of the Union the budget would immediately go into a huge surplus. We could lower taxes on all the blue states, invest in green energy, provide free healthcare all while paying down the debt. Having these States in the Union is like having your crazy alcoholic uncle bubba living in your mansion.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353774140970-35</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you agree. Your double standards are showing. I didn't vote for your guy because I already saw the first act. Bush actually stood up for those things. He wan't acting.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353774140970</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:22:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353775392149-36</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Is A Potential 10 Bagger!</Title><Username>vazquezroman635</Username><Timestamp>1353691574681</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 12:26:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"CSCO Is A Potential 10 Bagger!" Thanks. I'll just take two, and leave the rest for you. I am feeling so generous.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353775392149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:43:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353775807604-37</Id><Topic><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really need to get a life and quit making a fool of yourself on this board.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1353775807604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:50:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776116545-38</Id><Topic><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth hurts doesn't it bubba?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776116545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:55:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353776270586-39</Id><Title>That's over $9.00 an hour, what is the matter with those lazy moochers</Title><Msg>Several points here - the workers for Hostess had given 3 concessions over an 8 year period. A worker making around $45k in 2005 was going to make less than $20k if they had accepted the latest "deal", and greatly reduced benefits. In that 8 year time since private equity took over, Hostess had 6 CEOs, none of which had any industry experience whatsoever. The latest CEO, meanwhile, saw a 300% pay raise over the past year. The "wind down", as you call it, will easily pay back creditors, and I suspect the sale of the widely recognized brands will net the private equity firm a profit. we have to get the GOPERS in the house to eliminate the minimum wage so company managments don't have to pay such outragious hourly salaries!!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776270586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:57:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776320678-40</Id><Topic><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Truth?? Look at how people on this board answer your posts. You are an unfunny joke.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1353776320678</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776394994-41</Id><Topic><Title>That's over $9.00 an hour, what is the matter with those lazy moochers</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776270586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the big problem started when the liberal dems came up with child labor laws, if Hostess could just hire 10 year olds and pay them in twinkies they could be making a fortune, the executives could be making millions and the job creators would be doing fine.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776394994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:59:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776551312-42</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in WW2 we sent Japanese soldiers to jail for life for doing what Bush ordered, fact</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776551312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:02:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776588806-43</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush can't leave the country without being arrested, soon we will extradite him to the Hague</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776588806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:03:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776791830-44</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead I was referencing the statement of a different member of the Senate: John McCain. On November 29, 2007, Sen. McCain, while campaigning in St. Petersburg, Florida, said, "Following World War II war crime trials were convened. The Japanese were tried and convicted and hung for war crimes committed against American POWs. Among those charges for which they were convicted was waterboarding." Sen. McCain was right and the National Review Online is wrong. Politifact, the St. Petersburg Times' truth-testing project (which this week was awarded a Pulitzer Prize), scrutinized Sen. McCain's statement and found it to be true. Here's the money quote from Politifact: "McCain is referencing the Tokyo Trials, officially known as the International Military Tribunal for the Far East. After World War II, an international coalition convened to prosecute Japanese soldiers charged with torture. At the top of the list of techniques was water-based interrogation, known variously then as 'water cure,' 'water torture' and 'waterboarding,' according to the charging documents. It simulates drowning." Politifact went on to report, "A number of the Japanese soldiers convicted by American judges were hanged, while others received lengthy prison sentences or time in labor camps."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776791830</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:06:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353776952495-45</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler believed on his #$%$ too. I guess that absolves him of any crime. You are becoming stupider with each statement. Keep going man, you are a car wreck in slow motion.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353776952495</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:09:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353777497813-46</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why hasn't the extradition process even been started? Bush has been out of office almost four years and its no secret where he is at. You are a dope.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353777497813</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:18:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353777762547-47</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When is Obama going to JAIL. Bush waterboarded which made Terrorist uncomfortable, Obama has been MURDERING terrorist with drones and the use of the Seals. WHY is one different from the other. NEITHER had a trial. Obama also MURDERED 3 teenage pirates when he ORDERED their dealths. Tell us how it is HYPOCRITE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353777762547</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:22:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778022053-48</Id><Topic><Title>That's over $9.00 an hour, what is the matter with those lazy moochers</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776270586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right. Obama should draw up a bailout and give them our tax money so they can negotiate the concessions directly with the union.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353778022053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:27:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778147418-49</Id><Topic><Title>That's over $9.00 an hour, what is the matter with those lazy moochers</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353776270586</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:57:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a LIAR dumb dumb. Interview with a hostess employee who said he would rather lose his job than take concessions( How's that working out for him ) was making over $16 plus over $5 in benefits. Company wanted to take away part of the benefit package. FYI, Teamsters were willing and DID take their deal. You once again are proven to be a LIAR and an idiot.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353778147418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:29:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778449152-50</Id><Topic><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EVERYONE thinks Dumb Dumb is a #$%$ EVERYONE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353778449152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:34:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778655663-51</Id><Topic><Title>It is easy to balance the budget and get the country back on track</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353774006844</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 11:20:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL his ids are dumb. Same communist thinking runs through all of them.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353778655663</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353778724940-52</Id><Title>If Obama tells you to scream fire in a crowded theater</Title><Msg>and you DO IT, does that make you righteous? A broken argument that ignorant people make.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353778724940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:38:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353778737609-53</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A simple grammatical error. Easily corrected. The word waterboarding describes a similar CIA technique developed by the CIA in 2002, and first described by the media as "waterboarding" in 2004. All you just said, is that John McCain is capable of the same type of grammatical error as yourself. Why would the CIA need to develop a specialized manual on a technique known to be a form of torture for hundreds of years? Perhaps they intended to use a similar technique which would not cause any permanent injury, and therefore be called "enhanced interrogation," instead of torture. They call it the CIA because they are intelligent enough to recognize the mandates of their work and simple grammatical nuances. CIA stands for "CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY." You are called dumb.ivan for similar reasons?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353778737609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:38:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779191635-54</Id><Topic><Title>GOP is the party of family values!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353772694938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 10:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Family values??? How much you think that cigar Clinton used to cram up Monica would go for on E-bay?? Your hypocrisy is showing again, dummy.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353779191635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:46:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779234579-55</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One might also become aware of another grammatical nuance. Torture is a form of punishment which is used after interrogations, not during them. A qualified interrogator with any intelligence would have to recognize the thin gray line between the one and the other.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353779234579</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:47:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779480216-56</Id><Topic><Title>SURFSINURINE , Virtualdipshet, IrrationalAge11 and Juniorsbuhtmate</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1353706602993</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 16:36:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but don't forget: they all fist each other too so you wouldn't want to shake hands with any of these qwears!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779480216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:51:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353779739077-57</Id><Title>SurfnforBoyz Caught trying to teach a</Title><Msg>a 5 yr. old to jack off...he told the kid's mom he was just playin around--but then why did surf have a dong stuck up his but?</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779739077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353779840792-58</Id><Topic><Title>SurfnforBoyz Caught trying to teach a</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779739077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:55:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779840792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:57:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353780096096-59</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, the perfidious combattants should have been summarily executed after any interrogation. Holding them in small cells after interrogation could be deemed a torture by most liberals. The legal recourse for perfidy is execution. It is the proper way to deal with perfidy. Perfidy is one of the most insidious forms of warfare and war crime, and the scourge should be removed from the face of the earth at the earliest moment, unless intelligence can be gathered through interrogation. It is listed as one of the highest crimes of war because it degrades the honor of the combattants. Honorable combattants must not portray themselves as citizen warriors unless there are no other alternatives. It degrades the professional warrior to "spy" status, and makes the military suspicious of civilians to the extent of causing other war atrocities.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353780096096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:01:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353780838523-60</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is clearly one of the more inane arguments you could make. It wasn’t torture because the CIA wrote a manual on how to do it. LOL We can put that one right next to Nixon’s “It’s not a crime if the President does it.” And since your into name calling you are a poopy head and my mommy can beat up your mommy!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353780838523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:13:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353780843153-61</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Running at the police with a Hamas flag, screaming "Allah Akbar" in the US would be called "suicide by cop" in the US. If Liberals (and terrorists) didn't have double standards, they wouldn't have any.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353780843153</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:14:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353780905079-62</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They weren't farmers.They were trying to strip down a disabled jeep. And warning shots were fired. They chose to ignore them. Liberals on this board sure have a hard time with the truth.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1353780905079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:15:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353781278668-63</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should try it in a airport. Makesure Homeland security is nearby with loaded weapons.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353781278668</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:21:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353781541471-64</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unarmed?? In Vietnam we shot any VC who didn't follow our orders EXACTLY! We lost guys to VC who hid a weapon or explosive until they could get close enough to kill you. Likewise we left any dead ones we found in the jungle to rot since the VC would booby trap the bodies. Sounds cruel but you want to stay alive.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1353781541471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353781998245-65</Id><Topic><Title>When is obama being sentenced to the electric chair?</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353781537021</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:25:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You don't get the chair for double standards. Try to act like a conservative and don't be a facetious bozo like the libbies. We know you appreciate that side of obama.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353781998245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:33:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353782397897-66</Id><Topic><Title>Israeli Gunfire Kills Palestinian, Wounds 19 Near Border</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1353688060020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 11:27:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They only get the koolaid from the script writers who pay them to post. Don't expect them to actually have any facts.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353782397897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:39:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353783722058-67</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They want to establish a model economy in Palestine, based entirely on foodstamps. You don't expect people to actually work for a living when they can get paid to #$%$ and moan about the injustice of the world, do you?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353783722058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:02:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353784497340-68</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure explains why Obama got 69% of the jewish vote, LOL how retarded are you people? and then you post Israelis who have lived peacefully in their own holy land for several thousand years. LOL Israel was set up in 1948 (only in rabbit hole land is 2012-1948= several thousand years) Oh yeah and that period of the Crusades was one of my favorite peaceful periods, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353784497340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:14:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353785745419-69</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Challenging facts, Ivan? Not your forte. "Israel" the nation, declared independence from the British Mandate of Palestine in 1948. The British Mandate was a combination of the Trans Jordan area, which included the area called Israel since the 1300's, and Judea before that. Judea could be translated "the land of the Jewish people," but is more commonly recognized as The Kingdom of the Jews. Isreal was set up by the UN in 1947, but was divised by map makers as an indefensible collage of discreet territories, somewhat like Palestine is today. The Zionists envisioned a more defensible contiguous area, and declared the space, and won the war against the UN, the British, and seven or eight arab states to declare their indepedence. Prior to the first world war, the entire space was part of the Ottoman empire: a state which failed economically and militarily in WWI. At that time, most of the land was owned by the caliphate and only rented by the occupants. There are no Palestinian landholders. Only squatters who showed up after WWI.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353785745419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:35:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353786779944-70</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"sure explains why Obama got 69% of the jewish vote" What it doesn't explain is why liberals think Obama won't kiss their #$%$.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353786779944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 14:52:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353788206793-71</Id><Topic><Title>SurfnforBoyz Caught trying to teach a</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779739077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:55:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tell your wife I am sorry about your son.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353788206793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 15:16:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353794665605-72</Id><Topic><Title>Bush supporters better be prepared</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353715058755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His 8 years of presidency gelded our economy and we still feel the after affects.</Msg><Username>daytraderfbf</Username><Timestamp>1353794665605</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:04:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353794807981-73</Id><Topic><Title>Bush supporters better be prepared</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353715058755</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 18:57:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His 8 years in office destroyed our economy and we are still suffering for it.</Msg><Username>daytraderfbf</Username><Timestamp>1353794807981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:06:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353797877537-74</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That would be kind of odd. Israel held the Sinai, Gaza, and the west bank in 1967. Do you think they meant pre-1967 borders?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353797877537</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 17:57:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353799335293-75</Id><Topic><Title>SurfnforBoyz Caught trying to teach a</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779739077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:55:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, I did bump 'im.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353799335293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353799516144-76</Id><Topic><Title>SurfnforBoyz Caught trying to teach a</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1353779739077</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 12:55:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So Surf finally admits he's a homosexual pedophile!! Need to remember this and bump it once in awhile.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1353799516144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 18:25:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353804625806-77</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you would history, you'd know that the Romans kicked their #$%$ out about 2000 years ago. So your message is wrong</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1353804625806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 19:50:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353810212378-78</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, I would insist that "Paulianity," the religion that most people call "Christianity" is just a disguised form of Judaism, which would allow Jews to exist in Palestine even if the Romans tossed the official Jews out.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353810212378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 21:23:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353811463971-79</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Egypt lost the war. Still the accused “colonial, racist apartheid” state of Israel returned the Sinai desert." They should have given the Sinai to the Palestinians, and this crap would be over. Egypt invaded and took the land from others. It was probably the land which spawned the Palestinian migrant workers which are now called "Palestinians." Yes, the Jews hired migrant workers numbering in the hundreds of thousands when they built Israel out of a desert wasteland. Those migrant workers now claim Palestine as their homeland. It would be like your mexican gardener claiming your house because he mowed the lawn for so many years.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353811463971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 21:44:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353812582273-80</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I might also state categorically, that some of the Palestians HAD legitimate claims to SOME of the land in 1948. Their failure to reaquire those lands and take possesion for over 60 years makes most of those people dead, and their ancestors would have no legal right to property under the principles of adverse possession and emminent domain. Under emminent domain, they would be entitled to reimbursement. End of conflict. Let them build casinos on their remaining lands and become rich Indians.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353812582273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:03:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353813485549-81</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently, the Ottoman empire kept records on the taxes paid in the territory. The taxes would include references to the "jizya" or "tax paid by Jews and Christians" living in the israeli territory. It would als probably include a head tax on those who were neither, presumably Muslim.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353813485549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:18:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353815347639-82</Id><Topic><Title>Kind of ironic that the liberals hate the Israelis</Title><Username>blindboa</Username><Timestamp>1353782923701</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 13:48:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The UN partition was Trans Jordan for the Arabs, the Kingdom of Jordan was #$%$, not based in history. Most of the Bedouin live there, Arafat was Egyptian as most of Fatah. So why did King Hussein kill 30,000 on black september? because they were troublemakers. The Bedouin claim the west bank, but Jordan didn't give it to them for a state. Gaza was Egypts why did Sadat give it to Israel, they didn't ask for it, it was a favor to Egypt that Israel took it. Why didn't Egypt give it to the Bedouin? They were troublemakers. Arafat took over part of Lebanon, why did the Lebanese help Israel push Arafat out? They killed one of the Gemail brothers, made trouble, and couldn't get along with the large Christian Lebanese community. Once again Troublemakers. When Saddam Hussein took over Kuwait, the so called Pallies (Bedouins) took Saddam's side and when the USA thru Hussein out, the Kuwaities tossed the Pallies out because they were troublemakers. So it was stupid for Ariel Sharon to give away Gaza, throw his own Israelis out of their homes and businesses. The gave land and got 8,000 rockets and mortars shot at homes, hospitals and schools. That is what troublemakers do. One good deed deserve treachery to the Bedouin.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353815347639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:49:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353815374714-83</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are funny. I simply referenced the name you chose for yourself and asked if that is why you chose it. Are you too incompetent to understand the use of a question mark? I stated that "CIA" refers to intelligent use of similar techniques that might otherwise be called torture. It is a shame that you cannot interpret intlligent uses of the English language. Is that why you chose Dumb.Ivan as your ID?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353815374714</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 22:49:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353816024450-84</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(It is a shame that you cannot interpret intlligent uses of the English language. Is that why you chose Dumb.Ivan as your ID?) Using 'intelligent' and 'Dumb.ivan' in the same sentence is like putting an elevator in and outhouse, it just doesn't belong there.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353816024450</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 23:00:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353816367362-85</Id><Topic><Title>why bush is going to jail</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353724853695</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-23 21:40:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Using 'intelligent' and 'Dumb.ivan' in the same sentence is like putting an elevator in and outhouse, it just doesn't belong there." For your information, I only used it in the same paragraph, not the same sentence. I will try to avoid such inconsistancies for the sake of"thought police" if they should ever appear; especially if they show to be somewhat mentally disturbed by challenging conundrums.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353816367362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-24 23:06:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>