<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-13"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350100846551-1</Id><Topic><Title>common denominator:</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1350099265112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 23:34:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You left these off the list: - Adolph Hitler (directly responsible for more than 30 million deaths, including 6 million Jews, and supported and fawned over by large numbers of American right-wingers through most of the 1930s -- INCLUDING one Prescott Bush, father to Bush 41 and grandfather to Bush 43 -- until, you know, he overplayed his hand...) - Charles &amp; David Koch, - Grover Norquist, - Augusto Pinochet (who ordered the tortures and deaths of thousands of his political opponents, and was closely linked to Milton Friedman, the "Chicago School" and other prominent right-wingers in the United States), - the de Sola family (closely linked to the Salvadoran death squads - and to Mitt Romney and Bain Capital), - the Salaverria family (closely linked to the Salvadoran death squads - and to Mitt Romney and Bain Capital). An oversight, surely.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1350100846551</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 00:00:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350108523109-2</Id><Title>JOE BIDEN HAS IRAN UNDER HIS THUMB AND IRAN IS NO PROBLEMO. RYAN CANT FIND IRAN ON A MAP</Title><Msg>Joe biden has iran under his thumb and iran is no problemo. ryan cant find iran on a map</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350108523109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350109401285-3</Id><Title>JOE BIDEN THROWS CIA UNDER BUS ON BENGAZI LIBYA THEN SAYS CIA KNOWS IRANS EVERYMOVE</Title><Msg>JOE BIDEN THROWS CIA UNDER BUS ON BENGAZI LIBYA THEN SAYS CIA KNOWS IRANS EVERYMOVE. Joe can't have it both ways. Seriously no intelligent thinking person believes that the CIA told Joe Biden and Obama that an anti-islam movie maker youtube video caused the assasination of USA Libyan Ambassador and Obama and Biden immediately send Susan Rice to broadcast this caca-maymee story to the world. This caca-maymee movie maker tall tale was most likely invented by the Obama administration to make the movie maker their straw man that Obama / Biden could blame and to allow the Obama administration to apologize the the islamic Libyan terorists who murdered Ambassador Stevens. Obama / Biden had the anti-islam movie maker arrested to show the Libyan murderers that Obama admin wants to appease these killers by arresting the anti-islam movie maker. Now under Congressional Investigation the Caca-MayMee tall tale that Obama adminstration crafted and had Susan Rice parade around is collapsing and they need to come up with a new straw man to blame (the CIA). After Biden threw the CIA under the bus for Ambassador Stevens death, Biden brags that the CIA keeps him up to the minute on Irans every move. The Obama administrations deceitfullness and dishonesty is unprecedented.</Msg><Username>kwanza_beauty_queen</Username><Timestamp>1350109401285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:23:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>24</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350109968202-4</Id><Topic><Title>Proverbs 29:9 Applies to Joe Biden (the fool)</Title><Username>arnold_schwarzenegger_sukks</Username><Timestamp>1350070161807</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 15:29:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden's silly and stupid looking jeering and laughing at every issue, convinced me that he is indeed a fool and not qualified to be VP. These are serious issues and this fool laughs at everything. Biden convinced me that he is a weak and stupid idiot.</Msg><Username>friendsoftheseaotter</Username><Timestamp>1350109968202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:32:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350110550306-5</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN ACTED LIKE DEGENERATE JERRY SPRINGER GUEST</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350060201612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden convinced my democrat lover parents to vote for Romney. He really repulsed my mom. She went on and on about what a despicable rude stupid immature old codger he is. She really despised Bidens stupid grin and dorky laugh. LOL!</Msg><Username>homos_r_mentally_ill</Username><Timestamp>1350110550306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350113170913-6</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN ACTED LIKE DEGENERATE JERRY SPRINGER GUEST</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350060201612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan stayed composed and didn't stoop to Biden's level. Remember, Biden is next in line for the Presidency - scary thought, huh?</Msg><Username>xtromania</Username><Timestamp>1350113170913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 03:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350113553513-7</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN HAS IRAN UNDER HIS THUMB AND IRAN IS NO PROBLEMO. RYAN CANT FIND IRAN ON A MAP</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350108523109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All Joe can do is laugh nervously when under pressure. He disgraced the President.</Msg><Username>xtromania</Username><Timestamp>1350113553513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 03:32:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350113929961-8</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA MUST INTERRUPT ROMNEY NONSTOP AND LAUGH AT EVERYTHING ROMNEY SAYS AT NEXT DEBATE</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350090375305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 21:06:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden is a clown. We have a clown for VP - reason enough to not vote for that ticket.</Msg><Username>xtromania</Username><Timestamp>1350113929961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 03:38:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350125045773-9</Id><Title>ALL ROMNEY HAS TO DO IS ASK "WHY DID JOE BITEME SAY YOUR A CLEAN BLACK GUY" ???</Title><Msg>"WHY DID JOE BITEME SAY YOUR A CLEAN BLACK GUY" ??? While laughing historically non stop !!! BACK AT YOU DIM LIBS !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1350125045773</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:44:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350125220809-10</Id><Title>CISCO, THE SOUTHERN BORDER OF THE INTERNET</Title><Msg>ALLOWING THE CYBER PEARL HARBOR ??? Cause they hired to many ARABS being an BIG SELLOUT INTERNATIONAL Corp now.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1350125220809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 06:47:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350131261068-11</Id><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Msg>Cisco Systems, In (NasdaqNM: CSCO ) is definitely getting some attention lately.. The market is only going to increase in volatility so we can count on more sideways trading on Cisco Systems, In (NasdaqNM: CSCO ). Great opportunity for the short term traders who can play dips. Also Check Out... Copy &amp; Paste this to your browser -- mcaf.ee/yfq49</Msg><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350133764991-12</Id><Title>Maybe you are not GOP voter? Global warming,,kill social security and medicare</Title><Msg>More wars,,,less regulations on Wall Street,food we eat,medicine we take,air marshalls,cut fundings for our kids education,, BUT more tax breaks for BIG oil and rich..</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1350133764991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350133806481-13</Id><Title>How did Peewee Herman get to be a Vice Pres candidate???? he is another dan quayle</Title><Msg>Have another sip of water Peewee</Msg><Username>daleelama</Username><Timestamp>1350133806481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:10:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350134449272-14</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope it contains great info. I just joined. Many thanks</Msg><Username>rhonda.browning47</Username><Timestamp>1350134449272</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:20:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350134540231-15</Id><Title>Joltin Joe, no letup</Title><Msg>Biden Shares 20-Minute Post-Debate Kiss With Janna RyanOctober 11, 2012 | ISSUE 48•41 | More News in Brief DANVILLE, KY—Following Thursday night’s debate at Centre College, Vice President Joe Biden and Janna Ryan, wife of Rep. Paul Ryan (R-WI), shared a passionate 20-minute-long kiss that eyewitnesses described as lustful, vulgar, and sloppy. “Janna rushed past her husband and into Biden’s arms. He grabbed her and plunged his tongue deep into her mouth, and then they started going at it like crazy,” said debate moderator Martha Raddatz, explaining that the embracing couple caressed each other’s bodies while fervently kissing and tearing off various articles of clothing. “When the vice president began nibbling on her ears and fondling her breasts, Mrs. Ryan stuck her tongue straight out of her mouth and Biden just started licking all around it. She was literally shaking.” At press time, Biden told reporters he had Janna Ryan “gushing like Old Faithful.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1350134540231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:22:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350135361884-16</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'd like to see the rest of this has anyone watched</Msg><Username>carminecarr840</Username><Timestamp>1350135361884</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350135899120-17</Id><Title>Fact check says Joltin Joe was wrong about stimulus</Title><Msg>PAUL PORK - Sam Stein and Jason Cherkis: "During Thursday night's vice presidential debate, Vice President Joe Biden attacked Rep. Paul Ryan (R-Wis.) for criticizing the president's stimulus act despite having sent two separate requests for stimulus funds for his district. Biden was wrong. Ryan sent at least four requests. A Freedom of Information Act request for correspondence between Ryan's office and the Environmental Protection Agency, filed by The Huffington Post, unearthed two additional instances in which the Wisconsin Republican petitioned for American Recovery Act funds. In addition, there were many other occasions in which the GOP vice presidential nominee asked the EPA for grant money for projects in Wisconsin's 1st District, which encompasses Ryan's hometown of Janesville and has a slight Democratic lean. Combined, the letters muddy Ryan's claim that the stimulus wasn't helpful and that government spending, more broadly, doesn't assist small businesses."</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1350135899120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350137853125-18</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good Investor Report?</Title><Username>merilynguuq146392</Username><Timestamp>1350084425092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are extremely good. So far I am very happy.</Msg><Username>valenciatbeh861939</Username><Timestamp>1350137853125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:17:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350137936869-19</Id><Title>Here is the one precent, now lets look at Nancy Pelosi and Harry Reid</Title><Msg>Al Gore’s commitment to promoting green energy has brought him widespread acclaim, a Nobel Prize and even an Oscar. It’s also brought him more than a pretty penny. The author of An Inconvenient Truth has swelled his net worth to about $100 million, largely due to his investments in green energy, after being worth less than $2 million during his time as Vice President, The Washington Post reports.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1350137936869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:18:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350138986503-20</Id><Topic><Title>Fact check says Joltin Joe was wrong about stimulus</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1350135899120</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 09:44:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now THAT'S Funny!</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1350138986503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:36:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350139008994-21</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beautiful women always come around when there is money. The game is get those beautiful women to pay for you :)</Msg><Username>wilburnoliver242</Username><Timestamp>1350139008994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350139275340-22</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good Investor Report?</Title><Username>merilynguuq146392</Username><Timestamp>1350084425092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>valenciatbeh861939</Username><Timestamp>1350139275340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 10:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350140983660-23</Id><Title>Fresh analysis of Romney's Tax Plan</Title><Msg>http://blogs.wsj.com/washwire/2012/10/12/fresh-debate-over-new-tax-study/</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350140983660</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350143114103-24</Id><Title>Down on America......</Title><Msg>Down On America: As Economy Improves, Republicans Remain In Denial October 12th, 2012 10:58 pm Joe Conason When Joe Biden said “I’ve never met two guys more down on America across the board,” he meant Mitt Romney and Paul Ryan — who provoked the vice president’s snipe during their debate by insisting, utterly falsely, that unemployment is still worsening across the nation. But the vice president’s complaint also applies to the Republican leadership at large, in Congress and across the right-wing media, where the talking points on U.S. economic prospects and progress are always negative. Certainly the Republicans have tried to do their part to sink the economy, as last year’s manufactured debt crisis demonstrated beyond doubt. But whenever the news is good, they insist that the encouraging data must be inaccurate or even manipulated – as former General Electric boss Jack Welch proclaimed in his infamous tweet about the newly improved unemployment data last week. This week the right-wing propaganda machine disparaged a big reduction in new jobless claims as a statistical anomaly, supposedly based on California’s failure to report its data to the Bureau of Labor Statistics in Washington. The only problem with this theory is that California officials did report those numbers.Meanwhile both the mainstream and right-wing media largely ignored the latest report by the Financial Times and the Brookings Institution, which found that the United States is “the sole bright spot” in a sluggish world economy. Just how much uplifting data must appear before the persistent naysayers admit that the economy is improving? It is true that the numbers cut against their political interest, so they’re likely to deny any signs of economic health unless and until they can claim credit. Yet the signs are present and increasing. On Friday, the Treasury Department reported that the federal budget deficit will again exceed $1 trillion, mostly as a consequence of the Bush tax cuts—but the good news is that tax revenue went up anyway by 6.4 percent, solely because of growth in jobs and income. (And in fact, the deficit was lower than last year, thanks to a reduction in government spending as American troops left Iraq.) So the president is reducing the deficit, as promised, in the only sensible and equitable way that can be done—by eliminating the cost of a pointless war abroad and stimulating growth at home. Consumer confidence—another key indicator—has risen to the highest level since September 2007, according to a survey released today by Thomson Reuters and the University of Michigan. The measure climbed to 83.1, jumping almost five points from the August rating of 78.3. Reuters reported that the new number significantly exceeded the expectations of most analysts, “who expected the rating to drop.” There is more almost every day. Ask the bankers, who also seem to have noticed positive indicators (when they take a break from raising money for Romney). The chief financial economist for the Bank of Tokyo, for instance, told the Los Angeles Times that even if the new jobs numbers require correction—as such statistics almost always do, “the [improved] direction of the labor market is real.” Reporting record profits for JPMorgan Chase on Friday, Jamie Dimon released a statement saying that the housing market has “turned a corner.” His company’s investment banking unit earned more in underwriting fees for equity and debt instruments—another indicator that firms are finally putting money into plants and equipment, rather than continuing to sit on trillions of dollars. Polls suggest that the setbacks of the past few years have left voters with little patience for White House boasts of economic progress. But recent improvements open space for President Obama to say that things are finally getting better—and that changing course toward the radical right would be dangerous and foolish.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1350143114103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:45:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350143139609-25</Id><Topic><Title>hey rhonda meanwhile in the real world, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1350091017073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 21:16:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check Biden's favoribility numbers next week.Guaranteed they went down.As people analyze the debate its plain Biden hurt the Obama campaign .Saying he and Obama didn't know about the security requests makes it seem they were out of the loop. Saying we dont need more M-1 tanks make the M-1 tank builders in Ohio worry about their jobs.Lying about the contraception mandate stirred up the Catholic clergy again.There's more but you get the drift. Joe Biden...the gift that keeps on giving.Thanks,Joe.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350143139609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:45:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350143674380-26</Id><Topic><Title>hey rhonda meanwhile in the real world, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1350091017073</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 21:16:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've seen one poll that says Biden won and three that Ryan won. But none are important. By Monday no one will be talking about Biden/Ryan as the big debate approaches Tuesday. But I 'll repeat that Biden actually hurt Obama. You want to deny the obvious,go ahead. His Libya remarks especially hurt their campaign.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350143674380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 11:54:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350144395060-27</Id><Topic><Title>Report inside with a good link Cisco Systems, Inc.</Title><Username>laticiahzycf47705</Username><Timestamp>1350054501688</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 11:08:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>lashandrahgs92898</Username><Timestamp>1350144395060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350146209464-28</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN THROWS CIA UNDER BUS ON BENGAZI LIBYA THEN SAYS CIA KNOWS IRANS EVERYMOVE</Title><Username>kwanza_beauty_queen</Username><Timestamp>1350109401285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everybody in America believed that the US Embassy in Libya was attacked because of the anti-islam you tube video. Obama did the right thing when he arrested the you tube video film-maker. By Obama's arresting this anti-islam radical, Obama showed all musslims that America apologizes to musslims for this reprehensible anti-islam video and that as long as Obama is in charge anti-islam videos will not be tolerated. Obama deserves a Nobel Peace prize for arresting film makers who make anti-islam videos.</Msg><Username>loretta_sanchez_is_smart</Username><Timestamp>1350146209464</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:36:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350146799951-29</Id><Title>Obama State Dept Official said that funding was NOT a factor in Rejecting Ambassador Stevens Request for more Security</Title><Msg>Charlene Lamb was asked in the Congressional hearings if funding was a factor in rejecting the ambassadors request for more security.Lamb said it was not. Democrat liars need to find another excuse.</Msg><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350146799951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350148324654-30</Id><Topic><Title>Obama State Dept Official said that funding was NOT a factor in Rejecting Ambassador Stevens Request for more Security</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350146799951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"By Rep. Mike Kelly, Special Op-Ed to the Washington Times "In a May 3, 2012, email, the State Department denied a request by a group of Special Forces assigned to protect the U.S. embassy in Libya to continue their use of a DC- 3 airplane for security operations throughout the country. The subject line of the email, on which slain Ambassador Chris Stevens was copied, read: “Termination of Tripoli DC-3 Support.” Four days later, on May 7, the State Department authorized the U.S. embassy in Vienna to purchase a $108,000 electric vehicle charging station for the embassy motor pool’s new Chevrolet Volts. The purchase was a part of the State Department’s “Energy Efficiency Sweep of Europe” initiative, which included hundreds of thousands of taxpayer dollars on green program expenditures at various U.S. Embassies. In fact, at a May 10 gala held at the U.S. embassy in Vienna, the ambassador showcased his new Volts and other green investments as part of the U.S. government’s commitment to “climate change solutions.” The event posting on the embassy website read: “Celebrating the Greening of the Embassy.” While the embassy in Vienna was going green, the consulate in Benghazi was getting bombed, and little was done to stop it. Before the terrorist attack that took the lives of Ambassador Chris Stevens, Sean Smith, Glen Doherty and Tyrone Woods, there were more than 230 security incidents in Libya between June 2011 and July 2012. Of those attacks, 48 took place in Benghazi, two at the U.S. diplomatic compound and scene of the September 11, 2012, terrorist attacks. This first attack on the Benghazi compound occurred on April 6, 2012, when two Libyans threw a crude improvised explosive device over the compound wall. Two months later, another IED exploded at the compound, wounding one person and leaving a hole in the perimeter wall large enough for 40 people to run through. The second attack was linked to the “Brigades of the Imprisoned Sheikh Omar Abdul Rahman,” a jihadist, pro-al Qaeda group named after the mastermind of the 1993 World Trade Center bombing. The same group was responsible for subsequent attacks on the British ambassador to Libya and the International Committee of the Red Cross, both of which took place in Benghazi just months before the September attack. While these steady and increasingly violent attacks on western interests mounted, the U.S. State Department repeatedly rejected requests for additional protection measures for our security teams in Libya. According to Eric Nordstrom, a regional security officer of the U.S. Mission to Libya from September 2011 to July 2012, the State Department not only refused his requests for greater security, but actually reduced the number of Diplomatic Security Service (DSS) agents assigned to foreign service officers based in Libya. Ironically, as the State Department withdrew security resources, it increased hazard pay for its employees based in Libya by 5 percent."</Msg><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1350148324654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:12:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350148372473-31</Id><Topic><Title>Obama State Dept Official said that funding was NOT a factor in Rejecting Ambassador Stevens Request for more Security</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350146799951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you are buying $47000 Chevy Volts and building a $108000 charging station for the Vienna embassy is there money left over for Benghazi ? When you have a marine detachment protecting the Paris embassy do you have marines leftover for Benghazi?? When you are paying for a full time Secret Service detail for Valerie Jarrett does that leave money for Benghazi?? This administration has its priorities all screwed up.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1350148372473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:12:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>21</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149393974-32</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN ACTED LIKE DEGENERATE JERRY SPRINGER GUEST</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350060201612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In his mind Biden thought he looked smart and dashing. In reality Bidens looked like an idiot. What an embarrassment he is for the USA.</Msg><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1350149393974</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:29:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149673979-33</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN HAS IRAN UNDER HIS THUMB AND IRAN IS NO PROBLEMO. RYAN CANT FIND IRAN ON A MAP</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350108523109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe is a disgrace to America. I dont know of any other world leader that is as stupid and immature or as infantile as Joe.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1350149673979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:34:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350149697357-34</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good Investor Report?</Title><Username>merilynguuq146392</Username><Timestamp>1350084425092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. I love it.</Msg><Username>natalieswls21012</Username><Timestamp>1350149697357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:34:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350150373349-35</Id><Topic><Title>Obama State Dept Official said that funding was NOT a factor in Rejecting Ambassador Stevens Request for more Security</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350146799951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From Breibart News Website: State Department Cut Libyan Security While Spending on Chevy Volts The Washington Times is reporting that at the same time State Department officials were cutting security for our diplomatic stations in Libya, they were increasing the budget for our embassy in Austria in order to purchase Chevrolet's electric powered Volt: In a May 3, 2012, email, the State Department denied a request by a group of Special Forces assigned to protect the U.S. embassy in Libya to continue their use of a DC- 3 airplane for security operations throughout the country. . . Four days later, on May 7, the State Department authorized the U.S. embassy in Vienna [Austria] to purchase a $108,000 electric vehicle charging station for the embassy motor pool’s new Chevrolet Volts. The purchase was a part of the State Department’s “Energy Efficiency Sweep of Europe” initiative, which included hundreds of thousands of taxpayer dollars on green program expenditures at various U.S. Embassies. In fact, at a May 10 gala held at the U.S. embassy in Vienna, the ambassador showcased his new Volts and other green investments as part of the U.S. government’s commitment to “climate change solutions.” . . . Before the terrorist attack that took the lives of Ambassador Chris Stevens, Sean Smith, Glen Doherty and Tyrone Woods, there were more than 230 security incidents in Libya between June 2011 and July 2012. Of those attacks, 48 took place in Benghazi, two at the U.S. diplomatic compound and scene of the September 11, 2012, terrorist attacks. The American embassy in Austria is considered one of the safest diplomatic postings in the world. The American mission in Benghazi, Libya is considered one of the most dangerous. While the State Department Rules of Engagement for Libya signed by Secretary of State Hillary Clinton within the last eighteen months specifically prohibits the stationing of Marines at any diplomatic station in that country, the American embassy in Austria has a full complement of Marines. Among their duties are the presenting of the American flag at the annual 4th of July picnic held at the embassy in Vienna every year." Read full story at Breibart website.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1350150373349</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:46:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>20</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350150586626-36</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN HAS IRAN UNDER HIS THUMB AND IRAN IS NO PROBLEMO. RYAN CANT FIND IRAN ON A MAP</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350108523109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(I dont know of any other world leader that is as stupid and immature or as infantile as Joe.) Obama?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1350150586626</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350151132790-37</Id><Topic><Title>UNDOCUMENTED IMIGRANT KILLED WHILE WORKING ON 405 FREEWAY WHERE IS OSHA???</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350001429071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another undocumented imigrant union worker killed after being cooked in a steamer at the Bumble Bee Tuna Plant in Santa Fe Springs California. There is an epidemic of undocumented imigrant union worker deaths due to failures of following OSHA safety standards in America.. We need to protect the safety of undocumented imigrant union workers in America.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350151132790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 13:58:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350151736616-38</Id><Title>MILLION MUPPET MARCH PLANNED TO PROTEST MITT ROMNEY ATTACK ON BIG BIRD</Title><Msg>From Reuters: (Reuters) - Plans to save Big Bird, the fuzzy yellow character on U.S. public television's "Sesame Street," from possible extinction are taking shape in the form of a puppet-based protest next month dubbed the "Million Muppet March." The demonstration is planned for November 3 at the National Mall in Washington, D.C., three days before the general election. Read full story at Reuters website and support the Muppets.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350151736616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152019740-39</Id><Topic><Title>UNDOCUMENTED IMIGRANT KILLED WHILE WORKING ON 405 FREEWAY WHERE IS OSHA???</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350001429071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont worry.Out here in CA we'll make sure the illegals family gets all the welfare benefits available, pay his lawyer fees if they sue for wrongful death,help pay for all of his kids to go to college,grant them a special drivers license for illegals,and several other things Americans cant get. And people wonder why CA is going bankrupt??? We are a socialist state.Watch out,America, you are next.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1350152019740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:13:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152186484-40</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN HAS IRAN UNDER HIS THUMB AND IRAN IS NO PROBLEMO. RYAN CANT FIND IRAN ON A MAP</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350108523109</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:08:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is evil (not stupid). Biden is a fool (evil and stupid).</Msg><Username>kenya_bolshevik_from_chicago</Username><Timestamp>1350152186484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152237293-41</Id><Topic><Title>MILLION MUPPET MARCH PLANNED TO PROTEST MITT ROMNEY ATTACK ON BIG BIRD</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350151736616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Notice Obama campaign pulled their Big Bird ad and quit bringing up the subject.Guess somebody told them Americans have a lot more to worry about than Big Bird.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1350152237293</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350152538323-42</Id><Topic><Title>MILLION MUPPET MARCH PLANNED TO PROTEST MITT ROMNEY ATTACK ON BIG BIRD</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350151736616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw the video of the Democrat Party Big Bird ad. I think Democrats should run that ad 24/7. It is good for a laugh and nothing more.</Msg><Username>kenya_bolshevik_from_chicago</Username><Timestamp>1350152538323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153103504-43</Id><Title>UNION TEACHER PASSENGER WHO WORE BULLET PROOF VEST, FLAME RETARDENT PANTS AND HAD ARSENAL OF WEAPONS IN LUGGAGE PLANNED TO MURDER LITTLE GIRLS</Title><Msg>UNION TEACHER PASSENGER WHO WORE BULLET PROOF VEST, FLAME RETARDENT PANTS AND HAD ARSENAL OF WEAPONS IN LUGGAGE PLANNED TO MURDER LITTLE GIRLS. This is the kind of lowlife that 'teaches' in classrooms everyday. From AP via yahoo news: "LOS ANGELES (AP) — A teacher arrested at Los Angeles International Airport wearing a bulletproof vest and with checked bags containing knives, body bags, a smoke grenade and other weapons also had files on his computer detailing how to kidnap and kill people, federal authorities disclosed Friday. In addition, Yongda Huang Harris had items on his computer revealing he has a "strong interest" in sexual violence against girls, including a video titled "Schoolgirls in Cement," Assistant U.S. Attorney Melissa Mills said. One publication was entitled "Man Trapping" and showed how to hunt and trap humans, she said. He also had a document with schedules for schools in Japan showing when students arrived and left. The prosecutor detailed the discoveries during a court appearance by Harris, 28, a Boston University graduate who had been working in Japan as a junior high school teacher. The bespectacled Harris was shackled in handcuffs and wore a white prison-issued jumpsuit, along with a blue surgical mask over his mouth due to a throat infection. Before the detention hearing, he crossed and rubbed his arms, appearing to be cold. He often turned and spoke with his attorney Steven Seiden. U.S. Magistrate Judge Paul Abrams declared Harris to be a flight risk and ordered him held without bond until he stands trial. Harris is charged with one count of transporting hazardous materials, for the grenade, and could face up to five years in prison if convicted. He did not enter a plea. Seiden said the weapons Harris was carrying were meant for protection and necessary because Harris was once attacked on the streets of Boston. "He may have interests that are not of the norm, but that doesn't mean he's carrying out any type of harm to anyone," said Seiden, who described his client as shy and timid. Seiden also said Harris didn't have any previous psychological issues. Harris was arrested on Oct. 5 during a stopover in Los Angeles on his trip from Japan to Boston. He was wearing the bulletproof vest under a trench coat along with fire-resistant pants and kneepads. His attire attracted the attention of law enforcement, and when his luggage was checked the weapons cache was found, authorities said. The search of his checked luggage uncovered numerous suspicious items, including a hatchet, knives, collapsible baton, biohazard suit, billy clubs, handcuffs, leg irons and a device to repel dogs, authorities said. The items "looked like a kidnap kit," prosecutor Mills said. Seiden, who also represents the man believed to be behind an anti-Muslim film that roiled the Middle East, said the clothing worn by Harris when he was arrested is common in Asian countries and described the outfit as resembling martial arts attire.</Msg><Username>panty_clad_hippo</Username><Timestamp>1350153103504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350153861521-44</Id><Title>Romney Lie (not 20%)</Title><Msg>Immediate repeal of some of the most popular tax benefits would pay for only a 4 percent cut in U.S. income tax rates, according to an estimate by Congress’s nonpartisan scorekeeper that illustrates the mathematical and political challenges of financing rate cuts by limiting tax breaks. The analysis by the Joint Committee on Taxation emphasizes the difficult choices facing lawmakers as they balance the benefits of rate cuts against the consequences of changing or ending deductions, such as for mortgage interest and charitable contributions. Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney proposes a 20 percent income-tax rate cut and says he would pay for it by limiting deductions, credits and exemptions.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1350153861521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350154073290-45</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN THROWS CIA UNDER BUS ON BENGAZI LIBYA THEN SAYS CIA KNOWS IRANS EVERYMOVE</Title><Username>kwanza_beauty_queen</Username><Timestamp>1350109401285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm a democrat and it took me 5 minutes to see that Obama and Biden are covering up their screw up with all kinds of #$%$. They should have come clean and be straight with America but now they have created a mess. Coverups are always worst than the truth.</Msg><Username>ferrari_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1350154073290</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350154629944-46</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN THROWS CIA UNDER BUS ON BENGAZI LIBYA THEN SAYS CIA KNOWS IRANS EVERYMOVE</Title><Username>kwanza_beauty_queen</Username><Timestamp>1350109401285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 02:23:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Totally agree. Appears the bad decision not to increase security at Benghazi was made by Charlene Lamb at the State Dept. I seriously doubt Obama even knew of that.But after the attack people much higher than Lamb decided to put out the cover story about the video and" spontaneous demonstration". Hillary, Jarrett and Obama come to mind.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350154629944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:57:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350154694831-47</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gonna raise the deal" this time as much</Msg><Username>collinsstacey774</Username><Timestamp>1350154694831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350156684112-48</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO - Good Data for CSCO Traders</Title><Username>ochoaarlene514</Username><Timestamp>1350131261068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 08:27:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wild one, GOD bless you and Thank You!</Msg><Username>cabrera.mabel44</Username><Timestamp>1350156684112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350157104359-49</Id><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Msg>What Romney believes! 1 Reducing taxes and regulations will create jobs. This was the policy under Bush that took our country from a budget surplus to a budget deficit and failed to sustain a vital growing economy. 2. Only those individuals currently covered by medical insurance should be covered for pre-existing conditions. 3. Competition between the insurance companies will reduce medical costs. Isn’t this what we have today for everyone under the age of 65? Have you premiums gone up and health care improved? 4. The current Social Security system should be changed to allow individuals to invest their retirement funds in the stock market in hopes of getting a higher return. How much money would you have lost if you had sold the stocks in your retirement fund at the bottom of the recession? 5.You believe that higher income earners (those in the top 10%) should pay taxes at lower rate than Warren Buffet’s secretary or the average wage earner. 6. Taxes and regulations, not the lack of demand, were the major cause of the recession. 7. That the banking and financial industry does not need to be regulated. What do you think caused the housing industry to collapse and the banks to need financial aid from the government to survive? 8. Women should be paid less than men for the same job. 9. That the United States should increase its military spending even though the U.S. already spends more on defense than the next 13 countries with the highest defense budgets. 10 That companies are people and should be allowed to make unlimited political contributions without disclosure. It is your vote. This former Republican is voting for Obama</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157886523-50</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strange that you liberals always try to tear down Romney instead of trying to build up Obama.Why dont you brag on what Obama has done instead of whining about what Romney might do??</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350157886523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350157943176-51</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good Investor Report?</Title><Username>merilynguuq146392</Username><Timestamp>1350084425092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks. Please always share this to us.</Msg><Username>keshafxlnp62669</Username><Timestamp>1350157943176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350158055133-52</Id><Topic><Title>UNDOCUMENTED IMIGRANT KILLED WHILE WORKING ON 405 FREEWAY WHERE IS OSHA???</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350001429071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"America, you are next." To bad Canada didn't see it coming, To scared and PC I guess, Would of been cheaper for Canada to build the fence on MexiHole/America border along with Canadian military troops. While that fence would of been a lot shorter and cheaper to build... Get ready Canada for the Latino WMPE, Weapon of Mass Population Explosion...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1350158055133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:54:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350158238346-53</Id><Topic><Title>UNDOCUMENTED IMIGRANT KILLED WHILE WORKING ON 405 FREEWAY WHERE IS OSHA???</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350001429071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey DUMB DUMB ivan, look at this one 10 thumbs up !!!!!!!!!! Are illegals your next voter pandering base or GAYS ? (probably both since Obonobo threw BLACKS under the bus, sure NOT Asians, they are to smart to be libs)</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1350158238346</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350158472707-54</Id><Topic><Title>Obama State Dept Official said that funding was NOT a factor in Rejecting Ambassador Stevens Request for more Security</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350146799951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 12:46:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bidens response was that the CIA (who keeps him informed minute by minute of every move by Iran) screwed up and told him and Obama that the anti-islam movie caused Libyans to murder Ambassador Stevens. Obama and Biden promptly had the anti-islam movie maker arrested to show the Libyans that Biden wont tolerate any anti-islam you tube movies in the USA. Does anyone really believe the CIA is that stupid to tell Obama and Biden to arrest a youtube anti-islam movie maker for the murder of Ambassador Stevens??? Obama's State Department run by Hillary Clinton are the ones who had Susan Rice spread the rumour (that they made up) that the anti-islam you tube video caused the assasination of Ambassador Stevens. Obama admin created the anti-islam video straw man to blame. Now they want to blame the CIA??? Susan Rice does not work for the CIA, she works for Hillary Clinton.</Msg><Username>ron_paul_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1350158472707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350158619740-55</Id><Topic><Title>UNDOCUMENTED IMIGRANT KILLED WHILE WORKING ON 405 FREEWAY WHERE IS OSHA???</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350001429071</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-11 20:23:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Illegal Alien criminals dont belong in the USA.</Msg><Username>ron_paul_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1350158619740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350159031469-56</Id><Title>Florida Passes Plan For Racially-Based Academic Goals</Title><Msg>Florida Democrats Pass Plan For Racially-Based Academic Goals. Democrats Lowered standards for blacks and latinos and raised standards for Asians and Whites. Democrats taking racism to new highs. Race should not matter. The goal should be that everyone (regardless of race) gets the best education possible.</Msg><Username>ron_paul_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1350159031469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350159786531-57</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They also think that they are clever by falsely claiming that they are former republicans and that real republicans are dumb enough to believe that and join them in voting democrat.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1350159786531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160055239-58</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay. 1. He saved the automobile industry and thereby thousands of jobs. 2. Passed a heath care program that allows individuals with pre-existinf conditions to get insurance. 3.Got a stimulus bill passed that saved thousands of job. It just was not big enough! 4. Completed the withdrawal from Iraq. 5. Got a bill passed to regulate the banks and financial institutions. May not have gone far enough. Those are a few for starters. Do I wish that he could have done more -certainly. I'm not completely satisfied with his performance or with that of the obstructionist Congress.</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350160055239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350160150650-59</Id><Title>MESSAGE TO DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO DESTROY OIL COMPANIES</Title><Msg>Message to cretin democrats who want to destroy oil companies destroying oil companies = no gas for your suvs</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1350160150650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350160150723-60</Id><Title>MESSAGE TO DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO DESTROY OIL COMPANIES</Title><Msg>Message to cretin democrats who want to destroy oil companies destroying oil companies = no gas for your suvs</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1350160150723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160464798-61</Id><Topic><Title>MESSAGE TO DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO DESTROY OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1350160150723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats dont want to destroy the oil company. Democrats want the oil company at its own expense to produce refined oil and to give free oil to these democrats. The only problem with this kind of fantasy island irrational greed and stupidity is that nobody will produce oil at their own expense and give it away for free.</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1350160464798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160559521-62</Id><Topic><Title>MESSAGE TO DEMOCRATS WHO WANT TO DESTROY OIL COMPANIES</Title><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1350160150650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:29:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats dont really want to destroy the oil company. What Democrats really want is for the oil company at its own expense to produce refined oil and to give free oil to these democrats. The biggest problem with this kind of irrational greed and fantasy island stupidity is that nobody will produce oil at their own expense and give it away for free.</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1350160559521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160608523-63</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, I still believe in financial responsibility and trying to balance the budget. Clinton balanced the budget. Bush did not. I'm not sure what the Republican party believes in any more except less taxes and less regulation both of which along with two wars and unfunded mandates helped created our current financial problem.</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350160608523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350160847880-64</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama had two years with Democrats Pelosi and Reid completely controlling congress. They could have done anything they wanted to do. Two years is alot of time when a Democrat President has a Senate and House of Reps that is controlled by Democrats. Yet democrats like to repeat the lie that republicans obstructed Obama his entire Presidency as an extremely lame excuse for Obama's failure.</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1350160847880</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:40:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350161002842-65</Id><Topic><Title>Florida Passes Plan For Racially-Based Academic Goals</Title><Username>ron_paul_sucks</Username><Timestamp>1350159031469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:10:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats are the biggest racists in my opinion. It seems that every piece of their legislation and policies have race as a criteria and treat each race differently (basically racism).</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1350161002842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:43:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350161277833-66</Id><Topic><Title>MILLION MUPPET MARCH PLANNED TO PROTEST MITT ROMNEY ATTACK ON BIG BIRD</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1350151736616</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 14:08:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats are so childish that they really believe that unemployed and poverty stricken adults who are struggling in their daily lives because of Obamanomics have infantand small child mentalities that these starving adults will run out there and vote Democrat to save Big Bird. Its incredible how dumb democrats think most Americans are.</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1350161277833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350161433049-67</Id><Topic><Title>Is this a good Investor Report?</Title><Username>merilynguuq146392</Username><Timestamp>1350084425092</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:27:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>keshafxlnp62669</Username><Timestamp>1350161433049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350162646336-68</Id><Title>ILLEGAL ALIEN UNION WORKER COOKED TO DEATH IN BUMBLE BEE TUNA STEAMER MACHINE</Title><Msg>ILLEGAL ALIEN UNION WORKER COOKED TO DEATH IN BUMBLE BEE TUNA STEAMER MACHINE. It does not surprize me that uneducated, illiterate unskilled illegal alien union worker who habitually disregard USA laws and USA safety rules would be dumb enough enter a tuna steamer cooking machine while it is running.</Msg><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1350162646336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350162750589-69</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush started the auto bailout.Gave an initial 13.4 to GM and Chrysler. Obamacare remains unpopular and the estimated cost has already tripled The stimulus was a failure according to most economists Yes,he completed the Iraqi withdrawal on Bush's timetable Now I see why you dont talk about Obama accomplishments.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350162750589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:12:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163491477-70</Id><Topic><Title>JOE BIDEN ACTED LIKE DEGENERATE JERRY SPRINGER GUEST</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1350060201612</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 12:43:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've never seen any world leader acting as immature, uncivilized and stupid as Joe Biden (giggling, laughing, jeering at serious issues). Joe is obviously proud of being a jerk and having a reputation of being stupid.</Msg><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1350163491477</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350163631392-71</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't long ago you were bragging how Obama saved the banks and auto industry.Now you say Bush was forced to do it. Barney Frank and Chris Dodd were more responsible for the recession than Bush. If Clinton had taken Bin Laden when offered there would have never been a 9/11. You celebrate kool-ade. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350163631392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350164001248-72</Id><Topic><Title>Billy Graham Endorses Romney Then Scrubs His Site Calling Mormonism A ‘Cult’</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1350161297769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 16:48:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you the guy who makes fun of old people on this board. Now you are citing 93 year old Billy Graham?? You are such a phony hypocrite it is amazing. And you wonder why everyone thinks you are an idiot???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350164001248</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:33:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350168602063-73</Id><Title>Mitt willing to spend up to 30% of his time</Title><Msg>on the Presidency just like when he was in MA BOSTON — When the ceiling collapsed in the Big Dig tunnel here, Gov. Mitt Romney was at his vacation home in New Hampshire. When the Bush administration warned that the nation was at high risk of a terror attack in December 2003, he was at his Utah retreat. And for much of the time the legislature was negotiating changes to his landmark health care bill, he was on the road. The New York Times During Mr. Romney’s four-year term as governor of Massachusetts, he cumulatively spent more than a year — part or all of 417 days — out of the state, according to a review of his schedule and other records. More than 70 percent of that time was spent on personal or political trips unrelated to his job, a New York Times analysis found.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1350168602063</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:50:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350169022808-74</Id><Topic><Title>What Romney Believes</Title><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1350157104359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 15:38:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dems had total control for 4 months you dimwitted idiot yeah and they couldn't fix all of Bushes disasters in 4 months!!! What's the matter with the Dems, it only took Bush 8 years to destroy the world economy.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1350169022808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 18:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350170570318-75</Id><Topic><Title>I CORRECTLY PRODICTED THE BIDEN DEBATE WIN. HERE IS ANOTHER PREDICTION:</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1350163631590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 17:27:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You " prodicted" Obama would humiliate Romney in the first debate.How did that turn out ?</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1350170570318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350172766215-76</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Lied about Libya and they are throwing Hillary to the Wolves</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1350084496778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hopefully when Bill does the new interns he will do better than that fat cow Monica.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1350172766215</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 19:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350174961845-77</Id><Title>Rank has its privileges.</Title><Msg>Twenty kids from a charter school were invited to watch the vp debate.They made an 8 hour bus trip to get there. Upon arriving they found their seats had been given to some vips and reporters. They were sent back to their hotel and watched it on tv in their rooms.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1350174961845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350176026322-78</Id><Title>Should be funny</Title><Msg>Wanna bet SNL makes fun of Goofball Biden tonight??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1350176026322</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350176342922-79</Id><Title>Another democrat crook</Title><Msg>Democrat Jesse Jackson Jr. under investigation for financial "improprieties ".</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1350176342922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 20:59:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1350180451766-80</Id><Title>Romney - Bain - 47% of the people - hidden tax returns</Title><Msg>Thats enough information - for the American voter to see what this guy is about</Msg><Username>amagine2000</Username><Timestamp>1350180451766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350182104240-81</Id><Topic><Title>Romney - Bain - 47% of the people - hidden tax returns</Title><Username>amagine2000</Username><Timestamp>1350180451766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:07:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney overpaid his taxes, he could have deducted every dollar of the $3 million dollars in very generous CHARITY, something Obama doesn't know about. Romney gave 3 million to strangers Obama won't and has never given a dime to his brother who lives in a hut earning $5 per day. Romney didn't deduct the $3 mil in charity so he overpaid his taxes by a real big margin.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1350182104240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:35:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1350182311404-82</Id><Topic><Title>Biden Lied about Libya and they are throwing Hillary to the Wolves</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1350084496778</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-12 19:28:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think in the next debate the Zebradouche is going to throw Hillary under the bus. Why do I think this. Because the President makes excuses, never takes his lumps for his mistakes, he is still blaming Bush. He will blame Hillary. It won't work.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1350182311404</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-13 22:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>