<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-29"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348892704376-1</Id><Topic><Title>“The reality is that (Republicans are) losing, they can’t accept it, and they’re going to find some reason to dismiss every poll that makes them unhappy no matter what its composition is,” Jensen added. “This isn’t really about Party ID, it’s about hardcore denial.”</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348880165994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:56:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ObamaCare ObamaBucks ObamaPhones ObamaFood Stamps ObamaMortgages ObamaSchools Obama.......... LET'S BECOME LIKE FAILED EUROPE! Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1348892704376</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 00:25:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348904162408-2</Id><Title>Obama phones, Ipads, HDTV's , cars, food stamps, enough, never enough, redistribution</Title><Msg>Well come election day, we the people who pay for spreading it around will get retribution at the ballot box like in 2010.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348904162408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:36:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348916495585-3</Id><Topic><Title>WAY TO GO RHONDA!! PILE IT ON!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348879625538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:47:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Intelligent women are definitely attractive, but I'm deeply committed already! So much fun to watch you Dems deny reality! Oh yeah, the deluge is coming, the irresponsible, abusive, manipulative days of Democrats are coming to a close. But not before you caused so much damage!! LOOK AT THE EMPTY SHELL THAT WAS DETROIT LOOK AT THE UNEDUCATED, ABANDONED CHILDREN OF YOUR PUBLIC EDUCATION SYSTEM LOOK AT THE TRILLIONS IN STUDENT DEBT PROMOTED BY OBIMBO...sad, sad, sad. The wreckage of the Democratic party, the millions enabled to become non-productive, angry and disappointed. Sooner or later, Democrat, you run out of 'other people's money' then the party is over</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348916495585</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:01:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348918277413-4</Id><Title>4 years at Western Carolina</Title><Msg>Mother, do you think they'll drop the bomb? Mother do you think they'll like this song? Mother do you think they'll try to break my balls? Oooh, ah, Mother, should I build the wall? Mother, should I run for president? Mother, should I trust the government? Mother, will they put me in the firing line? Oooh, ah, is it just a waste of time? Hush, now, baby, baby, don't you cry. Mama's gonna make all of your nightmares come true. Mama's gonna put all of her fears into you. Mama's gonna keep you right here under her wing. She won't let you fly, but she might let you sing. Mama's gonna keep baby cozy and warm...Oooh, baby, oooh, baby of course mama's gonna help build the wall......</Msg><Username>medical.mpp_4u</Username><Timestamp>1348918277413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:31:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348918952374-5</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS IT IS WHITE...I WILL VOTE FOR A MARSH MELLOW FOR PRESIDENT...</Title><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348880505603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't that cute, the Obots being riddled with facts and all they have is to copy someones ID and post racist remarks. Sad and desperate.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348918952374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348919495415-6</Id><Title>Which candidate wants to abolish SLavery? This candidate will get my vote.</Title><Msg>After masked protesters vandalized banks and a Whole Foods grocery, leading to violent clashes with police, the Occupy Oakland movement works to protect its non-violent image and wavered from its stance on MPP. However Police hesitated and when the smoke cleared social change through violence didn't work this time. Jack didn't want to be called an anarchist.</Msg><Username>medical.mpp_4u</Username><Timestamp>1348919495415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348919548419-7</Id><Title>csco dividend</Title><Msg>when is div ex-date?</Msg><Username>krasasc</Username><Timestamp>1348919548419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:52:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348920501461-8</Id><Title>CIVIL RIGHTS ARE VERY IMPORTANT</Title><Msg>the civil rights of ordinary folks in America are extremely important and we all know that! It is time to demand a stable, functioning, balanced budget Federal govt., since the chaos and uncertainty, plus lack of jobs this creates destroys all CIVIL LIBERTY. Rampant inflation, and no job, NO SECURITY, NO LIBERTY......why do Democrats not see this? When can we flush these stinking fecal deposits? IN NOVEMBER!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348920501461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:08:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348920689799-9</Id><Topic><Title>csco dividend</Title><Username>krasasc</Username><Timestamp>1348919548419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 07:52:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next Tuesday, October 2nd.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348920689799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348920795705-10</Id><Title>FBI says you're spending too much time on Facebook</Title><Msg>THE FBI THINKS YOU SPEND TOO MUCH TIME ON FACEBOOK - ACLU: "Justice Department documents released today by the ACLU reveal that federal law enforcement agencies are increasingly monitoring Americans' electronic communications, and doing so without warrants, sufficient oversight, or meaningful accountability. The documents, handed over by the government only after months of litigation, are the attorney general's 2010 and 2011 reports on the use of 'pen register' and 'trap and trace' surveillance powers. The reports show a dramatic increase in the use of these surveillance tools, which are used to gather information about telephone, email, and other Internet communications. The revelations underscore the importance of regulating and overseeing the government's surveillance power." Also, Field Agent McNally really thinks you should stop messaging your ex... it sends the wrong signals. [ACLU]</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348920795705</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 08:13:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348924071196-11</Id><Title>BLACK AND LATINO FIGHTING IN L.A., .........why can't we all just get along?</Title><Msg>I lament the sad state of affairs between Latino's and Black Americans. Why do they fight and distrust one another? Why is it that Hispanics so often attack and abuse black Americans? Do all blacks mistrust and view with suspicion all Latino's?? Why is it that all Latino's will not vote for Barack Obimbo because he is the first half black President of America? Does this deep divide extend to the bedrock of American civility? Will this distrust and animosity guarantee the defeat of Barack Obimbo? It sure seems likely. All of America rejoices at the near election of President Romney who can heal this great divide and bring jobs, prosperity, integrity, honesty, and old fashioned trust back to a land of broken dreams. Broken by Obimbo. Yes, America, black people, Latino people, Asian people and even white people can prosper with President Romney, they will not have to fight each other for the few low paying jobs left, after Barack Huessein Obimbo robbed America of all its jobs and raised horrid levels of taxes wit ObimboCare. Oh, America, lift up your eyes, and see the great man, Romney, riding into Washington to bring liberty and jobs....good jobs....not Burger King jobs.......back to this once great nation. Oh yeah!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348924071196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:07:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348924843328-12</Id><Topic><Title>BLACK AND LATINO FIGHTING IN L.A., .........why can't we all just get along?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348924071196</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But there are 10's of thousands temp jobs waiting to be filled for the holidays and elections... OBAMA !!! He gonna pay my bills !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348924843328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 09:20:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348927769682-13</Id><Title>Ann Romney worries Mitt will have a mental breakdown if elected!!</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON, Sept 28 (Reuters) - Ann Romney told a Nevada television station her biggest concern if her husband, Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney, becomes president was his "mental well-being." In an interview Thursday with television station KTVN, Mrs. Romney was asked what her biggest worry was should Mitt Romney be elected to serve in the White House. "I think my biggest concern obviously would just be for his mental well-being," she said. "I have all the confidence in the world in his ability, in his decisiveness, in his leadership skills, in his understanding of the economy. ... So for me I think it would just be the emotional part of it."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348927769682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348927874238-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama phones, Ipads, HDTV's , cars, food stamps, enough, never enough, redistribution</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348904162408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:36:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well come election day, we the people who pay for spreading it around will get retribution at the ballot box like in 2010. 41 million Tea Voters if they turn out Obama can go to his new Hawaii home and stay there.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348927874238</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348927939946-15</Id><Topic><Title>Tea Party Conservatives who voted in 2010 ready to ride to the rescue</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348875630637</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>badabing</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348927939946</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348927965251-16</Id><Topic><Title>Obama phones, Ipads, HDTV's , cars, food stamps, enough, never enough, redistribution</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348904162408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 03:36:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fact is Rhonda never worked a day in her life, she and Harv are part of the 47%, she has never paid a penny in taxes and now lives off of Harvs social security.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348927965251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:12:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348928010959-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ohio</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348878782771</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:33:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney in PA I guess its still in play</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348928010959</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:13:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348928049068-18</Id><Topic><Title>21 Ways Obama has Raised your taxes</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348876253050</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 19:50:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama never met a tax he didn't like</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348928049068</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:14:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348928260710-19</Id><Topic><Title>WAY TO GO RHONDA!! PILE IT ON!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348879625538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:47:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love Greece its a nice place to visit, great food and beautiful, but the people have become lazy socialists and now live at the mercy of the hard working German peoples charity. It is truly sad that their economy is in the toilet. Obama is running us into that toilet of socialism</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348928260710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:17:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348929406518-20</Id><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Msg>except for North Korea that has nuclear weapons and hasn't signed the NPT Israel already crossed own nuclear red line: Iran (AFP) – 24 minutes ago TEHRAN — Israel has already breached its own red line set by Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu by acquiring "dozens of nuclear warheads," Iranian Defence Minister Ahmad Vahidi said on Saturday. "If having the atomic bomb is passing the red line, the Zionist regime, that possesses dozens of nuclear warheads and weapons of mass destruction, has passed the red line years ago, and it has to be stopped," he said, according to the ISNA news agency. Vahidi was responding to a speech by Netanyahu to the UN General Assembly this week in which -- using a cartoon bomb diagramme -- the Israeli leader called for a "clear red line" to be applied to Iran's nuclear activities, which he charged are aimed at developing atomic weapons. "Is the occupying and aggressor Zionist regime that possesses nuclear weapons more dangerous? Or an Iran that doesn't have nuclear weapons and which insists more than anybody on nuclear disarmament, and seeks only to have peaceful nuclear energy abiding by international rules," Vahidi asked. Israel is the Middle East's sole, though undeclared, nuclear weapons state. Analysts estimate it has more than 200 nuclear warheads. It is a member of the International Atomic Energy Agency but has never signed the nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348929499422-21</Id><Topic><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh wait, I take that back, even North Korea has signed the NPT</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929499422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:38:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348929727446-22</Id><Topic><Title>“The reality is that (Republicans are) losing, they can’t accept it, and they’re going to find some reason to dismiss every poll that makes them unhappy no matter what its composition is,” Jensen added. “This isn’t really about Party ID, it’s about hardcore denial.”</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348880165994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:56:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not exactly, reprobate. Obama's popularity numbers now are just about where they were in 2010 when Democraps LOST in a landslide... Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1348929727446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:42:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348929828152-23</Id><Topic><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AND we all know how trustworthy NK is. Why is it you people care MORE about countries like North Korea and Iran than you do Israel. Last time I checked Israel wasn't standing in front of the UN threatening to wipe another country off the map. You people are MENTAL. You must be one of George Soro's little minions.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348929828152</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:43:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348930030049-24</Id><Title>Christian Science explains the defecit</Title><Msg>Where did the mammoth US budget deficits come from? Let's go back about a decade, when budget surpluses were predicted for the foreseeable future. Somehow, the math went terribly wrong, by trillions of dollars. Here's an accounting of what happened. By Peter Grier | Christian Science Monitor – 17 hrs agoEmailShare35PrintMore From India launches 101st space mission, and looks to Mars Polls favor Obama. A conspiracy by Democrats and the media? A rare apology in the Middle East. Cherish it Note to tweeting #Romney, #Obama campaigns and #journalists: Chill What’s the cause of the federal government’s huge budget deficits? That’s a question that is harder to answer in the particular than you might think. The general problem is obvious: Uncle Sam has been spending more money than he takes in. The specific reasons as to why this state of affairs exists are a mix of human decisions, economic circumstance, and the cumulative effect of time. Context is important here. So let’s start with 2001. That year, the Congressional Budget Office looked out over the decade to come and saw ahead nothing but blue skies and black ink. It predicted that between 2001 and 2011 the US would run budget surpluses totaling $5.6 trillion. That didn’t happen. Instead, the US racked up $6.1 trillion in deficits over that period. CBO’s prediction was a whopping $11.7 trillion off the mark. How did things go so wrong? CBO has gone back and studied that, as it happens. In a paper published earlier this year, the group’s economists tried to pull out and compare the reasons for the multitrillion swing. RECOMMENDED: Obama vs. Romney 101: 5 ways they differ on debt and deficits One big problem was that CBO isn’t magical. Unblessed with the ability to predict the future, it didn’t accurately foresee the economic troubles of coming years, including the crash of the Great Recession. This meant that less tax money came in than anticipated. Overall, CBO says that about $3.3 trillion of its $11.7 prediction error can be attributed to “economic and technical changes” to projected revenues. Then there were the tax cuts. President George W. Bush instigated most of these, but President Obama also pushed through Congress a payroll tax cut intended to pump money into a moribund economy. Tax cuts accounted for a further $2.8 trillion of the $11.7 trillion discrepancy. (Yes, the big kahuna here is Mr. Bush’s 2001 reduction in income-tax rates, which alone accounts for about $1.2 trillion in revenue foregone over the decade.) Finally, there are the increases in outflows unpredicted by CBO. Between 2001 and 2011, increased discretionary spending amounted to about $3 trillion. This category includes defense spending related to the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, homeland security upgrades in the US, spending on food stamps and other hard-times safety net programs, and other general budget categories that are supposed to be approved annually by Congress. Mandatory spending – a category that includes the Medicare prescription-drug program approved under Bush, the TARP bank bailout, and Mr. Obama’s economic stimulus package – went up by about $1.4 trillion during the period in question. (This type of outflow is called “mandatory” not because we had to do it, but because it results from formulas established by Congress instead of appropriated dollar totals.) Charles Blahous, a former economic official in the Bush White House who is currently a Hoover Institution research fellow, has rolled all these numbers together into a simple pie chart. His answer to the question “where did the $11.7 trillion go?” is this: 27 percent went away due to projection inaccuracy; 24 percent went to tax cuts; and 49 percent can be accounted for by various forms of increased spending. Yes, yes, but who’s to blame? It’s election season, after all, and accusations as to which party is responsible for most of this damage are as thick on the ground as October leaves after a windstorm. Asked why the debt has increased during his four years in office during a “60 Minutes” interview last week, Mr. Obama pointed a finger at his predecessor: “Over the last four years, the deficit has gone up, but 90 percent of that is as a consequence of two wars that weren’t paid for, as a consequence of tax cuts that weren’t paid for, a prescription-drug plan that was not paid for, and then the worst economic crisis since the Great Depression.” That answer is not accurate. Obama appeared to be talking about numbers that reflect the cumulative debt since 2001, not just his term. According to a White House-produced chart on the national debt, if you take the 10-year period of 2001 to 2011, Bush policies accounted for 55 percent of that figure. Obama-initiated policies such as the stimulus accounted for 11 percent, while the recession took care of the rest. (The White House chart puts the total debt at $12.7 trillion, not $11.7 trillion, as does the CBO. The White House uses different underlying economic assumptions.) But even that chart is something of an apples-to-mangoes comparison. Bush was president for eight years, and Obama for three. This is where the passage of time comes in – Bush’s tax cuts in particular had more time to accumulate and thus appear as a bigger part of the overall picture than the later-arriving Obama stimulus package. Washington Post fact checker Glenn Kessler has looked at this in depth, and made his attempt at adding up who is responsible for the $1.3 trillion 2011 deficit alone. His rough estimate is that economic factors accounted for about 46 percent of this single-year shortfall, while Obama policies accounted for 44 percent, and Bush-era policies for about 10 percent. Splitting up deficit causes by administration may be politically interesting. It’s possible, though, that it’s effectively pointless, in that it doesn’t lead to a better understanding of the choices that will confront US policymakers in years to come. A more useful way of looking at things could be to reslice deficit numbers into cyclical and structural figures. The cyclical deficit is caused by stuff that varies from year to year, like food stamp spending, which is driven by unemployment. The structural deficit is welded into the structure of the federal budget like steel beams. It reflects chronic problems that only worsen, such as the rising cost of health care. According to CBO, about $367 billion of the $1.3 trillion 2011 deficit was caused by cyclical stuff. Some $928 billion was structural. This is the part we really need to worry about, according to such budget watchdog groups as the Concord Coalition. The most important of these structural factors should come as no surprise. They are the aging of the baby boom population, which will drive up the number of people enrolled in Social Security and Medicare; and the continued increase in health-care costs, which makes Medicare, Medicaid, and other government health-care programs more expensive on a per-person basis. Population aging accounts for 64 percent of the cost growth of Social Security, Medicare, and Medicaid through 2035, according to a Concord Coalition analysis published earlier this year. Thirty-six percent is due to rising health-care costs. “Borrowing our way through this is not a viable option because the rising cost of Social Security, Medicare and Medicaid is not a temporary blip. It gets bigger with time. Incurring permanently rising debt would result in staggering interest costs and ultimately a total debt burden that would crush the economy,” concludes the Concord Coalition analysis.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348930030049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348930413809-25</Id><Title>Romney more unpopular then Bush, LOL</Title><Msg>A wave of recent polls has shown Romney struggling to keep up with President Barack Obama. A lower favorability rating than Bush, who was recently named the most unpopular living U.S. president, shows how difficult it has been for the GOP nominee to resonate with voters during his current presidential bid. Romney has avoided mentioning Bush's name while campaigning across the country, often referring to the former president only as Obama's "predecessor." Bush was also noticeably absent from the Republican National Convention in Tampa in August, but has stated his support of Romney.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348930413809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348930711783-26</Id><Topic><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of Soros, the board loons have been wailing and whining about Edelman dumping money into Romney's campaign, but not a word about Soros giving $ 2,000,000 to Obama yesterday.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348930711783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:58:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348932083631-27</Id><Title>Jim Webb proudly talks abot a Vietnam war hero</Title><Msg>Jim Webb Rewrites Mitt Romney's Idea of the 47 Percent Posted: 28 Sep 2012 07:00 PM PDT Lawrence O'Donnell skewered Mitt Romney for his time writing love letters in the sand to Ann on the beach in France during the Vietnam war, and for being one of the few people out there to actually protest in favor of that war, while simultaneously getting draft deferments. And he wrapped things up with Sen. Jim Webb who while introducing President Obama at a campaign event in Virginia, reminded Mitt Romney of just who that 47 percent he was talking about that fundraiser includes and what they're owed -- Webb to Romney: A ‘thanks’ would have been nice: Introducing President Obama in Virginia Beach, retiring Sen. Jim Webb (D-Va.), condemned Mitt Romney for failing to mention veterans or the military in his GOP convention speech. The omission was all the more damning, Webb suggested, because Romney is of an age where he might have served in Vietnam but did not. “If nothing else, at least mention some word of thanks and respect when a presidential candidate who is their generational peer makes a speech,” said Webb, a former Navy secretary and decorated Marine who served in Vietnam. Romney was exempted from the draft, first as a student and then as a missionary. “This was a time when every American male was eligible to be drafted. People made choices,” Webb said. “Those among us who stepped forward to face the harsh unknowns did so with the belief that their service would be honored.” Webb also tied in Romney’s much criticized remark that 47 percent of Americans believe they are “victims” who feel entitled to federal handouts, saying some of those benefits go to veterans. “Those young Marines that I led have grown older now. All gave some. Some gave all. That’s not a culture of dependency,” he said. ”They paid. Some with their lives, some with their wounds, disabilities. Some with emotional scars. Some with lost opportunities. Not only did they pay, they are owed. They are owed.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348932083631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348933006023-28</Id><Title>Bammy has has FOUR YEARS</Title><Msg>To start ALL of the #$%$ he's now campaigning on. WHERE WAS HE on all of this the past 4 years? It's all a Democrap SCAM just to get re-elected as a LAME DUCK. Think about it...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1348933006023</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:36:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348934142473-29</Id><Title>SWHC is looking GREAT!!!</Title><Msg>My power chair has a very nice storage compartment under the seat. Room for my weed and the low-glare stainless Blawkhawk. Never know about those executive orders after Nov.</Msg><Username>medical.mpp_4u</Username><Timestamp>1348934142473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:55:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348934413433-30</Id><Topic><Title>Jim Webb proudly talks abot a Vietnam war hero</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348932083631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:21:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a Vietnam vet I can tell you John Kerry was worse than any of those who used deferments to avoid Vietnam . He enlisted only after his deferments ran out. Once in country he used three phony scratches to qualify for the navy's policy of leaving a combat zone due to war injuries.Once home he used the war and lied about the true heroes just to get his political career started. You cant get any lower than Kerry. I've seen people on this board defend Kerry. You should be ashamed.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1348934413433</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:00:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348934556756-31</Id><Topic><Title>AS LONG AS IT IS WHITE...I WILL VOTE FOR A MARSH MELLOW FOR PRESIDENT...</Title><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348880505603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 21:01:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm all in but he must be a moderate Jew. One who recognizes limited idividual rights who will designates more census-designated areas across the fluted plane. Alos offers a tax deduction for power chairs in elementary schools.</Msg><Username>medical.mpp_4u</Username><Timestamp>1348934556756</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348935016423-32</Id><Title>The proper way to start a new life</Title><Msg>Neil Armstrong's Wife Glad To Finally Get Rid Of All The Space Hobby Crap September 26, 2012 CINCINNATI—Carol Held Knight told reporters on Wednesday that, though she was still mourning her husband Neil Armstrong’s death, it was frankly a relief to finally be able to clear out all the “space hobby crap” her late husband kept lying around the house. “I loved my husband very much, but, honestly, what am I supposed to do with a pile of useless rocks, a moon man figurine of some kind, and a stack of journals he wrote about space in?” said Knight, who recalled that Armstrong once “practically threw a fit” when she tried to get rid of his little plastic space shuttles. “I’m just going put it in a box and leave it on the curb. Some kids from the neighborhood might want it, you never know.” Knight confirmed she planned on giving the spacesuit Armstrong wore on the moon to a thrift store, noting that “it doesn’t fit [her].”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348935016423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348935021610-33</Id><Title>Scientist Who Saw Drowned Polar Bears Reprimanded</Title><Msg>Reprimanded? Hang the pecker-wood right beside Al Gore! Some one, some place, some time has to stop these silly lies! Hear that cut-and-paste Donna, Junior, Surf and Magoo?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348935021610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348935246871-34</Id><Topic><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAAAH excuse me DUMB DUMB, MOOOOSLIME love death remember ? and the MOOOOSLIMES are chanting DEATH TO AMERICA remember ??? If you not already, You can be our honorary message board ISLAMIC DEVIL okay ???</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348935246871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:14:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348935382413-35</Id><Topic><Title>The proper way to start a new life</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348935016423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:10:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are an idiot.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348935382413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348935974408-36</Id><Title>IS ANY ONE WORRIED PAKISTAN DOESN'T LIKE US ???</Title><Msg>I'm not. But those here on temp visa's should be, and should be given the boot to stop the protests or join them... Either way STOP THE HANDOUT TO THEM UNCLE SAM ! F'n ISLAMIC DEVILS !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348935974408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348936433028-37</Id><Topic><Title>IS ANY ONE WORRIED PAKISTAN DOESN'T LIKE US ???</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348935974408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama just sent another $450 million in aid to our "buddies" in Egypt .The White House released the news on Friday afternoon so most Americans wouldn't see it. The Arabs must consider us total wimps and fools. No matter what they do to us,Obama keeps kissing their fannies.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348936433028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:33:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348936966926-38</Id><Topic><Title>IS ANY ONE WORRIED PAKISTAN DOESN'T LIKE US ???</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348935974408</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:26:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe I saw on CABLE NEWS some Female Senator has it on hold. The AMBASSADOR to libia was dragged though the streets and RAPED !!! F'n ISLAMIC DEVILS AND Pedifile PIG MOHAMMED !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348936966926</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348937062093-39</Id><Topic><Title>Romney more unpopular then Bush, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348930413809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Syphilis is more popular than Junior .</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348937062093</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 12:44:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348938506765-40</Id><Title>IT'S A GREAT DAY AT THE TRAILER PARK...</Title><Msg>We are all doing meth, drinking beer and fondling my niece.</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348938506765</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 13:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348941878557-41</Id><Title>by by teabaggers and ur extremist redneck ways!!!!</Title><Msg>4 more years</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1348941878557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:04:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348942860730-42</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932569638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>capriceecw895</Username><Timestamp>1348942860730</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348944381826-43</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932569638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is what I am looking for.</Msg><Username>marhtazii482</Username><Timestamp>1348944381826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 14:46:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348945651066-44</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>vinaout959</Username><Timestamp>1348932569638</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 11:29:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>giselehsg77012</Username><Timestamp>1348945651066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 15:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348949279305-45</Id><Title>Other contents in my glove box</Title><Msg>My scooter has a 6 volt battery which is only accessible behind the hidden glovebox under the seat. Even though it was a free gift from the gobment if they ever aquire(not the board game) the contents they may take it back. Maybe they will return all the monthly payments from the last 39 years but seriously doubt it. But I got some blueberry monglow, honey fungus armillaria imported from Australlia, a 2016 DVD(from Chinatown), Goodys and a porcelain claw slide bowl in it. Oh and a map of Cullowhee, NC.</Msg><Username>medical.mpp_4u</Username><Timestamp>1348949279305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:07:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348949457835-46</Id><Title>I WENT ON A BLIND DATE TO SEE 2016</Title><Msg>And when this really smart girl told me that it was a bunch of crap, I took her behind the dumpster and legitimately raped her. No big deal though, she is not going to get pregnant.</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348949457835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:10:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348954021397-47</Id><Topic><Title>Israel is the only country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348929406518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 10:36:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(but not a word about Soros giving $ 2,000,000) --- That is because gfo99 aka cut-and-paste Donna aka Junior aka surf aka magoo aka dumb, tend to forget which lies they tell for moment to moment.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348954021397</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:27:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348955632027-48</Id><Title>Let's Pretend for a Moment that you just</Title><Msg>got word that a drugged up driver hit and killed your son, after viewing body for identification, you hear that the car used was a car from the police department. Being very upset, you go the prosecuting attorney and are given the run around and told the case has been sealed. Now you know how Brian Terry's family feels! Isn't life a #$%$?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348955632027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348956909390-49</Id><Topic><Title>I WENT ON A BLIND DATE TO SEE 2016</Title><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348949457835</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 16:10:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh isn't that cute the little baby needs some attention. Changing the g to a q doesn't change the fact that everyone thinks your an idiot. One has to wonder the intelligence of such a person. Keep em coming dude, just continues to show how pathetic and needy you kids are.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348956909390</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:15:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348957152598-50</Id><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Msg>4 dead Americans, one of which was an Ambassador and the administration LIED to the American people from day 1 to cover up their pathetic security. Did Obumbles get a good night sleep the night of the murder and did he enjoy Vegas the next day. O'Loser is out of touch.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348958646672-51</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>always wondered why Bush wouldn't testify under oath about what he knew about 9-11? Course we know he is a war criminal, he can't even leave the country, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958646672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:44:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348958951370-52</Id><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Msg>PALM BEACH, Fla. -- Investigations into whether a firm hired by the Republican Party of Florida to register voters handed in forged registration forms spread from Palm Beach County to at least six other counties in the state Friday. In one case, in Santa Rosa County, a form was filled out in the name of a dead person. While supervisors of elections were handing suspect forms to prosecutors around the state, the Florida GOP announced it would file an elections fraud complaint against the firm, Strategic Allied Consulting, a company started by Arizona-based consultant Nathan Sproul. The firm has been fired, not only by the Republican Party of Florida but also by the Republican National Committee, which hired it to register voters in crucial swing states, including Florida. The state GOP had been paying the firm $1.3 million to register voters and the RNC about $3 million. A spokesman for Florida's GOP said the matter was being treated very seriously. "We are doing what we can to find out how broad the scope is," said Brian Burgess, the spokesman. The Florida Democratic Party called on the state to "revoke" the ability of state Republicans to register voters while the investigation continues. Oct. 9 is the deadline to register to vote in the Nov. 6 presidential election. "It is clear that the Republican Party of Florida does not have the institutional controls in place to be trusted as a third-party, voter registration organization," said Scott Arceneaux, executive director of the Florida Democratic Party.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348959076479-53</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try and stay on topic TARD. O'Loser still in charge and running the country down the toilet.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348959076479</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348959320098-54</Id><Topic><Title>Let's Pretend for a Moment that you just</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348955632027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 17:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Captgail have I ever professed my gay love for you ? Well it is about time I do. I fluteman_greg love you and want you to move into my single wide with me. I need some Brokeback Mountain action. Love BigFlute.</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348959320098</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:55:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348959326998-55</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The difference between Republicans and Democrats, Reps fired the firm responsible, Democrats embrace FRAUD. Now you know.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348959326998</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:55:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348959701527-56</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hushhhhh dumbdumb and make monkey love to me. I am finally out, I have broken the chains of rectitude and I am ready for some rectum action. If you wear a Bush mask or Karl Rove mask I will let you mount me like an ally cat. Grrrrrrrrrrrr !</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348959701527</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:01:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348959923945-57</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just read that Valerie Jarrett has a full time Secret Service detail yet we cant protect our ambassador in Libya. What is this administration thinking????</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348959923945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348960311289-58</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody think Susan Rice decided on her own to start lying about Benghazi on the national newsi??? Somebody above her told her to do it. Wonder who that might be?LOL She should resign but it aint gonna happen.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348960311289</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:11:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348960327043-59</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flute imposter IGNORED. Typical vile hatred from the left when they LOSE. I won't be reading your garbage anymore. Over and out, CHILD.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960327043</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:12:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348960402816-60</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I was defrauded myself. I went to Haiti looking for some brokeback mountain action with a touch of dark meat, I found this very large nhegro and we went in the back of a building and when I put my hairy #$%$ up in the air we run away with my hundred dollars. Niggggahz are all the same around the world. Horrible I tell you</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348960402816</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348960438570-61</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The entire administration was repeating the same message. It came for Obama and his community organizing crew.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960438570</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:13:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348960556260-62</Id><Title>GDP revised DOWN to 1.25%</Title><Msg>Obumbles economy on the verge of ANOTHER recession. More hope and change, just in time.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960556260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348960825954-63</Id><Topic><Title>GDP revised DOWN to 1.25%</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960556260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:15:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Board loons defend this as slow but steady growth. At this rate UE should drop under 7.0 in early 2025. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348960825954</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:20:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348960826624-64</Id><Title>BenghaziGATE continues</Title><Msg>5 days before the attack the US State Department posted an Overseas Security Advisory memo saying there was NO credible threat of violence for the September 11th anniversary. That memo has been scrubbed from government websites. Impeachment NOW.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960826624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348961386757-65</Id><Topic><Title>BenghaziGATE continues</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960826624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obama is leading the country to believe he's defeated Al-Qaeda they cant be talking about terrorists attacks. Which is more important....American lives or Obama getting reelected??</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348961386757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:29:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348962979380-66</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you posted 'The difference between Republicans and Democrats, Reps fired the firm responsible, Democrats embrace FRAUD.The firm has been fired, " Guess reading comprehension isn't your strong suite skin flute player, guess it was just to hard for you to keep your attention level all the way to paragraph three, line one. "The firm has been fired, not only by the Republican Party of Florida but also by the Republican National Committee, which hired it to register voters in crucial swing states, including Florida." I think the fact the GOP baggers are unable to connect to reality, even unable to read to paragraph three is hurting them with the non retarded.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348962979380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348963518651-67</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>woopsie, my apologies you were right, they were fired, to much Italian Amarron at dinner</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348963518651</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:05:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348963803399-68</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From YOUR article. " The firm has been fired, not only by the Republican Party of Florida but also by the Republican National Committee, " Now when I read " HAS BEEN FIRED " My reading comprehension tells me EXACTLY what I posted. Apparently it is YOU who has the IQ of a GNAT. Thanks for confirming. Once AGAIN you confirm how ignorant you people from Media Matters are. DUMB DUMB....what a fitting ID for you.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348963803399</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:10:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348964021930-69</Id><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Msg>What does that say for Obama who for 3 1/2 YEARS can't get an UE number to get lower than Bush's WORST month. LMMFAO What does that say for THEIR Messiah....... I think it makes them look really STUPID.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348964136405-70</Id><Topic><Title>BenghaziGATE continues</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348960826624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 19:20:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrorism will always exist wankah it is just part of our world, just like our meth fuel crazy love. Remember when I split you like wood and you squealed like Ned Betty. Oh wonka come back to me !</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348964136405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:15:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348964159118-71</Id><Topic><Title>Finally a case of voter fraud</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348958951370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:49:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems to happen a lot with you. You should pay close attention to me, I am very intelligent. :)</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964159118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348964400599-72</Id><Topic><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I asked again you lib 't'urds what does it say when you can't fix 8 years of disaster in 3 years !!! Why can't you do it. Is it because the banks are broke and they won't lend any money, who needs money ! Just give it away like in the Bush years, create a bubble. A bubble is better than long term solutions. I want to live in the here and now, fk the country 10 years from now, I won't even be alive then.</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348964400599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:20:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348965103919-73</Id><Topic><Title>New study out of Princeton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348752185405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-27 09:23:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>at least that explains the ignorance shown in your posts</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1348965103919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:31:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348965155513-74</Id><Topic><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey flute you haven't looked at the polls, the far right considers Bush the worst president in history,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965155513</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348965275507-75</Id><Topic><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>most people understand, you don't blame the policeman that shows up to the car crash for the car crash, (unless of course you're a brain dead bagger)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965275507</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348965303090-76</Id><Topic><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont think anyone expected Obama to get everything just great by now....But 1.25% GDP after 3 1/2 years????. He has failed to deliver on the things HE promised to. Blaming Bush,hurricanes,ATM machines,whatever doesn't work anymore</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348965303090</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348965360740-77</Id><Title>Moderates understand</Title><Msg>Tombstone had more gun control then the U.S. today</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965360740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:36:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348965708976-78</Id><Topic><Title>Moderates understand</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965360740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a stupid post!! And you claim to be a Yale graduate???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348965708976</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:41:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348966102948-79</Id><Topic><Title>The far left considers Bush a terrible President</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348964021930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:13:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a DUMB analogy. Leaders don't blame other people, they take responsibility, fix the problem and move on. O'Loser hasn't met a microphone he wasn't affraid to tell whose fault it was. 3 1/2 YEARS of the most SLUGGISH recovery since the great depression. Obumbles has been his worst enemy.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348966102948</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:48:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348966947667-80</Id><Title>Obama's Pathetic UE record</Title><Msg>So I ask again, WHAT does that say for President Oblamo, whose BEST monthly UE number can't even match GW Bush's worst. The extreme far left claims Bush was bad, O'Loser must be the worst ever. Why don't you koolaid chuggers have an answer to this?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348966947667</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:02:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348967252273-81</Id><Topic><Title>Has impeachment hearings started on BenghaziGATE yet?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348957152598</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 18:19:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The administration purposely MISLED the American people from day 1. It is time to impeach the community organizer. NOW</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348967252273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:07:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348967460520-82</Id><Topic><Title>Moderates understand</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965360740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonka you are making me jealous. Stop talking to evil ivan. Come to me wonka, the trailer is warm and I have the kerosene cooker running like a fireplace. It is lovely !</Msg><Username>fluteman_qreg</Username><Timestamp>1348967460520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:11:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348967695721-83</Id><Topic><Title>Moderates understand</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965360740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Grow up,kid. You aint funny, just making a fool of yourself .I'm putting you on ignore to. Bye!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1348967695721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:14:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348969334454-84</Id><Topic><Title>Moderates understand</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348965360740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 20:36:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he went in the front door came out the back door</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1348969334454</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:42:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348970125534-85</Id><Title>Recession 100% certain when Durable Goods indicator goes this negative</Title><Msg>Economists often note that durable goods orders is one of the more volatile economic indicators that we get every month. However, there wasn't much sugar-coating anyone could do to the Thursday's report that showed durable goods orders plunged 13 percent in August. Economists were looking for a 5.0 percent decline. In his latest Breakfast with Dave note, David Rosenberg points to one sub-component of the durable goods report that sent a particularly scary signal. The three-month moving average of core capex orders (i.e. nondefense capital goods excluding aircraft) was -4.1 percent in August. "History shows when the trend weakened to the level we see today, the economy was in recession 100% of the time," wrote Rosenberg. "So stick that in you pipe and smoke it!" This is also bad news for jobs. According to Rosenberg's data, this measure has an 83 percent correlation with private employment. We need to kick Obama out of office. Obama says 4 years is not enough, heck, you should be able to graduate college in four years, seems like a lot of time to me.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348970125534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 21:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348970711192-86</Id><Topic><Title>WAY TO GO RHONDA!! PILE IT ON!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348879625538</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-28 20:47:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You know Hannity played the audio of that Ghetto leech who is voting for Obama because he gave her a cellphone. Then there is the tape of the perpetual college student now over 30 years old who doesn't know Walmart sells birth control pills for $11, yet wants the taxpayer to pay for her sex aids. Libs are so needy and stupid, the rest of us don't owe them contraceptives, electronic gadgets, let them pay for theirs own wants, if they were asking for food, and were sick, then charity would be our answer and churches will help them but government has become their Nanny in exchange for their votes, and that is self serving and corrupt.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348970711192</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-29 22:05:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>