<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-22"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353561628789-1</Id><Title>What was Romneys Agenda ?</Title><Msg>I forget,,oh he wanted all of us.....to move our moneys overseas</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1353561628789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 00:20:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353561751153-2</Id><Title>Obamas Birth Cert...found between Anns Romneys Legs</Title><Msg>Those nasty Republicans can never find a Birth Certificate</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1353561751153</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 00:22:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353561854877-3</Id><Topic><Title>Too much, the Republicans have sent the Kenyan a letter telling the #$%$ that he</Title><Username>ivanhoeofoloxly</Username><Timestamp>1353447640494</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-20 16:40:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Whitey always Crying,,,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1353561854877</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 00:24:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353561970669-4</Id><Title>Republicans Moving to Gingrichs Moon Colony</Title><Msg>Thank god they are leaving</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1353561970669</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 00:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353583757048-5</Id><Title>DON'T FORGET TO WATCH ALL THOSE WHITE PEOPLE FEEDING ALL THOSE BLACK PEOPLE</Title><Msg>TODAY, Don't you just hate all those GOOD LOOKING White people always feeding those BLACK people ??? I wish they would all go back to Europe and leave along with OUR MUD country !!! Besides this being a MOOOOOSLIME nation it's MUD person's religion !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353583757048</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 06:29:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353584255341-6</Id><Topic><Title>Unions cutting their own throats</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1353547201903</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-21 20:20:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the UNIONS can only organize the 25-50 million illegals and their SPAWN. What UNITY that would be...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353584255341</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 06:37:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353586553298-7</Id><Title>Giving Thanks 2012</Title><Msg>This year I want to take a moment to express my deep gratitude for the American voter. Despite our on-again, off-again relationship over the past 3 decades, and some very harsh words on my part, you really came through in 2012, Kiddos. BFF, Ok?!?! (At least until 2014...) I also want to thank Anonymous (you know who you are) for preventing.Karl Rove and our own beloved domestic oligarchs from subverting American democracy ,,, AGAIN! And since fair is fair, I must also thank Karl Rove himself for diverting and then squandering and dissipating several hundred million dollars of our own American oligarchs' money (with no discernible effect on the 2012 race whatsoever), all while skimming a cool $50 or $60 million off the top and stashing it deep within the rancid, sweaty, moldy folds of his porcine carcas, to fund his own retirement. (It may be coming sooner than you thought, Karl...) Finally, I want to thank Anonymous once again - this time in advance - for the upcoming evidence dump decisively tying Karl Rove and his inner circle to election fraud/treason on a massive scale in 2012 (and indirectly to the same sorts of slimy criminal conspiracies in 2000 and 2004, and to the subsequent impeccably-timed Mike Connell "accident"), thus preventing him from ever enjoying his aforementioned $50-60 million skim. PROVIDENCE WILLING.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1353586553298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 07:15:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353586727892-8</Id><Topic><Title>Hostess laying off 18,500 workers</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1353071396777</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-16 08:09:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Far better to die on one"s feet than to live on one"s knees.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1353586727892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 07:18:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353591234427-9</Id><Title>We have much to be thankful for</Title><Msg>Common sense prevailed and you can rest assured that there will never be a President Bachmann, Perry, Santorum or Romneyor Ryan, or Gingrich or Christie or 9999, or a Rubio! Yes, you have much to be thankful this holiday season.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353591234427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 08:33:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>9</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353593234864-10</Id><Topic><Title>We have much to be thankful for</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353591234427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 08:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Common sense prevailed and you can rest assured) Are you taking with Ambassador J. Christopher Stevens or Border Agent Brian Terry?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353593234864</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:07:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353593770757-11</Id><Title>Happy Thanksgiving... Obama Diktatorship 1445 Days Remain...</Title><Msg>...and counting.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353593770757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353593770764-12</Id><Title>Happy Thanksgiving... Obama Diktatorship 1445 Days Remain...</Title><Msg>...and counting.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353593770764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:16:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353596369332-13</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Thanksgiving... Obama Diktatorship 1445 Days Remain...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353593770757</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and then you can look forward to Hilary for 2,912 days</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353596369332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:59:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353598601107-14</Id><Topic><Title>We have much to be thankful for</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353591234427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 08:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Now Capn, I blame these low gasoline prices on Drill Here, Drill Now, Capain America not approving the Keystone pipeline and the fact that the U.S. will be the largest producer of oil and gas in the world come 2020, when Hilary is president, nice gift, no? We'll finally be rid of the oil cartel and our gasoline prices will ALWAYS be .01 cheaper than the world prices! AHAHAHAHAH AAAHAh</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353598601107</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:36:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353599391302-15</Id><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Msg>Thankful that although the Libertarian Party did not win, at least I don't live in a country where abortions must be performed in back alleys, and the President is deciding WHICH First Lady he should bring to WH ceremonies before they all get shipped to Planet Kolob.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353600483741-16</Id><Topic><Title>Giving Thanks 2012</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1353586553298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 07:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You liberals wont the election.You should be happy.Yet you are still consumed with vitriol and hate. My candidate lost and I have already moved on. So who really won and lost ?? You or me??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1353600483741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:08:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353600672087-17</Id><Title>THANKING LEVEL HEADED AMERICANS FOR PUTTING GOP IN CHARGE OF THE HOUSE</Title><Msg>as the cleverest way known, given the proliferation of Blue Parasites to keep America from disappearing under the burden of debt created by Democrats and the drooling Obimbo, stooge of thugs, and perhaps Choomer in Chief of Thugs. Who knows, but once again, ordinary Americans, sick of Democratic debauchery, lies and waste, you showed your insight and wisdom in keeeping the GOP in charge of important matters...WELL DONE AMERICANS....at least half of you are NOT #$%$. The other half are indeed dimwitted and drooling but we can take of that in two more years</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1353600672087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:11:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353601038644-18</Id><Topic><Title>THANKING LEVEL HEADED AMERICANS FOR PUTTING GOP IN CHARGE OF THE HOUSE</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1353600672087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:11:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do know that if they don't capitulate with Captain America by 31 Dec, they will lose control in 2014, ya, I thought you did!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353601038644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353601223741-19</Id><Title>Fiscal Cliff?</Title><Msg>Robert Reich: GOP Loses if U.S. Goes Over Fiscal Cliff Posted: 21 Nov 2012 07:00 PM PST “Viewpoint” host Eliot Spitzer and Robert Reich, professor at the University of California, Berkeley, discuss the latest fiscal cliff negotiations in Washington. Robert Reich believes Democrats have the power in the budget battle, because the Bush tax cuts for the rich — which Republicans want to extend and Democrats oppose — will expire no matter what anyone agrees on come January. “The question is, will the Democrats actually hold firm?” Reich asks. Reich also addresses whether limiting tax deductions instad of raising marginal tax rates on the rich could generate the $1.6 trillion in new tax revenues that Obama has set as a goal: “Just by limiting deductions for the wealthy you can’t get anywhere near the $1.6 trillion. … Now if you made the tax on capital gains equal to the tax on ordinary income, maybe that preference would get you closer. But nobody is talking about doing that, unfortunately.” Reich said that Republicans would be the losers if Congress failed to negotiate a deal to avert the so-called fiscal cliff. “I think we are moving in the right direction and we are moving in the right direction because the Democrats are holding most of the trump cards,” he said. “If nothing is done, remember, we go back to the Clinton tax rates of the 1990s, which were not all that bad, in fact the economy did quite well under those tax rates. If nothing is done, basically the Republicans lose.” “And, if the Republicans try to make a case that they are not going to vote for an extension of middle class tax cuts unless the rich also get a tax cut that puts the Republicans in the position of showing America that they are going to hold the middle hostage and they sure are shills for the very rich -- something that a lot of people suspect anyway, but that kind of demonstration is not going to be good for the GOP,” Reich added. Across-the-board spending cuts are set to go into effect at the beginning of 2013 if Congress fails to pass a budget that reduces the federal deficit. The Bush tax cuts are also set to expire. Democrats have said they won’t accept any fiscal cliff deal that doesn’t let the tax cuts for the wealthiest Americans to expire, however they want to leave tax rates for middle and lower-income Americans unchanged. Republicans have said they will oppose any increase in tax rates, but are open to reducing tax write-offs to increase revenue. “Just by limiting deductions for the wealthy you can’t get anywhere near the $1.6 trillion,” Reich noted. Robert Reich has served in three national administrations, most recently as secretary of labor under President Bill Clinton. He also served on President-Elect Obama's transition advisory board. He has written twelve books, including The Work of Nations, which has been translated into 22 languages; the best-sellers The Future of Success and Locked in the Cabinet; and his most recent book, Supercapitalism. Mr. Reich is co-founding editor of The American Prospect magazine. His commentaries can be heard weekly on public radio's "Marketplace." In 2003, Reich was awarded the prestigious Vaclav Havel Vision Foundation Prize, by the former Czech president, for his pioneering work in economic and social thought. In 2008, Time Magazine named him one of the ten most successful cabinet secretaries of the century. He received his B.A. from Dartmouth College, his M.A. from Oxford University where he was a Rhodes Scholar, and his J.D. from Yale Law School.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353601223741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:20:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353601969720-20</Id><Topic><Title>THANKING LEVEL HEADED AMERICANS FOR PUTTING GOP IN CHARGE OF THE HOUSE</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1353600672087</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:11:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So, you agree that Odiktator means it when he says, 'it's my way or the highway...' In other words he's the only one that's right in his mind and everyone, even all the Dems who rejected EVERY budget he proposed over the last 4 years? You agree with that narcissistic, tyrannical viewpoint? You sir are nothing but an Obama sycophant and sadly there are many more like you that have been cut from the same rag cloth ...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353601969720</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:32:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353602155385-21</Id><Topic><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a coincidence,Surf. I just happen to be in Barcelona today just like you.LOL Sitting here now with my laptop drinking a cup of expresso. Is that you over there in the corner with your laptop ?? Notice you and that big hairy Spaniard have really been smooching it up. Maybe you guys should get a room.Other customers here are frowning at you two.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1353602155385</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:35:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353604427342-22</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff?</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353601223741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:20:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reich is exactly correct. If the Republican House doesn't compromise, they will be perceived to be a bunch of elitist obstructionist losers, like the Democrat House before them, and the current Democrat Senate.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353604427342</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:13:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353604609644-23</Id><Topic><Title>We have much to be thankful for</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353591234427</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 08:33:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is high and magnificent; the whole earth rejoices to see it! Washington DC is the city of the great King! All his subjects live in 3 story houses solar swimming pools, only the finest of meals 24/7 new cars in sit in each driveway -- unlimited cocaine and everyone wearing diamonds as big as horse turds. No one has to pay for anything, the rich will. What a world Obama has giving the cool aid drinkers to look forward to. Just a bump in the road about Stevens and Terry. Obama he is our man, yes he can, yes he can!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1353604609644</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:16:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353606530898-24</Id><Title>Why Capital Gains Rate will change, and how much should it be adjusted</Title><Msg>Capital Gains is how wealth is created, and as any CSCO owner knows, how it is destroyed. By increasing the tax on Capital gains, you also subsidize the risk of the losers who so often frequent this stock board. Capital gains tax rates should by no more than 2 percent per year. Capital gains directly affects the risk/reward of all investors, and impacts the markets as much as any easing the FED could possibly create. Please discuss this alternative. It will affect the middle class, but mostly it will affect the winners and the losers in a positive way. Capital losses are possible, even with CSCO. Wouldn't you buy more CSCO if the governent agreed to subsidize your losses by two percent more? Capital creation should be taxed. When new stock is issued by a company, it often creates capital from nothing, creating a huge tax loophole. The possibilty of loss in an IPO was also subsidized. The entire risk/reward calculation is altered by a capital gains tax increase.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353606530898</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:48:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353608553106-25</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Analyst Report Revealed</Title><Username>aliceking267</Username><Timestamp>1353345615099</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-19 12:20:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent</Msg><Username>ralphanderson780</Username><Timestamp>1353608553106</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:22:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353608973123-26</Id><Topic><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hee, hee. Carey if you are really there let me know. I can recommend a couple of tapas restaurants that are very fun. However they are on the Raval district, it has a bunch of pakies and morrocans hanging around in the corners, it looks menacing but it really isn't. Just put your wallet in your front pocket.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353608973123</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:29:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353609081563-27</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Thanksgiving... Obama Diktatorship 1445 Days Remain...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353593770764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 09:16:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that what they call delivering an electoral college trouncing and winning the popular vote, back in FaackWater Kansas ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353609081563</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:31:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353609789942-28</Id><Topic><Title>I ADMIRE AND RESPECT PETREUS...STILL...brilliant, driven and capable man</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352830248255</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-13 13:10:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad indeed. This crap of having people resign over their personal life issues is ridiculous, particularly since she was a grown woman. I suppose there is a possibility of blackmailing, and that is why when you apply for a secret clearance you are asked if you did drugs or take it in the butt like flute_man, they don't care if you do they just want it out so they know you can't be blackmailed.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353609789942</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:43:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353610185333-29</Id><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Msg>The CIA asked the WH not to call Bengahzi a terrorist attack because they were tracking terrorist communications, and the repukes pounced on Obama because they knew he would not compromise intelligence, would not revealed this, and be defenseless to republican attacks. Now how much of a #$%$ can you be !!! Thank God the electorate told the repukes to go FAAACK themselves. FOUR MORE YEARS. Suuckit to me !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353610697730-30</Id><Topic><Title>THE MOST DESPICABLE THING REPUKES DID THIS PAST ELECTION...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353610185333</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:49:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So asking for clarification is despicable? It really depends on how you perceive a question. For instance: Are you stoned or stupid?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353610697730</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 13:58:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353611838981-31</Id><Topic><Title>POWELL: SORRY! MY BAD! NO WMD!</Title><Username>biqflyfisher</Username><Timestamp>1075247469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2004-01-27 18:51:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the final moments of the seige of Bagdad, Saddam ordered his troops to gas ours. Evidently, the weapons existed, but even the Iraqis couldn't find them.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353611838981</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 14:17:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353612695459-32</Id><Topic><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gave yourself away again, Magoo. If you were really in Spain you would have said " if you really are here" not " if are you really there ". You just aint too bright.LOLOLOLOLOOLOLOLOOOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1353612695459</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 14:31:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353613242355-33</Id><Topic><Title>POWELL: SORRY! MY BAD! NO WMD!</Title><Username>biqflyfisher</Username><Timestamp>1075247469000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2004-01-27 18:51:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And then there was that "fun and games" with the weapons inspectors. Do you suppose Saddam had the balls to play cat and mouse with fake weapons? Facing the most powerful nations in the world with a bluff? Yeah, he was that crazy, but seriously do you think he was hiding phosphorus in the tunnels of fallujah, or the US used chemical weapons to burn the flesh off of the Iraqis? Check the bodies. Phosphorus burns over 90% on some of them.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353613242355</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 14:40:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353615242002-34</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff?</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353601223741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:20:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rob Rogers cartoon in today's Pittsburgh Post-Gazette Large turkey ID'd as "GOP 2012" : "Pardon me." "I didn't mean all those nasty things I said about deviant gays, uppity blacks, slutty women, dirty illegals, and lazy moochers!"</Msg><Username>murrymom</Username><Timestamp>1353615242002</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 15:14:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353615714159-35</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO take a clutch of all to go onward on - rudely active takings</Title><Username>marjorie.carrillo45</Username><Timestamp>1353606548797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 12:49:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>really good post</Msg><Username>richard.burnett64</Username><Timestamp>1353615714159</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 15:21:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353615858009-36</Id><Topic><Title>Fiscal Cliff?</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1353601223741</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 11:20:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It never ceases to amaze me how the left can elevate the dialogue with such intelligent remarks. None of those nasty things were said. You assume them when we argue against freebies. I believe we did mention your tendency to feel like you are always the victim of a vast white wing conspiwacy.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1353615858009</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 15:24:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353618678414-37</Id><Topic><Title>Giving Thanks 2012</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1353586553298</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 07:15:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let me clear this up for ya: WE won. YOU lost. My continued revelry and gloating does nothing to change this fact. Your rapid completion of the denial/ anger/ bargaining/ acceptance process doesn't change it either. Got it?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1353618678414</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 16:11:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353619709892-38</Id><Title>HAPPY THANKSGIVING ILLEGALS, GIVE THANKS FOR ALL THE OBAMA STUFF... AND as for S.I.</Title><Msg>Staten Island !? Go to HELLo operator... Your all racists and many are republicans. OBAMA ! he gonna pay JOSE and JOSANNA bills !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353619709892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 16:28:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353619877132-39</Id><Topic><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why be back in the USA when you could do better and be in MexiHole ?!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353619877132</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 16:31:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353619900892-40</Id><Topic><Title>BACK IN THE USA, HAPPY THANKSGIVING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1353599391302</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 10:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ops, I forgot, NO FREE STUFF !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1353619900892</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 16:31:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353626854200-41</Id><Title>Truce broken by Pallies already, 12 rockets hit Israel</Title><Msg>Twelve rockets fired from the Gaza Strip hit Israel on Wednesday in the first hours that followed a ceasefire agreement ending hostilities in the week-long Gaza conflict, a police spokesman told AFP. The Israeli spokesman added that the attacks caused no injuries or damage, with the rockets mostly landing in open fields in the south of the Jewish state. A ceasefire agreement announced in Cairo on Wednesday went into effect at 1900 GMT, requiring both sides to halt fire immediately and for Israel to start opening Gaza's crossings if the truce holds for 24 hours. The Israeli defence forces said a total of 915 rockets had hit Israel since the start of the conflict on November 14, most of the them landing in southern Israel And Obama gave these creeps money to get this truce deal. Obama gave money to Hamas and Egypts Muslim Brotherhood PM. Sorry, I don't like paying terrorists, Their word is worthless. Hillary is really vapid, putting this deal together.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353626854200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 18:27:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353629705673-42</Id><Topic><Title>Truce broken by Pallies already, 12 rockets hit Israel</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353626854200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 18:27:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrorists don't honor a cease fire. Apparently, Obama and Hillary didn't get the memo ...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1353629705673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 19:15:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1353630324193-43</Id><Topic><Title>Truce broken by Pallies already, 12 rockets hit Israel</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353626854200</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 18:27:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Spot on, Bush didn't bargain with terrorists, Carter tried and got led around by the nose. The holy Islamic teachings say to mislead the infidel is good. Amateurs never learn.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353630324193</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 19:25:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353635420105-44</Id><Title>FM Liberman: Israel will eventually need to overthrow Hamas</Title><Msg>FM tells Channel 2 that launching IDF ground operation to occupy Gaza and overthrow Hamas regime would take 4 months; says launching such an operation would have been the wrong move just two months before elections. Foreign Minister Avigdor Liberman said Thursday that despite the government's decision to agree to a cease-fire on Wednesday, Israel would "eventually need to overthrow the Hamas regime" in Gaza. Liberman said in an interview with Channel 2 that a ground operation in Gaza would entail reoccupying the Gaza Strip, and partaking in such an effort only two months before elections was the wrong move. "The occupation of Gaza and the overthrow of Hamas is a process that would take more than four months." Liberman stated that the government decided to agree to the cease-fire despite the fact that they knew "the public was against it." The foreign minster said that the cease-fire was the best agreement Israel could have made at this time. He said that Israel had met its three goals for the mission: stopping rocket fire on the South, regaining Israel's power of deterrence and destroying Hamas's stock of long-range Fajr 5 missiles. Defense Minister Ehud Barak on Thursday rejected the notion that Israeli public opinion against a cease-fire agreement with Hamas should have any bearing on the Israeli leadership's decision-making process. "We don't have to listen to the public on these issues - the leadership must make the decisions," Barak said in an interview with Channel 2 when asked about the perceived unpopularity of the cease-fire among the public. Barak expressed confidence that the cease-fire with Gaza factions would be "relatively long," adding that "Hamas did not truly achieve anything - Israel has control of all the understandings with them." He rejected the idea that the conflict ended in a victory for Hamas, stating that Gazans were celebrating imaginary feats that did not actually occur, such as the alleged shooting down of an Israeli F-16 and rockets falling in Tel Aviv and causing damage.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1353635420105</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 20:50:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353636158147-45</Id><Title>Israel loves Obama</Title><Msg>after saving Israel, funding the iron dome and then forcing the pallies to stop shooting rockets he has cemented the jewish vote for the DNC forever, there is talk about parades in Jeruselum honoring Obama, one has to start to wonder if Rhonda is really jewish, her opinions and policies are at such odds with the rest of the jewish world, could be she is taliban trying to act like a double agent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353636158147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 21:02:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1353643068451-46</Id><Title>Rhonda</Title><Msg>meanwhile in the real world Hamas cries victory; truce with Israel holds your worst nightmare cause you're stupid</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1353643068451</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-22 22:57:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>