<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-10-07"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349582946934-1</Id><Topic><Title>From Canada : Obama: Beware the Silent Majority- a Great Article</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349573134637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbuummpp</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349582946934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349585412896-2</Id><Title>Over 2,000 dead in Afganistan, media gives Obama a pass</Title><Msg>We were supposed to be out of there Obama broke his promise. All I know is every death in Iraq was endlessly hurled at Bush as his fault. Obama is the Media Teflon empty suit.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349585412896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349585817217-3</Id><Title>Media helping Obama cover up his Libyan Embassy scandal</Title><Msg>That is right it was a planned attack, not a result of a video. You don't bring Mortars and RPG's to a protest about a movie. The embassy was the subject of other attacks and threats. You Obama supporters, don't care about the Americans who died, you don't care about the truth. The truth is that one of the people Obama released from Gitmo planned this attack, so the blood and fault for the attack is on Obama's hands. The embassy requested more security, requested a plane standing by to evacuate the embassy and Obama's administration turned them down. Wait Until Romney states these facts at a debate. Just wait.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349585817217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:56:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349588889782-4</Id><Topic><Title>From Canada : Obama: Beware the Silent Majority- a Great Article</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349573134637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mmmuuummmuuuup</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349588889782</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 01:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349590268903-5</Id><Topic><Title>From Canada : Obama: Beware the Silent Majority- a Great Article</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349573134637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>To the TOP!</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1349590268903</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 02:11:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349590534385-6</Id><Topic><Title>Media helping Obama cover up his Libyan Embassy scandal</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349585817217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if we are not going to discover that Obama was complicit in the attacks: he knew they were coming. He was planing his UN speech about needing an new international law to stop defaming of the Prophet &amp; Islam. So he allowed the attacks to happen. Allowed him to complain about the USA's First Amendment too (or to subvert it with a new international law.)</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1349590534385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 02:15:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349590622044-7</Id><Topic><Title>Over 2,000 dead in Afganistan, media gives Obama a pass</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349585412896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:50:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If we still had a Republican President the press would be listing the names of each soldier killed, on a daily basis.</Msg><Username>travisthechimp.alsharpton</Username><Timestamp>1349590622044</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 02:17:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349605955213-8</Id><Topic><Title>Romney treated Obama like a busboy or a bellboy at the debate</Title><Username>gliderpilot7777</Username><Timestamp>1349567577863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 19:52:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(If Mitt gets elected it will be fun to watch people treat him like a leeper.) People will be to busy working!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1349605955213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 06:32:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349607719979-9</Id><Title>Any idea which way CSCO will trade next week?</Title><Msg>I was watching some trade videos on TheContrarianTrader blog and found some great videos. His analysis was really good and be being new I got a lot out of them. I watched his older videos and his calls were accurate as well. I know there are a bunch of guys that pick stocks and send alerts but the contrarian trader puts himself out there to prove himself unlike other so called pros. Does anyone know of his paid services?</Msg><Username>jermain.mcbride</Username><Timestamp>1349607719979</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 07:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349611914207-10</Id><Title>I HEARD ALL WEEKEND ON CABLE NEWS HOW ILLEGALS COULD CONTRIBUTE</Title><Msg>To TAX REVENUES if they could only be made legal... Think about it ??? Isn't NOT PAYING TAXES a big argument for getting them OUT and NOT having them live here ??? And besides why become legal when the US govt will give them JOBS, ID's, drivers licenses, credit cards, free medical, housing, food, education, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, MO SOCIAL SERVICES, Libs will do anything for votes, all an illegal has to do is change IDs and let STUPID gringos pay for everything including the the defaulted, house, car, credit loans...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349611914207</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349613594148-11</Id><Topic><Title>Is CSCO Poised For A Huge Win?</Title><Username>thadmendoza170</Username><Timestamp>1349523928197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great , i just subscribed!</Msg><Username>colongill436</Username><Timestamp>1349613594148</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 08:39:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616450239-12</Id><Topic><Title>Rumor has said that Obama raised tons of Arab money by not meeting BiBi</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349554427907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 16:13:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>good image</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616450239</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616504231-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney winning in Illinois</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349563051045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 18:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This morning Romney ahead in Ohio too</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616504231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616574267-14</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch explains why the UE numbers are #$%$</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349541807938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jack Welch doubled down on his observation that the report is made up Sunday</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616574267</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616602799-15</Id><Topic><Title>Reality/ check, the biased lib media NOW and when GOP was in office</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349572272522</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:11:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BBBUUUMMMPPP</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616602799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616701130-16</Id><Topic><Title>Media helping Obama cover up his Libyan Embassy scandal</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349585817217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 00:56:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't wait for the next Romney debate, I don't have to Ryan gets to humiliate Biden</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616701130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:31:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349616939729-17</Id><Topic><Title>23 million still without jobs, that is the TRUE Obama jobs report card</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349538903333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 11:55:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>june, there is no way around it this is the FooD Stamp President, the UE President. 23 million Americans out of work, Come Jan 20 it will be 23 million and one when Obama is out of work too.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349616939729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:35:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349617067709-18</Id><Topic><Title>how Canadians look at Amerca</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349546553131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:02:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Canadians have a higher opinion of Americans than our left wing media, and Our Sorry President who keeps apologizing for the greatest nation on earth</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349617067709</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:37:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349617138824-19</Id><Topic><Title>Todays Polls show Romney Surge</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349541305337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:35:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is leading in Electoral votes too.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349617138824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618083370-20</Id><Title>Mandel tied up Ohio Race</Title><Msg>Sunday, October 07, 2012 The U.S. Senate race in Ohio is now a tie. The latest Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Ohio Voters finds incumbent Democrat Sherrod Brown and his Republican challenger Josh Mandel each earning 46% support. Two percent (2%) like another candidate, and six percent (6%) are undecided. (To see survey question wording, click here.) Ohio now shifts back from Safe Democrat to a Toss-up in the Rasmussen Reports Senate Balance of Power rankings.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618083370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 09:54:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618430757-21</Id><Title>New campaign lawn sign an empty wooden chair on the lawn</Title><Msg>Used in Romney debate preparations. Obama wasn't there</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618430757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618612599-22</Id><Title>After 800 million dollars in nasty Obama adds, his likability is a sick joke</Title><Msg>Even Moochelle is more likable, and Oprah is interviewing the Romney's so that shows how much Oprah likes the Mooch.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618612599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349618870652-23</Id><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Msg>Updated election forecasting model still points to Romney win, University of Colorado study says October 4, 2012 • Social Sciences An update to an election forecasting model announced by two University of Colorado professors in August continues to project that Mitt Romney will win the 2012 presidential election. According to their updated analysis, Romney is projected to receive 330 of the total 538 Electoral College votes. President Barack Obama is expected to receive 208 votes -- down five votes from their initial prediction -- and short of the 270 needed to win. The new forecast by political science professors Kenneth Bickers of CU-Boulder and Michael Berry of CU Denver is based on more recent economic data than their original Aug. 22 prediction. The model itself did not change. “We continue to show that the economic conditions favor Romney even though many polls show the president in the lead,” Bickers said. “Other published models point to the same result, but they looked at the national popular vote, while we stress state-level economic data.” While many election forecast models are based on the popular vote, the model developed by Bickers and Berry is based on the Electoral College and is the only one of its type to include more than one state-level measure of economic conditions. They included economic data from all 50 states and the District of Columbia. Their original prediction model was one of 13 published in August in PS: Political Science &amp; Politics, a peer-reviewed journal of the American Political Science Association. The journal has published collections of presidential election models every four years since 1996, but this year the models showed the widest split in outcomes, Berry said. Five predicted an Obama win, five forecast a Romney win, and three rated the 2012 race as a toss-up. The Bickers and Berry model includes both state and national unemployment figures as well as changes in real per capita income, among other factors. The new analysis includes unemployment rates from August rather than May, and changes in per capita income from the end of June rather than March. It is the last update they will release before the election. Of the 13 battleground states identified in the model, the only one to change in the update was New Mexico -- now seen as a narrow victory for Romney. The model foresees Romney carrying New Mexico, North Carolina, Virginia, Iowa, New Hampshire, Colorado, Wisconsin, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, Ohio and Florida. Obama is predicted to win Michigan and Nevada. In Colorado, which Obama won in 2008, the model predicts that Romney will receive 53.3 percent of the vote to Obama’s 46.7 percent, with only the two major parties considered. While national polls continue to show the president in the lead, “the president seems to be reaching a ceiling at or below 50 percent in many of these states,” Bickers said. “Polls typically tighten up in October as people start paying attention and there are fewer undecided voters.” The state-by-state economic data used in their model have been available since 1980. When these data were applied retroactively to each election year, the model correctly classifies all presidential election winners, including the two years when independent candidates ran strongly: 1980 and 1992. It also correctly estimates the outcome in 2000, when Al Gore won the popular vote but George W. Bush won the election through the Electoral College. In addition to state and national unemployment rates, the authors analyzed changes in personal income from the time of the prior presidential election. Research shows that these two factors affect the major parties differently: Voters hold Democrats more responsible for unemployment rates, while Republicans are held more responsible for fluctuations in personal income. Accordingly -- and depending largely on which party is in the White House at the time -- each factor can either help or hurt the major parties disproportionately. In an examination of other factors, the authors found that none of the following had a statistically significant effect on whether a state ultimately went for a particular candidate: The location of a party’s national convention, the home state of the vice president or the partisanship of state governors. The authors also provided caveats. Their model had an average error rate of five states and 28 Electoral College votes. Factors they said may affect their prediction include the timeframe of the economic data used in the study and that states very close to a 50-50 split may fall in an unexpected direction due to factors not included in the model. “As scholars and pundits well know, each election has unique elements that could lead one or more states to behave in ways in a particular election that the model is unable to correctly predict,” they wrote.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349618951921-24</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Nevada is still a tossup</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618951921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349619937300-25</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as long as were going crazy I'm saying CA is going to Romney</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349619937300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349620150470-26</Id><Topic><Title>how Canadians look at Amerca</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349546553131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:02:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>truth is Canadians think the GOP are a bunch of crazies, they are liberal in Canada, you know the Canada with Universal Healthcare, a social safety net, income equality, you know Canada a country the baggers like to call a socialist state.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349620150470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349620501179-27</Id><Title>THE OBAMA MIRACLE</Title><Msg>In spite of the collapse of europe and the slowdown of china the united states stock market has doubled.</Msg><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1349620501179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:35:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349620683158-28</Id><Topic><Title>THE OBAMA MIRACLE</Title><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1349620501179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, the fat cats are doing great. Its the little guy suffering under Obama.Thanks for posting about it.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349620683158</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349621082487-29</Id><Topic><Title>how Canadians look at Amerca</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1349546553131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 14:02:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow!!!Canada sounds great!!! Why dont you take all your millions and move there?????</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349621082487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:44:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349623222629-30</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dear Dumb, I like your name its so descriptive of you but not the Real Ivan, who is as sharp as Romney</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349623222629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:20:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349623299687-31</Id><Topic><Title>From Canada : Obama: Beware the Silent Majority- a Great Article</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349573134637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 21:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>send this article to all your friends</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349623299687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:21:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349623733684-32</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ThGravis Marketing conducted a presidential poll in the state of Nevada that had President Obama with a 1.1% lead in that state. Obama was at 48.9% compared to 47.8% for Romney. Third party candidates combined with undecided voters were at 3.3% statewide. Gravis Marketing finished their presidential poll for Nevada on October 3, 2012. " This Gravis poll was completed before the debate, I think it tell me that Romney has got the momentum in this state of Nevada "</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349623733684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349624837892-33</Id><Title>Today is Pulpit Freedom Sunday</Title><Msg>From the Washington Post: LOS ANGELES — In a matter of days, some 1,400 American pastors are planning to break the law. And they’re likely to get away with it. As part of “Pulpit Freedom Sunday,” on Oct. 7, religious leaders across the country will endorse political candidates — an act that flies in the face of Internal Revenue Service rules about what tax-exempt organizations, such as churches, can and cannot do.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349624837892</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:47:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349625037983-34</Id><Title>Biden so afraid of Ryan he's taking 6 days off to prepare for the debate</Title><Msg>Remarkable that a man with 40 years in politics is so scarred of a very young man like Ryan</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349625037983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349625176277-35</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama hears the footsteps, Romney is catching up, and more lying by Obama won't help. Soon the Media will be forced to produce honest polls, I predict it will happen on Oct 21.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349625176277</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626382798-36</Id><Topic><Title>THE OBAMA MIRACLE</Title><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1349620501179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Populist has nothing to do with it .Rich people are still doing just fine.The middle class and poor are not .If you are unemployed or on food stamps ,you probably dont care about the market. You are the main one who brags about the Obama market. Kinda dumb, dont you think??</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349626382798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:13:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626416319-37</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its now a close race</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349626416319</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:13:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626586919-38</Id><Topic><Title>Biden so afraid of Ryan he's taking 6 days off to prepare for the debate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349625037983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Think dems learned their lesson in Obama's buttkicking. Biden will be prepared and so will Obama next time. But so will Romney and Ryan ....we'll see what happens.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349626586919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:16:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626604584-39</Id><Topic><Title>THE OBAMA MIRACLE</Title><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1349620501179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:35:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The fact is that the Futures market is being manipulated on low volume overnight since the futures have about a 24 hour session. It doesn't take much to manipulate the futures, not many shares, and there is a lot of leverage. The market open is influenced by the futures.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349626604584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626703046-40</Id><Topic><Title>Biden so afraid of Ryan he's taking 6 days off to prepare for the debate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349625037983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Biden has to control his stupid strange way of saying things. Gaff prone Biden can be preparred for everything but himself</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349626703046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:18:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349626910913-41</Id><Topic><Title>Biden so afraid of Ryan he's taking 6 days off to prepare for the debate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349625037983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm hoping Biden will be Biden.LOL But guaranteed he's getting a crash course in debating.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349626910913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:21:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349628038371-42</Id><Topic><Title>Newt Gingrich: Romney Flip-Flopped On Tax Cuts</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1349627793532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:36:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now you like Newt???? You are such a phony its unbelievable.!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349628038371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349628319639-43</Id><Topic><Title>Newt Gingrich: Romney Flip-Flopped On Tax Cuts</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1349627793532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:36:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the one quoting him not me. lol You a phony,buddy.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349628319639</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:45:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628364074-44</Id><Title>the same super polished CEOs almost destroyed this country just 4 years ago. and they hope you</Title><Msg>forgot about it!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628364074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:46:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628500428-45</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts is now against tax cuts for the rich and for insuring</Title><Msg>people with preexisting conditions. really?</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628500428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628595590-46</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts who was for self deportation is now for the Dream Act</Title><Msg>I'm Mitt Romney let's go party</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628595590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349628597208-47</Id><Topic><Title>Newt Gingrich: Romney Flip-Flopped On Tax Cuts</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1349627793532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:36:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Time for football. Find someone else to make a fool out of you.....bye</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1349628597208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628700561-48</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts who outsourced your job 4 years ago is now</Title><Msg>for, well, outsourcing your job. you can only flip flop so much...</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628700561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628832418-49</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts is no longer severely conservative? Is the 1% still going to vote for him?</Title><Msg>I'm very confused</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628832418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:53:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349628952996-50</Id><Title>for abortion - against abortion, for self deportation - again self deportation, for obamacare - against obamacare</Title><Msg>what is it Mitt? I've never been so confused in my entire life!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628952996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629056834-51</Id><Title>Ted Kennedy was right, give Mitt two more weeks and he will vote for Obama!</Title><Msg>this guy is just unbelievable</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349629056834</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629269172-52</Id><Title>Mitt was for Obamacare before he was against before he was for it. This guy is John Kerry cubed</Title><Msg>There has to be a better term for Mitt than flip flopper.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349629269172</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629436675-53</Id><Title>Mitt was for abortion before he was against it before he was for it.</Title><Msg>Is he going to be for or against it on November 6th?</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349629436675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629545278-54</Id><Title>Mitt was for tax cuts before he was against them before he was for them, before he was against them</Title><Msg>and right before he was for them!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349629545278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349629753190-55</Id><Topic><Title>Jack Welch explains why the UE numbers are #$%$</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349541807938</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 12:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There was some very fishy things going on at GE when Welch was in charge. If we had true laws to protect shareholders from CEO ethically challenged guys like Welch would be sitting in prisons.</Msg><Username>michsteve09</Username><Timestamp>1349629753190</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:09:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629761595-56</Id><Title>One thing Mitt will never flip flop on is OUTSOURCING</Title><Msg>he will fire your sorry American rear end in a New York second and 4 years later he will ask your if you are better off!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349629761595</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349629817740-57</Id><Topic><Title>Is CSCO Poised For A Huge Win?</Title><Username>thadmendoza170</Username><Timestamp>1349523928197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-10-06 07:45:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when it will start the move then nothing can be stop it</Msg><Username>hildayang711</Username><Timestamp>1349629817740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:10:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349629836755-58</Id><Title>Obama had a Rick Perry moment for 90 minutes of the Presidential debate--shocking</Title><Msg>He was Romneys punching bag for 90 minutes. One more debate like that and the Obamas can start packing and call the moving van. Obama Nodded his head in agreement as Romney attacked him.</Msg><Username>gliderpilot7777</Username><Timestamp>1349629836755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349631011727-59</Id><Topic><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts is no longer severely conservative? Is the 1% still going to vote for him?</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349628832418</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 12:53:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I watched the debate, I'm voting Romney, he is going to cut taxes on everyone by 20%, increase defense spending, increase spending on medicare and social security and balance the budget by cutting out the 50 million a year that goes to PBS and one other tax loophole to be named at a secret date in the future, what's not to love?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349631011727</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:30:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349631247311-60</Id><Title>Mitt's plan is against insuring people with pre-existing conditions, but Mitt is for it!</Title><Msg>this guy is incredible</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349631247311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:34:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349631401545-61</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt's plan is against insuring people with pre-existing conditions, but Mitt is for it!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349631247311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:34:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt is going to provide everyone in America with free snake oil</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349631401545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:36:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349631855060-62</Id><Title>Mitt's plan to tell everyone what they want to hear is actually pretty smart.</Title><Msg>I don't think there is any other plan that could have a chance but this one. Confuse the heck of the 70% that were for the Iraq war, and see if you can squeeze 21% of them. Pretty smart, if you ask me.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349631855060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:44:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349632128122-63</Id><Topic><Title>Obama had a Rick Perry moment for 90 minutes of the Presidential debate--shocking</Title><Username>gliderpilot7777</Username><Timestamp>1349629836755</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:10:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama does another impression of a doormat at the next debate he will lose the election. Just saying, He is making Thurston Howell Romney the man who likes to fire people into a winner. I thought that would be impossible but I never expected Obama to be a doormat to Romney.</Msg><Username>gliderpilot7777</Username><Timestamp>1349632128122</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349632149602-64</Id><Title>Canadian citizenship is not for sale</Title><Msg>Unlike in America.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349632149602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349632230470-65</Id><Topic><Title>Canadian citizenship is not for sale</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349632149602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you are correct...it is free!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349632230470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349632690894-66</Id><Title>Smoochers and freeloaders</Title><Msg>My ?itch got a dancing horse -- Mitt</Msg><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349632690894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:58:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349632919332-67</Id><Topic><Title>Canadian citizenship is not for sale</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349632149602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Aren't you sick and tired of all the minorities in America calling everyone a racist as a means to an end, and saying America is a nation of immigrants ? Well "WAS" and the past does not equal the present. And these "fine" people always being put on pedestal, expect special privileges, affirmative action, College breaks etc... Show America how "FINE" you are and FIX YOUR OWN DANG countries ! THIS IS A NO PC ZONE, (And a someone who does not give ONE penny to illegals or MUD people )</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349632919332</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:01:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349633227106-68</Id><Topic><Title>Canadian citizenship is not for sale</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349632149602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:49:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>currently, over 10 million illegal immigrants. take that Canada!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349633227106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349633503805-69</Id><Title>Romney= show your taxes,,,what loop holes would you change,,quit flip floping on everything</Title><Msg>MIT IS UNFIT</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349633503805</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349633503847-70</Id><Title>Romney= show your taxes,,,what loop holes would you change,,quit flip floping on everything</Title><Msg>MIT IS UNFIT</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349633503847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:11:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349633764466-71</Id><Topic><Title>Romney= show your taxes,,,what loop holes would you change,,quit flip floping on everything</Title><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1349633503847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:11:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't worry, I have it on good authority his taxes will be leaked closer to the election</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349633764466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:16:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349633963469-72</Id><Title>woopsie</Title><Msg>) - U.S. President Barack Obama's campaign and its Democratic allies raised $181 million in September for his re-election effort, the largest total that either side has announced yet in the 2012 campaign. The big September number and a good jobs report on Friday that showed unemployment dipping to 7.8 percent from 8.1 percent shifted some attention from Obama's lackluster debate performance on Wednesday against Republican Mitt Romney.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349633963469</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:19:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349635173372-73</Id><Topic><Title>Smoochers and freeloaders</Title><Username>gopsrsobs</Username><Timestamp>1349632690894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 13:58:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>paid for by sheltering my money and jobs overseas</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349635173372</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349636077838-74</Id><Title>boo</Title><Msg>Republican vice presidential candidate Paul Ryan received a chilly reception from a seniors' group on Friday as he argued that popular health and pension programs for U.S. retirees need to be overhauled to ensure their stability. Members of the retiree group AARP booed and heckled Ryan as he laid out the Republican ticket's case for repealing President Barack Obama's healthcare law and partially privatizing the Medicare health plan. "I had a feeling there would be mixed reactions," Ryan told the crowd.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349636077838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 14:54:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349640300658-75</Id><Title>WITHOUT OBAMA GREEN BERETS WOULD HAVE FAILED TO GET BINLADEN</Title><Msg>WITHOUT OBAMA GREEN BERETS WOULD HAVE FAILED TO GET BINLADEN. Those green berets needed Obama to manage every detail of the get binladen operation. Without Obama giving them second by second instructions they would have failed for sure.</Msg><Username>gay_tv_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1349640300658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349642054578-76</Id><Title>Unskewed Polling ; Polling without dem biased weighting</Title><Msg>UnSkewed Polling Data Sunday, October 07, 2012 1:30:42 PM Poll Date Sample MoE Skew Obama(D) Romney(R) Spread UnSkewed Avg. 9/24 - 10/4 -- -- +4.3 D 46.8 48.7 Romney +1.9 Rasmussen 10/3 - 10/5 1500 LV 3.0 +3 D 45.0 51.0 Romney +6 Gallup 9/29 - 10/5 3050 RV 2.0 +5 D 46.0 48.0 Romney +2 NPR 9/26 - 9/30 800 LV 4.0 +7 D 49.0 47.0 Obama +1 National Journal 9/27 - 9/30 LV 4.5 +7 D 46.0 49.0 Romney +3 Quinnipiac 9/25 - 9/30 1912 2.2 +6 D 49.0 48.0 Obama +1 CNN/ORC 9/28 - 9/30 783 LV 3.0 +3 D 46.0 50.0 Romney +4 ABC News/Wash. Post 9/26 - 9/29 813 LV 3.5 +3 D 49.0 49.0 Tied Fox News 9/24 - 9/26 1092 LV 3.0 +4 D 46.0 44.0 Obama +2 NBC News/WSJ 9/26 - 9/30 832 LV 3.4 +6 D 48.0 49.0 Romney +1 Monmouth Univ. 9/13 - 9/16 1344 LV 2.5 +6 D 45.0 50.0 Romney +5 QStarNews 9/24 - 9/28 5061 LV 1.4 +0.0 D 47.0 50.0 Romney +3 Read it and weep Obama is gonna lose just like the U. Of Colorado model says.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349642054578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349642788800-77</Id><Title>Why repubs love Joe</Title><Msg>Joe Biden has done it again.Challenged those " who dont believe me can fact check me". Well they did and found several instances of Joe not telling the truth . Too funny !!!!Ryan is going to tear this fool up.LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349642788800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349644917503-78</Id><Topic><Title>Why repubs love Joe</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349642788800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:46:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said the same thing about Obama whipping Romney last week.How did that go??/LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL They are still whimpering at MSNBC.LOLOLOLOLOL BTW, The DNC main talking point is "call them liars,liars,liars." Hows that kool-ade taste??LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349644917503</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:21:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349646367823-79</Id><Title>Somebody's Got to Care about CISCO Besides me!</Title><Msg>...anyone?</Msg><Username>toonawish</Username><Timestamp>1349646367823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647076222-80</Id><Title>I love Obama and Obamacare! He gave me a tax cut, forced my polished CEO to provide health care</Title><Msg>for my kids in college, doubled my money in the stock market, killed Bin Laden, saved GM, created 5 million jobs, and kept us safe at home. I think I can deal with 4 more years of that!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647076222</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:57:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647168006-81</Id><Title>HP LAYING OFF 27,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Hp laying off 27,000 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>kenya_bolshevik_from_chicago</Username><Timestamp>1349647168006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:59:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647444049-82</Id><Title>Supervalue food chain laying off 3300 workers while obama brags about recovery</Title><Msg>Supervalue food chain laying off 3300 workers while obama brags about recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647444049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:04:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647509969-83</Id><Title>LOCKHEED MARTIN LAYING OFF 10,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Lockheed martin laying off 10,000 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647509969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647565129-84</Id><Topic><Title>HP LAYING OFF 27,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>kenya_bolshevik_from_chicago</Username><Timestamp>1349647168006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HP is run by Meg Withmen a republican. When you have a republican running the show you get layoffs and outsourcing. You should have learned that by now!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647565129</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647595943-85</Id><Title>BEST BUY LAYING OFF 2800 INCLUDING 600 GEEK SQUAD WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS THAT WE ARE IN A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Best buy laying off 2800 including 600 geek squad workers while obama brags that we are in a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647595943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647642481-86</Id><Title>KRAFT FOODS LAYING OFF 1600 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Kraft foods laying off 1600 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647642481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:07:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647687650-87</Id><Topic><Title>LOCKHEED MARTIN LAYING OFF 10,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647509969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need to cut spending and pay down the debt. your grandchildren will thank you for that</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647687650</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:08:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647707343-88</Id><Title>APPLIED MATERIALS LAYING OFF 1300 WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Applied materials laying off 1300 while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647707343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647758679-89</Id><Topic><Title>KRAFT FOODS LAYING OFF 1600 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647642481</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:07:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO wants a bigger bonus this year</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647758679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:09:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647779776-90</Id><Title>SPRINT LAYING OFF 2500 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Sprint laying off 2500 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647779776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:09:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647831281-91</Id><Topic><Title>BEST BUY LAYING OFF 2800 INCLUDING 600 GEEK SQUAD WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS THAT WE ARE IN A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647595943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO is an incompetent. have they even heard of Amazon?</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647831281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647886227-92</Id><Title>JC PENNY LAYING OFF 1350 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Jc penny laying off 1350 workers while obama brags about recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647886227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647904145-93</Id><Topic><Title>SPRINT LAYING OFF 2500 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647779776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:09:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO and his so called executive team want mo money</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647904145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647958405-94</Id><Topic><Title>JC PENNY LAYING OFF 1350 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647886227</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO and his so called executive team want mo money</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647958405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349647961171-95</Id><Title>ROCKWELL COLLINS LAYING OFF 1000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Rockwell collins laying off 1000 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647961171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:12:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349647990787-96</Id><Topic><Title>ROCKWELL COLLINS LAYING OFF 1000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647961171</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:12:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO and his so called executive team want mo money</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349647990787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648027265-97</Id><Topic><Title>APPLIED MATERIALS LAYING OFF 1300 WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647707343</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:08:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the rich super polished CEO and his so called executive team want mo money</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648027265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648066823-98</Id><Title>ARCHER DANIELS MIDLAND LAYING OFF 1200 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Archer daniels midland laying off 1200 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648066823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:14:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648178502-99</Id><Title>the rich super polished CEOs laying off and outsourcing people to receive a bigger bonus this x-mas</Title><Msg>tell me something I already don't know</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648178502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648192179-100</Id><Title>Challenger Gray and Christmas LAYING OFF 352,200 WORKERS in 2012 while Obama brags about recovery</Title><Msg>Challenger Gray and Christmas LAYING OFF 352,200 WORKERS in 2012 while Obama brags about recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648192179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648232392-101</Id><Topic><Title>Unskewed Polling ; Polling without dem biased weighting</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349642054578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Polls will only get worse when the layoffs hit the Air.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349648232392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:17:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648312279-102</Id><Title>AMERICAN AIRLINES LAYING OFF 14,200 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>American airlines laying off 14,200 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648312279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648318139-103</Id><Title>Mitt Romney would be laying off people right about now too!</Title><Msg>Too bad he is running for presidency, he used to love to layoff people right before x-mas</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648318139</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648418499-104</Id><Title>Obama violating the WARN act so defense industry layoff notices aren't sent before election day</Title><Msg>Sens. Chuck Grassley of Iowa and Kelly Ayotte of New Hampshire are seeking an explanation from the administration over its move on Friday to prevent contractors facing sequestration cuts from issuing layoff notices required by law. The senators say they are "seriously concerned" about an Office of Management and Budget memorandum and a Labor Department letter addressing the applicability of the Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act. "In particular, we are concerned about the authority of the executive branch to instruct private employers not to comply with federal law," the senators wrote to OMB Ccting Director Jeffrey Zients. The WARN Act requires companies with 100 or more employees to give workers 60 days' notice before plant closings or mass layoffs. In this case, the Labor Department issued guidance in July saying that the layoff notices would be inappropriate because sequestration could be averted, National Journal reported. On Friday, OMB issued guidance saying that if sequestration occurs necessitating WARN Act notices and if the contractor followed Labor Department counsel, then resulting WARN Act liability costs could be covered by the contracting agency. The senators take issue with both administration positions, and in particular, worry about the potential cost burden the administration might be undertaking. "Although the precise amounts of the judgments and costs are unknown, they could potentially reach tens or hundreds of millions of dollars, if not billions of dollars, all of which would be paid for with taxpayers' dollars," the senators wrote.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349648418499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:20:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648428142-105</Id><Title>overpaid CEOs laying people off right before x-mas. Challenger has the proof, these c-riminals</Title><Msg>have no scrupulous. They would outsource your job in a NY second</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648428142</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:20:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648503745-106</Id><Title>Obama not sending defense cut layoff notices out before election day</Title><Msg>Sens. Chuck Grassley of Iowa and Kelly Ayotte of New Hampshire are seeking an explanation from the administration over its move on Friday to prevent contractors facing sequestration cuts from issuing layoff notices required by law. The senators say they are "seriously concerned" about an Office of Management and Budget memorandum and a Labor Department letter addressing the applicability of the Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act. "In particular, we are concerned about the authority of the executive branch to instruct private employers not to comply with federal law," the senators wrote to OMB Ccting Director Jeffrey Zients. The WARN Act requires companies with 100 or more employees to give workers 60 days' notice before plant closings or mass layoffs. In this case, the Labor Department issued guidance in July saying that the layoff notices would be inappropriate because sequestration could be averted, National Journal reported. On Friday, OMB issued guidance saying that if sequestration occurs necessitating WARN Act notices and if the contractor followed Labor Department counsel, then resulting WARN Act liability costs could be covered by the contracting agency. The senators take issue with both administration positions, and in particular, worry about the potential cost burden the administration might be undertaking. "Although the precise amounts of the judgments and costs are unknown, they could potentially reach tens or hundreds of millions of dollars, if not billions of dollars, all of which would be paid for with taxpayers' dollars," the senators wrote.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349648503745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648504838-107</Id><Title>PEPSI LAYING OFF 8700 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Msg>Pepsi laying off 8700 workers while obama brags about a recovery</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648504838</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:21:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648560566-108</Id><Topic><Title>LOCKHEED MARTIN LAYING OFF 10,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647509969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGREE, Just look at dice or monster 99% of all high tech jobs are govt contractors like Lockheed and the like.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648560566</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648609615-109</Id><Title>overpaid worthless CEOs almost destroyed this country 4 years ago. WE REMEMBER!</Title><Msg>we will always remember!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648609615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:23:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648718931-110</Id><Title>Mitt outsourced your job 4 years ago and now wants to know if you are better off?</Title><Msg>what do you say?</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648718931</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648755674-111</Id><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Msg>To mach all the private company layoffs, the latter can't support the former !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648812089-112</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mach- LOL another GED failure, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1349648812089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:26:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349648838836-113</Id><Title>overpaid worthless CEOs asked us to bail them out 4 years ago. REMEMBER?</Title><Msg>we will always remember!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349648838836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:27:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648948849-114</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should start with cutting union teacher jobs. These greedy dishonest union teachers are destroying America's future by failing to teach and giving kids cheat sheets with the answers toa all the test questions during a test so that the kids will get high scores and the unionized school districts can justify a large pay raise for all these dishonest union 'teachers'.</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648948849</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:29:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349648949096-115</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We should start with cutting union teacher jobs. These greedy dishonest union teachers are destroying America's future by failing to teach and giving kids cheat sheets with the answers toa all the test questions during a test so that the kids will get high scores and the unionized school districts can justify a large pay raise for all these dishonest union 'teachers'.</Msg><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648949096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:29:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349649073669-116</Id><Title>overpaid worthless CEOs outsourced our jobs to China! A COMMUNIST COUNTRY!</Title><Msg>so few of them could get rich, and in the process shared our technology ...the technology developed by the American worker!.... with a communist country who is using the money to build their military! jail these criminals now!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349649073669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:31:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349649134049-117</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>govt union jobless rate is 4.3% that is why the deficit is so high. Lets spread the wealth around and make the govt. union rate 11.4% just like the real UE rate is</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649134049</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:32:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349649582569-118</Id><Title>Catholic Assoc. 2012 voters guide give Mitt "A+" rating and Obama an "F"</Title><Msg>The Christian Coalition has gained attention over the past few decades with the “voter guides” it distributes to Evangelical Christians. Now, The Catholic Association has just released its own “voter guide” as part of the group’s effort to make “religious freedom” a 2012 campaign issue. The Catholic Association’s voter guide gives Republican Mitt Romney an over-all grade of “A+” and gives Democrat Barack Obama an “F”.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649582569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349649582591-119</Id><Title>the American people created technologies, and CEOs sold it to China!</Title><Msg>these c-riminals should be jailed immediately.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349649582591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:39:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349649631915-120</Id><Topic><Title>Catholic Assoc. 2012 voters guide give Mitt "A+" rating and Obama an "F"</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649582569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:39:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Commie got what he deserved.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649631915</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:40:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349649946700-121</Id><Title>Snoop Dog voting for Obama because "Mooche has a big Booty"</Title><Msg>A booty Ms. Romney can't touch.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649946700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:45:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349650242778-122</Id><Title>Oprah interviews the Romneys is the F finger to the Mooche</Title><Msg>Oprah likes to go with a winner. Mitt is going to win. Oprah thinks Mooche is a #$%$</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349650242778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349650287927-123</Id><Topic><Title>Oprah interviews the Romneys is the F finger to the Mooche</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349650242778</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oprah Mitt Romney Interview: Winfrey Talks to Romneys For First Time Oct 06, 2012 11:32 AM EDT « PREV NEXT » inShare Share 2 mail print 0 (Photo : Reuters) Republican presidential nominee Mitt Romney and his wife Ann greet diners during a visit to La Tersesita Restaurant in Tampa, Florida October 5, 2012. Oprah Winfrey was invited to Mitt Romney's holiday home in New Hampshire for an interview where he and his wife Ann Romney opened up about their family, his favorite foods, favorite songs and hopes for the country. Winfrey talked with the Republican Presidential Candidate as he dressed casual and even packed food for Oprah to take home. "Ann makes these little meatloaf cakes with sweat sauce on top. Meatloaf cakes and mashed potatoes. Best thing in the world," Romney told Oprah for the interview featured on O Magazine's November issue. Romney told Oprah that he never imagined being a president until he became older. "I never imagined being the president in my youth. As a little boy, I wanted to be a policeman," he said. "And then as I got older and I saw my dad in the car business, an automobile executive," he added. However, now that he is running for office Romney told Oprah what his vision for the world is: "More liberty. More freedom. Opportunity. And hope," Romney said.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349650287927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349650360409-124</Id><Topic><Title>Catholic Assoc. 2012 voters guide give Mitt "A+" rating and Obama an "F"</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649582569</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:39:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>millions of Mormons will vote for Mitt too.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349650360409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349651639519-125</Id><Topic><Title>MORE MITT MYTHS</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1349441325817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a/k/a "The Twelve Lies of Mitt-ness"</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1349651639519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349653595981-126</Id><Topic><Title>MORE MITT MYTHS</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1349441325817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny you loons keep trying to tear Romney down. Why dont you brag about what a great debate Obama did.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL....OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOPSIE!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349653595981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349654426824-127</Id><Topic><Title>MORE MITT MYTHS</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1349441325817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your opinion and the opinion of the FAR LEFT who major in lies. Who said, " I will cut the deficit in half "? A LIAR Who said, " I will have UE down to 5.6% ? A LIAR Who said, " I will close gitmo "? A LIAR Who said, " I will be transparent" ? A LIAR I could go on but I think you get he jist. You people can't prove a single thing Romney says is a lie just like AT THE TIME what O'Loser said wasn't a lie. IT IS NOW. Have another chug of the koolaid, APOLOGIST.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349654426824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349654709231-128</Id><Topic><Title>romney stood in front of america and lied his #$%$ off</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1349651344723</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 19:09:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama stood in front of America and looked like Clint's empty chair.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349654709231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:05:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349654769686-129</Id><Title>Phoney Catholics support the antiChrist.</Title><Msg>The first Commandament, thou shall have no other God before me. Remember that phoney Christians. If you believe Jesus is the Christ and Messiah who left the Holy Spirit to guide us afterhe went to be with the Lord, then you also must know that Joe Smith and Mormons are non believers in the divinity of Jesus. The Christian Bible is the last and only word of God. Vote for the one that believes in the Word, Obama the only true Christian.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349654769686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:06:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>8</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349654990707-130</Id><Topic><Title>MORE MITT MYTHS</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1349441325817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-05 08:48:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jason a/k/a "A compulsive liar" A compulsive liar may also have difficulties with poor self esteem. For the most part, compulsive liars are not overly manipulative and cunning, rather they simply lie out of habit</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1349654990707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349655038504-131</Id><Title>Overpaid CEOs get raises while laying of thousands as they vote for Mitt</Title><Msg>Yup, That's Mitt's buddies' way of helping the economy.</Msg><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1349655038504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349655509483-132</Id><Title>Obama Change = 23,MILLION UNEMPLOYED</Title><Msg>There are currently 23 MILLION UNEMPLOYED thanks to Obama. Obama brags that he created 114,000 jobs last month. At this rate it would take 201.75 months (17 Years) to get those 23 million UNEMPLOYED Americans on the employed column.</Msg><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349655509483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349655540652-133</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And let you teach? Good luck with that!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1349655540652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:19:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349655592581-134</Id><Topic><Title>Phoney Catholics support the antiChrist.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349654769686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The following excerpts are taken from an address to the Harvard Divinity School in March 2001 by Robert L. Millet, former dean of religious education at Brigham Young University. What Do We Believe About Jesus Christ? Latter-day Saints are Christians on the basis of our doctrine, our defined relationship to Christ, our patterns of worship and our way of life. What Do We Believe About Christ? •We believe Jesus is the Son of God, the Only Begotten Son in the flesh (John 3:16). We accept the prophetic declarations in the Old Testament that refer directly and powerfully to the coming of the Messiah, the Savior of all humankind Why do socialist dem. want to deceive people.</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349655592581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:19:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349655762170-135</Id><Topic><Title>LOCKHEED MARTIN LAYING OFF 10,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647509969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:05:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Might happen because Congress passed this bill (including Paul Ryan's signature).</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1349655762170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349655868374-136</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICAN AIRLINES LAYING OFF 14,200 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648312279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:18:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AMR declared bankruptcy because of poor management. Next.</Msg><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1349655868374</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:24:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349655875597-137</Id><Title>socialist dem. strategy,SPECIFIC &amp; DETAILS</Title><Msg>Obama said Romney not giving SPECIFIC'S on his economic plan,socialist dem. on Sunday morning talk show"Romney does not give DETAILS . Socialist Dem specific's and details on Obamacare only several days before the vote,dem Nancy Pelosi “We have to pass the bill so we can find out what is in it”. Socialist Dem want specific's and details.HAHAHAHAHA</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349655875597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:24:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349656019213-138</Id><Topic><Title>socialist dem. strategy,SPECIFIC &amp; DETAILS</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349655875597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:24:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This strategy is a lame attempt to divert attention away from Obama's poor economic job performance. Romney should continue to focus on Obama's economic job performance and keep hammering on Obama's record.</Msg><Username>homos_r_mentally_ill</Username><Timestamp>1349656019213</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:26:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349656349258-139</Id><Title>OBAMA CELEBRATES RAMADAN DINNER (ISLAM RELIGIOUS HOLIDAY) at the White House</Title><Msg>That obviously makes Obama an ALLAH worshipper and moooooslim.</Msg><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1349656349258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:32:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349656436848-140</Id><Title>Obama administration GINNED up the UE numbers.</Title><Msg>The drop from 8.5% to 7.8% over the last 2 months would ONLY be supported by an economy growing at 4-5%. This criminal administration will do anything and everything for political gain. Obama is a LIAR.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349656436848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349656740698-141</Id><Topic><Title>Obama administration GINNED up the UE numbers.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349656436848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately for Obama, nobody believes his bogus job numbers. People look around and see economic depression everywhere they look (layoffs, empty foreclosed homes, bank closures, business closures ect).</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1349656740698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349656740897-142</Id><Topic><Title>Obama administration GINNED up the UE numbers.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349656436848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:33:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately for Obama, nobody believes his bogus job numbers. People look around and see economic depression everywhere they look (layoffs, empty foreclosed homes, bank closures, business closures ect).</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1349656740897</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:39:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349656849446-143</Id><Topic><Title>Phoney Catholics support the antiChrist.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349654769686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a modern Christian. I believe Jesus was a wonderful man, that tried to change many wrongs, but he was not god. We now know that there are at least thousands of earth like planets, some with new forms of life most likely. Joseph Smith was a strange fellow.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1349656849446</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349656943864-144</Id><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Msg>Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse want does that represent? A) belief systems B) end time events C) none of the above</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657000679-145</Id><Topic><Title>Snoop Dog voting for Obama because "Mooche has a big Booty"</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349649946700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:45:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mrs Romney wouldn't want to touch that ogre of a beast and neither would I.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1349657000679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657014258-146</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA CELEBRATES RAMADAN DINNER (ISLAM RELIGIOUS HOLIDAY) at the White House</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1349656349258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In that case, GW Bush is mooooslim too for issuing two stamps (8/2001) honoring your moooslim holidays. LOL!</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1349657014258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:43:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657031323-147</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA CELEBRATES RAMADAN DINNER (ISLAM RELIGIOUS HOLIDAY) at the White House</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_terror</Username><Timestamp>1349656349258</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:32:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It makes him President of all of the people, including you, me and those in our prisons.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1349657031323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349657075106-148</Id><Title>Just the Facts:</Title><Msg>MEDICARE Look clearly at the 2014 rate compared to the 2013 rate. For those of you who are on Medicare, read the following. It's short, but important and you probably haven't heard about it in the Mainstream News: "The per person Medicare Insurance Premium will increase from the present Monthly Fee of $96.40, rising to: $104.20 in 2012 $120.20 in 2013 And $247.00 in 2014." These are Provisions incorporated in the Obamacare Legislation, purposely delayed so as not to confuse the 2012 Re-Election Campaigns.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1349657075106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657721260-149</Id><Topic><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>socialist have strong views on religion but no challenge ,socialist dem.are PHONY</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349657721260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:55:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349657990837-150</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Change = 23,MILLION UNEMPLOYED</Title><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349655509483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney should mention this fact repeatedly at the next debate</Msg><Username>black_congressional_cacas</Username><Timestamp>1349657990837</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658257028-151</Id><Topic><Title>the American people created technologies, and CEOs sold it to China!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349649582591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:39:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And private/public colleges for training undeserving foreigners...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349658257028</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:04:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658344528-152</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>MachNics (no matter FOOL !)</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349658344528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:05:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658420781-153</Id><Title>always remember TARP and the incompetent so called executives that almost destroyed this country</Title><Msg>now these c-riminals want to drive again. Obama will jail these c-riminals next year</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658420781</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:07:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658526243-154</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts who outsourced your job 4 years ago now wants to know</Title><Msg>if you are better off</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658526243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658568406-155</Id><Title>OBAMA TSA UNION WORKER ARRESTED FOR ROBBING PASSENGER</Title><Msg>From CBS Local Los Angeles: "Transportation Security Administration officer was arrested at Los Angeles International Airport after being accused of stealing $100 from a passenger. Clyde Reese, 47, of Gardena, was arrested on suspicion of theft about 8 a.m. Friday and booked at the 77th Street Station in response to an airline passenger complaint in Terminal 5, Los Angeles Airport police Sgt. Karla Ortiz told the Daily Breeze. The victim, who wasn’t identified, said he put his wallet and other items in a bin and passed it through the X-ray machine, and Reese said it needed to go through a second time, Ortiz said. When the bin emerged, the victim said his wallet was open and his credit cards were scattered inside, Ortiz said. She told the Daily Breeze the victim said his boss gave him $500 for expenses and $100 was missing."</Msg><Username>black_congressional_cacas</Username><Timestamp>1349658568406</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:09:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658590695-156</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the only history they teach is slavery in America as if it was ONLY done here and forever...! Students in public schools are better off with a GED: Slavery. The awful truth is that Arabs ravaged Africa for almost a thousand years before Europeans ever began to export black slaves. In fact, it was the foundation of slave procurement and trading established by the Muslims (usually through Jihad) that enabled the European practice. Far more Africans were swallowed up in the fourteen hundred years of Islamic slave trading than in the three centuries of European practice. An estimated 17 to 20 million Africans were exported from their native land to the Muslim world, but this isn't the whole story. With a transport survival rate of less than 1 in 3, Dr. John Alembellah Azumah estimates that perhaps 50 to 80 million more died in route. Here is a quote from an observer in Zanzibar that sheds light on the harsh conditions of Islamic slavery: "As they filed past, we noticed many chained together by the neck... The women, who were as numerous as the men, carried babies on their backs in addition to a tusk of ivory or other burden on their heads... It is difficult to adequately describe the filthy state of their bodies; in many instances not only scarred by [the whip], but feet and shoulders were a mass of open sores... half-starved ill-treated creatures who, weary and friendless must have longed for death." The text (quoted from Dr. Azumah's The Legacy of Arab-Islam in Africa) goes on to describe the fate of those who became too ill or too weak to continue the journey - as related by a Muslim "herdsman": "Spear them at once! For, if we did not, others would pretend they are ill in order to avoid carrying their loads. No! We never leave them alive on the road; they all know this custom." When asked who carries the ivory when a mother gets too tired to carry both her baby and the ivory, the herdsman replied, "She does! We cannot leave valuable ivory on the road. We spear the child and make her burden lighter." After Muhammad's companions overthrew the Christians in Egypt shortly after his death, they began demanding slaves from the Nubians to the south. For over 600 years, the black African kingdom was forced to send a tribute of slaves to Cairo on a regular basis. Although the Qur'an does not distinguish between races, there is a strong legacy of racism against people of African descent in early Islam. Ha ha !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349658590695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658602888-157</Id><Title>Mitt was for tax cuts before he was against them before he was for them, before he was against them</Title><Msg>and right before he was for them</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658602888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:10:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658721046-158</Id><Title>the CEO with Swiss Bank Accounts is no longer severely conservative</Title><Msg>hmm, the 1% is in trouble!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658721046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:12:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349658907644-159</Id><Topic><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The death of the Repubs antiChrist leader Mr. 666 and his party. Long live Jesus and death to the worshipers of Ronald Wilson Reagan. The antiChrist. Lol.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349658907644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:15:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349658992067-160</Id><Title>from losing 800,000 jobs a MONTH, to gaining 100,000+. From 12% UE to 7.8%</Title><Msg>7.2% in Ohio.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658992067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659004741-161</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt was for tax cuts before he was against them before he was for them, before he was against them</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658602888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:10:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles was AGAINSt gay marriage before he evolved. What is your point, we could play tihs game all night.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349659004741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:16:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659031599-162</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When will ISLAM come to terms and talk about it's evil SLAVE trade ??? where are the REPARATIONS from those RICH $$$ islamic DEVILS ?! ARAB GUILT !!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349659031599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659100734-163</Id><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Msg>incredible.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659109422-164</Id><Topic><Title>TIME TO CUT AND GUT THOSE EXTREME, RADICAL, VIOLENT, GREEDY GOVT UNION JOBS</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349648755674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:25:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ADMIT your wicked ways, GIVE REPARATIONS or face an all BLACK army rise from South Africa to reclaim what's theirs and SEEK REVENGE !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1349659109422</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659219987-165</Id><Title>S&amp;P from 600 to over 1400! Obama more than doubled my money!</Title><Msg>love the man!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659219987</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659229352-166</Id><Topic><Title>Phoney Catholics support the antiChrist.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349654769686</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:06:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A true Christian understands that Jesus IS GOD. There are No prophets after Jesus until he comes back. Again Mormons are not Christians. They just pretend to be. Remember the devil knows scriptures but won't accept Jesus as Lord.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349659229352</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:20:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659353116-167</Id><Title>Obama cut my taxes, and forced my super polished CEO to pay the health care bill for</Title><Msg>my kids in college.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659353116</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659415710-168</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry WRONG again, it was just like Healthcare getting rammed down our throats, O'Loser does what he wants, he doesn't care about anyone or anything else, JUST HIMSELF. THe majority of AMericans were AGAINST Obamacare and he did it anyway. I suppose according to your train of thought, The majority of Americans were also working against Obama. I really think EVERYONE is getting sick and tired Of Obama and you people whining, complaining and BLAMING everyone else for YOUR FAILURES. Sometimes one has to just step back and admit they are WRONG</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349659415710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659443124-169</Id><Topic><Title>from losing 800,000 jobs a MONTH, to gaining 100,000+. From 12% UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658992067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>12.0 in Nevada....10.6 in California . Why didn't you mention those?? BTW, the national UE never got to12.0...so you are a liar.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349659443124</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:24:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659453772-170</Id><Title>Jesus IS God. Let there ne No mistake.</Title><Msg>Mormons aren't Christian. Romney won't accept Jesus as God and last prophet.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349659453772</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:24:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659594379-171</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UE was 7.8 when he took over and its 7.8 today.Only that changed is we are 5.4 trillion deeper in debt.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349659594379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349659739534-172</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm just mentioning facts, the only one complaining and whining is you. I say 7.8%, you say the numbers were cooked. I say 800,000 jobs were lost the month Obama took office, you say? you are simply a naysayer. just another month and it will be all over. YES!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659739534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349659759788-173</Id><Title>JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS...still NO JOBS...despite goofy Labor report.....</Title><Msg>students living at home, after college degree...it's time to toss Obimbo</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1349659759788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349660027201-174</Id><Title>The Devil was a shape shifter like Romney</Title><Msg>Long live the truth. As the Holy Spirit guides the True Christians. The Bible has no mention of Mr Smith. Being against abortion doesn't make you a Christian. Only accepting Jesus as Lord and savior will allow you into his kingdom. Don't be fooled by the antiChrist and his henchmen.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349660027201</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:33:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349660126426-175</Id><Title>National debt under Bush, from 5 trillion to 11 trillion. Were you guys as angry than? I WAS!</Title><Msg>The Iraq war alone will cost over 3 trillion when all is said and done. The 50,000 injured during the illegal war in Iraq will continue to see a doctor decades to come. Someone has to pay for that!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660126426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349660259545-176</Id><Title>Bush wasted 3 trillion in Iraq and Romney is mad at the 90 billion Obama wasted in this country!</Title><Msg>I would rather waste the money here than building an embassy in Iraq!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660259545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660287210-177</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interesting you didn't mention anything about the MAJORITY of Americans who opposed his Healthcare WHO according to YOU fought him every step of the way. Thats the funny thing about YOUR facts, it's hard for you to stay on topic. Since you think you're so smart, explain in detail how the UE rate can drop from 8.5% to 7.8% to 2 months when economic growth is at or just barely above recession level of 1.25%. 25 economists who weighed in on the jobs report Friday came up with an AVERAGE 114K jobs, which they almost NUTTED. Interesting thing is that with that number they called for UE to raise to 8.2%. BUT......the Obama people say UE dropped to 7.8%, a MOVE in the number not seen since 1983. By the way, a move of that magnitude would call for a 4 -5% GDP growth. Those are the facts, why don't you spin your LIES and explain them away.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349660287210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660391542-178</Id><Topic><Title>Bush wasted 3 trillion in Iraq and Romney is mad at the 90 billion Obama wasted in this country!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660259545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Iraq/Afghanistan cost 1.3 trillion per Obama.You calling him a liar??</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349660391542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660521624-179</Id><Topic><Title>Bush wasted 3 trillion in Iraq and Romney is mad at the 90 billion Obama wasted in this country!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660259545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libturds can't help repeating the same LIE over and over. To them repeating a lie make it fact.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349660521624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:42:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660668741-180</Id><Topic><Title>National debt under Bush, from 5 trillion to 11 trillion. Were you guys as angry than? I WAS!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660126426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush raised the debt 5.2 trillion in 8 years. Obama raised it 5.4 trillion in 4 years. Both disgusting.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1349660668741</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349660789105-181</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>70% of the American people were for the Iraq war, so don't ever mention MAJORITY to me again. Did you know that the "majority" was against Medicare and Social Security when they were first introduced? Personally, I LOVE OBAMACARE, and I think eventually all the dummies will love it too. regarding the drop in UE, once again, you are complaining and whining.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660789105</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:46:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661103530-182</Id><Topic><Title>from losing 800,000 jobs a MONTH, to gaining 100,000+. From 12% UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349658992067</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Currently there are 23 MILLION UNEMPLOYED thanks to Obama. Obama brags that he created 114,000 jobs last month. At this rate it would take 201.75 months (17 Years) to get those 23 million UNEMPLOYED Americans on the employed column.</Msg><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349661103530</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:51:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661106345-183</Id><Topic><Title>National debt under Bush, from 5 trillion to 11 trillion. Were you guys as angry than? I WAS!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660126426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree, but again, when Bush left office, the Iraq war bill did not stop. It will continue for decades. Moreover, the Bush economy was collapsing and Obama had to spend 1 trillion to revive it. Bad decisions of a previous administration don't just end the second the person leaves the office. Many just don't get that...</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661106345</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661279707-184</Id><Topic><Title>Bush wasted 3 trillion in Iraq and Romney is mad at the 90 billion Obama wasted in this country!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349660259545</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:37:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you just don't get it dummy. You think when Bush left office, his poor costly decisions stopped right there. don't you?</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661279707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661355929-185</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gave you FACTS and asked you to refute them, you cannot. That usually means you don't have a clue what you're talking about or you're simply being an apologists for O'Loser. Many still think the Iraq war was justified and a good thing. There are millions of Iraqie mother, fathers and children who are grateful for our intervention. I thought you libtards were for the unfortunate and downtrodden. I guess that's only when it's convenient. The only whiner I see here is YOU. Every night you post the same DRIVEL and JIBBERISH......That is your classic WHINING crybaby.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349661355929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:55:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349661464874-186</Id><Title>out of the 5 trillion debt under Obama, at least 4 trillion could be attributed to Bush</Title><Msg>Poor decisions take years to clean up. They don't just stop when the monkey leaves the office!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661464874</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661480736-187</Id><Topic><Title>JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS...still NO JOBS...despite goofy Labor report.....</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1349659759788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:29:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are currently 23 MILLION UNEMPLOYED thanks to Obama. Obama had his surrogates produce a bogus jobs report claiming that the unemployment rate fell to 7.8% and that he created 114,000 jobs last month, then he proceeded to toot his horn citing these bogus numbers. Even with the bogus numbers at a rate of 114,000 jobs per month it would take 201.75 months (17 Years) to get those 23 million UNEMPLOYED Americans on the employed column and this does not even count all the young people who are entering the job market during the 17 years in the future. His fantasy OBAMAVILLE job statistics does not fix the problem!! LOL!</Msg><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349661480736</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:58:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661493177-188</Id><Topic><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The answer is (A) belief systems. The Four Major Belief Systems in the World 1)White Horse represents Catholicism the official color of the church,that's why the Pope dresses in White and when he travels the vehicle even the plane that's supplied by Air ALITALIA are White. “I looked, and there before me was a white horse! Its rider held a bow, and he was given a crown, and he rode out as a conqueror bent on conquest.” 1st crown was given to Pope Gregory 960 AD,bow with no arrows represents power but not military. 2)Red Horse represents Socialism Communism the official color of Red Communist China the USSR ,Romania,NK Then another horse came out, a fiery red one. Its rider was given power to take peace from the earth and to make men slay each other. To him was given a large sword.” "men slay each other"Socialist Communist will kill each other for power 20 million Russians were killed by the Communist 60 million Chinese were killed by the Communist Cultural Revolution Great Sword represents strong military power</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349661493177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349661795212-189</Id><Title>we are still paying for all the bad decisions the born again #$%$ has made</Title><Msg>Obama needs to remind people of that</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661795212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:03:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349661999428-190</Id><Topic><Title>republicans fought Obama every step of the way, and he was still able to bring down UE to 7.8%</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349659100734</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 21:18:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Virtual, amen to you. Don't worry these devils won't accept truth. As for fluteman, he has lost his cash on this stock for years. He is a loser. Lol. Go Forward.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349661999428</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:06:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349662023640-191</Id><Title>it takes years to recover from a deep recession; it took over 15 years and a World War</Title><Msg>to recover from the great depression.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349662023640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:07:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349662051859-192</Id><Topic><Title>we are still paying for all the bad decisions the born again #$%$ has made</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661795212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry SHELLACKING 2.0 will rid the country of O'Loser once and for all. No more community organizer, we will finally get a REAL leader.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1349662051859</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:07:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349662061980-193</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Change = 23,MILLION UNEMPLOYED</Title><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349655509483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama formed a jobs creation comittee around 6 months ago (for the DNC news headlines) and has not yet met with them.</Msg><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1349662061980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:07:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349662139724-194</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Change = 23,MILLION UNEMPLOYED</Title><Username>weeping_oil_soaked_obama_pelican</Username><Timestamp>1349655509483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:18:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama formed a jobs creation comittee around 6 months ago (for the DNC news headlines) and has not yet met with them in the last 6 months to discuss jobs.</Msg><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1349662139724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:08:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>17</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349662269535-195</Id><Topic><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must be one of those Mormon looneys. Tell your garbage to Lyin Ryan, Mr phoney Christian.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349662269535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:11:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349662477841-196</Id><Title>3 million jobs created during Obama years. Zero for Bush.</Title><Msg>Face the facts. Repubs don't know anything about building a nation. Lol.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349662477841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:14:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349662646340-197</Id><Topic><Title>we are still paying for all the bad decisions the born again #$%$ has made</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349661795212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:03:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not worried at all! and, like I said, 70% were for the Iraq war, so everything is possible. btw, I'm from Ohio, and everyone that I know that voted for Obama in 2008 will do so again in 2012. The ones that voted for McCain will vote for Romney, but none of them think he is a "real" leader. Not one!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1349662646340</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:17:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349662966325-198</Id><Title>Why Romney will win Ohio</Title><Msg>I am going to take a break from promoting my just released book, The Catholic Tide Continues to Turn to write about another interest of mine; election polling and demographics in my home state of Ohio. Lately my dander has been raised more than once by polls which are totally inept in their sampling rational. This article will attempt to explain why at this point Governor Mitt Romney is in the driver’s seat in my home state. Full disclosure; I did not vote for Governor Romney in the GOP primary, my vote went to Senator Rick Santorum. Also until the mid 1990s I was a conservative Democrat; my political work began in the 1980s as in intern in the Ohio State House and then continued for the Democratic Leadership Council on Capitol Hill in 1994-95. I saw no hope for conservative Democrats like myself after my stint in Washington DC. I view myself not as a Republican, but a conservative. The 2008 General Election was a perfect storm for Democrats across the country and Ohio was no exception. By 2010, the gains the Democrats made had evaporated and the GOP returned to the levels it had enjoyed in the 1980s. However, political polling across the country has not reflected this change. Obviously this makes a huge difference in Midwestern swing areas, especially suburban locations, the area of most states that continue to grow, even if that state’s total growth is stagnant. For example in Ohio the area surrounding Franklin County (Columbus) and the area surrounding Hamilton County (Cincinnati) are the fastest growing areas of the state. These areas generally go GOP 65%-35%. Conversely, the Democratic strongholds of Lucas (Toledo,) Cuyahoga (Cleveland,) Summit (Akron,) and Mahoning (Youngstown) are the areas of the state that have seen a freefall in residents since the late 1970s. While many people are aware of this statistic, one area few seem to realize is the age demographic, Democratic voters are dying off faster than the younger (40 and 50 something) Reagan era GOP voters of the fast growing GOP strongholds of suburban Columbus and Cincinnati. Now let’s take a look at raw voter counts in Ohio and what we can expect after the polls close at 7:30 PM on November 6. A cursory glance of the 2004 and 2008 election results in the Democratic strongholds in the northern part of the state might make one reason that a serious error had occurred. How could Massachusetts Senator John Kerry possibly get more votes than the first African American standard bearer, then Illinois Senator Barack Obama in areas like Cuyahoga County which is over 30% African-American, the highest percentage in the state? The answer is simple, thousands of voters had died or moved from that area of the state in those four years, and many more thousands have done so since the economic meltdown of 2008. For example in 1980 Cuyahoga County had 1,500,000 residents compared to 1,280,000 in 2010, Lucas County had 471,000 in 1980 compared to 441.000 in 2010 and Mahoning County had 290,000 residents in 1980, compared to 239,000 in 2010. Many left for southern and western states. As recent as a few days ago (early October 2012) election officials had reported a huge drop off in eligible voters for this Democratic rich area of the state. Let’s give the President the benefit of the doubt and say his numbers in Cleveland, Toledo and Youngstown only drop 5% (due to shifting demographics) this is still a nightmare scenario for the Obama-Biden ticket when one realizes that Romney-Ryan ticket will certainly gain at least 5% in the Columbus and Cincinnati fast growing suburban areas. Now let’s take a look at the GOP strongholds of suburban Columbus and Cincinnati. In 1980 Butler County (outside of Cincinnati) had 258, 000 voters compared to 368,000 in 2010 and Warren County directly north of Cincinnati had 99,000 residents in 1980 versus 212,000 in 2010. Let’s look at Columbus, Delaware County which for years was the fastest growing county in the Midwest had 53,000 residents in 1980 compared to 174,000 in 2010 and Fairfield County had 93,000 residents in 1980 versus 146,000 in 2010. Still not convinced; let’s look’s at the vote totals. The suburban counties that ring Columbus (Franklin County) saw them go 59-41 for Senator John McCain in 2008. This was a drop off of six percent compared to vote totals received by President George W Bush in 2004. GOP officials with access to data have assured me that internal polls show Governor Romney at least getting the percentages that President Bush won in 2004, if not higher. Let’s take a look at the Cincinnati area; in 2008 Senator McCain won the suburban counties that surround Cincinnati 63-37, again like Columbus a six percentage drop off from 2004. In 2004 President Bush won Warren County (still the second fastest growing county in the state) 72-28. In addition, President Bush won Hamilton County (Cincinnati) while Senator McCain lost Hamilton County. Again, I have been assured by those who know that Hamilton County will not go for President Obama this time. Let’s take a look at the eastern part of Ohio, coal country. With the exception of Athens County home of my alma mater Ohio University, every county is expected to be in the Romney column. Some counties like Monroe, Belmont and Jefferson have only been in the GOP column a couple of times since the inception of the Republican Party. While these are not huge vote rich areas, they certainly will help Governor Romney. Now some knowledgeable observers will say, wait a minute. What about Franklin County (Columbus) a one time GOP sure thing. Won’t that help the President’s re-election chances? True, Franklin County was once the epitome of the establishmentarian, button down Mr. Thurston Howell III GOP politics. While Franklin County only gave 40% of her vote to Senator McCain, it is growing at a much smaller rate of growth than the suburbs who ring her. So even if Governor Romney gets the same totals, he will still win the vote rich suburban counties that ring Columbus (mentioned in raw numbers above) 2-1 and then some. Franklin County reflects a growing trend in Midwest vote demographics; liberal voters, who are often single, moving into the city center (often lofts in converted old warehouses) and her near-by environs full of university and alternative lifestyle neighborhoods, areas that a few decades ago were once blight ridden but now have been gentrified. Some of these stately old homes can easily sell for hundreds of thusands of dollars. This all seems lost on many conservative oriented voters who often want larger spaces for their families. They are moving to the faster growing suburban counties that ring the county in question. Now let’s not so much look at political poll results as much as we look at sampling data in a state that is the epitome of middle of the road partisan support. Before Governor Romney’s debate performance which was nearly universally acclaimed, he trailed in the Buckeye state from anywhere between 2 and 10 points. Yet, the CBS poll which had him down nearly 10 points weighted the poll with a +10 Democratic statistical advantage. The sampling method appeared for all intents and purposes to be outrageous. Even Scott Rasmussen dubbed by many to be GOP friendly in his surveys gives Democrats a statistical advantage of sampling in a state where one could argue that Ohio is as close to parity as anyone in the nation. In addition, poll after poll shows the GOP voters more motivated to get the polls than Democratic voters. A couple more points before I conclude; the religious vote in Ohio will be very interesting. Catholics and Evangelicals who go to church regularly will go Romney 2-1, though the mainstream media will certainly concentrate on self identified Catholics who perhaps haven’t been to Mass since the Ford Administration. Catholics make up an interesting religious dynamic, while a Baptist or Methodist who hasn’t been to church in a long time will probably just identify themselves as Christian, a Catholic because of cultural identity will almost always say Catholic. This leaves us with an interesting question regarding Jewish voters. Normally, one would expect Jewish voters to vote overwhelming for President Obama, perhaps 3-1 or 4-1. However, the candidacy of 34 year old Ohio State Treasurer Josh Mandel, for the United States Senate seat currently held by US Senator Sherrod Brown may bring an interesting dynamic to the race. About 75-80% of Jewish residents in Ohio live in the greater Cleveland, Columbus and Cincinnati areas. Many in Cleveland live in the eastern areas of Solon, Shaker Heights and University Heights, while in Cincinnati many live in the Montgomery/Blue Ash area. In the Columbus area the highest numbers live in Bexley and New Albany. A Mandel victory would bring certainly launch him to the most promising GOP conservative Jewish elected official outside of Majority leader Eric Cantor. Mandel would be the biggest Jewish rising star in Ohio since the late US Senator Howard Metzenbaum. Though President Obama will certainly win the Jewish vote, his numbers may be diminished by first the candidacy of Treasurer Mandel, and secondly the controversial Middle East policy of President Obama who has hardly had what anyone would call a cozy relationship with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. Any drop in the Jewish vote for President Obama will not help his cause in Ohio. Finally, these Ohio demographics of industrial Democratic areas losing voters, while suburban areas are gaining GOP voters are not unique to Ohio. They are indicative of the entire Midwest. One only needs to look at the tremendous loss of population in Detroit. The city has lost 250,000 residents just from 2000-2010. It is now smaller than Columbus. Again like Northeast Ohio, many of those residents left the state. Governor Romney, who was born in Michigan and whose father casts a long positive shadow in the state, may not be behind as much as the polls indicate. He certainly will do much better in the Detroit suburbs than did Senator McCain. I will leave that analysis up for someone in the state up north to extrapolate. Now anything can happen from today until election day, bad debate performances (though that seems a little less likely after the first debate) or some sort of scandal. However, using the data I have outlined, it is easy to see that not only will Ohio go for Governor Romney, but so could a host of upper Midwest states.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349662966325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:22:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663125797-199</Id><Topic><Title>Bible study for socialist dem.</Title><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349656943864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 20:42:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3) Black Horse represents Capitalism the official color of Capitalism is Black,when a company reports a profit they call it being in the Black.How about Friday after Thanksgiving start of Xmas shopping the biggest shopping day of the year,BLACK FRIDAY, . before me was a black horse! Its rider was holding a pair of scales in his hand,saying, ‘A quart of wheat for a day's wages, and three quarts of barley for a day's wages, and do not damage the oil and the wine!’” describes commerce, measurement balance scales,products &amp; prices. NO WEAPONS 4)Pale Green Horse represents Islam the official color of Islam is Green I looked, and there before me was a pale green horse! Its rider was named Death, and Hell was following close behind him. They were given power over a fourth of the earth to kill by sword, famine and plague. "death rides the horse" Islam glorifies death that's why they have no problem recruiting suicide bombers. Fourth of world population believe in Islam. Most Islamic countries are poor</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1349663125797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663272694-200</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbuummpppp</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349663272694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:27:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663387797-201</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup full of Crap now that Obama spanked him in private</Title><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1347759594305</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 21:39:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbuummppp</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349663387797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663417999-202</Id><Topic><Title>Unskewed Polling ; Polling without dem biased weighting</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349642054578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bbuummmppp</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349663417999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:30:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663513480-203</Id><Topic><Title>Why Romney will win Ohio</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349662966325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:22:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Romney wins Ohio and Florida say bye to the Zebradouche and the Moochedouche</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349663513480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663621806-204</Id><Topic><Title>U. of Colorado poll update predicts Romney 330 electoral votes to 208 for Obama</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349618870652</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 10:07:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Winning Ohio is key to 330 electoral votes for Romney</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349663621806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349663862971-205</Id><Topic><Title>Why Romney will win Ohio</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349662966325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:22:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol. Rhonda, you are delusional. Ohio is Obamas by 3. Watch and learn. What do you know about Catholics? Lol.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349663862971</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664068455-206</Id><Topic><Title>Unskewed Polling ; Polling without dem biased weighting</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1349642054578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 16:34:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol. You are off your meds? Lol.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349664068455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664467801-207</Id><Topic><Title>Challenger Gray and Christmas LAYING OFF 352,200 WORKERS in 2012 while Obama brags about recovery</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349648192179</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Challenger Gray LAYING OFF 352,000 workers in 2012. This dont sound like a economic recovery to me.</Msg><Username>high_falutin_heifers</Username><Timestamp>1349664467801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349664505604-208</Id><Title>Obama has already won. the data only gets better.</Title><Msg>Four more years of misery for Repubs. but Americans, we must rid the House of these teabag #$%$. Long live the coffee drinkers.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349664505604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:48:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664529444-209</Id><Topic><Title>HP LAYING OFF 27,000 WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS ABOUT A RECOVERY</Title><Username>kenya_bolshevik_from_chicago</Username><Timestamp>1349647168006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 17:59:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HP LAYING OFF 27, 000 WORKERS does not sound like an economic recovery to me.</Msg><Username>high_falutin_heifers</Username><Timestamp>1349664529444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664597991-210</Id><Topic><Title>BEST BUY LAYING OFF 2800 INCLUDING 600 GEEK SQUAD WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS THAT WE ARE IN A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647595943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BEST BUY LAYING OFF 28000 WORKERS does not sound like an economic recovery to me.</Msg><Username>high_falutin_heifers</Username><Timestamp>1349664597991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:49:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1349664778137-211</Id><Topic><Title>BEST BUY LAYING OFF 2800 INCLUDING 600 GEEK SQUAD WORKERS WHILE OBAMA BRAGS THAT WE ARE IN A RECOVERY</Title><Username>obama_a_foreign_policy_failure</Username><Timestamp>1349647595943</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 18:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you are cheering? Sad sad Repub. Go get a job and stop collecting welfare. Lol.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1349664778137</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 22:52:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1349665369826-212</Id><Title>OBAMA, PELOSI AND REID CONTROLLED EVERYTHING FOR 2 YEARS</Title><Msg>OBAMA, PELOSI AND REID CONTROLLED EVERYTHING FOR 2 YEARS yet they want to blame GOP for their failures.</Msg><Username>high_falutin_heifers</Username><Timestamp>1349665369826</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-10-07 23:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>