<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-06"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346904450907-1</Id><Title>TONIGHT ON TV IS CLINTON SPREAD HIS BUTTOCKS OPEN FOR OBAMA!</Title><Msg>and after that he got on his knees and shamelessly deepthroated Oby! LOLOLOLOL And when he was done talking his kissed Oby's #$%$ LOLOL</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346904450907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:07:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346904871789-2</Id><Title>BILL CLINTON FKED clayveuss/deepscrotum SO HARD...</Title><Msg>The inbreeds had to rush to the keyboard.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346904871789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:14:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346905602858-3</Id><Topic><Title>NOTHING LIKE HAVING A WORTHLESS POS LOSER LIKE CLINTON ADDRESS</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903812427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just thought Clinton made Obama look like an amateur, Clinton still doesn't need a teleprompter. Clinton is old and probably even a case of Viagra can't get little Billy up any more, but Clinton sure showed Barry that He couldn't get Clinton Coffee like Bill once said. Bill kept Barry waiting an extra 20 minutes with his long winded speech. Clinton and the Republican congress under Newt balanced the budget and ended welfare without work. Obama added 5 trillion dollars instead of balancing a budget. Obama never even tried to work with the GOP. As a result we haven't had a budget for 3 years and it shows in Obama's failure. Clinton may have been a degenerate but he didn't have 23 million unemployed Americans, and college kids the graduate and can't find a job. Welfare has been set back to the pre Clinton days where you could just sit on the couch and watch tv all day drinking beer. I don't think even Clinton if he wanted to help Obama could, but Clinton hates Obama so tonights speech just showed Obama up. I bet most Dems wish Clinton was running instead of Obama.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346905602858</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:26:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346906011047-4</Id><Topic><Title>DNC puts Jerusalem back in platform</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346884880830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 18:41:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will bet you that Obama won't get anywhere near 75% of the Jooish vote he got last time. First I don't think they will go to the polls , they won't vote for Romney, but they won't vote for Obama either. This could cost Obama a couple of states. Also, some younger Joos will vote for GOP for the first time. The biggest thing is that the DNC gets 60% of their donations from Joos, that will shrink after today.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346906011047</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:33:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346906152847-5</Id><Topic><Title>BILL CLINTON FKED clayveuss/deepscrotum SO HARD...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346904871789</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:14:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sixty-nine percent approval rating,* baaaaaby! Just like Clinton to give Lady Liberty some sweet lovin' with the ol' soixante-neuf, too. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL :P ------ *Or put another way, twenty-three times higher approval rating than RepubliCONs currently have in Congress.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346906152847</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:35:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346908155693-6</Id><Title>Dem Convention Delegates Made Up Of Nothing but a BUNCH of</Title><Msg>sandnegars and touwelhead mooslims. Pathetic and slick kissed all of their anuses tonight and licked their sacks.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346908155693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 01:09:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346908370748-7</Id><Topic><Title>NOTHING LIKE HAVING A WORTHLESS POS LOSER LIKE CLINTON ADDRESS</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903812427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton is a joke, all he did was #$%$ people, that's all he has ever done, and lie his #$%$ off</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346908370748</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 01:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346908924473-8</Id><Title>SAD CRAP CON-VENTION FULL OF EMPTY SEATS! AND THAT</Title><Msg>AFTER they moved it indoors based on the lame excuse "it migjht rain though!" LOL What a bunch of ball-less #$%$ ALMOST NO ONE IS THERE!! Shades of things to come election day!</Msg><Username>drive1973honda</Username><Timestamp>1346908924473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 01:22:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346929784673-9</Id><Title>the only arithmetic clinton knows is 69 with monica</Title><Msg>ask hilary, she'll tell you about bill and his respect for women</Msg><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1346929784673</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346930012700-10</Id><Title>Great speeches by Clinton and Michelle Obama</Title><Msg>Obama has already won...</Msg><Username>cadmium_nitrate</Username><Timestamp>1346930012700</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:13:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346930175713-11</Id><Title>clinton only reaped buget surplus because of Reagan/Bush ending Soviet Union, which ended hundreds of billions in spending</Title><Msg>Thank you Reagan/Bush for ending the Soviet Union threat for many years, which now, under obama, is rising again through Russia and Putin's hate of obama.</Msg><Username>uvbenfard</Username><Timestamp>1346930175713</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346930903678-12</Id><Title>REPUBS SAY: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Title><Msg>This is the PATHETIC REPUBLICAN ECONOMIC ARGUMENT to chose ROMNEY/RYAN: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346930903678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346931068405-13</Id><Topic><Title>GOPERS say the DNC convention isn't enthusiastic LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346895732923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 21:42:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Chris Wallace saying the DNC sounds FLAT- no enthusiasm BHWAAA!!!! FOX NEWS- LIES THEIR BUTT OFF !!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346931068405</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346931325810-14</Id><Title>GOP convention BORING all attendees were silver-haired white folks.</Title><Msg>Are there NO minorities that are Republicans ? Jeesh...</Msg><Username>tracker57888</Username><Timestamp>1346931325810</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346932096442-15</Id><Title>GOP voters are so negative,,glad Im not one !!!! Self centered,,,followedrs,,, me,,,me = sad bunch</Title><Msg>THINKING would help GOP voters so much..</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1346932096442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:48:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346932354023-16</Id><Topic><Title>European Stocks Could Correct Up to 20%: Faber</Title><Username>buffet_graham</Username><Timestamp>1346925593469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 05:59:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>20% ?? ROFLOL More like 80%. Now is best period in world history to sell stocks, bonds , other so-called financial assets. Finance capitalism (debt capitalism) is dead. What will emerge will not be the grow-by-debt model of the last 40 years. The current model is structurally flawed. Impossible to "grow way out" of this debt with tax cuts. Only default, liquidation will solve the problem.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1346932354023</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:52:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346932608181-17</Id><Title>GOP wants a WINNER TAKE ALL AMERICA- THE RICHEST THRIVE</Title><Msg>THE POOR &amp; MIDDLE CLASS are left the crumbs!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346932608181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346934112848-18</Id><Title>Bush will never be able to leave the country</Title><Msg>without being arrested, history will judge him as a war criminal on par with Hitler and Stalin CAIRO -- Human Rights Watch said it has uncovered evidence of a wider use of waterboarding in American interrogations of detainees than has been acknowledged by the United States, in a report Thursday that details further brutal treatment at secret CIA-run prisons under the Bush administration-era U.S. program of detention and rendition of terror suspects. The report also paints a more complete picture of Washington's close cooperation with the regime of Libya's former dictator Moammar Gadhafi in the wake of the 9/11 attacks. The U.S. handed over to Libya the Islamist opponents of Gadhafi that it detained abroad with only thin "diplomatic assurances" that they would not be mistreated, and several of them were subsequently tortured in prison, Human Rights Watch said. The 154-page report features interviews by the New York-based group with 14 Libyan dissident exiles. They describe systematic abuses while they were held in U.S.-led detention centers in Afghanistan -- some as long as two years -- or in U.S.-led interrogations in Pakistan, Morocco, Thailand, Sudan and elsewhere before the Americans handed them over to Libya. "Not only did the U.S. deliver (Gadhafi) his enemies on a silver platter, but it seems the CIA tortured many of them first, said Laura Pitter, counterterrorism adviser at Human Rights Watch and author of the report. "The scope of the Bush administration abuse appears far broader than previously acknowledged," she said.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934112848</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346934445763-19</Id><Title>no bounce</Title><Msg>In short, Romney is the only nominee since at least 1988 who, after three straight days of balloons, banners, and fawning speeches on primetime TV, couldn’t manage to convince more voters to like him than dislike him.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934445763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346934977332-20</Id><Title>tomorrow will be</Title><Msg>the 30th month in a row of private job sector growth, why would we want to go back to Bush's policies where we were losing 750,000 jobs a month?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934977332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:36:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346935866283-21</Id><Title>GDOT upgraded from Neutral to Overweight, Sell CSCO &amp; Buy GDOT</Title><Msg>Yesterday (09/05) Piper Jaffray upgraded GDOT from Neutral to Overweight Is it worth hanging on to CSCO with a PE of 9.84 and PEG ratio of 1.25? Won't it be wise for small to medium investors to sell CSCO and buy GDOT whose P/E is 8.46 and PEG ratio is just about 0.40 ... The 09/05 upgrade of GDOT by Piper Jaffray from Neutral to Overweight could just be the beginning of a monster run up ... Could GDOT be closing above $20/share or above $25/share by end of this year ...</Msg><Username>delphioracle2009</Username><Timestamp>1346935866283</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346936339539-22</Id><Topic><Title>tomorrow will be</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934977332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GW bush added NET millions in jobs. GW Bush averaged 5.3% over 8 years. You and your ilk friends keep cherry picking your data or LYING about it. You WISH you had as good a record as Bush. LMMFAO Your Messiah has NET lost jobs over 3 1/2 years, he has 44 straight months of UE above 8%, the longest since the great depression. The sad thing is that you libTURDS are proud of that. 48 million people on food stamps. Poverty level higher than when he took office. Hundreds of thousands who lost their homes. Hate and Division throughout the country. 700k fewer women working. " oopsie " You go ahead and keep running on your record skippy, WE love it. SHELLACKING 2.0 coming this November. Catch it.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346936339539</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:58:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346936667099-23</Id><Title>Sandra Fluke: The DemoCRAP answer to the countries problems. LMMFAO</Title><Msg>This lifetime student stood up and whined about her lot in life and then LECTURED Americans on how they should be paying for her birth control. What a pathetic excuse for a human being. whine whine whine, gimme gimme gimme........ I hope this isn't what you libTURDS really stand for. She is a JOKE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346936667099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:04:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346937089330-24</Id><Title>Nancy Pelosi is not a DIVIDER....... REALLY</Title><Msg>In Pelosi's speech last night she claimed Republicans don't care about kids, they don't care about seniors, and all they care about are the top 1%. Now tell us AGAIN how the far left is not trying to divide the country. Such pathetic and hateful rhetoric. Seems the far left can't help themselves with their hatespeak.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346937089330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:11:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346937722289-25</Id><Title>POST HIDDEN because you ignored this user</Title><Msg>Go peddle your garbage somewhere else 30 different magoo's, I can't see your ignorance. bye bye skippy.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346937722289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:22:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346937788625-26</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBS SAY: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346930903678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IN A NUT SHELL, THAT'S WHAT IT IS!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346937788625</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:23:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346937973944-27</Id><Title>DOes Mario the Dragon fix things today?????</Title><Msg>Will the Euro be saved</Msg><Username>jimtalkner</Username><Timestamp>1346937973944</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:26:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346938549015-28</Id><Topic><Title>tomorrow will be</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934977332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But dad I don't know why your angry at me, I was driving really well before I got drunk, drove at 100 mph and drove the car off the road!! I should be judged on how I left the driveway not how I left the road!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346938549015</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346938679358-29</Id><Topic><Title>POST HIDDEN because you ignored this user</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346937722289</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:22:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf,dumdum,junior,webber,virtualghost, ad nauseum .The fake ids by Magoo are endless and all stupid. Why would anyone enjoy the derision he gets here??? He must be one lonely dude.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346938679358</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346939294114-30</Id><Topic><Title>tomorrow will be</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346934977332</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 08:36:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats and Obumbles were in control of congress for Bush's last 2 years. WHY do you far left extremists leave that little factoid out? You people don't care about the facts all you care about is politics. Party before country, the libTURD way.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346939294114</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:48:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346940086485-31</Id><Topic><Title>“This will be the moment that probably re-elected Barack Obama. Bill Clinton saved the Democratic Party once, it was going to far left, he came in, the new democrats took it to the center. He did it again tonight.”</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1346939521244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny..you are using the same style to post as virtualgh0st has been doing.LOLOLOLOL Magoo is one dumb dude.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346940086485</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346940333547-32</Id><Topic><Title>“This will be the moment that probably re-elected Barack Obama. Bill Clinton saved the Democratic Party once, it was going to far left, he came in, the new democrats took it to the center. He did it again tonight.”</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1346939521244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Check out last weekend . All Magoo did on Labor Day weekend was sit there by himself posting under his phony ids . What a boring and lonely holiday that is.Pathetic. A total loser!</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346940333547</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:05:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346940416080-33</Id><Title>Enough is enough</Title><Msg>Just open our cotton pick'n -- oil wells, coal mines and let American's get back to work, the rest will work out! Lot's of stupid pecker-woods in this world - mostly tree huggers!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346940416080</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:06:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346940440658-34</Id><Title>Market short squeeze on Europe</Title><Msg>Selling 1/3 into the run. This is just some sugar, reality will come back tomorrow or next week. Take some profits.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346940440658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:07:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346941084622-35</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHERE ARE OBIMBO'S COLLEGE TRANSCRIPTS?? They are hidden, not just because his grades are inferior, but because he is enrolled as an Indoneisan national, a citizen of Indonesia....just a minor 'oops' for a President. Demonstrates clearly how much of a liar he is. SHOW US THE TRANSCRIPTS!!! Redact the grades....just show us the data!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346941084622</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:18:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346941386958-36</Id><Title>Are they better off today ??</Title><Msg>Report out says 17 million Americans either go hungry or miss one meal a day because of being poor. Lets hear Magoo brag about the stock market being up.LOL</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346941386958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:23:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346941392812-37</Id><Title>OBAMA RALLY...THANKS B.C.</Title><Msg>Bill Clinton dismantle every bit of lies the repukes have manufactured for the last 4 years. Market likes another 4 years of Obama. Hell the market loves Obama. Up more than 100%</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346941392812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346941581370-38</Id><Topic><Title>Dem Convention Delegates Made Up Of Nothing but a BUNCH of</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346908155693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 01:09:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep! and they hate God and Israel too, last nights vote showed that</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346941581370</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:26:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346941733095-39</Id><Topic><Title>NOTHING LIKE HAVING A WORTHLESS POS LOSER LIKE CLINTON ADDRESS</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903812427</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:56:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what!??? you mean we can't believe a rapist and known liar like clinton who lied under oath to a grand jury?!! "I did not have sex with that woman!" LOL</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346941733095</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:28:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942000938-40</Id><Title>WITH ALL THE EMPTY SEATS AT THE DENSEOCRAP CONVENTION, IS AMERICA</Title><Msg>saying they agree with Eastwood's "Empty chair" routine exposing the empty suit obama??? OH WE THINK SO! LOL</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346942000938</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942052765-41</Id><Topic><Title>TONIGHT ON TV IS CLINTON SPREAD HIS BUTTOCKS OPEN FOR OBAMA!</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346904450907</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 00:07:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw it happen!</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1346942052765</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942192151-42</Id><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Msg>and here is why. BOOM BOOM BOOM POW ! He dismantled the puppet limb by limb !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942216732-43</Id><Title>Billy #$%$ Clinton</Title><Msg>He sure is #$%$ but he talks pretty so I should worship him. Goo goo. Idiots idolize #$%$s because they can give a good speech. Hahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942216732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942317467-44</Id><Title>Billy says so it must be true.</Title><Msg>Hahahahahahahaha idiots.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942317467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:38:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942328213-45</Id><Topic><Title>Billy #$%$ Clinton</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942216732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Excellent speech... Bulletproof! bill just helped re-elect obama!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346942328213</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942365729-46</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Egads! Are they all atheists in the dem party!!!??? Evidently!!</Msg><Username>thefirstmagoo</Username><Timestamp>1346942365729</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:39:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942366540-47</Id><Title>CLINTON TO REPUKES "ARITHMETIC #$%$</Title><Msg>Arithmetic ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942366540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:39:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942391639-48</Id><Topic><Title>“This will be the moment that probably re-elected Barack Obama. Bill Clinton saved the Democratic Party once, it was going to far left, he came in, the new democrats took it to the center. He did it again tonight.”</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1346939521244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:52:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and you're too stupid to know that magoo is only magoo and not the other dem posters here! HAR HAR HAR!!! there's a whole lot of stupid in you!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346942391639</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942408823-49</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBS SAY: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346930903678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BILL NAILED IT!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346942408823</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:40:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942449683-50</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON TO REPUKES "ARITHMETIC #$%$</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942366540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:39:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>like deadpainting's spelling, it doesn't work! LOL!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346942449683</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:40:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942574244-51</Id><Topic><Title>Billy #$%$ Clinton</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942216732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was a good speech. And Clinton was a good president (his morals aside). Should have been embarrassing for the incompetent Obama to have Clinton try to save his presidency for him.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346942574244</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:42:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942634510-52</Id><Topic><Title>Billy #$%$ Clinton</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942216732</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES, MUCH BETTER THAN CLINT EASTWOOD'S babble, or PAUL RYAN's LIES debunked by BILL!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346942634510</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:43:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346942725323-53</Id><Title>LAST NIGHT THE DEMS Gave tribute to Womanizer and Murdering swimmer Ted Kennedy AND</Title><Msg>had known rapist of FIVE DEM women Bill Clinton address them! Anyone wonder where their party stands on how they view women!! LMAO</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1346942725323</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:45:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942891704-54</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, we don't pray for solutions, we work on solutions. And this is not the United States of Israel. Schooled !!! Next #$%$ in line !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942891704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:48:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346942989121-55</Id><Topic><Title>LAST NIGHT THE DEMS Gave tribute to Womanizer and Murdering swimmer Ted Kennedy AND</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1346942725323</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill loves women, you fhagg ! He doesn't hang around airport bathrooms toe tapping ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942989121</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:49:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943044853-56</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBS SAY: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346930903678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so true, Bush was losing 750,000 jobs a month 4.5 million in his last 6 months in office, fastest job losses in history and the pinheads want to go back to those policies, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346943044853</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943288469-57</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if Obama gets a 1% bounce it's more then Mitt got, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346943288469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:54:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346943648022-58</Id><Title>era of hyper inflation starting</Title><Msg>Gold oil soaring on news of unlimited money printing. $6 a gallon gasoline by year end.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1346943648022</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346943711239-59</Id><Title>ROMNEY "JOB CREATOR"...</Title><Msg>In 1992, Bain acquired Ampad, the American Pad &amp; Paper Co. Employing hundreds of workers, the company was profitable when Bain took over. Bain was able to borrow $400 million against the company, a debt burden Ampad could not repay. By 2001, Ampad was forced to close its doors, their stockholders were wiped out and workers were jobless — but Bain made $100 million on an initial investment of $5 million. Perhaps Ampad could have been saved if Bain had pumped some of its excessive profit back into the company. While Romney may not have been at the helm of Bain when Ampad went under, Romney carries some responsibility for the destruction of those American jobs. According to the Los Angeles Times, "Sometimes Bain investors gained even when companies slid into bankruptcy." Apparently, Romney sees nothing wrong with this version of capitalsm. Voters, however, may interpret this as a permutation of capitalism, another example of the 1 percent rigging the system for their own profit at the expense of workers. Considering his background at Bain, it's harder for Romney to make the case that he cares about average Americans.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943711239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943756977-60</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>80% of the country believe in GOD....... Do you practice stupidity or does it come natural?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346943756977</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:02:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943778980-61</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He is right. Republicans wrecked it, and since the Dems could not fix it in three years, they think that we should give it back to the??? I don't think so!!!</Msg><Username>gman310</Username><Timestamp>1346943778980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:02:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943926937-62</Id><Topic><Title>LAST NIGHT THE DEMS Gave tribute to Womanizer and Murdering swimmer Ted Kennedy AND</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1346942725323</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton was a RAPIST and a LIAR. You people are proud of that. Clinton is the libTURD hero. YUP</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346943926937</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346943972889-63</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>90% of Germans believed in Hitler ! 80% is basically the number of mhorons/mediocre people in a society. So why are you taking the mhoron's side ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943972889</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:06:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346944005764-64</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY "JOB CREATOR"...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943711239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney: Job CREMATOR.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346944005764</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346944877237-65</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY "JOB CREATOR"...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943711239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>those employees are on food stamps now and Mitt is blaming Obama</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346944877237</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346945715520-66</Id><Title>29 MILLION AMERICANS OUT OF WORK...ALL OF THEM BLAME OBIMBO!!! ROMNEY WILL</Title><Msg>put them all back to work. Romnew can do it, Obimbo is a joke. HE NEVER HAD A REAL JOB IN HIS LIFE AND NEVER, NOT ONCE, ever, CREATED JOBS FOR SIX OTHER PEOPLE, MUCH LESS 30 MILLION WHO NEED JOBS WHEN ROMNEY TAKES OVER!!! Whoooooooo Raaaaaaaaaayyyyy!!!!! for the TEA PARTY...AMERICA'S HOPE FOR CHANGE!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346945715520</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346945877264-67</Id><Title>POST CONVENTION 'BUMP'? or post conventions SLUMP????</Title><Msg>I'm votin' for the SLUMP, since watching the Gay Old Party, the Democrats, they just seem so out of touch with family oriented Latin Americans, and black Americans who actually have not destroyed their brains with malt liquor and crack and are NOT felons, will be voting for Romney, because of the Democratic party's support of GAY MARRIAGE, further isolates them from main stream Americans!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346945877264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346945927831-68</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obimbo is an Indonesian...it say's so on his college transcript...LET'S SEE IT!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346945927831</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946054084-69</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY "JOB CREATOR"...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943711239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Asking, ‘Are You Better Off?’ In August of 2008, America lost 592,000 jobs. Osama bin Laden was alive. The Iraq War seemed endless. And apparently the GOP wants to remind us of this by constantly asking Ronald Reagan’s classic question “Are you better off now?” They can cherry pick statistics that make their case. But find me one American who wants to go back to the shock of the financial crisis and fear that came from knowing the same incompetent guys who planned the Iraq War were now dealing with a global economic meltdown. That we ever stopped losing jobs is a miracle.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346946054084</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:40:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946065076-70</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can tell you are an extreme far left libTURD. You don't seem to grasp of the concept of a majority. AND NO, 90% of the German people didn't believe in Hitler. Gawd you are an ignorant redneck.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346946065076</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346946075103-71</Id><Title>ALL SLUMP, NO BUMB FOR THE OBIMBO!!! he deserves it! A PRESIDENT WITHOUT A BUDGET FOR 3 YEARS?</Title><Msg>unheard of !!! Never has happened in history...what's wrong with the Democratic party? The entire Senate voted down Obimbo's last budget proposal...the goober can't even get Democrats on board... Same reason they abandoned the stadium...just too derned embarrassing BUT IT'S MORE EMBARRASSING FOR US!!! AMERICANS!!!! TIME TO TOSS THE OREO OUT!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346946075103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:41:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946248134-72</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You loons are HILARIOUS today. Did you expect Clinton to praise Romney/Ryan??His task was to try to save Obama's lousy presidency. And as usual he gave a very good speech. Clinton is a master politician regardless of his other failings.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346946248134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:44:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346946363147-73</Id><Title>CSCO Rise Is Crushing Republican Shorties Caves</Title><Msg>Republican anti-American shorties hide in terrorist caves of Cayman and Swiss bank accounts.</Msg><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1346946363147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:46:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946526371-74</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whose GOD are you talking about? There is a force beyond man.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1346946526371</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:48:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946537540-75</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY "JOB CREATOR"...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346943711239</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:01:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like I have to put your LYING backside in order AGAIN. Bain did acquire Ampad in 1992, the business grew for the following 4 years that Bain controlled the company. Bains control ended in 1996 FOUR FULL years before AMpad met financial difficulties from overwhelming pressure from the big box retailers. Once AGAIN you LYING far left extremists leave out all the facts. Schooled once again BOYsurfer. I'm laughing at you, BOY.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346946537540</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346946790870-76</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>//[A]theists may not report themselves as such, to prevent suffering from social stigma, discrimination, and persecution[.] ... Because some governments have strongly promoted atheism and others have strongly condemned it, atheism may be either over-reported or under-reported for different countries.// - Wikipedia, Demographics of Atheism CASE IN POINT: I've been agnostic (tending toward atheism) since I was 14 or 15, but having grown up in the Bible Belt, did not openly profess this until I entered university. //Statistics on atheism are often difficult to represent accurately for a variety of reasons. Atheism is a position compatible with other forms of identity. Some atheists also consider themselves Agnostic, Buddhist, Hindu, Jains, Taoist, or hold other related philosophical beliefs [Ed. note - e.g. deism, pantheism, panentheism, pandeism, demiurgic Neoplatonism, etc.]. Therefore, given limited poll options, some may use other terms to describe their identity.// - Wikipedia, Demographics of Atheism EXAMPLES: By the standards of the dominant American religion, Christianity, MANY of the deist founding fathers themselves could have been considered atheists, though they certainly did not see themselves in this way. Likewise, Einstein's professed belief in A God (to wit, "the God of Spinoza") would be considered by many theists, Christians included, as little more than wordplay, defining away THEIR concept of God entirely. Yet all these individuals professed a belief in deity, thus would have been included within your "80%" number.* ------------------- *BTW, that self-reported number seems still to be falling.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346946790870</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:53:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346947064351-77</Id><Topic><Title>Market short squeeze on Europe</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346940440658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just sold 1/3 of my Cisco portfolio. Nice little profit. Will wait for the market to decide that Europe is in trouble again and buy the dip. If we continue north I will sell the next 1/3. Bulls make money, bears make money, PIGS get slaughtered.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346947064351</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:57:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346947291157-78</Id><Topic><Title>THE DIM MOTION TO RECOGNIZE GOD AND ISRAEL VOICE VOTE FAILED</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346903224865</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 23:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>//AND NO, 90% of the German people didn't believe in Hitler. // 80%, then?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346947291157</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346947561704-79</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Rise Is Crushing Republican Shorties Caves</Title><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1346946363147</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:46:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Strong Balance Sheet Sets Cisco Up For Success September 6, 2012 by: Efsinvestment | about: CSCO, includes: BAC, FNSR, JNPR Edited by Adam Isaac Cisco Systems (CSCO) designs, produces and sells Internet Protocol-based networking and other products associated with the communications and information technology industry. It also offers services related to these products. The company offers a wide range of products for transporting, voice, data and video inside buildings, across campuses, and around the world. Cisco carries out its business globally and is run in four segments: United States and Canada, Europe, Emerging Markets, and Asia Pacific. The Emerging Markets section is made up of Latin America, Eastern Europe, Africa and the Middle East, and Russia and the Commonwealth of Independent States. Cisco Systems, Inc was incorporated in California in December 1984, and its headquarters are in San Jose, California. In May 2011, Cisco announced its plan to realign its services, sales and engineering organizations to simplify its operating model and focus on five priorities, which include collaboration, video, data center visualization and cloud, leadership in its core business and architectures for business transformation. The firm expects to complete the transformation by the end of year 2012. These changes will streamline the operations of the company and give it a clear focus. In my previous article about the company, I predicted a rise in the stock price and since then, the stock has gained about 16% in value. In this article, I look at the financial strength of the company and analyze in detail the debt and cash flows. Free Cash Flows: Free Cash Flows 2011 2010 2009 Net Income $6,490 $7,767 $6,134 Depreciation and Amortization $2,486 $2,030 $1,768 Funds from Operations (FFO) $8,976 $9,797 $7,902 change in noncash current assets $2,884 $2,965 $1,985 change in noncash current liabilities $1,820 $2,136 $1,786 Operating Cash flows $7,912 $8,968 $7,703 Capital Expenditures $1,440 $6,287 $1,431 Free Operating Cash Flow $6,472 $2,681 $6,272 Long Term Debt $16,234 $12,188 $10,295 Figures taken from SEC filings As it is evident from the table above, Cisco has strong free operating cash flows. According to the most recent earnings report, the firm has more than $10 billion in cash. Moreover, total cash and cash equivalents including investments stood at $48.4 billion; this represents an increase of almost $2 billion from the same quarter last year. Cisco has incredibly strong funds from operations, and the situation looks even more stable in the future. Meanwhile, Cisco has been increasing its noncash current assets and decreasing its noncash current liabilities. Cisco owes its improving cash flow position to a better inventory and credit policy management. The firm has been able to decrease DSO to 31 days form 37 days, as a result, the firm has been able to decrease its accounts receivable and increase the cash collections. During the last year, the firm has been able to improve the accounts receivable position by more than $300 million. On the other hand, the company has been able to shave off some of the short term liabilities. Short term debt went down by almost $2.5 billion and accounts payable decreased by $19 million. A small decrease in accounts payable as compared to a substantial decrease in accounts receivable indicates the firm is managing the assets efficiently. In the meantime, Cisco has also been active in the acquisitions front and has made significant acquisitions in the previous two years. Cisco has the highest amount of capital expenditure in the year 2010, amounting to more than $6 billion.</Msg><Username>scovey2</Username><Timestamp>1346947561704</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346947705921-80</Id><Title>Sad fact is, not one republican at the RNC could not point to GWB 's two terms as president as an example of how good the economy was!</Title><Msg>Sad fact is, not one republican at the RNC could not point to GWB 's two terms as president as an example of how good the economy was! they just have the wetbrains who believe that it is obamas fault bush crashed the economy lololool</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947705921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346947738950-81</Id><Title>Clinton'sspeech.</Title><Msg>DickMorris critiqued Clinton's speech .You loons should go to his site and listen.You wont like it. LOL</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346947738950</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346947787134-82</Id><Title>Elizabeth Warren quoted from the BIBLE during the DNC; during the GODLESS RNC, no one did!</Title><Msg>EGADS!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947787134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346947828875-83</Id><Topic><Title>Sad fact is, not one republican at the RNC could not point to GWB 's two terms as president as an example of how good the economy was!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947705921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound just like Junior..LOL you phony.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346947828875</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346948088532-84</Id><Topic><Title>Sad fact is, not one republican at the RNC could not point to GWB 's two terms as president as an example of how good the economy was!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947705921</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:08:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice comeback potsy !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346948088532</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:14:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346948173963-85</Id><Topic><Title>Market short squeeze on Europe</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346940440658</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:07:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny to see SurfMagoo give Obama credit for todays market. It's mostly due to Europe and some not quite so bad economic news here. Magoo has the i.q. of a turnip.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346948173963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346948656045-86</Id><Topic><Title>Billy says so it must be true.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942317467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill also said " I did not have sex with that woman,Monica Lewinsky. " But his weener and that cigar did.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346948656045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:24:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346948810518-87</Id><Topic><Title>Billy says so it must be true.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942317467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you do like talking about his "weener &amp; cigar", eh?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346948810518</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346948879814-88</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBS SAY: We left him a total mess, he hasn’t cleaned it up fast enough, so fire him and put us back in.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346930903678</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 07:28:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BILL PUTS BARACK over the top !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346948879814</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346949081346-89</Id><Title>Putin: Obama ‘An Honest Person’ - wonder how he feels about ROMNEY? BHWAA!!!</Title><Msg>Putin: Obama ‘An Honest Person’ Russian President Vladimir Putin called President Obama an "honest man who really wants to change much for the better" in an interview Thursday. Putin told RT television that Mitt Romney's criticism of Russia is "mistaken," according to Reuters. as colin powell said of mitt and his advisers when he wondered what Romney was thinking when he heard that Romney had declared that Russia was the top geopolitical foe of the United States: “C’mon, Mitt, think.” he made clear he is concerned about what he called the positions of some of Romney’s foreign policy advisers AKA BUSH RETREADS “Some of them are quite far to the right, and sometimes they, I think, might be in a position to make judgments or recommendations to the candidate that should get a second thought”</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949081346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:31:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346949087606-90</Id><Topic><Title>Billy says so it must be true.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1346942317467</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:38:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo,you'd love for Bill to stick his "cigar 'in your pooper or throat. Obvious you are a #$%$</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346949087606</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346949384852-91</Id><Topic><Title>Putin: Obama ‘An Honest Person’ - wonder how he feels about ROMNEY? BHWAA!!!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949081346</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:31:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WOW!!!! Putin likes him . If Castro and Hugo Chavez voice support, Magoo will be ecstatic.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346949384852</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:36:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346949495672-92</Id><Title>NTWK $4.8...UP!!... RECORD 4Q and FY 2012.....GUIDES FOR $1/SHARE NET AND 30%+ REVENUE GROWTH IN 2013</Title><Msg>No1 GLOBAL CLOUD/LICENSE SOFTWARE PROVIDER FOR LEASING AND FINANCING APPLICATIONS...............3M SHARE FLOAT TARGET $10+ ............ANALYST AVERAGE TARGET: $16 .............MAX: $21 ===== 9/4/2012 NTWK REPORTED RECORD 4Q AND FULL YEAR RESULTS - Fourth Quarter 2012 Revenue Surges to an all-time quarterly record of $14.3 Million on Increased License Revenues and associated maintenance and service agreements going forward - Fourth Quarter 2012 Earnings Advance Significantly to $0.25 per Diluted Share - Full Year 2012 revenues a record $38M - Full Year 2012 Earnings of $0.39/share - Company Expects Record Fiscal 2013 Annual Revenue Growing over 30% to $46 million to $49 million, With Earnings per Diluted Share Advancing to $0.80 to $1.00 - Per the CC, Company anticipates doubling revenues and net income by 2015 ==== NTWK HIGHLIGHTS: - Fast growing profitable US-based global cloud and license-based software company with 8 offices worldwide (US, China, Australia, UK, Pakistan, Singapore, Thailand, Saudi Arabia) – - Trading at 5 PE and 1 times sales – This is about 25% of sector average - Revenues are increasing at double digit rates, - Guidance calls for 30% revenue growth in 2013 - 3 consecutive quarters of profitability, - Guidance calls for $1/share net income in 2013!!! - Global alliances with Mercedes Benz and SANY Corp of China. - No. 1 in China and the APAC region in its niche market of leasing and financing software - It’s Vroozi Division is a fast growing Cloud Computing Play with strong relations with SAP, ORCL, MSFT. - Vroozi’s SAP-approved smartOCI procurement search catalog software built on SaaS is being adopted rapidly. Revenues exploded in 4Q 2012 and are expected to multiply in 2013 and a big reason for the 30%+ 2013 projected revenue increase - Vroozi has been created as independent entity to potentially IPO it or sell it to a cloud-acquiring giant like SAP and others - Strong balance sheet with $1/share Cash - With every license they sell a lucrative 5-year service and maintenance agreement building strong recurrent revenues - Huge and consistent insider buying. Insiders bought over 5% of the outstanding shares since 2010 - Strong institutional investor support grew to almost 20% from 11% last year - NTWK has over 50 Fortune 100 loyal customers. Never lost a customer. None of the customers is over 5% of the total revenues - partial customer list: CitiGroup, Mercedes Benz, Santander, BMW, Volvo, Ford, GE Capital, Cisco Capital, Paribas, GMAC, Toyota, Nissan, Hyundai, BYD, SANY Corp. China, etc. TAKE A LOOK AT NTWK's CHART........SIMILAR TECHNICAL &amp; FUNDAMENTAL CONDITIONS MADE THE STOCK TRIPLE IN 2007 and 2010</Msg><Username>joeyggrecco</Username><Timestamp>1346949495672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346949758156-93</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS are the JOB CREATORS ! “Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Title><Msg>“Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949758156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346949994718-94</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren quoted from the BIBLE during the DNC; during the GODLESS RNC, no one did!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947787134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The people in MA know how phoney she is...she is a joke...in the finest tradition of the liars at the Kennedy compound.</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1346949994718</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:46:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950056299-95</Id><Topic><Title>ALL SLUMP, NO BUMB FOR THE OBIMBO!!! he deserves it! A PRESIDENT WITHOUT A BUDGET FOR 3 YEARS?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346946075103</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 11:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>did you mean 'ALL SLUMP AND NO BUMP', or did you mean 'ALL SLUMP AND NO BUMB'? ANYWAY YOU PUT IT, IT'S ALL BAD FOR THE OBIMBO!!! HE'S SUCH A CREEP....</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1346950056299</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:47:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950180219-96</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren quoted from the BIBLE during the DNC; during the GODLESS RNC, no one did!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947787134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The current GOVERNOR of MA knows how PHONEY his predecessor (MITT ROMNEY) was too!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346950180219</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:49:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950213615-97</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS are the JOB CREATORS ! “Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949758156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JFK and Clinton were good presidents. LBJ got 58k Americans killed. Carter and Obama are neck and neck for worst president ever. What's your point???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346950213615</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346950214837-98</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS....TOO LATE TO RELY ON THE 'GOD' YOU THREW OUT OF YOUR CONVENTION!!!</Title><Msg>cat out of the bag, no need to shut the barn door after the horse escaped, Democrats are drugged and demented...all those folksy sayings. Maybe our favorite is 'Democrats are drugged and demented'...that's been around for decades....you are the Gay Old Party, Democrats!!! Everyone can see it! You are in favor of dead babies and gay marriage.,......get over it!!! We will never get over it!!!! YOU ARE DOOMED ha ha ha hahhhahhahaha I'm laughing with joy, for your exit in November!! COME SOON, NOVEMBER!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346950214837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950287976-99</Id><Topic><Title>Elizabeth Warren quoted from the BIBLE during the DNC; during the GODLESS RNC, no one did!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346947787134</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:09:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP BLEW IT, BIG TIME!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346950287976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:51:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950356470-100</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS are the JOB CREATORS ! “Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949758156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its about jobs this election cycle ! That's the point</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346950356470</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:52:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950482782-101</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS....TOO LATE TO RELY ON THE 'GOD' YOU THREW OUT OF YOUR CONVENTION!!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346950214837</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:50:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In tennis its called 'an unforced error". Radical libs in DNC shot themselves in the foot. If they'd mentioned God just one time,repubs would have one less thing to carp about. Really dumb move.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346950482782</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:54:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346950630214-102</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS are the JOB CREATORS ! “Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949758156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>23.5 million unemployed or underemployed. You libs want to bring up jobs???LOL Better get back to bashing Bush or Palin. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346950630214</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:57:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346950655924-103</Id><Title>JOHN BOEHNER THE COWARD: Obama and his aides argue that the House speaker backed away from a deal because he couldn't stand the political heat inside his own party – or even, perhaps, get the votes to pass the compromise. They say he took the president's proposal for more revenue as an excuse to pull out of talks altogether.</Title><Msg>Obama and his aides argue that the House speaker backed away from a deal because he couldn't stand the political heat inside his own party – or even, perhaps, get the votes to pass the compromise. They say he took the president's proposal for more revenue as an excuse to pull out of talks altogether.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346950655924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:57:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346950777384-104</Id><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Dressage Horse Wife?</Title><Msg>My dressage horse wife disobeyed my commands that I barked to her this morning and now she has wandered away when I was busy pranking my son Tag, you're it with some rank smelling butter into his face. Hahaha this prank still works after 40 years.</Msg><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346950777384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346951046435-105</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Dressage Horse Wife?</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346950777384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hire an English teacher and learn some sentence structure,fool. You embarrassed yourself.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346951046435</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346951720781-106</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRATS are the JOB CREATORS ! “Since 1961,” Clinton said, from the start, “the Republicans have held the White House 28 years, the Democrats 24. In those 52 years, our economy produced 66 million private sector jobs. What's the jobs score? Republicans 24 million, Democrats 42 million!”</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1346949758156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:42:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He also said "He did not have sexual realations with that woman, Ms Lowinsky". He may have created some jobs, but more jobs were lost during his 4 yrs.</Msg><Username>cheryl186</Username><Timestamp>1346951720781</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:15:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346951831568-107</Id><Topic><Title>JOHN BOEHNER THE COWARD: Obama and his aides argue that the House speaker backed away from a deal because he couldn't stand the political heat inside his own party – or even, perhaps, get the votes to pass the compromise. They say he took the president's proposal for more revenue as an excuse to pull out of talks altogether.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346950655924</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:57:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the GOP knew if it compromised and got the economy and jobs going again it would help Obama be reelected, they were willing to sell out the American public for political gain</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346951831568</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:17:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346951971156-108</Id><Title>Did anyone see W's speech at the convention?</Title><Msg>or Cheney's? Oh yeah war criminals weren't invited, just their policies</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346951971156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:19:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952179969-109</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone see W's speech at the convention?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346951971156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was much better that his speech at the 2008 Republican Convention. Sometimes you can say a lot by keeping silent.</Msg><Username>gman310</Username><Timestamp>1346952179969</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:22:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346952233359-110</Id><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Msg>Still bitter over his firing, thrown out of the DNC for lack of morals, accepted into the GOP for lack of morals. On August 29, 1996, Morris resigned from the Clinton campaign after tabloid reports stated that he had been involved with a female prostitute, Sherry Rowlands, as reported by the Washington Post. A New York tabloid newspaper, the Star, had obtained and published a set of photographs allegedly of Morris and the woman on a Washington, D.C., hotel balcony. News of the impending publication broke during the third day of the 1996 Democratic Convention. The Electronic Telegraph reported unverified claims that in order to impress the woman, S. Rowlands, Morris invited her to listen in on his conversations with President Clinton.[11][12][13] It was also alleged he had an illegitimate child from an affair with a Texas woman.[14] Morris resigned on the same day that Bill Clinton spoke and accepted the nomination at the Democratic National Convention. In his resignation statement, he said that "while I served I sought to avoid the limelight because I did not want to become the message. Now, I resign so I will not become the issue."[15] In his response, President Clinton praised Morris as a "friend", and thanked him for his years of service. Privately, several of Clinton's aides were furious that in his resignation statement Morris credited himself with helping the President "come back from being buried in a landslide" and that Morris ended by comparing himself to Robert Kennedy.[16]</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952326660-111</Id><Topic><Title>Did anyone see W's speech at the convention?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346951971156</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:19:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since you said the Americans who went to Vietnam deserved whatever they got,you considered them war criminals too,right Deepharbor?????</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346952326660</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:25:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952425360-112</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least he wasn't the typical GOP GAY MAN!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346952425360</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:27:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952505693-113</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical lib response...dont like the message,attack the messenger. Morris nailed Clinton,,Magoo. Morris is a sleaze but he knows his politics.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346952505693</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:28:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952680069-114</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't like the message? I don't waste my time reading GOPER propaganda, I prefer actual news.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952680069</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952831000-115</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo bringing up Morris's morals after he's been slobbering all over about Clinton today.That's FUNNNNNNEEEEEEEEE!!! Did Morris ever use a cigar on his #$%$???? LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346952831000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346952895181-116</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YES, THAT IS THE POINT- MORRIS WAS A SLEAZE!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346952895181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:34:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346953223805-117</Id><Topic><Title>Dick Morris one class act</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346952233359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:23:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like I have you on the run,Magoo.Better switch to one of your other ids and fool me . Try junior,or dumdum,or virtual or jason,or hick, or verk, or linduh, or......lol</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346953223805</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 13:40:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346954802868-118</Id><Title>If I HATE the MIDDLE CLASS, HATE the POOR, HATE Women, why wouldn't I vote REPUBLICAN?</Title><Msg>wonk, deadhead, other repukes, help magoo out on this.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346954802868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:06:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346955283115-119</Id><Title>3 and 1/2 QE's and a Europe QE can't get Cisco over $20</Title><Msg>we're stuck for another 5 million years on perma frozen TEENAGE PRICES!!!</Msg><Username>scott4usa</Username><Timestamp>1346955283115</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346955499767-120</Id><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Msg>that they have almost no contact with reality and the reality of Americans, the 30 million that want to work, but find their jobs were either OUTSOURCED BY THE GUYS ON OBIMBO'S JOB COUNCIL...the one he hasn't met with for six month...(we all know that was just a facade anyway, but thanks Obimbo, for helping us prove it! YOU DON'T CARE ABOUT JOBS FOR AMERICANS!).... AND all Democratic excuses are the same tired ones we've heard for four years...FOUR FRICKIN' YEARS, OBIMBO....YOU HAVE BEEN PRESIDENT, IN CASE YOU DIDN'T REALIZE THAT!!!! The buck stops with you, cretin!!! It's all about you...NOW AND ALWAYS!!! So take it like a man, weep, cry, pound the desk, play basketball, go play more golf, but GIT OUT THE WAY!!!! YOU ARE NOTHING BUT IN THE WAY OF RECOVERY..... It's bye bye time in November...for the GOOD OF AMERICA...and the Tea Party (gonna stick it to ya)</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346955544680-121</Id><Title>GOP is like the school bully</Title><Msg>who finally #$%$ off so much of the school they ganged up and beat the #$%$ out of him. For a short period yesterday evening, a moment of panicked confusion broke out among those of us obsessively watching and tweeting the Democratic National Convention, when Sandra Fluke did not go on stage as scheduled. It turns out that we needn't have worried; convention organizers made an apparently last minute decision to move Fluke's speech to later in the night, giving her a prime-time audience. It's a move that indicates Democrats have finally stopped freaking out at the first sign of reactionary histrionics, and instead have embraced the strategy of taking the fight to conservatives. After decades of playing along with conservatives who dress up their hostility to female sexuality as nothing more than an interest in "life," Democrats have finally realized that baiting the anti-choice right into showing its misogynist, sex-phobic side may just be a winning strategy. Apparently, all it takes to set off the desired response is a reasonably attractive 31-year-old law student who is willing to speak about contraception in public. Twitter absolutely exploded last night with conservatives returning to the claim that being a mild-mannered thirtysomething who is engaged to be married makes a woman a pervert and radical feminist beyond all imagining. The Moderate Voice and Salon collected some of the more creative right wing reactions on Twitter, and here are some of our "favorites":</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346955544680</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346955587448-122</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't it really time to show Obimbo's college transcripts, think about it...REALLY!!! IT'S TIME</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955587448</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:19:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346955934834-123</Id><Title>B. Clinton Exposes Romney's and Ryan's Lies</Title><Msg>The GOP has said that "Fact Checkers Don't Matter". R&amp;R lies will not stand.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1346955934834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956336651-124</Id><Title>foaming bagger hatred</Title><Msg>''My only regret with Timothy McVeigh is he did not go to the New York Times Building.'' —Ann Coulter</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956336651</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:32:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956391372-125</Id><Title>and stupidity</Title><Msg>''Carbon dioxide is portrayed as harmful. But there isn't even one study that can be produced that shows that carbon dioxide is a harmful gas.'' —Rep. Michelle Bachmann, April, 2009</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956391372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346956432759-126</Id><Topic><Title>B. Clinton Exposes Romney's and Ryan's Lies</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1346955934834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Clinton Mops Floor With Republicans September 6, 2012 By mario piperni 2 Comments I could not express it any better than Tomasky did. Holy smokes. That was the best political speech more or less ever. There wasn’t a thing he didn’t touch on, and there wasn’t a thing he didn’t just blast out of the park. His carriage and delivery nailed it for partisans and for persuadables. He hit Republican obstructionism. He slammed the Romney and Ryan plans on virtually every point they’ve raised in the last six months, from the welfare ads to the tax cuts to the Medicare “cuts” to so much more, and he did it in detail. Amazing detail! Who else could burrow into those details, give a wonky speech—which this was, in a huge way—but a wonky speech that brought people to their feet two dozen times? … The Democrats are just wiping the floor with the Republicans so far. I’m not saying it will decide things, but the disparity in sheer talent is enough to make people look at Republicans as swimming in the kiddie pool. Sitting there and watching a Democrat clearly articulate and shred to pieces every major talking point and lie Republicans have uttered in the last six months was a joy. It says much about the Democratic Party that they are able to showcase their last president proudly. Compare that with Republicans who just held a convention where they did their best to create the impression that the years 2000-2008 never happened. Bush who? Furthermore, and with few exceptions, Republicans who took the stage in Tampa spent more time talking about their own accomplishments than those of their presidential nominee. Bain Capital and Romney’s time as governor were hardly mentioned. Republicans have nothing. Absolutely nothing…except for the fictional Obama they’ve created to feed to the Fox News minions they keep protected in a hermetically sealed bubble safe from the harming effects we call truth and facts. BTW, the trailer for the above image can be viewed here.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346956432759</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956511734-127</Id><Title>on hating</Title><Msg>''The feminist agenda is not about equal rights for women. It is about a socialist, anti-family political movement that encourages women to leave their husbands, kill their children, practice witchcraft, destroy capitalism and become lesbians.'' —Pat Robertson</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956511734</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956575064-128</Id><Title>GOP loves Nazi's they share values</Title><Msg>''I've always been fascinated by the fact that here was a relatively small country that from a strictly military point of view accomplished incredible things.'' —Ohio GOP House candidate and Tea Party favorite Rich Iott, explaining why for years he donned a German Waffen SS uniform and participated in Nazi re-enactments as part of a group that calls itself Wiking (Atlantic interview, Oct. 2010)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956575064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956697273-129</Id><Title>On meatballs</Title><Msg>''I was dabbling into every other kind of religion before I became a Christian. I was dabbling in witchcraft, I've dabbled in Buddhism. I would have become a Hare Krishna but I didn't want to become a vegetarian. And that is honestly the reason why -- because I'm Italian, I love meatballs!'' —Delaware GOP Senate candidate Christine O'Donnell, on ''Politically Incorrect,'' July 19, 1999</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956697273</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:38:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956762731-130</Id><Title>Owned by big oil</Title><Msg>''I'm ashamed of what happened in the White House yesterday. I think it is a tragedy in the first proportion that a private corporation can be subjected to what I would characterize as a shakedown -- in this case a $20 billion shakedown ... I'm only speaking for myself. I'm not speaking for anyone else, but I apologize. I do not want to live in a county where anytime a citizen or a corporation does something that is legitimately wrong, [it is] subject to some sort of political pressure that, again, in my words, amounts to a shakedown.'' —Rep. Joe Barton (R-Tex.) during a congressional hearing with BP CEO Tony Hayward, referring to a $20 billion fund for damages that President Obama pressured BP to set up to pay for the Gulf oil spill. Barton, the biggest recipient of oil and gas industry campaign contributions in the House of Representatives, was later forced by Republican leaders to apologize for his BP apology</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956762731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:39:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956790804-131</Id><Title>CSCO up $0.70 !!!! - I am on the window sill ready to jump ...</Title><Msg>CSCO up $0.70 - I am on the window sill ready to jump ... Its extremely hard to jump out of the basement window. Long and strong on Cisco shares - go John C.</Msg><Username>basicarmandy</Username><Timestamp>1346956790804</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:39:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956865883-132</Id><Title>Big fat, diabetic drug addicts help keep healthcare costs down</Title><Msg>''Exercise freaks ... are the ones putting stress on the health care system.'' —Rush Limbaugh, June 12, 2009</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956865883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956912293-133</Id><Title>Hey why not end the world</Title><Msg>''The only way to reduce the number of nuclear weapons is to use them.'' —Rush Limbaugh</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956912293</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346956964473-134</Id><Title>why Baggers are easily fooled by GOP propaganda</Title><Msg>''Fool me once, shame on you. Fool me twice, shame on you.'' —Rep. Virginia Foxx (R-North Carolina)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956964473</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346957079687-135</Id><Title>Your not a quitter as long as you are willing to quit</Title><Msg>'It may be tempting and more comfortable to just keep your head down, plod along, and appease those who demand: 'Sit down and shut up,' but that's the worthless, easy path; that's a quitter's way out.'' —Sarah Palin, quitting her job as governor, adding, ''Only dead fish go with the flow,'' July 3, 2009</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346957079687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346957471119-136</Id><Topic><Title>If I HATE the MIDDLE CLASS, HATE the POOR, HATE Women, why wouldn't I vote REPUBLICAN?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346954802868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>............................</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346957471119</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346957624045-137</Id><Topic><Title>Big fat, diabetic drug addicts help keep healthcare costs down</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956865883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pure delight! Ol Rush is right on target as usual. What is there not to like about that guy? BRILLIANT....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346957624045</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:53:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346957662331-138</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just want to keep this message at the top of the page. he he he he</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346957662331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:54:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346957691958-139</Id><Topic><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post!!!!</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1346957691958</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:54:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346957795398-140</Id><Title>HOMICIDE IN CHICAGO....WOW.....DEMOCRATS ARE KILLIN' OTHER DEMOCRATS.....</Title><Msg>the only sad part of that is the children that get shot. The rest of it is pure Darwin.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346957795398</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:56:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346958517755-141</Id><Topic><Title>Your not a quitter as long as you are willing to quit</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346957079687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As a graduate of Yale / Wharton you should know "your" is grammatically incorrect. Should have been"you're" or " you are ". Most people learn this in grade school, not Yale .Maybe you should stop tee heeing others typos, Magoo.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346958517755</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:08:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959157856-142</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's no law saying Romney has to release 'em, but he darn sure isn't getting elected by hiding 'em. That's a fact, whether it's fair or not.</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346959157856</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:19:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959221359-143</Id><Topic><Title>Your not a quitter as long as you are willing to quit</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346957079687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You saying Magoo stepped in it again?LOL You notice he ignores any comment about what he said about our soldiers . He needs to spend a few minutes in a locked room with a couple of veterans.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346959221359</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959223321-144</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The desperate cries of an old man on the losing side of history...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346959223321</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959357976-145</Id><Topic><Title>Big fat, diabetic drug addicts help keep healthcare costs down</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956865883</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Obama is reelected, I wonder if Rush will go back to spinning records, or will he simply overdose? He's definitely on the celebrity deathwatch list...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346959357976</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:22:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959537170-146</Id><Topic><Title>If I HATE the MIDDLE CLASS, HATE the POOR, HATE Women, why wouldn't I vote REPUBLICAN?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346954802868</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:06:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what I've been saying. I honestly don't blame millionaires for voting Romney. A lower cap gains and isolation from the masses are great things. What gets me is when poor chain email forwarding saps like Walter support Romney, when they have nothing to gain from it...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346959537170</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:25:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959654659-147</Id><Topic><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Someone get Walter a job!</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346959654659</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:27:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346959842707-148</Id><Topic><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THANK YOU FOR YOUR COMPASSION SIR! You have the hollow ring of a Democrat. You do not care about jobs for us working poor. Us ordinary slobs, us felons on parole. We are Democrats just like you. Useless beggar, bleeding the system to death so we have no responsibility and can lie around drugged and addled all day long! Thank you sir, for your kindness...do you have any malt liquor on you, sir?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346959842707</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960050085-149</Id><Topic><Title>Has Anyone Seen My Dressage Horse Wife?</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346950777384</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 12:59:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Speaking of horses, my wife and I took a carriage ride in Savannah, GA last weekend, and who was pulling the carriage? None other than Ann Coulter herself! True story.</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346960050085</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960089258-150</Id><Topic><Title>IF HACKERS HAVE ROMNEY'S TAX RETURNS, THEN WHY NOT OBIMBO'S COLLEGE DATA?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346887822961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-05 19:30:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>History is as history does!! Tea Party took the Congress in 2010...they made history.. Sort of puts YOU on the wrong side of history, don't it? he he he (wheeze, gasp, cough...old man coughing noise) Well sonny, let me tell you something, just give me a minute while I change my Depens, just took a 6 lb crap in them, ate too many prunes and way too much fiber!...but hold on just a sec....be right back. Gift wrapped that special set of '6 pound Depens' just for you. Fed Ex'd it just a minute ago, and it'll be on your doorstep in a day or two. Breath deeply, Museum, you got lots of living ahead of you...all of it ON THE WRONG SIDE OF HISTORY!!! HE HE HE HE HE Oooooops, just made a poops....(another package headed your way, Museum!!!)</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346960089258</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346960137731-151</Id><Title>MUSEUM, YOU MIGHT BE MOVING TO THE TOP OF THE LIST......</Title><Msg>of my favorite posters!!! You are so very much fun to abuse...and so easy too!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346960137731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960224386-152</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crankie, it wasn't a great speech. It was a great economics class. He told you exactly how the R/R team and the repuke party in general has been lying about the results of what Obama has done. Furthermore it quoted Senator Turtle "Our job is not to create jobs, our job is to get rid of this president". C'mon crankie open your eyes, somehow I got the feeling that you are someone that could be rescued from the clutches of the cult.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346960224386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960295514-153</Id><Topic><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, I'm no longer drugged and addled!</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346960295514</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:38:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960566097-154</Id><Topic><Title>MUSEUM, YOU MIGHT BE MOVING TO THE TOP OF THE LIST......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346960137731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, your post is 100% not creepy at all!</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346960566097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:42:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346960571592-155</Id><Title>"CLINTON SPEECH WAS 'MOMENT THAT PROBABLY REELECTED OBAMA' ".</Title><Msg>"CHARLOTTE, N.C. -- Former President Bill Clinton's speech on Wednesday night was a tour de force that exhibited his best qualities as an easily relatable communicator and effective yet likeable attack dog. And in a telling nod toward its effectiveness, the one aspect that Republicans felt comfortable attacking was its length of nearly 50 mintues. Some conservatives didn't bother with that. Appearing on CNN shortly after Clinton finished, Alex Castellanos, a longtime cable commentator and former aide to Mitt Romney, spoke in awe of the 42nd president's address. "I would recommend to my friend Paul [Begala] here, tonight when everybody leaves, lock the doors. You don't have to come back tomorrow. This convention is done," Castellanos said. "This will be the moment that probably reelected Barack Obama. Bill Clinton saved the Democratic Party once, it was going too far left, he came in, the new Democrats took it to the center. He did it again tonight."</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346960571592</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960749030-156</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I DID 'NOT' HAVE SEX WITH THAT WOMAN"</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346960749030</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:45:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346960877797-157</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you only do like the boys capt ! (FAGGY YOU)</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1346960877797</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:47:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961052703-158</Id><Topic><Title>and stupidity</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956391372</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:33:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The statements that pass through my mental filter and somehow spew out of my mouth are both deceitful and un-American. My dimwittedness and historically unprecedented ignorance is a disgrace to our republic. Is this thing on? Ohh sh..." -Rep. Michelle Bachmann, sometime very soon, 2012</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346961052703</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961249869-159</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think YOU had sex with ANY woman.</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346961249869</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961379954-160</Id><Topic><Title>Your not a quitter as long as you are willing to quit</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346957079687</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:44:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump...come on junior or Magoo or whatever id you choose...speak up about our soldiers .Aren't you proud of shooting off your mouth???</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346961379954</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:56:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346961758525-161</Id><Title>Something we can ALL rejoyce</Title><Msg>Drew Peterson found guilty in murder trial. Cop to jail, they are going to have their way with him. MotherF'er.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346961758525</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:02:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346961852234-162</Id><Title>Couldn't fill out door stadium</Title><Msg>Democrats couldn't give enough tickets away so they move to small indoor stadium. 20% chance of rain. LMFAO people aren't falling for it in 2012. Cage</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1346961852234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:04:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961873549-163</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo, I am not like you Pecker-woods! Clinton being know as one of the biggest liar around was someone they could have on and still not out do Obama on the lying part!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346961873549</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:04:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346961940065-164</Id><Topic><Title>MUSEUM, YOU MIGHT BE MOVING TO THE TOP OF THE LIST......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346960137731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walter, Please dont compliment Magoo.It gives him a woody and he'll hurt his weener again.!</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346961940065</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346962582097-165</Id><Topic><Title>CLINTON SAID "PAUL RYAN IS A JOKE"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346942192151</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 10:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes - Clintoon wants a favor from the O'boched presidency...</Msg><Username>gigsurfer</Username><Timestamp>1346962582097</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346962620995-166</Id><Topic><Title>THE HOLLOWNESS OF DEMOCRATIC EXCUSES......IS.......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346955499767</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:18:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>mission accomplished oooooops</Msg><Username>joyceeeeeei23</Username><Timestamp>1346962620995</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:17:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346965094565-167</Id><Title>WALTER PREDICTS..."NO BUMP, ALL SLUMP....FOR OBIMBO..." HIS SPEECH TONITE WILL</Title><Msg>be so utterly boring that all the peeps sitting around wearing funny hats and waving funny signs will drift into the deep torpor so common to Democrats. Drug addled thuggishness will be the hall mark of tonite's great Obimbo disaster! The man's teleprompter will get hacked and he'll start reading the story of Hansel and Gretel. MARK MY WORDS!! ANONYMOUS IS GONNA GIT 'EM!!!!!!!!! Hilarious, a hacked teleprompter will show the nation what a goober Obimbo is..he is a doofus!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965094565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:58:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346965236819-168</Id><Topic><Title>WALTER PREDICTS..."NO BUMP, ALL SLUMP....FOR OBIMBO..." HIS SPEECH TONITE WILL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965094565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walter you are so stupid that pity is all that is left for you. I think everyone but you knows by now that anonymous is not leaning right.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346965236819</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:00:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346965257702-169</Id><Topic><Title>MUSEUM, YOU MIGHT BE MOVING TO THE TOP OF THE LIST......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346960137731</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 15:35:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>See? You're doing it again!!!!! You are hilarious. Please, make a coherent comment so we can turn you into a puree'd mash of Democratic mumble mouth mush. It's easy for us and sort of fun for you, eh? Now, remember it has to be in paragraph form, using acceptable grammatical construction, the same way they taught you in school.....Ooooops, forgot, you went to PUBLIC SCHOOL, run by a Democratic Teacher's Union so you learned: DIDDLY SQUAT AND NOW YOU LIVE IN A VAN, DOWN BY THE RIVER!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965257702</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346965354014-170</Id><Title>IN A VAN.........DOWN BY THE RIVER!!!!!</Title><Msg>Is where we will be moving all Democrats after November. Free plastic water bottles, small energy bars, and bales and bales of grass will keep them alive, barely, until the Re-Education Camps are ready in Idaho. Fun time with potatoes!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965354014</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346965558424-171</Id><Topic><Title>GOP loves Nazi's they share values</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956575064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You do know that Nazi is a contraction of National Socialist, right? Nazis are socialists, just like Obama. Any Republican that admires anything about a nazi needs to switch to the donk party.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1346965558424</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:05:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346966297207-172</Id><Title>Chicago style politics</Title><Msg>Story going around David Axelrod tried to strongarm Gallup because they showed Romney with five point lead .The thugs are getting desperate.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346966297207</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:18:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346966578382-173</Id><Title>Be Sure to tune into Bammy Tonight</Title><Msg>Should be good for a laugh....</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346966578382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346966830839-174</Id><Topic><Title>B. Clinton Exposes Romney's and Ryan's Lies</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1346955934834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:25:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is an excellent essay. The truth is finally being told.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1346966830839</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:27:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346966997442-175</Id><Topic><Title>Be Sure to tune into Bammy Tonight</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346966578382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you have a wide screen tv for his Pinocchio nose. Guy is a professional liar. All politicians are but with Obama its an art.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346966997442</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:29:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967225261-176</Id><Topic><Title>Be Sure to tune into Bammy Tonight</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346966578382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yup, gonna use the 56". Wide enough?</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346967225261</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:33:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967348834-177</Id><Topic><Title>Be Sure to tune into Bammy Tonight</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346966578382</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:22:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>P.S., hopoe he doesn't break my set(with my steel toes)</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346967348834</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:35:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346967435264-178</Id><Title>WHY ARE DEMOCRATS SO ANGRY, SO AGGRESSIVE, SO PUZZLED????</Title><Msg>Sure, we push them down, take their lunch money, mess up their hair, give them a 'twirly' in the toilet (twirly= held upside down, over toilet, gently lowered into toilet, head first and then flushed, so that your hair has that nice 'twirled' effect), kick'em in the balls...(what teeny, tiny nads they actually have), mock them, excoriate them, humiliate them, belittle them, trick them, deceive them and finally beat them like a red headed step child, or a rented mule in the general elections,........... but why are they so angry?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346967435264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:37:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346967616754-179</Id><Topic><Title>GOP loves Nazi's they share values</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346956575064</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 14:36:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thought I'd check in on dumb.ivan, and sure enough, he's still DUMB</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346967616754</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:40:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346968247511-180</Id><Topic><Title>WHY ARE DEMOCRATS SO ANGRY, SO AGGRESSIVE, SO PUZZLED????</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346967435264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>its fun to abuse Democrats! It should be done frequently and often, to quote my favorite poster, Walter!!!!!! push'em down stairs, Walter</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1346968247511</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346969462663-181</Id><Title>Romney Leads Obama again today 47% to 44%, lead increased one percentage point</Title><Msg>This after Moochelle spoke. No Obama bounce yet. The question is , since Obama hasn't kept his promisses so far how can he make people believe anything he will say now?</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346969462663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:11:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346969587488-182</Id><Topic><Title>WALTER PREDICTS..."NO BUMP, ALL SLUMP....FOR OBIMBO..." HIS SPEECH TONITE WILL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965094565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama has kept his old promises why will he be trusted now.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346969587488</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:13:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346972059843-183</Id><Topic><Title>WALTER PREDICTS..."NO BUMP, ALL SLUMP....FOR OBIMBO..." HIS SPEECH TONITE WILL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346965094565</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 16:58:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Which promise has he kept. Be specific.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1346972059843</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346972739008-184</Id><Title>Democraps will be happy</Title><Msg>When there are concentration camps all over AmeriKa. Bottom line; Jews who have the same hatred as the neo-Nazis for their own blood in Israel…can *NEVER* be trusted.</Msg><Username>celltones</Username><Timestamp>1346972739008</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:05:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346973031181-185</Id><Topic><Title>WHY ARE DEMOCRATS SO ANGRY, SO AGGRESSIVE, SO PUZZLED????</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346967435264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reads like a memoir, WalWal. Autobiographical?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346973031181</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:10:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346973045833-186</Id><Title>Dems running amok</Title><Msg>Democratic delegate Julia Rodriguez-NY told The Blaze "If I see Romney,I will kill him". The Secret Service is now investigating. Really nice bunch at the democratic convention. LOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973045833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:10:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346973286386-187</Id><Topic><Title>Dems running amok</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973045833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess the Secret Service doesn't think so,fool. Probably just a stupid remark but needs to be checked out.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973286386</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:14:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346973393338-188</Id><Topic><Title>Dems running amok</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973045833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>//The Secret Service is now investigating.// Wow, are they done with Karl Rove ALREADY?!</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346973393338</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:16:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346973624612-189</Id><Topic><Title>Dems running amok</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973045833</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why dont you call the Secret Service and ask them, Jason. I'm sure they will appreciate your humor. Or would you just rather say stupid stuff on the net?</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346973624612</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346974422259-190</Id><Title>What will Joe do?</Title><Msg>Will Gaffe a Minute Joe follow the script tonight or say something really stupid?? Joe Biden= Democratic Leader. LOL</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346974422259</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:33:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346975757961-191</Id><Title>Independent Fact Checking Organizations say</Title><Msg>Clinton tells the truth, Ryan and Romney Lie, not only that but they admit they lie and they don't care they are caught, LOL baggers are so stupid they are told they are being lied to and they still believe it Former President Bill Clinton’s exhaustive endorsement of President Obama’s reelection Wednesday night was stocked with statistics on nearly every major issue of the election, from healthcare to job creation and the national debt. With frequent off-the-cuff citations of facts and figures, Clinton’s speech was sure to be scoured by the army of fact-checkers that has been kept busy with the truthiness (instead of truthfulness) of the 2012 election. For the most part, the fact police gave Clinton high marks. Bloomberg TV succinctly declared: “No False Claims in Clinton’s Speech.” PHOTOS: Protests of the DNC Reporter Megan Hughes said the Bloomberg team looked at Clinton’s biggest potential “whoppers.” The assertion, for example, that since 1961 there were 24 million jobs created during Republican presidencies and 42 million created during Democratic ones checked out. Perhaps some of the high marks stem from savvy appeals to the jury by the former president. Clinton took the Romney campaign to task for continuing to run ads that said Obama gutted the work requirements for welfare, even after myriad fact-checkers and news organizations said the attacks were inaccurate. “I am telling you, the claim that President Obama weakened welfare reform’s work requirement is just not true. But they keep on running ads,” Clinton said Wednesday night. “You want to know why? Their campaign pollster said, ‘We are not going to let our campaign be dictated by fact-checkers.’ “Now, finally I can say: That is true,” he continued, to applause and laughter in the arena. “I couldn’t have said it better myself.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346975757961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:55:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346976394113-192</Id><Title>I support Ryan's budget</Title><Msg>As long as all that additional money seniors have to pay (that ruins them financially) as long as it goes to cut Mitt's taxes from 13% to 1%, I really don't care if those old people starve and can't see their children. Under the Ryan plan seniors have to pay a higher portion of their medical costs, it could lead to their financial ruin, especially if they have dementia, a study asserts. Ryan's medicare reform proposals have suggested that seniors should pay a much higher percentage of their healthcare costs. To identify how much Medicare beneficiaries spend on healthcare costs in the last five years of life, a National Institute of Aging study analyzed data over six years from 3,209 individuals with Medicare coverage. They found that out-of-pocket spending for individuals or their spouses dying of dementia was more than twice the average when compared to spending on those dying of gastrointestinal disease or cancer. The bulk of these costs were related to nursing home expenses, which accounted for 56% of average spending in those suffering from Alzheimer's disease. (You know the ones Ryan's budget cuts right away, starting next year, not ten years from now). “As more baby boomers retire, a new generation of widows or widowers could face a sharply diminished financial future as they confront their recently-depleted nest egg following the illness and death of a spouse,” the study states. The study was published online in the Journal of General Internal Medicine.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346976394113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346976489923-193</Id><Topic><Title>I support Ryan's budget</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346976394113</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:06:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The study was published online in the Journal of General Internal Medicine. Now who knew the Journal of General Internal Medicine was part of the lame-stream media. LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346976489923</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:08:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346976758305-194</Id><Topic><Title>What will Joe do?</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346974422259</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:33:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They all lie,fool. Party makes no difference.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346976758305</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346976944920-195</Id><Topic><Title>Independent Fact Checking Organizations say</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346975757961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:55:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I did not have sex with that woman,Monica Lewinsky !!" Maybe Bill didn't lie last night but...........</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346976944920</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346977392684-196</Id><Title>Wow Eva Longoria is hot</Title><Msg>enough to be a republican, but she is just way to bright</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346977392684</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346978149697-197</Id><Topic><Title>WHY ARE DEMOCRATS SO ANGRY, SO AGGRESSIVE, SO PUZZLED????</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1346967435264</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 17:37:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can tell the Dems are losing. I asked myself why if Clinton was supposed to intro Obama it didn't happen last night. Why didn't Obama follow Clinton to the podium. Then after thinking about it I just figured that since they moved to another venue that Obama didn't have his Teleprompter set up yet. Clinton really doesn't need a teleprompter, just like Romney he is a very smart guy, which Obama really isn't. After all Mitt got 2 simultaneous Harvard degrees, and Clinton got into Oxford, didn't graduate, but that was probably because he was too busy doing the English Lasses. Obama won't show us his grades, papers, etc, because they are embarrassing.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346978149697</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346978553947-198</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Leads Obama again today 47% to 44%, lead increased one percentage point</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346969462663</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 18:11:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>last nights ugly booing of God and Jerusalem must have turned off Joos and Christians alike. How many moderates liked the way the Democraps behaved? not many could approve of booing God.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346978553947</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:42:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346978607131-199</Id><Title>This is a serious question</Title><Msg>I remember Trump said he was going to have a "really, really big surprise at the convention" did I miss it? What was it?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346978607131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:43:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346978800763-200</Id><Topic><Title>This is a serious question</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346978607131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Trump got surprised when Romney told him to keep his big mouth shut. LOL</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346978800763</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:46:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346979089330-201</Id><Topic><Title>This is a serious question</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346978607131</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:43:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no really, it was a "a really, really big surprise?" One of you Baggers must know what it was, it was really, really big?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346979089330</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:51:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346979443791-202</Id><Title>Traitor at the podium</Title><Msg>Any other Vietnam vets watch Kerry's speech? The backstabbing s.o.b.makes me want to throw up</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346979443791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:57:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346979633303-203</Id><Topic><Title>Traitor at the podium</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346979443791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah the guy who volunteered twice in Vietnam, (while Bush pulled strings to avoid it) then came back and had the courage to help end a war killing 58,000 americans for no reason at all. You know the guy who probably saved another 100,000 American Veteran deaths before we pulled out anyway.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346979633303</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:00:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346979962737-204</Id><Topic><Title>Traitor at the podium</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346979443791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey I understand the Vietnam outrage over Kerry saying the Vietnam war should end, all those vietnam vets feel their friends died for nothing What I can't understand is why they wanted to have a lot more of their friends die before they admitted it was a mistake</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346979962737</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346979981672-205</Id><Title>Mitt this, Mitt that</Title><Msg>All predictions have come true, dems can't run on their record because, well it shameful.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1346979981672</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:06:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346980005591-206</Id><Topic><Title>Traitor at the podium</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346979443791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You should #$%$Magoo .You said Americans deserved what they got in Vietnam. Kerry played the system on his three purple hearts(not even one deserved) and shot a15 year old kid in the back so you dont have a clue,buddy. I was with some real heroes.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346980005591</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:06:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346980427676-207</Id><Title>LOL! Montana Gov. Brian Schweitzer lit into ROMNEY! OUCH</Title><Msg>Highlighted Romney's poor record as Gov lol</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1346980427676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:13:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346980791682-208</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! Montana Gov. Brian Schweitzer lit into ROMNEY! OUCH</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1346980427676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:13:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What poor record. He had 5 or under UE rate and he turned a billion plus deficit into a few million deficit. You Messiah worshippers are so brainwashed you wouldn't recognize a good record. Geez</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346980791682</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346981121544-209</Id><Topic><Title>Traitor at the podium</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346979443791</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 20:57:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if all Americans had morals, and were Christian we never would had gone into a foreign country to murder women and children to support a dictator, I understand if you did it you will psychologically try to justify murdering woman and children by saying it was patriotic, Of course I pity you, having been misused by the Government I understand your feelings. History will of course judge the fact that you were a pawn sent in to murder innocent people in the name of patriotism. Fact is you are no more evil then the men that went to war for Hilter. The scale of the war is a lot smaller but the fact you are in part responsible for not standing up and saying no to Nixon like a lot of Germans never standing up to Hitler, means you helped kill a million people. perhaps you should have been a christian first and a patriot second.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346981121544</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346981499812-210</Id><Topic><Title>Sandra Fluke: The DemoCRAP answer to the countries problems. LMMFAO</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346936667099</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 09:04:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who wants to be the first to step up and pay for a person to sleep around. 48 million people on food stamps and this JOKE of a whiner is focused on her promiscuity. LibTURDS have lost touch with the common man. SHELLACKING 2.0 coming in November. Catch IT.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346981499812</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:31:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346981502418-211</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! Montana Gov. Brian Schweitzer lit into ROMNEY! OUCH</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1346980427676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:13:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lol! Yeah right!</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1346981502418</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346981604287-212</Id><Title>DNC --- divided nation conquer</Title><Msg>Clinton is a know liar, lied on national TV and became the DNC's greatest leader? John Kerry lied before congress on national TV and became one of DNC's Leaders? and they are trying to run the most divisive President this nation has ever seen and has put one lie on top and another, Obama? Bet Edward is mad because he was not included this year, next time? No the DNC has a new meaning: divided nation conquer "Every kingdom divided against itself is laid waste, and no city or house divided against itself will stand."</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346981604287</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346981715173-213</Id><Title>why is that the 6th Veteran to talk at the DNC and there were none at the GOP convention?</Title><Msg>what is that all about, just imagine if Obama didn't have any veterans talk like Romney?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346981715173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:35:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346981927176-214</Id><Title>Biden</Title><Msg>Swears Obama has a big sdick</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1346981927176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346981972794-215</Id><Topic><Title>LOL! Montana Gov. Brian Schweitzer lit into ROMNEY! OUCH</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1346980427676</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:13:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I gave you the facts. Refute them, responding with " yeah right " shows your lack of knowledge of the facts. Let me know when you can back up your, " yeah right ".</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1346981972794</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:39:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346982150276-216</Id><Topic><Title>Biden</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1346981927176</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:38:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo says he wishes he would wash it more. Says it tastes like Biden's butt</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346982150276</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:42:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346982231136-217</Id><Title>I know Biden's kids are in the Military</Title><Msg>Mitt, his brothers, his son's and his nieces and nephews, well they don't, didn't, never did serve. Did W serve? Oh yeah, in the rabbit hole folks like W who used family connections to avoid the draft aren't heroes like Biden and Kerry.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346982231136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:43:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346982259528-218</Id><Title>Netanyahu chews out US ambassador over Obama Iran policy</Title><Msg>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and U.S. Ambassador to Israel Dan Shapiro allegedly argued over the Obama's administration's Iran policy. (Reuters) Rep. Mike Rogers, the Michigan Republican who chairs the House Intelligence Committee, says that his much-discussed meeting with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu in Jerusalem late last month did, in fact, devolve into an sharp confrontation between Netanyahu and the American ambassador to Israel, the former National Security Council official (and former Obama campaign Jewish liaison), Dan Shapiro. Rogers told a Michigan radio interviewer earlier this week that he had not previously witnessed such a high-level confrontation, and he described Israeli leaders as being at "wits' end" over what they see as President Obama's unwillingness to provide them with his "red lines" in the effort to stop Iran's nuclear program. He also said that neither the Israelis nor the Iranians believe that Obama would use force to stop the nuclear program. (UPDATE: Rogers said as well he believes the Israelis will "probably" bomb Iran if they don't get clearer red lines from the U.S.) Rogers description of the meeting directly contradicts repeated Administration assertions that there is "no daylight" on the Iran issue with the Israeli government. Shortly after the meeting took place, Israeli press reports appeared suggesting that Netanyahu and Shapiro had engaged in an argument, but Shapiro soon dismissed those reports, calling them "silly" and saying, "The published account of that meeting did not reflect what actually occurred in the meeting. The conversations were entirely friendly and professional." Rogers, speaking to WJR radio host Frank Beckmann, painted a very different picture. He said the meeting, originally scheduled to be a discussion of intelligence and technical issues between himself and the prime minister, spun out of control when Netanyahu began lambasting Shapiro over the Administration's Iran policy. When Beckmann asked Rogers to describe the tenor of the meeting, he said: "Very tense. Some very sharp... exchanges and it was very, very clear the Israelis had lost their patience with the (Obama) Administration." He went on, "There was no doubt. You could not walk out of that meeting and think that they had not lost their patience with this Administration." Rogers said Israeli frustration grows from what they see -- and he sees -- as a refusal by the Obama Administration to outline an endgame: "(I)t was very clear the overarching policy has been frustrating mainly because I think it's not very clear. What we walked out of that meeting knowing is that the Administration was trying to defend itself." By the end, he said, there was a "sharp exchange between the Administration's representative there, our ambassador there, and Mr. Netanyahu, which was unusual to say the least, but I thought at the end of the day maybe productive." Beckmann then asked: "Is it inaccurate to say it was a shouting match?" Rogers answered: "I can say that there were elevated concerns on behalf of the Israelis." When asked if he had "ever seen that sort of thing before," Rogers answered: "No not that directly. We've had sharp exchanges with other heads of state and in intelligence services and other things, but nothing at that level that I've seen in all my time where people were clearly that agitated, clearly that worked up about a particular issue where there was a very sharp exchange." Rogers went on to describe what he understands to be the Israeli frustration, and, apparently, his frustration, with the impact of sanctions: "Here's the problem. ....I support the sanctions. But if you're going to have a hammer you have to have an anvil. You have to have at least a credible threat of a military option. So it's having an effect, yes, it's having an effect on the Iranian economy. It is not impacting their race on enrichment and other things, and that's very very clear." He went on, "I think the Israeli position is, 'Hey, listen, you've got to tell us -- I mean, if you want us to wait' -- and that's what this Administration's been saying, you've gotta wait, you've gotta wait, you've gotta wai -- got that -- 'but then you've gotta tell us when is the red line so we can make our own decisions about should we or shouldn't we stop this particular program." And Rogers had harsh words for the Administration, which he says has made it very clear to the Israelis what they shouldn't do, but hasn't delivered a message to the Iranians with the same clarity: "There's a lot of pieces in play on this. But I think again, their frustration is that the Administration hasn't made it very clea -- they've made it very clear to Israel in a public way that they shouldn't do it, but haven't made it very clear to Iran in a public way that there will be tougher action, which could include -- and I argue peace through strength, so you just need to let them understand that that's an option so we can deter them from their program. And right now the Israelis don't' believe that the Administration is serious when they say that all options are on the table, and more importantly neither do the Iranians. That's why the program is progressing." I'll post more of this interview as it is transcribed, in a few minutes, in this space. PART II: When asked by Beckmann at what he believes the Israelis willl say "enough is enough," Rogers answered: "Certainly when you walk out of that meeting you get the feeling that they are finally at wits' end, and that's what concerned me about the meeting." He went on, "I will say that as a part of their decision point or data point when they go through the process of should we or shouldn't we, it was clear that our American elections have worked its way into one of those data points. I thought, well, maybe that hedges their response until maybe after the election. But what I got out of that, walking out of that, wa,s yeah they're considering it, but at this point they're very frustrated because they don't' know what happens after the election, and their window for impacting the program they believe is starting to close." Rogers also said that what he calls Obama's uncertainty has caused problems for the U.S. across the Middle East. "You know, it's a very interesting argument when you're in the room and talking about options.The meeting was designed, it was supposed to be between Netanyahu and myself on some intelligence cooperation matters and other matters, when it came to Iran and Syria and other things, and kind of devolved into this meeting where the ambassador was confronted directly... what was very apparent to me was a lot of frustration with the lack of clarity and the uncertainty about what their position is on the Iranian nuclear program. And that's what I think I saw across the Middle East. The uncertainty about where the United States' position is on those questions has created lots of problems and anxiety that I think doesn't serve the world well and doesn't serve peace well." Rogers spoke, as well, about the Iranian nuclear timeline: "So the big question is the dash. And the dash is, we know they have an enrichment program, it's highly likely they have a weaponization program. You have to have both of those parts for a nuclear weapon program. And the dash is when does weaponization mean you can put it on a missile and fire it off? The Israelis are upset because that dash question seems to be shortening and they already believe they have enough enrichment for more than one nuclear bomb. That's why their anxiety is high and the United States position isn't all that clear." Beckmann then asked Rogers how close the Israelis believe that dash period to be. Rogers: "The Israelis believe it's short. I mean, Netanyahu made it very clear he thought it was a matter of weeks. If they decide to do the dash it could be four weeks to eight weeks, which is a month or two months. Our intelligence analysts believe it would be a little longer than that. But the problem is, nobody really knows for sure. But we do know, and I think everyone agrees, including, you know, our European intelligence allies and other things that they are clearly marching down this road." My fear is that if you corner Netanyahu and ask him to choose risking a first nuclear strike from Iran, without telling Israel what the US is going to do, your asking a leader to shirk his public responsibility to never again allow a Jooish Holocaust. No Jooish leader will do that to help any foreign leader get elected. Besides hasn't the history of the Holocaust of 6 million dead Joos, delivered the message that Israel cannot allow any other nation to tell them how to best protect the Jooish people.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346982259528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:44:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346982304588-219</Id><Topic><Title>why is that the 6th Veteran to talk at the DNC and there were none at the GOP convention?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346981715173</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:35:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Per Crank, you dont respect our troops, so why do you care . You are a lying hypocrite,Magoo.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346982304588</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:45:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346982542158-220</Id><Title>wow Biden is middle class</Title><Msg>don't think America likes the GOP attacking the Middle class, guess it probably helps them get the 1% vote, who doesn't love Biden?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346982542158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:49:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346982943277-221</Id><Topic><Title>wow Biden is middle class</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346982542158</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:49:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Most buffoons are lovable ......and laughable.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346982943277</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346983346395-222</Id><Topic><Title>I know Biden's kids are in the Military</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346982231136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your stupidity is amazing. Biden used his childhood asthma to avoid Vietnam.It went away the day the war ended.lol Kerry got three deferments.When he couldn't get anymore, he joined the navy and said " I want to be an officer, not some grunt". Yeah,what heroes!</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346983346395</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 22:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346984174795-223</Id><Topic><Title>I know Biden's kids are in the Military</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346982231136</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:43:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonder where Magoodumdum served. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1346984174795</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 22:16:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346986656800-224</Id><Title>Did he, or didn't he? Hypocrisy alert!</Title><Msg>Hypocrisy Alert: Paul Ryan Requested Obamacare Funding For His District September 6th, 2012 3:34 pm Henry Decker Recently uncovered evidence shows that Paul Ryan quietly requested Affordable Care Act funding while simultaneously campaigning for the law to be repealed, in one of his most glaring acts of hypocrisy yet. Lee Fang reports in The Nation that Ryan wrote a letter to the Department of Health and Human Services on December 10, 2010, recommending a grant to build a new facility in his district. As Fang points out, “The grant Ryan requested was funded directly by the Affordable Care Act, better known simply as healthcare reform or Obamacare.” Ryan’s letter can be seen here. While trying to build a community health clinic shouldn’t be controversial, it is when the request comes from Rep. Ryan. Over the past three years, Ryan has been one of the most vocal opponents of the law that he calls an abomination. Yet it didn’t stop him from requesting “job killing,” “budget busting” funds for his district. Apparently, while Ryan thinks that health care rights “come from nature and God,” he acknowledges that money for his district comes from the government. This isn’t the first time that Ryan has been caught using a government program that he derides; in August, it was revealed that Ryan had requested stimulus money while simultaneously claiming that “I’m not one who votes for something and then writes to the government to ask them to send us money.” As Bill Clinton said last night: “it takes some brass” to be Paul Ryan.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346986656800</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 22:57:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346987424422-225</Id><Topic><Title>Independent Fact Checking Organizations say</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346975757961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:55:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Duh, it's obvious those "fact-checkers" are in the realm of the liberal media, or as I call it, reality...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1346987424422</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:10:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346988422827-226</Id><Title>WHAT A PATHETIC, SAD FIGURE OBAMA WAS IN HIS "SPEECH" TONIGHT</Title><Msg>teary-eyed, crying, begging us to keep his job. Based on what you bum!!? You never gave an honest day's work in your commie life! Get the he ll out of here before the tar and feathers and rail are borught in and let someone who knows what he's doing take the reins! AHHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346988422827</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:27:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346988574350-227</Id><Title>What a Pathetic, sad figure the Mutt was in his "acceptance" speech tonight</Title><Msg>teary-eyed, crying, begging us to keep his job. Based on what you bum!!? You never gave an honest day's work in your commie life! Get the hell out of here before the tar and feathers and rail are brought in and let someone who knows what he's doing take the reins! AHHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1346988574350</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:29:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346988634234-228</Id><Topic><Title>Netanyahu chews out US ambassador over Obama Iran policy</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346982259528</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 21:44:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>FU and Israel !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346988634234</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:30:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346989087257-229</Id><Title>The MUTT was a Pathetic Figure tonight in his talk before the CON-vention!</Title><Msg>teary-eyed, crying, begging us to keep his job. Based on what you bum!!? You never gave an honest day's work in your commie life! Get the he ll out of here before the tar and feathers and rail are borught in and let someone who knows what he's doing take the reins!</Msg><Username>nomorebama_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346989087257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346989127429-230</Id><Topic><Title>The MUTT was a Pathetic Figure tonight in his talk before the CON-vention!</Title><Username>nomorebama_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346989087257</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:38:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will landslide AGAINST him!</Msg><Username>nomorebama_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346989127429</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346989138469-231</Id><Topic><Title>Independent Fact Checking Organizations say</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346975757961</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 19:55:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes the republican media does not have fact checkers, They just swallow the story and then rush to the front of the line and ask for a second facial.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346989138469</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346989227508-232</Id><Title>OBAMA LOOKED PATHETIC TONIGHT</Title><Msg>sad, begging for votes like a little teary-eyed crybaby. Shameless.</Msg><Username>nomorebama_2012</Username><Timestamp>1346989227508</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:40:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346989932162-233</Id><Title>Obama Perptuating Yet another MASSIVE FRAUDon the weak-minded</Title><Msg>Did you see those misty-eyed fawning #$%$ being duped once again by the con job liar?</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1346989932162</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-06 23:52:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>