<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-23"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348373340947-1</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(Secret revealed: Ohio woman unknowingly married father) Was Barack Hussein Obama's mother in Ohio?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348373340947</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:09:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348375264072-2</Id><Topic><Title>the rich C-riminal with Swiss Bank Accounts and businesses in Bermuda and the Cayman Islands paid just 14% in taxes. This is incredible. I go to work every day and pay more than twice in taxes than this c-riminal does. This c-riminal "legitimately" raped companies, outsourced the jobs overseas and stole billions from the shareholders. Now he wants to buy the presidency. Jail this c-riminal immediately.</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1348326645525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 11:10:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The Romneys have provided extensive information about their personal finances, including over 1,200 pages of federal tax returns that are now public on this website. Also posted is a letter from the Romneys' tax preparer, PricewaterhouseCoopers, LLP, which gives an overview of the Romneys' tax returns covering an additional 20 years, from 1990-2009. Governor Romney's tax returns show: First, as a successful businessman, Governor Romney has not only added value to our economy through his investment and business activity, but he has paid millions in taxes every year to the U.S. government. Second, the Romneys take to heart "to whom much is given, of him shall much be required." Accordingly, they have been generous in their charitable giving, donating over $7 million between 2010-2011 – donating more to charity than they paid in federal income taxes. Third, Mitt Romney has scrupulously complied with the U.S. tax code, and his income is reported and taxed at the applicable rates, and he has paid 100 percent of what he has owed. In addition, Gov. Romney has released nine financial disclosures since 2002, which are also posted on this site. There are 3 federal Public Financial Disclosures (from 2007, 2011, and 2012), and 6 Massachusetts Statements of Financial Interests (from 2002, 2003, 2004, 2005, 2006, and 2007). With a decade's worth of financial disclosure documents and the Romneys' recent tax returns, the American people have extensive information about their personal finances, above and beyond what is required by the law."</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1348375264072</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 00:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348387417983-3</Id><Title>Obama knew the embassy was under attack and went to sleep.</Title><Msg>Forget the 3 AM phone call. Obama couldn’t even be trusted with an 11 PM phone call. They say that only a man with a clear conscience, or no conscience at all, can sleep this way. But hey, he had to be rested for the next fundraiser and the next party. Jay-Z and Beyonce, unlike dead ambassadors and Libyan militias, actually matter. Barack Obama knew of the attack on the Libyan consulate within 90 minutes of it beginning. There is no doubt that Obama knew that the attacks involved AK-47s, along with Rocket propelled grenades. He knew that his ambassador was in grave danger and yet knowing all of this, and not knowing the status of Ambassador Stevens, Obama went quietly to sleep. I am sure he was dreaming of Beyonce instead of the Wookie Michelle.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348387417983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 04:03:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406296717-4</Id><Title>Why does the Pentagon get all this money? yet Wingnuts say it's not enough</Title><Msg>July was a tough month for the Pentagon. The Washington Post revealed that three U.S. special operations soldiers died in Mali when their vehicle plunged off a bridge with three Moroccan prostitutes in the vehicle at the time. The special inspector general for Iraq reconstruction issued one of his final reports on U.S. reconstruction efforts in that country and estimated that $6 billion to $8 billion of the $51 billion spent on reconstruction was likely wasted, embezzled, or misplaced. The inspector general's investigations have produced 90 indictments, 72 convictions, and $177 million in fines and other penalties, with the highest percentage of convictions coming against military officers and defense contractors. Worse still, this came not long after the bean counters at the Government Accountability Office had issued yet another damning report on the F-35 Joint Strike Fighter, finding that the cost estimate for developing the F-35 had jumped an additional $15 billion since 2010. The reaction from the political class was swift and decisive, but not in the way you would think. Republican standard-bearer Mitt Romney called for an additional $2.1 trillion in defense spending over the next decade and called for adding 100,000 additional active-duty military personnel -- even as the United States winds down wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. The ranking Democrat on the House Armed Services Committee, Adam Smith, made an impassioned plea supporting the Defense Department's foreign assistance programs. And much of Congress continues to react as if sequestration budget cuts -- a sword of Damocles that they themselves voted for -- would prove apocalyptic even though they only reduce Pentagon spending to 2006 levels. The Pentagon has become the federal bureaucracy's version of a perpetual motion machine. Despite the fact that the military budget has roughly doubled over the last decade and the United States spends more on defense than China, Britain, France, Japan, Russia, Saudi Arabia, Germany, India, and Brazil combined, most members of Congress continue to see a vote for more defense spending as the safest vote in town. And for good reason. But because voting for defense spending is a painless vote for members of Congress, more and more lobbyists and interest groups have pushed their activities under the broad umbrella of the Pentagon in order to find safe harbor. This has led to the Pentagon to take on more and more activities that have very little to do with traditional definitions of national security. Take breast cancer, for example. As the Post notes, the Pentagon has received more than $3.6 billion for cancer research over the last 20 years, despite the fact that no president has ever requested this funding and that breast cancer research has nothing to do with the Pentagon's traditional limited purview in health -- battlefield medicine. Iowa Sen. Tom Harkin once bragged to his constituents that he had been able to double spending on breast cancer research by putting the additional funds in the Pentagon's budget. Of course, since the Defense Department doesn't have much expertise in breast cancer research, it turns around and relies on agencies like the National Institutes of Health, where the money should have been put in the first place, to oversee its grants under these programs. But Congress is not solely to blame for the Pentagon's ever growing mandate. The Defense Department itself has become increasingly fixated on the idea of "expeditionary economics." In a nutshell, the concept is that small teams of military professionals well versed in economics will be deployed to assist in the reconstruction of war-torn and disaster-prone countries. Any post-conflict expert worth his or her salt agrees that getting economic life restarted after a conflict is vital. However, the idea of putting an institution that has become synonymous with billion-dollar cost overruns in charge of setting economic policy in postwar settings seems risible. Indeed, there is probably no agency in the world that has been more insulated from basic economic realities over the last decade than the Pentagon. But still, no other federal agency is willing to say that the emperor across the Potomac has no clothes. Let us remember that Pentagon-led projects in Iraq and Afghanistan have been flush with cash but rife with problems. Just this week, the special inspector general for Afghanistan reconstruction reported that about $400 million in large infrastructure projects in Afghanistan are badly behind schedule and unlikely to make a dent in the Taliban insurgency. And this only underscores the Pentagon's power to get what it wants. When every other agency fails, Congress threatens to reduce its budget. When the Defense Department fails or makes grievous mistakes, it is automatically assumed that it went astray because it did not have enough money. But both Congress and the Pentagon itself should recognize the fundamental long-term risk of turning America's military budget into a catchall for everything from breast cancer research to roving teams of economists in combat boots. Military officers are great at fighting and winning wars because that is what they are trained to do. It's bad enough that there are already more people in U.S. military bands than in the entire Foreign Service, but does the country really want to train fighting men and women to build swimming pools in Iraq? The more amorphous America makes the U.S. military's purpose as an institution, the more likely the Pentagon will turn into a giant, muddled marshmallow of bureaucratic excess. Back in the 1990s, Republicans routinely wrung their hands over the idea that "mission creep" was undermining the military. Those concerns seem to have been quietly set aside as both parties acquiesce in building a military that can't say no. With major budget battles brewing, don't be surprised when people try to slip everything from domestic road building to arts funding into the behemoth defense budget. Oh, wait, those have already happened.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348406296717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:18:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348406424516-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why does the Pentagon get all this money? yet Wingnuts say it's not enough</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348406296717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:18:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And wingnuts scream about 500 million wasted on Solyndra?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348406424516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:20:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406639982-6</Id><Title>Mitt Ronmey is slipping in the polls,,big time,,,,whats wrong?????</Title><Msg>Nothing but a empty suit</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1348406639982</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:23:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406700907-7</Id><Title>Mitt Ronmey wants to take regulations off Wall Street and Banks,,,,do you?????</Title><Msg>I sure dont</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1348406700907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:25:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348406777177-8</Id><Title>Mitt Ronmey must think all americans are stupid==SHOW YOUR TAXES</Title><Msg>What are you hiding??</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1348406777177</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348407739750-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ignore the polls saying Obama is going to win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348279149749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At best now the polls are tied both Gallup and Rasmussen say so. And Scott Peley is an Arrogant A Hole. The undecided break hard for the challenger, so Romney is ahead.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348407739750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348407830682-10</Id><Topic><Title>Obama knew the embassy was under attack and went to sleep.</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348387417983</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 04:03:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama went to sleep, sleep, dreaming about someone that ain't his wife. Obama sleeps, the Embassy Burns.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348407830682</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:43:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348407847684-11</Id><Title>ISN'T IT GREAT TO KNOW ROMNEY WILL BE THE NEXT PRESIDENT? AND OBIMBO GONE!!!</Title><Msg>Truly, morning in America! Such a relief to know sanity, probity, intelligence and savvy is returning to the White House and Senate!! All of America will breathe a sigh of relief when Romney is seen to be the new President in November!!! WHAT JOY!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348407847684</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:44:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348407961194-12</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the world is a broken place. That is the message of Jesus... Redemption is available, in the meantime, hold on</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348407961194</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:46:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348407992033-13</Id><Title>Romney Overpaid on his taxes, and paid more to Charity than both Obama and Biden earn</Title><Msg>Romney is a decent man, and he is running against idiots, who go to sleep while the country is being attacked.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348407992033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:46:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348408136877-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ignore the polls saying Obama is going to win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348279149749</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 21:59:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Sunday shows President Obama and Mitt Romney each attracting support from 46% of voters nationwide. Three percent (3%) prefer some other candidate, and five percent (5%) are undecided. See daily tracking history. When “leaners” are included, the candidates are tied at 48%. Leaners are those who are initially uncommitted to the two leading candidates but lean towards one of them when asked a follow-up question. Obama is supported by 89% of Democrats. Romney gets the vote from 85% of Republicans and holds a 12-point advantage among unaffiliated voters. Fifty-eight percent (58%) of Republican voters are following the race on a daily basis, along with 47% of Democrats. Interest in the race is often a good indicator of turnout. Platinum Members can see demographic breakdowns, voter intensity and additional information from the tracking poll on a daily basis.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348408136877</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:48:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348408218498-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Overpaid on his taxes, and paid more to Charity than both Obama and Biden earn</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348407992033</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:46:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut up Harry Reid and show your taxes</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348408218498</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:50:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348408362184-16</Id><Title>ISN'T IT TIME FOR ALL DEMOCRATS TO SLINK BACK INTO THE SLIME FROM WHICH THEY EMERGED?</Title><Msg>seriously, it must be embarrassing to be a Democrat with 50 million Americans out of work...an amazing number of people, looking for work and unable to find a job due to Obimbo's policies... WOW, DEMOCRATS, GO HOME, SLINK AND SLITHER BACK TO YOUR DENS...and hide</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348408362184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:52:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348408403707-17</Id><Topic><Title>### CSCO Featured on Squawk Box ###</Title><Username>culttradeers</Username><Timestamp>1347910268996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:31:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like it</Msg><Username>jackalbert205</Username><Timestamp>1348408403707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 09:53:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348409435794-18</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes people hold on for another 2,012 years. Just hang in there !!! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348409435794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348409680940-19</Id><Topic><Title>Lindsay Graham, R-SC “The demographics race we’re losing badly,” said Sen. Lindsey O. Graham (S.C.). “We’re not generating enough angry white guys to stay in business for the long term.” --Washington Post, August 29, 2012</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348246775996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-21 12:59:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morning reminder of what the GOP thinks the core of their base is. Stupid old angry white guys still stick to them like dog shjjjt to a shoe.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348409680940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:14:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348410314046-20</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Surf's brother and sister had married each other,maybe he wouldn't be called the family bastid.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348410314046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348411443696-21</Id><Title>We were safe under GWB, AHAHHHAAAH</Title><Msg>Fox's McGlowan: Under Bush We Knew We Were Protected and Had 'Peace Through Power' Posted: 23 Sep 2012 07:00 AM PDT From Fox's America's News Headquarters this Saturday, after endless segments throughout the morning attacking the Obama administration for the response to the embassy attack in Libya and carping about whether they should have known or announced immediately that they considered it a terrorist attack, the audience was treated to this segment where Fox regular Angela McGlowan tied herself in verbal knots pretending that George W. Bush somehow kept the country safe from terrorism. MCGLOWAN: Foreign policy is very important. National security is very important. Jamie, if we don't protect homeland, we're not going to have an economy. And Julie, he might have come out and said that this was a terrorist attack, the day of, but Jay Carney, our U.S. ambassador and Sec. Clinton all said that these were spontaneous attacks. And now we know, we have information that was classified, that's now being released that this was a planned terror attack and the problem is, we don't know what our national security plan is. When we had President Bush, we knew where we stood. We knew we were protected. We knew we had power through strength, strength through power, or peace through strength... strength... peace through power. The bottom line is this. With this administration, we don't have that. And we're not secure. Someone needs to remind this ding-dong that 9-11 along with a number of other attacks happened on Bush's watch and that his policy of invading countries that were not a threat to us did nothing to keep us "safer." As for the rest of the verbal diarrhea that came out of her mouth, I'm not even going to try to begin to interpret that nonsense.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348411443696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348411491763-22</Id><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Msg>The media insist that Mitt Romney is running a bad campaign. Whether that’s true or not, one thing is certain: Barack Obama’s campaign is undoubtedly worse. From day one, Obama’s re-election effort has been a microcosm of his failures in office. Here is a list of the top ten Obama campaign disasters--and there are still six weeks to go! 1. AttackWatch The sequel to Obama’s “Fight the Smears” website from 2008, and his “flag@whitehouse.gov” rat-out-your-neighbors effort during the Obamacare debate, #AttackWatch was part of a larger effort to target Obama’s opponents for confrontation. Conservatives quickly defused AttackWatch by spoofing it--and even the mainstream media was forced to acknowledge (briefly) Obama’s thin-skinned and vindictive tactics. 2. Charlotte Democrats hoped to expand on their gains in 2008 by hosting their 2008 convention in North Carolina. But unions balked at North Carolina’s right-to-work laws, and Democrats--having demonized banks--were embarrassed that Obama was to hold his acceptance speech in the outdoor Bank of America Stadium. In the end, the Obama campaign couldn’t even fill enough seats, and had to move the speech back indoors. 3. Joe Soptic’s Wife How desperate do you have to be to accuse your opponent of killing an innocent woman? That’s what the Obama camp did when Obama’s super PAC aired a commercial featuring untrue claims by Joe Soptic, a man laid off at a company once owned by Bain Capital. The Obama campaign claimed they had no knowledge of Soptic’s crazy story--until it was revealed that they had touted it on a conference call. 4. “Felon” In another sign of desperation, the Obama campaign alleged that Romney may have committed a felony in signing Bain Capital’s reports to the SEC after Romney was no longer actively running the company. Even the Obama-friendly fact-checkers at mainstream news outlets weren’t buying that one. Given the chance to back away from his campaign’s outrageously false accusation, President Obama doubled down on it. 5. “You Didn’t Build That” When Obama decided to mock small business owners and the idea of individual achievement, he gave Romney a much-needed opportunity to clarify his differences with the president, and rally support around his economic policy. “You Didn’t Build That” became the main knock on Obama at the Republican National Convention, and was a consistent punching bag in ads targeted at swing states. 6. Won’t Say if America is Better Off Than Four Years Ago Every single Obama surrogate--even head guru David Axelrod himself--failed to answer the most basic question a president running for re-election must face: are we better off than we were four years ago? In their defense, Obama himself had already acknowledged that we aren’t, so the responsibility for that particular bungle goes straight to the man on top. 7. Biden “Back in Chains” Vice President effectively conceded to newly-nominated Romney running mate Paul Ryan when he embarrassed the Obama campaign in August by warning a largely black audience that Romney would “put y’all back in chains.” The campaign, typically, refused to denounce Biden’s racial scare-mongering. But Biden sealed impressions of him as incompetent--even in the mainstream media. 8. Jerusalem Floor Fight Obama broke his 2008 campaign promise to recognize Jerusalem as Israel’s capital--and Democrats changed their platform to conform to his new policy. When outrage erupted over the omission of pro-Israel language, and any mention of God, in the party platform, Obama forced through amendments--but not before a noisy floor fight made it clear where many in the party actually stood. 9. 9/11 Embassy Attacks Not only did Obama fail to protect the ambassador in Libya and the embassy in Cairo, but he also kowtowed to the attackers over any offense caused by an anti-Muslim film, propagating the lie that the film provoked the attacks, and giving Romney an opening on foreign policy. Obama--campaigning rather than governing--compounded the damage with a gaffe claiming that Egypt was no longer an ally. 10. Giving Up on “Change” Facing tough questions for virtually the first time on the campaign trail, Obama told a Univision audience that, after four years in office, he did not believe he could change Washington “from inside.” Romney immediately pounced--and left-wing critics of Obama agreed--on what became a metaphor for Obama’s failure to fulfill the ambitious, messianic hopes of his 2008 campaign--or even basic promises.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348411675184-23</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is a Binary Election with "no shades of gray". Obama=1 ; Romney=0</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1348411675184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:47:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348411995886-24</Id><Title>How can a country put a devote ARAB ISLAMO</Title><Msg>In any position requiring a Security Clearance, Bio lab or military ??? SELLOUT NATIONS ???</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348411995886</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:53:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348413378441-25</Id><Title>A description of Obama</Title><Msg>Ben Franklin said it best..." He who is good at making excuses, is seldom good at anything else " .</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348413378441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348413645801-26</Id><Title>Romney will win big</Title><Msg>Why? Because the vast majority of America's citizens are not stupid!</Msg><Username>gtcld_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348413645801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:20:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348417548204-27</Id><Topic><Title>A description of Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348413378441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:16:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And those that can't do, Teach, and those that can't teach, teach constitutional law at Harvard !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348417548204</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:25:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348417610629-28</Id><Title>new Election motto: Dope and Chance</Title><Msg>The Dope want's another chance.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1348417610629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:26:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348417810797-29</Id><Topic><Title>Romney will win big</Title><Username>gtcld_2000</Username><Timestamp>1348413645801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 11:20:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad that Romney is right that the 47% will vote for the freebees and Obama. Romney's point was that talking about tax cuts doesn't matter if you don't pay taxes. My question is of the 47% how many should pay 5% or 10%, and how many are not means tested to see if they need these programs and freebees , many can afford to pay for themselves, and would rather that you carry them for a lifetime,, lazy slobs that is what they are.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348417810797</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348418275452-30</Id><Title>Obama wants to release one third of Gitmo Terrorists</Title><Msg>This guy doesn't learn, the latest attack on the US Embassy has been linked to a Gitmo terrorist that was previously released President Barack Obama is about to release or transfer 55 Gitmo prisoners, despite reports that the Libyan believed to be behind the killing of US Ambassador Christopher Stevens was a former Guantanamo inmate transferred to Libyan custody. The large percentage of those scheduled to be released are Yemeni, according to a list made public by the Obama administration. Obama stopped the release or transfer of Yemeni inmates in 2010, because the conditions in the country were viewed as too "unsettled" at the time. A release or transfer of 55 inmates means Obama is moving out one third of the prisoners at Guantanamo. And while it doesn't represent a shutdown of the facility, it's certainly indicative of a move toward that end. Could it be that Obama is trying to set himself up to campaign as the man who is taking steps to finally close Gitmo, just as he recently reversed the Afghanistan surge in order to campaign as the man who's winding down the war in the Afghanistan? The ACLU has praised the releases as "a partial victory for transparency." ______</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348418275452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:37:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348420286462-31</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If it was easy, it would be easy. Surfy, what is the purpose of 'faith'? You seem to be a man of IMMENSE FAITH, since against all obvious evidence you still think Obimbo should be re-elected. Your immediate senses tell you he is a CATASTROPHE!! Right? So, in faith, you want him to have another chance because you BELIEVE he will do better, even though the present reality tells everyone the opposite, eh? So Surfy, what about God?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1348420286462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348420533610-32</Id><Topic><Title>GODLY PUKES, PLEASE EXPLAIN THIS TO ME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348372685378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-22 23:58:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wrong, I don't think Obama is a miracle worker. I just think your party is a bunch of creeps that I would be ashamed to be associated with under any circumstances.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348420533610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:15:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348420667582-33</Id><Topic><Title>We were safe under GWB, AHAHHHAAAH</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1348411443696</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the Russians were to attack today, Bush would invade Yemen. That guy should have stayed in his preferred vocation...CLEARING BRUSH.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348420667582</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348421264475-34</Id><Title>MITT ROMNEY SAID ONLY RICH PEOPLE CAN ABORT...</Title><Msg>The poor should suck it up and act as war baby incubators. Mitt Romney's son, Tagg Romney, has been discovered to have engaged in a contract with a surrogate mother with the stipulations that if the child being carried was not up to the Romney's specifications, that the Romney family would have the final say if the child would be aborted or not. In other words the Romney family used their money to buy the power to end a human life, something that Mitt Romney has spoken out against vehemently in the past. Apparently money changes everything.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348421264475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348421959870-35</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY SAID ONLY RICH PEOPLE CAN ABORT...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348421264475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Willard was going to pull that embryo out himself if the chromosomes weren't measuring up to robot standards.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348421959870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348422136925-36</Id><Title>THE WILLARD TELLS TEACHER "SHUT YOUR MOUTH BTTTCH"</Title><Msg>When i was asked to speak with Mitt Romney it seemed like a very important thing to me, and I wanted to put a lot of careful thought into what I would say. So, I went to the round table discussion very optimistic and interested in hearing what he had to say. When he sat down, one of the first questions he asked was, he said "I understand there is a teacher here today, which one of you is a teacher?" So, I raised my hand, thinking that's a good thing, he's interested in education, but it wasn't a good thing. I felt like his view was a little old-fashioned and I was surprised by it. He went on to kind of lecture me about schools and how bad they are. He talked bad about the teacher's union. He was talking about the importance of private schools and voucher systems. At one point, I said to him, "I have an answer for that." And he said, "I didn't ask you a question."</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422136925</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:42:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348422741321-37</Id><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Msg>When The Willard bows to Obama come November, the pukes will be at a crossroad, will they follow the creeps that have brought them disaster, or will the thinking conservatives finally purge the party of the cancer of angry white trash that has turn them into a parody of themselves. Oh the irony of it all, Obama's victory has the potential to save the GOP.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348423257013-38</Id><Topic><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, Mr.Millionaire, Are you having another fun weekend all alone with your computer?? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL What a miserable existence you must have.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348423257013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:00:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348423536950-39</Id><Title>More Lame Stream Media LYING for the MEssiah</Title><Msg>Lame stream media report huge crowds of 18,000 people in Milwaukee. Problem is the venue only seats 5,000 and there were empty seats. If O'Loser is doing so good WHY does the PAthetic far left media have to lie for him? No wonder over 50% of Americans don't trust the media anymore.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348423536950</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:05:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348423577602-40</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants to release one third of Gitmo Terrorists</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348418275452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On Jan.21st, 2009 he had a big photo-op saying he would close Gitmo by 1-21-10. WELL???????</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348423577602</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:06:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348424001071-41</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY SAID ONLY RICH PEOPLE CAN ABORT...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348421264475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad your family never considered aborting you. I'm sure you've been a lifelong embarrassment for them.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348424001071</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:13:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348424131310-42</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY SAID ONLY RICH PEOPLE CAN ABORT...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348421264475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:27:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surfingforboys mommy has no clue who the father might be. LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1348424131310</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348425599411-43</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants to release one third of Gitmo Terrorists</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348418275452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama had control of both houses his first two years.You are a very poor apologist and/or liar</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348425599411</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:39:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348426459505-44</Id><Topic><Title>David Brooks: Mitt Romney Is 'The Least Popular Candidate In History'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1348426029761</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:47:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VISIT THIS WEBSITE:prioritiesusaaction DOT org/mitt-romneys-america and see MITT ROMNEYS AMERICA Mitt Romney’s America Wall Street Unregulated In Mitt Romney’s America, Washington exists to serve the interests of Wall Street. Romney approaches Wall Street with a blind eye towards its past missteps and puts full faith in the industry’s ability to police itself and act in the best interest of the country. While Romney was a strong supporter of the Wall Street bailout, he opposes tough new rules to stop Wall Street excesses from causing another crisis. Along the campaign trail, Romney has frequently railed against the new financial regulation bill and has gone on the record as favoring its repeal. The former investment banker has time and again cited the “over-regulation and burden” of financial regulation and claimed that it “caused [Wall Street] to retreat.” Gone from his stump speech is any mention of the catastrophic collapse of our financial system, the millions of middle class jobs it took with it, and the need to ensure ordinary Americans that Wall Street will never again be allowed to gamble away their retirement accounts. Main Street Isolated In Mitt Romney’s America, our country’s wealthiest 1% can expect to have a best friend and confidant in the White House while the rest of the country struggles through economic hardship. Time and again Romney has shown himself to stand firmly on the side of big business and either unable or unwilling to relate to the concerns of regular Americans. During what Mitt Romney frequently references as his “25 years spent in the private sector,” Romney took over companies and made millions in profits while laying off thousands workers and bankrupting businesses. As the New York Post wrote, “there’s little question he made a fortune from businesses he helped destroy.” Speaking in one of the states hit hardest by the foreclosure crisis, Romney told the Las Vegas Review-Journal “don’t try to stop the foreclosure process, let it run its course and hit the bottom.” Romney’s promise to repeal the financial reform bill would also eliminate the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, letting big banks continue to exploit consumers with deceptive contracts and unwarranted fees. And through it all, he has never wavered in his defense of his elite friends. “As if Wall Street greed is something new. It’s been there for a long time, and that is not the reason we had an economic meltdown,” explains candidate Romney. Middle Class Decimated Because Romney looks out for Wall Street types like himself, the middle class would be forgotten in Mitt Romney’s America. According to a recent independent analysis, even though he is worth up to $250 million, Romney only pays about 14% in federal taxes—a rate far lower than many middle class families. Romney has called for keeping tax cuts that benefit the wealthiest 1% like himself and dismissed concerns that multi-millionaires like himself are often paying a lower tax rate than teachers, cops, and construction workers. While Romney will work to keep his own tax rate low, he opposed extending the payroll tax cut that benefits working Americans. The result would be a tax increase of about $1000 for hardworking Americans. Under Romney’s watch as Massachusetts Governor, conditions for Massachusetts’ middle class worsened. The average worker saw their wages fall during the Romney years, and Massachusetts was, as one expert put it, a “national leader” in rising housing costs and experienced “high levels of outmigration from the state of young families with children.” Regarding the general failure of Romney’s governorship, a commentator wrote, “a full-time governor who is deeply committed to the economic well-being of a state’s workers can, however, make some difference. The state unfortunately did not receive such leadership over most of the past four years.” While he was Governor, Massachusetts was 47th in job creation. American Jobs Relocated As Governor of Massachusetts, Romney vetoed and attacked a bill that would have prevented state vendors from sending work overseas. Romney’s top economic advisor is an economist who endorses the practice of outsourcing jobs overseas as “probably a plus for the economy in the long run.” In his private sector career, Romney’s actions show his only concern was profit for himself and other multi-millionaire investors – the impact on American jobs was not even considered. A President with that mindset would be dangerous for American workers. Supreme Court Stacked As a candidate, Romney has promised extreme conservatives to move the Supreme Court even further to the right than it already is. When questioned, Mitt Romney has said that “I would have favored justices like Roberts and Alito, Scalia and Thomas,” and has commented that he most identifies with Justice Roberts. Romney referred to Sonya Sotomayor’s nomination as “troubling” and was open to the idea of filibustering her. With Romney’s appointments, a woman’s right to choose could be overturned, workers and consumers would find themselves at an even greater legal disadvantage, environmental laws would be threatened, and protections for minorities in America could be in jeopardy</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348426459505</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 14:54:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348435972776-45</Id><Topic><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How come Obama sealed the investigation of Boarder Agent Brian Terry? The truth is going to be available, under the Romney/Ryan Administration? Of course, not many will watch, because most Americans will be WORKING!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1348435972776</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:32:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348437408962-46</Id><Title>The big Mo</Title><Msg>OP/ED | 9/23/2012 @ 4:50PM |2,221 views Poll Shows Romney Losing Ground, Now Down By 8 Points; Wrong Track Voters At 52% + Comment now A new Zogby Poll of 860 likely voters nationwide, conducted online September 21 and 22, shows President Barack Obama opening up an 8 point lead over GOP challenger and former Massachusetts Governor Mitt Romney. Among likely voters, Obama now leads 49% to 41%; when leaners are factored in and minor party candidates are included, Obama’s lead widens to 9 points, 49%-40%, with 2% each voting for Libertarian Party candidate Gary Johnson and Green Party’s Dr. Jill Stein, and 1% for Constitution Party Virgil Goode. The poll has a margin of sampling error of +/-3.4 percentage points. Obama has a 14 point lead among independents (46% to 32%), 33 points among moderates (60% to 27%), 36 points among 18-29 year olds (65%-29%), 11 points among 30-49 year olds (48% to 37%), and is down among 50-64 year olds by only 2 points (45%-47%) and 3 points among voters over 65 (44%-47%). The President maintains his huge leads among Hispanics (68% to 26%) and African American voters (93%-0%). Romney’s lead is only 50% to 39% among white voters and 48% to 40% among evangelicals. Obama continues his lead among NASCAR fans (49% Obama to 42% Romney). I won’t say that things are spinning out of control for Romney, but I can say that things are not spinning in control. He is off message, losing ground, not connecting with his own base, being severely chastised (and even dismissed) by GOP pundits who should be his friends. There are ups and downs in presidential campaigns. For Romney, this is a real down.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348437408962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:56:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348437441546-47</Id><Topic><Title>The big Mo</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348437408962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:56:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like crazy isn't selling anymore</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348437441546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 17:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348438540728-48</Id><Title>Reince Priebus</Title><Msg>On ABC interview today talking about what a great week Mitt had last week, LOL couple more great weeks like that and Mitt will lose by the largest margin in history, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348438540728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:15:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348438833221-49</Id><Title>ouch,</Title><Msg>Stonehill College political science professor Peter Ubertaccio called the “47 percent” remark “a hand-wrapped gift to the Obama campaign.” “The damage is probably done. Any further backlash will be due to the poor handling of the response by the Romney campaign,” he said. “You don’t win by playing defense and you lose handily when you are playing horrible defense, and that’s what the Romney campaign is doing at the moment.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348438833221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:20:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348439543030-50</Id><Topic><Title>Reince Priebus</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348438540728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:15:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called political spin.Romney had a bad week .But so did Obama thanks to Jay Carney and Susan Rice treating Americans like we are stupid. The Middle East is a mess and this admin.looks lost.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348439543030</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:32:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348439605978-51</Id><Topic><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's a "boarder agent", CappyCap? Is that the part of the ATF responsible for Bed &amp; Breakfast enforcement?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348439605978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:33:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348439841425-52</Id><Topic><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you consider noting someones misspelling a valid argument to their question or do you just enjoy acting juvenile?</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348439841425</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348439927798-53</Id><Title>Remember when the baggers</Title><Msg>said the sun went around the earth and arrested Galileo for saying it didn't? said blacks weren't human? said women weren't capable of voting and should stay at home? said if man was meant to fly God would have given him wings? said vaccinations were the work of the devil and would wipe out the human race? said we needed to stop communism in Vietnam or it would take over the entire world? said global warming was a conspiracy by every national science foundation in the world? thank God the baggers haven't been able to stop the advancement of the world, The last time they controlled things they called it the dark ages.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348439927798</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348440068381-54</Id><Title>can we review?</Title><Msg>lib·er·al   [lib-er-uhl, lib-ruhl] Show IPA adjective 1. favorable to progress or reform, as in political or religious affairs. con·serv·a·tive   [kuhn-sur-vuh-tiv] Show IPA adjective 1. disposed to preserve existing conditions, institutions, etc., or to restore traditional ones, and to limit change. So when conservatives are in charge we don't advance, and they think that's a good thing?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440068381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:41:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348440139840-55</Id><Topic><Title>HOPE IS COMING TO THE GOP...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1348422741321</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 13:52:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Depends. Thanks for asking.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348440139840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:42:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348440312898-56</Id><Title>In the bagger world the pen is not mightier</Title><Msg>HOUSTON (AP) -- A Houston police officer has fatally shot a one-armed, one-legged man in a wheelchair after police say the double amputee waved a metal object that turned out to be a pen. Police spokeswoman Jodi Silva says man cornered the officer early Saturday inside a group home after police were called there to check on a disturbance. Silva says the man was making threats while trying to stab the officer with the pen. She says the officer did not know what the metal object was at the time. Silva says the man came "within inches to a foot" of the officer and did not follow instructions to calm down and remain still. Police did not immediately release the man's name. The officer, Matthew Jacob Marin, has been placed on administrative leave.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440312898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348440358085-57</Id><Topic><Title>In the bagger world the pen is not mightier</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440312898</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:45:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when asked about the incident Mitt Romney said that the man was part of the 47% so he didn't care</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440358085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348440809011-58</Id><Topic><Title>can we review?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440068381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many ids you using today? I see at least three. Ridiculous.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348440809011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:53:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348443190861-59</Id><Title>Gibbs can't explain why Obama has no time for world leaders</Title><Msg>It's a game changer for the campaign and the beginning of the end for O'Loser. When Chris Wallace asked Robert Gibbs WHY President Obama can't find time to meet with world leaders BUT is finding time to appear on the View.........uh,oh, um, well, uh......I don't know EXPLAINS Gibbs.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348443190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:33:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348443427423-60</Id><Topic><Title>Gibbs can't explain why Obama has no time for world leaders</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348443190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah that's probably a game changer in the retarded world, LOL course we won't see any mention of it in the real world, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348443427423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:37:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348443533792-61</Id><Topic><Title>can we review?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440068381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I only use one id, how about you?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348443533792</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:38:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348443693833-62</Id><Topic><Title>Gibbs can't explain why Obama has no time for world leaders</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348443190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The incompetent one has time for Whoopee but no time to discuss Irans bomb with Netanyahu .Benjamin must be seething.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348443693833</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348443863695-63</Id><Topic><Title>Gibbs can't explain why Obama has no time for world leaders</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348443190861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:33:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No mention WHY, BEcause the Lame Stream Media COVER for your Messiah, the one we call O'Loser. You must enjoy his pathetic and complete incompetence.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348443863695</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:44:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348444062869-64</Id><Topic><Title>can we review?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348440068381</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 18:41:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a phony. I' dont lie about my riches,education,vacations,family,etc.like you do . I also try to refrain from silly posts like you just did about Romney and the man slain in a wheelchair . Really childish for a " highly" educated individual like you.LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348444062869</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348444343528-65</Id><Title>Lame stream media outlet CNN had Ambassadors Diary</Title><Msg>CNN hid Libyan Ambassador Chris Stevens diary for days KNOWING that the Obama administration was LYING about the events that unfolded. EVERYDAY that the Whitehouse told LIEs to the american public, CNN knew the truth. The Ambassadors diary even showed his worries about security, the administratio KNEW the whole time. TIME for impeachment hearings.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348444343528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:52:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348445516003-66</Id><Topic><Title>Lame stream media outlet CNN had Ambassadors Diary</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348444343528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did Susan Rice do the Sunday shows again today lying to the American public???</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348445516003</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:11:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348445842131-67</Id><Title>Egypt doesn't loves us anymore</Title><Msg>President Morsi today essentially told America to eff off . Whatever happened to" our buddy Mubarak"?? You know the dictator we controlled and Obama had kicked out and now Egypt has a dictator who hates us.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348445842131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348446599323-68</Id><Title>Calling Israel's concern about existential nuke Iran , "NOISE" will lose Obama votes</Title><Msg>In an interview to air tonight on CBS's 60 Minutes, President Barack Obama will refer to Israel's concern over Iran's march toward a nuclear program as "noise." NO SWEAT—I’LL JUST MAKE A SPEECH. "When it comes to our national security decisions -- any pressure that I feel is simply to do what's right for the American people. And I am going to block out -- any noise that's out there," Obama says, according to AFP. AFP also reports that Obama will say that "he understands and agrees with Netanyahu's insistence that Iran not be allowed to obtain nuclear weapons as this would threaten both countries, the world in general, and kick off an arms race." But, as the article points out, Obama will not be meeting with Netanyahu this week during the United Nations General Assembly. Romney, who also is interviewed on 60 Minutes tonight, will say, that Obama not meeting with Netanyahu "is a mistake and sends a message throughout the Middle East that somehow we distance ourselves from our friends and I think the exact opposite approach is what's necessary." With tens of thousands of Americans living in Israel and there relatives living here in Ohio, Florida, Pennsylvania and Nevada, Obama's insensitivity to their survival is callous.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348446599323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348446647394-69</Id><Topic><Title>Lame stream media outlet CNN had Ambassadors Diary</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348444343528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 19:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here's my one post for your Junior id. I dont play kid games like you .Try to act like an adult and we can converse. Other than that, leave me alone.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348446647394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348446879523-70</Id><Topic><Title>Egypt doesn't loves us anymore</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348445842131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Call your Senator they are going to debate a motion by Rand Paul to cut Egyptian aide off. I happen to agree with Rand, we have a lot of enemies we give foreign aide to that don't deserve it. Our credit rating just went down again, and we can't afford to support Rich Mooslims who are gouging us with $97 dollar per barrel oil.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348446879523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:34:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348447626572-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Further proof Obama is running a worse campaign than Romney, is his callous flippant statement tonight on 60 minutes In an interview to air tonight on CBS's 60 Minutes, President Barack Obama will refer to Israel's concern over Iran's march toward a nuclear program as "noise." NO SWEAT—I’LL JUST MAKE A SPEECH. "When it comes to our national security decisions -- any pressure that I feel is simply to do what's right for the American people. And I am going to block out -- any noise that's out there," Obama says, according to AFP. AFP also reports that Obama will say that "he understands and agrees with Netanyahu's insistence that Iran not be allowed to obtain nuclear weapons as this would threaten both countries, the world in general, and kick off an arms race." But, as the article points out, Obama will not be meeting with Netanyahu this week during the United Nations General Assembly. Romney, who also is interviewed on 60 Minutes tonight, will say, that Obama not meeting with Netanyahu "is a mistake and sends a message throughout the Middle East that somehow we distance ourselves from our friends and I think the exact opposite approach is what's necessary."</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348447626572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:47:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448053168-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants to release one third of Gitmo Terrorists</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348418275452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior your IQ is still going down, Obama wants to set all the America Hating Killers loose. Only problem for his is that these POS human refuse have no place to go because their countries of origin don't want them either. Iran will take them, because they fit in with our mortal enemies. Only a nutcase like you think letting homicidal maniacs loose is humanitarian. Junior , shut up and go sit in the corner.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348448053168</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:54:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348448087514-73</Id><Title>spend another 4 trillion?</Title><Msg>I'd rather save medicare, but hey that's just me, the GOP thinks it's better to start another useless war“ If Governor Romney is suggesting that we should start another war, he should say so,” Obama said in an interview for CBS’s “60 Minutes” program, being broadcast tonight, as world leaders, including Obama, prepare to attend the United Nations General Assembly meeting in New York tomorrow.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348448087514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448205094-74</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Never underestimate your opponent .Obama as a president is a dud. But his people know how to campaign. Remember what happened to the Clintons. They were"unbeatable". As bad as Obama's presidency has been he still holds a slight lead over Romney. Axelrod is a slime but he knows what he is doing.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348448205094</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:56:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448302389-75</Id><Topic><Title>spend another 4 trillion?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348448087514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How useless your life must be to spend 24/7 being the little puppet of Media Matters. Your life must be real sheit....... Sad if you ask me....</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348448302389</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:58:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448430027-76</Id><Topic><Title>spend another 4 trillion?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1348448087514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:54:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I saw Obama say just last week that Iraq/Afghanistan cost one trillion .Yet you continue with that far left lie of four trillion .Or do you know more than Obama??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348448430027</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:00:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448491493-77</Id><Topic><Title>Obama wants to release one third of Gitmo Terrorists</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348418275452</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 12:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must put junior on ignore like the rest of us have. He is an IDIOT...</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348448491493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:01:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348448945887-78</Id><Topic><Title>Egypt doesn't loves us anymore</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348445842131</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rands proposal lost 81 - 10. We keep sending money to those trying to kill us. Washington is a cesspool ----both parties.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1348448945887</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 21:09:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1348453346266-79</Id><Title>Top Hedge Fund Manager Warns on Hitler Scenario: Billionaire hedge fund manager Ray Dalio appeared on CNBC this morning and warned of potential social unrest and what it could mean.</Title><Msg>Top Hedge Fund Manager Warns on Hitler Scenario: Billionaire hedge fund manager Ray Dalio appeared on CNBC this morning and warned of potential social unrest and what it could mean. Billionaire hedge fund manager Ray Dalio appeared on CNBC this morning and warned of potential social unrest and what it could mean. Dalio said (via BI): I don't know whether we're beyond the point of being able to successfully manage this. And I worry then about – social disruption. I worry about – another leg down in the economies – causing – social disruptions. Because deleveraging – can be very painful, it depends how they're managed. But when people – get at each other's throat, the rich and the poor and the left and the right and so on, and you have a basic breakdown,that becomes very threatening. And for example, Hitler came to power in 1933, which was the depth of the Great Depression because of the social tension between the factions. So I think it very much is dependent on how the people work this through together and worry about the social elements. This is not the only major player I have heard this from. There are others who believe the die is cast and that it will be near impossible to get out of the current environment without major unrest (in the U.S.), and once the unrest hits, it is unclear what will emerge.</Msg><Username>singhlion2001</Username><Timestamp>1348453346266</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 22:22:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348456110127-80</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are full of #$%$. Obama is leading in the polls!!!!</Msg><Username>dilip007dalal</Username><Timestamp>1348456110127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:08:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348457094828-81</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh how we forgot the masterful karl rove and the idiot that got us into the mess we are in now and you think that the money launderer with his secret bank accounts is going to be the savior.</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1348457094828</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1348457664125-82</Id><Topic><Title>Calling Israel's concern about existential nuke Iran , "NOISE" will lose Obama votes</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348446599323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 20:29:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since when does a petty country dictate to the United States. Yes I said petty because that s what Isreal is and it would not exist if it were not for the USA. The people that say they have a right to Jeresulem are ful;l of S__t, the Romans kicked there sorry #$%$ out 2000 years ago and they have no country if it were not for the USA, so remember who dictates to who and it sure is'nt bibi.</Msg><Username>chgjt</Username><Timestamp>1348457664125</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 23:34:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>