<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-17"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347854751230-1</Id><Topic><Title>We can balance the budget and not cut Defense!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347849408461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 22:36:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I want to read the real Ivan not a dumb Ivan, Bad enough we have a dumb Obama</Msg><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1347854751230</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 00:05:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347856678492-2</Id><Topic><Title>who killed Jesus?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347839773779</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 19:56:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fugoff with the anti-Semitic bull/s/h/y/t, Ivanka. (And just fyi, I seem to remember it was the ROMANS who had the crucifixion fetish.)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347856678492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 00:37:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347874276925-3</Id><Topic><Title>U.N. Ambassador Rice is incompetent</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347811671567</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 12:07:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But she has such an authoritative voice like obama which says she is right and would never try to cover her #$%$ ! Perception perception perception... Dim Libs want packaging NOT content !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1347874276925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 05:31:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347881437984-4</Id><Title>It's never a stock bubble until it bursts</Title><Msg>Housing bubble was 'not a bubble', until it popped. DOW 14,000 was not a bubble until it hit DOW 6,600. Sell stocks and bonds with abandon. Buy after 50%-80% declines.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1347881437984</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:30:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347881455047-5</Id><Title>When will Obumbles help get teachers back to work?</Title><Msg>In previous speeches he says he will stand shoulder to shoulder with them in the picket line. Seems the kids are the ones hurting here while the Unions and Obama sit back and wait. WHY isn't the President discussing this? Notice the HYPOCRISY of the left when they attacked Scott Walker over Union issues but SAY NOTHING and are virtually SILENT when it's a Democrat at the heart of this.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347881455047</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:30:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347881686500-6</Id><Topic><Title>Watching FOX NEWS- Chris Wallace stating that ROMNEY is LOSING NOW! BWHAHAAA!!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1347822989841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 15:16:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you denying that Chris Wallace said that? Keep your friends close &amp; your enemies closer!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347881686500</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:34:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347882412736-7</Id><Topic><Title>THE REPUKE NUTWINGS CONCLUSION OF WHY ROMNEY IS FAILING</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347814952861</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 13:02:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sssssssssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347882412736</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:46:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347882486306-8</Id><Topic><Title>Santorum!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347801586300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 09:19:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aaaaaaaaa</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347882486306</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:48:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347882628791-9</Id><Topic><Title>a post from another recovering republican</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347756241117</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 20:44:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sssssssssssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347882628791</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:50:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347882760772-10</Id><Topic><Title>Romney vows when he is president</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347747981941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 18:26:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>personal attacks = you lost the argument !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347882760772</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347882822106-11</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt ain't no Ronald Raygun</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347718651471</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:17:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>personal attacks = you lost the argument</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347882822106</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347883041673-12</Id><Topic><Title>That 3 am Phone Call I keep thinking about that 3:00 am call at the White House. I don't want it to be Mittens who answers. Do you?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347557998369</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-09-13 13:39:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347883041673</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:57:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347883061569-13</Id><Topic><Title>Last REPUB to choose a CONGRESSMAN as VP RUNNING MATE - BARRY GOLDWATER in 1964 There has been a reason why this was never done in MAGOO's LIFETIME until now! (GOP IS VERY DESPERATE)</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1347644849779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-14 13:47:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xxxxxx</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1347883061569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 07:57:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347883957181-14</Id><Title>23 MILLION unemployed Americans</Title><Msg>Nuff said folks. Good old hope and change, courtesy of O'Loser.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347883957181</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347884123375-15</Id><Title>Worker participation rate LOWEST in 31 years.</Title><Msg>This is Oblamo's economy. His record is abysmal. SHELLACKING 2.0 coming in November.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347884123375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:15:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347885232762-16</Id><Title>Poverty rate at 50 year HIGH.</Title><Msg>46.2 Million people remain below the poverty line. I thought Obama was for the little guy, maybe if he focused MORE on putting those people to work instead of trying to figure out how to GIVE them a free lunch they would be better off. How can you focus on he economy when you have spent the last 2 years campaigning, 100 rounds of golf, and 5 times more vacations than the average American takes. This bozo is completely out of touch.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347885232762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:33:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347885341276-17</Id><Topic><Title>Worker participation rate LOWEST in 31 years.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347884123375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Post hidden because you ignored this user ".......... LMMFAO at the retards.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347885341276</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:35:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347886007145-18</Id><Title>woopsie</Title><Msg>Top story: Romney campaign in disarray Mike Allen and Jim Vandehei reveal the disarray within the struggling Romney campaign: ”Stuart Stevens, Mitt Romney’s top strategist, knew his candidate’s convention speech needed a memorable mix of loft and grace if he was going to bound out of Tampa with an authentic chance to win the presidency. So Stevens, bypassing the speechwriting staff at the campaign’s Boston headquarters, assigned the sensitive task of drafting it to Peter Wehner, a veteran of the last three Republican White Houses and one of the party’s smarter wordsmiths. Not a word Wehner wrote was ever spoken. Stevens junked the entire thing, setting off a chaotic, eight-day scramble that would produce an hour of prime-time problems for Romney.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347886007145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:46:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347886093743-19</Id><Title>if you can't manage a campaign</Title><Msg>you can't manage a whole country The bottom line of the Politico story: ”Romney associates are baffled that such a successful corporate leader has created a team with so few lines of authority or accountability.” Romney’s mishandling of the Middle East crisis was driven by desperation. ”Suddenly, the president was facing just the kind of externality that his team had been bracing for: a full-blown ­foreign-policy crisis less than eight weeks out from Election Day. And a campaign marked by stasis and even torpor was jolted to life as if by a pair of defibrillator paddles applied squarely to its solar plexus. Moments like this are not uncommon in presidential elections, and when they come, they tend to matter. For unlike the posturing and platitudes that constitute the bulk of what occurs on the campaign trail, big external events provide voters with something authentic and valuable: a real-time test of the temperament, character, and instincts of the men who would be commander-in-chief. And when it comes to the past week, the divergence between the resulting report cards could hardly be more stark…Here was ­America under attack, with four dead on foreign soil. And here was Romney, defiantly refusing to adopt a tone of sobriety, solemnity, or seriousness, instead attempting to score cheap political points, doubling down on his criticism.” John Heilemann in New York Magazine. @pourmecoffee: If the Romney campaign were the Salt Lake Olympics, they’d be calling Romney in to run it about now.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347886093743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347886358927-20</Id><Title>I get a $250,000 tax cut</Title><Msg>you folks get a $2,000 increase and a cut in your social security payments, LOL heads I win, tails I win lol</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347886358927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:52:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347886422641-21</Id><Topic><Title>woopsie</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347886007145</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:46:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles campaign got caught with their pants down removing God and Jeruselum from the platform. A verbal vote AGAIN showed the disarray and FORCED agenda by the leadership. Word is the entire campaign is struggling and in disarray as the far left and the main stream liberals can't agree. Woopsie time.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347886422641</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:53:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347886701194-22</Id><Title>Obama raising taxes on EVERYONE......</Title><Msg>Unless Republicans can gain control of Washington and reverse the UNPOPULAR Obamacare. EVERYONE will see some form of tax increase. If you CHOOSE, key word here choose, not to buy Health insurance, Obama's IRS will hunt you down and FINE you. I mean TAX you. ANOTHER lie by Obumbles.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347886701194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:58:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347887420952-23</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>artiejbo639330</Username><Timestamp>1347887420952</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347887429269-24</Id><Title>losing teams often lash out at themselves</Title><Msg>Stevens enjoys little of the internal affection that surrounded the brain trusts of the Bush and Obama campaigns. “I always have the impression Stuart must save his best stuff for meetings I’m not important enough to attend,” said one Romney campaign insider. “The campaign is filled with people who spend a lot of their time either avoiding him or resisting him.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347887429269</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:10:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347887568529-25</Id><Topic><Title>REPORT: COULD TAKE ANOTHER DECADE TO RECOVER FROM THE GREAT BUSH RECESSION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347884595098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:23:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>look at japan:crash their economy, they never recovered. LoL!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1347887568529</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:12:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347888866568-26</Id><Topic><Title>Worker participation rate LOWEST in 31 years.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347884123375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad Romney isn't going after all the mistakes Obama made, his commercials are timid. Your supposed to go after the opposition , Go after Obama on the $28 billion he spent on foreign jobs, the keystone pipeline, that gas is 2x what it was 4 years ago, the 33 million unemployed. The millions he doesn't count as UE in his phony jobs numbers. The foreclosures, the bankruptcies, the closed businesses, the clip of Obama saying shovel ready wasn't so shovel ready. The Clip of Obama saying don't go to Las Vegas. GE not paying taxes, and shipping jobs to China and Immelt being the head of the jobs council, and Ge running TV networks that criticize the GOP. That was the deal they don't pay taxes in exchange for giving Obama good press and tv coverage. Lots more but Romney has to treat Obama as his white opponent, not coddle him because he is biracial</Msg><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1347888866568</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:34:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347888881814-27</Id><Title>Republican leaders like to say that federal workers are paid twice as much as those in the private sector. Yet, the federal Office of Personnel Management and unions say federal workers are paid 26% less than colleagues in the private sector. Both rely on government statistics to back up their claims.</Title><Msg>Republican leaders like to say that federal workers are paid twice as much as those in the private sector. Yet, the federal Office of Personnel Management and unions say federal workers are paid 26% less than colleagues in the private sector. Both rely on government statistics to back up their claims.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347888881814</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347888947043-28</Id><Title>Mitt hides, Obama is an open book</Title><Msg>By law, Romney and other candidates have to reveal only the names of bundlers who are lobbyists. But, Briffault said, “It goes toward the whole notion of transparency in the campaign finance system. Obviously, the money matters.” If their candidates win, bundlers are often richly rewarded with ambassadorships and other administration posts, or personal access like overnight stays in the White House. According to the Center for Public Integrity, which tracks campaign finance issues, about 80 percent of Barack Obama’s and George W. Bush’s bundlers who raised $500,000 or more went on to win appointments. Critics say that by failing to disclose the names of his bundlers, Romney is out of step with past Republican presidentidal candidates — and his own practice in 2008 — as well as that of his Democratic opponent, President Obama. Obama revealed his bundlers’ names in 2008 and is doing so again this election year. The Romney campaign won’t say why it has declined to reveal names, despite pressure to do so from advocacy groups and the Obama camp.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347888947043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347888949278-29</Id><Topic><Title>Worker participation rate LOWEST in 31 years.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347884123375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also, Romney has to bring up all Obama's past socialist associations</Msg><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1347888949278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347889041543-30</Id><Title>CSCO the dog</Title><Msg>A mangy one at that. This dog couldn't catch a car with a flat tire.</Msg><Username>lucenatraveler</Username><Timestamp>1347889041543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890416251-31</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hides, Obama is an open book</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347888947043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles REFUSED to release the names of his contributors in 2008. He had thousands form abroad. I wonder who they were. Thanks for your LIES, you typical libTURD.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347890416251</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:00:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890546483-32</Id><Topic><Title>Worker participation rate LOWEST in 31 years.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347884123375</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:15:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he should be pointing out how Obama is a muslim communist!!! Us independents are influenced to vote for Mitt when we hear you wing nuts say stupid things.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347890546483</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890727463-33</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hides, Obama is an open book</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347888947043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what wing nut made you believe that lie? December 1, 2008, 12:12 PM Obama Releases Names of Donors By MICHAEL LUO and KATHARINE Q. SEELYE Update | 9:38 p.m. President-elect Barack Obama released the list of donors to his inaugural committee on Monday, and they included noteworthy names like the movie director George Lucas and Eric Schmidt, the chief executive of Google. Out of the 1,777 people who contributed a total of $1.2 million, more than 130 gave the maximum contribution of $5,000. In capping donations at that amount, Mr. Obama’s aides have said they are trying to reduce the influence of big money in the festivities. The largest donors included many of Mr. Obama’s biggest financial bundlers, who collected more than $500,000 each during his campaign, including Robert Wolf, president of UBS Investment Bank; Orin Kramer, a New Jersey hedge-fund executive; and Mark Gorenberg, a San Francisco venture capitalist. Also donating were the financier Steven Rattner and his wife, Maureen White, who were prominent supporters of Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton’s presidential run and later also raised money for Mr. Obama. “In keeping with President-elect Obama’s pledge to run the most open and transparent transition in history, the Obama-Biden Transition Project has voluntarily chosen to release the names of its donors on a monthly basis,” a statement from the transition team says. “As of November 15, 2008, a total of $1,170,937.44 had been raised from 1,776 donors.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347890727463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347890891348-34</Id><Topic><Title>"We will never have the media on our side, ever, in this country. We will never have the elite, smart people on our side," Santorum said in a speech to the gathering of conservative activists at a Washington hotel.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347800024108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-16 08:53:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>smart people don't support the GOP, according to the GOP</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347890891348</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347891403457-35</Id><Title>CSCO will trade down to low 18s</Title><Msg>Chambers is the problem. People are not convinced that CSCO can turnaround under his lacklustre leadership. He should gracefully retire and make way for a dynamic leader.</Msg><Username>gjjagan</Username><Timestamp>1347891403457</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:16:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347892366138-36</Id><Topic><Title>REPORT: COULD TAKE ANOTHER DECADE TO RECOVER FROM THE GREAT BUSH RECESSION</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347884595098</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 08:23:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How'd Greg figure it out so quick?? Took me about 7 weeks to see the boob didn't have a clue as to how to run the country.LOL Bring back Jimmy Carter!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347892366138</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:32:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347892542208-37</Id><Title>Facebook Nasdaq Stock FB has over 900 Million users. csco</Title><Msg>.......</Msg><Username>hogolddigger</Username><Timestamp>1347892542208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:35:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347893051334-38</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hides, Obama is an open book</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347888947043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You just gave the list of donors for his inaugural festivities......You jackwagon. I'm talking about his election you idiot and you know it. Where is the list of ALL the foreign donors he REFUSED to disclose? dollar to a dime says you won't rebut. any takers?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347893051334</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347894392649-39</Id><Topic><Title>Rep. Peter King (R-NY) found himself being grilled by CNN host Soledad O’Brien on Monday about the claim President Barack Obama had gone on an “apology tour” — and the congressman was unable to name a single instance in which the president had apologized for the United States.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347893411084</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 10:50:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it is where the mitt campaign is failing, they make unfounded accusations and then wonder why people don't believe what they are selling</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894392649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347894459928-40</Id><Title>Consensus on how much better off we are now then 4 years ago</Title><Msg>As politicians debate whether Americans are better off than they were four years ago, the stock market is saying yes. With 50 days before the national election, the Standard &amp; Poor’s 500 Index has rallied 82 percent to a four-year high since President Barack Obama took office. The advance puts the gauge 6.8 percent from its record, closer to the all-time high than any of the world’s biggest stock markets, data compiled by Bloomberg show. The benchmark index of American equity is trading at 14.9 times reported earnings (SPX), the biggest discount to MSCI’s global measure since March 2010. While bears say the index has risen too far, too fast given U.S. unemployment has remained above 8 percent for 43 straight months, bulls point to record earnings forecasts as evidence the economy and stocks have room to improve. Jim Chanos, who oversees about $6 billion at Kynikos Associates and profits from betting against individual stocks, says America is doing better. Goldman Sachs Group Inc.’s Abby Joseph Cohen says the firm’s “most thoughtful” clients are growing more confident. “We are in a healthier state right now,” Chris Hyzy, who helps oversee about $325 billion as chief investment officer of U.S. Trust in New York, said in a Sept. 12 phone interview. “Next year, we think the growth clip in the United States and the globe is going to be better than expected. Over the next three years, we are bullish.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894459928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:07:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347894498423-41</Id><Topic><Title>Consensus on how much better off we are now then 4 years ago</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894459928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but Mitt will continue to argue that we were better off losing 800,000 jobs a month with the stock market in a free fall</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894498423</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:08:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347894680619-42</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>jeaniernv99989</Username><Timestamp>1347894680619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347894735394-43</Id><Title>smells desperate</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON — Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney is reshaping his message from an all-economic pitch to an all-out challenge to what he argues is a failed status quo, aides said, taking a risk with barely 50 days to go in the campaign. A top Romney adviser confirmed that former Republican National Committee Chairman Ed Gillespie will have an elevated role in shaping the campaign message for the GOP nominee and that it will focus more tightly on a change-versus-status-quo strategy. The point, the aide said, is that if voters find all aspects of the status quo, including economic and foreign policy, acceptable, they should vote for Obama. But if they are fed up with what Romney argues is failure across the board by Obama, they will turn to Romney. The aide spoke on the condition of anonymity because the shift in message, and the elevation of Gillespie as its chief developer, had not yet been announced. With momentum currently on President Barack Obama’s side, Romney sought Monday to explain to voters more clearly what he would do as president, as he looked to right his struggling campaign and ease worries in Republican circles about its state seven weeks before Election Day.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894735394</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347895533813-44</Id><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Msg>Yup , and its time to close this book and move the entire library of deceit, malfeasance and inept bungling back to the city of violence, Chicago!!!! Right?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347895900312-45</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think Rush is on till 2:00, birdbrain will have to wait till then to tell you what he thinks, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347895900312</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:31:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347896109384-46</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still planning to vote for the Etch-a-Sketch/GlibFib ticket, eh Walt?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347896109384</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347897272699-47</Id><Topic><Title>Consensus on how much better off we are now then 4 years ago</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894459928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market is the result of Bernanke's easy money policy, absolutely nothing to do with Obama. Amusing that the liberal on this board castigates the one percenters but brags about how well the market has treated them. The middle and lower class in this country have done very poorly under Obama.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347897272699</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:54:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347897420446-48</Id><Title>WHO ON THIS BOARD THINKS OBIMBO IS DOING A GOOD JOB? OR REID?</Title><Msg>Wow...no one!!!!!!! Not a single poster offers one single shred of evidence that the alien in our midst, Obimbo, is helping America... True...now it's time for Romney</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347897420446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347897864196-49</Id><Topic><Title>WHO ON THIS BOARD THINKS OBIMBO IS DOING A GOOD JOB? OR REID?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347897420446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo will post under his various ids supporting Obama. He is one of those who choose idealogy over competence. I dont doubt Obama's desire to improve the country. The fact remains he is not capable.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347897864196</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:04:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347899066008-50</Id><Topic><Title>WHO ON THIS BOARD THINKS OBIMBO IS DOING A GOOD JOB? OR REID?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347897420446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I actually doubt his desire to 'improve' the country. If you mean 'improve' as defined by what most Americans feel is 'improvement'. I really do think Obama wants to see income's leveled and the influence of America on the rest of the world to be diminished. I know a lot of folks who want that same agenda. None of them should be in charge of American policy!!! I have 'friends' who believe America is raping the rest of the world. Taking copper, cobalt and banana's from every one all around the globe. Obimbo agrees with that. I don't.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347899066008</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:24:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347899231608-51</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>1.) ObamaCare is destructive, damaging and deceitfyl 2.) Present tax structure is horrid. 3.) No immigration policy by Obimbo 4.) Energy policy is similar to that of Karl Marx...take from those who have and give it to those who have not..... 5.) Golf game is great!! or good...or maybe mediocre. WE NEED TO ALLOW OBIMBO TO WORK ON HIS GOLF GAME FULL TIME, IN CHICAGO AND AWAY FROM ALL THE PRESSURES AND PROBLEMS THAT ARE MILDLY DISTRACTING HIM IN DC!!!! Agreed????</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347899231608</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347899487412-52</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An article that's worth a read.</Msg><Username>harriettemhq9110</Username><Timestamp>1347899487412</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:31:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347899690290-53</Id><Topic><Title>WHO ON THIS BOARD THINKS OBIMBO IS DOING A GOOD JOB? OR REID?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347897420446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I should have been more explicit.Obama is trying to improve the country as he sees it should be. I certainly dont agree with his way of doing it.I am amazed that so many Americans support his policies.But then it may be just apathy, not support. History shows many countries who have succumbed because of apathy. Perhaps it is our turn.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347899690290</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347900656235-54</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You still planning on continuing to make excuses for your Messiah, eh BOY. 23 million unemployed, 47 million on foodstamps, worker participation rate at 31 year lows, 44 straight months of 8% or above UE......... Keep yapping your mouth, BOY, I can do this all day. YOu know, make you look like a fool.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347900656235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:50:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347900728391-55</Id><Topic><Title>WHO ON THIS BOARD THINKS OBIMBO IS DOING A GOOD JOB? OR REID?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347897420446</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee Bird Brain, I've made millions in the market under Obama, he is by far the best president since Clinton, I understand the uneducated, unskilled haven't faired that well in the last 4 years but as the World goes international you guys are gonna continue to suffer. Still I don't think cutting your social security to give me a bigger tax cut is gonna help you much.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347900728391</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:52:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347901022544-56</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt hides, Obama is an open book</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347888947043</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 09:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HA, I told you big mouth Dumb Dumb wouldn't or couldn't rebut my FACTS. I said Obumbles REFUSED to release his contributors from his 2008 campaign, Dumb Dumb responds with Inaugural list.......This BOY is dumber than dirt.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347901022544</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 12:57:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347901945161-57</Id><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Msg>"Feds, write me a check for $1.3 Billion". Thanks 'genius'.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347901958405-58</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>dongkfy615</Username><Timestamp>1347901958405</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347902982518-59</Id><Title>SO LAST TIME YOU COMPLAINED I DIDN'T SHARE MY BUY OF GDXJ at 19s</Title><Msg>Not sure why I was supposed to make money for the Klobites that hate me. So here plebs, my gift to you because I feel sorry for your tard azzhes. Last friday I bought PGLC, 100K shares at .34. Do as you will with it.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347902982518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:29:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347904932007-60</Id><Topic><Title>SO LAST TIME YOU COMPLAINED I DIDN'T SHARE MY BUY OF GDXJ at 19s</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347902982518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:29:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BTW, the investment is speculative in nature and btch and moan about its ups and downs for the next 2 years.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347904932007</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:02:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347904949916-61</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now your guy, Obimbo, is at 4 FRICKIN' TRILLION AND COUNTING...1.3 billion sounds like a miracle of modesty and restraint!!!!! ALL HAIL ROMNEY!!!!!! surfy, you are weak..give it a rest...every time you critique Romney, you make him look better and better and Obimbo worse and worse!!! SO ACTUALLY, KEEP UP YOUR ATTACKS!!!!! he he hehehehehehhehe</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347904949916</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:02:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347904961222-62</Id><Topic><Title>SO LAST TIME YOU COMPLAINED I DIDN'T SHARE MY BUY OF GDXJ at 19s</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347902982518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:29:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I meant DON't btch and moan.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347904961222</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:02:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905135162-63</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wally, your boy loves government when it suits him. And comparing an olympic event to running a country is typical of what a bird brain you are. Pleeeeeeease. Going fishing Wally, will beat up on you later</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347905135162</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:05:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905145589-64</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep, begged gubmint for a handout. Myth RobbedMe, Salt Lake City welfare queen.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347905145589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905145679-65</Id><Topic><Title>SO LAST TIME YOU COMPLAINED I DIDN'T SHARE MY BUY OF GDXJ at 19s</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347902982518</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:29:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anyone who buys any stock touted on a message board is a fool.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347905145679</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:05:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905434058-66</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And being a community organizer is not equivalent to running a country either. Do you put much thought into your posts??</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347905434058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:10:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905546329-67</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love this report.</Msg><Username>analisacul6556</Username><Timestamp>1347905546329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:12:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905668520-68</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>UE rate 8.2%, down from 10.3%. Would be lower, but hey, BOOSCH 43 REALLY F/U/K/T US OVER BIGTIME. Wow, no wonder nobody wants to vote for Myth RobbedMe: BOOSCH 43 REALLY SUCKED A/Z/Z! He was so bad voters remember him EVEN WITHOUT a speaking slot at the RNC CONvention. You CONs can try to hide him, pretend he doesn't exist, but the STENCH gives him away every time. :D</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347905668520</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:14:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347905849826-69</Id><Topic><Title>Consensus on how much better off we are now then 4 years ago</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347894459928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:07:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The general and most accepted term for these #$%$ is HYPOCRITES. They HATE the rich but love the markets....... The markets are doing good because business is making money AS A RESULT of cutbacks, savings, slimming down.........GETTING RID OF EMPLOYEES...... LibTURDS don't get it, if it doesn't come with a free lunch they simply don't understand. SHELLACKING 2.0 in November can't come soon enough.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347905849826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347906134649-70</Id><Title>Let's see, Mitt is: Anti-women Anti-elderly Anti-disabled Anti-poor Anti-student Anti-union Anti-immigration Anti-unemployed Anti-welfare Anti-Medicare Anti-Social Security And Mitt is for: Angry OLD White men What could possibly go wrong? VOTE OBAMA 2012</Title><Msg>Let's see, Mitt is: Anti-women Anti-elderly Anti-disabled Anti-poor Anti-student Anti-union Anti-immigration Anti-unemployed Anti-welfare Anti-Medicare Anti-Social Security And Mitt is for: Angry OLD White men What could possibly go wrong? VOTE OBAMA 2012</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347906134649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:22:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347906277224-71</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Still no chance for Obimbo</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347906277224</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347907040216-72</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO IS AN OPEN BOOK......of lies, deceit, deception and bumbling...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347895533813</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 11:25:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That stench is the leftover BOX of Piglosi, old timer Reid and his just say NO to everything, and all those libTURD economy destroyers in the Whitehouse. You own it dumbazzszzzzzzzzzzzzzz. YOUR MEssiah Obumbles BEST monthly EU rate has YET to be as good as GW Bush's worst. That in itself should tell you the whole story for O'Loser. Sorry the FACTS don't agree with you tard.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347907040216</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347908227091-73</Id><Title>AMERICANS UNITED IN OPPOSITION TO OBIMBO!!!</Title><Msg>men, wimmin, college students out of work, Black pastors against gay marriage, Hispanic's out of work, all across America, blue collar, white collar, backwards collar, no collar, one and all, myriads, multitudes....many!!! All opposed to Obimbo... SEND HIM BACK TO CHICAGO...they all say... You know that buffoon ain't goin' back to Chicago!!! He's headed to retirement in the Big Island...on the beach, perpetual golf....good for him...starting in November...get out the White House, head to the Big Island and relax Obimbo...lots of work for Romney to fix your mess</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347908227091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:57:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347909226492-74</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep them coming.</Msg><Username>jaymesar29486</Username><Timestamp>1347909226492</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347909835314-75</Id><Topic><Title>HOW MITT SAVED THE OLYMPICS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347901945161</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 13:12:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have yet to see you post one semi-intelligent comment,Junior. If you wish to debate why I think Obama is a very poor president, I welcome that debate .If it's easier for you act like a child,fine,but don 't bother me with it. Now you have a nice day.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347909835314</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:23:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347910067320-76</Id><Title>Option expiration week</Title><Msg>Looks like the big money wants to stay around $19 to close the week. Them options boys control the price.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347910067320</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:27:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347910160900-77</Id><Title>Myth RobbedMe comments on China</Title><Msg>Myth says China's trade policies have gotten SO bad that, unless they fall into line really fast, he'll tell Bain Capital to move all its factories back to Mexico.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347910160900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347910229590-78</Id><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL PUTS ROMNEY AHEAD AGAIN...no hope for the Obimbo!!!</Title><Msg>all over but the shouting! Go home Democrats...it's in the oven. Obimbo is moving to the Big Island. Lots of golf and his children can be choomers too!!! Just like he was!!! Choomer in Chief NO MORE!! thank you, thank you, thank you.....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347910229590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:30:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347910389826-79</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I will be waiting for more great news to come.</Msg><Username>towandakpi0933</Username><Timestamp>1347910389826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347910396661-80</Id><Topic><Title>Myth RobbedMe comments on China</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347910160900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Obama should tell his pal Jeff Imelt to quit outsourcing all the GE jobs to other countries too</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347910396661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:33:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347910511733-81</Id><Topic><Title>Myth RobbedMe comments on China</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347910160900</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Loser takes 3 1/2 YEARS to finally acknowledge the cheating Chinese. Batter up BOY.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347910511733</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:35:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347910824310-82</Id><Title>Myth RobbedMe: Idiot, Con Artist, or Both?</Title><Msg>Myth just said not 20 minutes ago that the difference between the current U3 unemployment rate (8.1%) and the target unemployment rate (5.4%), a difference of (8.1 - 5.4 =) 2.7%, EQUALED NINE MILLION ADDITIONAL UNEMPLOYED WORKERS. Actually, it's not even HALF that number. Seems he just multiplied 2.7% by the TOTAL US population of 315 million, rather than the actual US labor force size of 154 million! Holy Krist, ain't Myth supposed to be a NUMBERS guy?! The guy's a fuggin BUFFOON!!!</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347910824310</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:40:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347910904332-83</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL PUTS ROMNEY AHEAD AGAIN...no hope for the Obimbo!!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347910229590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmuck also had your beloved McPalin ahead. LOL. How did that work out? LOL.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdtheturd</Username><Timestamp>1347910904332</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:41:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347911472846-84</Id><Title>WHY WOULD MOSLEMS ATTACK OBIMBO'S NATION. HE'S THE 'BOWER' IN CHIEF...</Title><Msg>of course he's also the Choomer in Chief...but that's another story. Don't we have a 're-set' with the Moslem world? Oh well, time to get rid of Obimbo, he's useless</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347911472846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:51:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347911533596-85</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL PUTS ROMNEY AHEAD AGAIN...no hope for the Obimbo!!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347910229590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>one of you guys, your many i'd's, posted the Rasmussen poll last week, just thought I'd make your day a little darker....heheehehehheheheehe</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347911533596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347911807319-86</Id><Title>ROMNEY'S GONNA RUN ON RONALD REAGAN'S RECORD- DID YOU SEE REAGAN BACKDROP AT THE RNC? TOO FUNNY!!! TRICKLE DOWN ECONOMICS, "THERE YOU GO AGAIN" ................. stay tuned.</Title><Msg>ROMNEY'S GONNA RUN ON RONALD REAGAN'S RECORD- DID YOU SEE REAGAN BACKDROP AT THE RNC? TOO FUNNY!!! TRICKLE DOWN ECONOMICS, "THERE YOU GO AGAIN" ................. stay tuned.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347911807319</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347911853169-87</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN POLL PUTS ROMNEY AHEAD AGAIN...no hope for the Obimbo!!!</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347910229590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>rasmussen was the most accurate poll of 2008 ---hitting Obama's winning per centage almost exactly Also McCain was ahead in mid to late Sept,08 before collapsing.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347911853169</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:57:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347911949268-88</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>don't forget RHONDA !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347911949268</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:59:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347912044817-89</Id><Title>NO JOBS, NO JOBS, NO JOBS, NO JOBS......UNEMPLOYMENT AT 23%</Title><Msg>Real unemployment is at Depression levels, not the Great Recession!! This is a Democratically produced Depression of generational proportion. Its all over for Democrats</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347912044817</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:00:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347912072194-90</Id><Title>National Debt</Title><Msg>National Debt Anyone who believes that Romney will actually reduce the national debt should be bidding on the Brooklyn Bridge! He seems to be treading in Bush's footsteps - lower taxes, less regulation, and more money for the military. What he should be doing is proposing a long-range economic plan that can be phased in over a period of years that will provide real economic growth. This plan should include a complete overhaul of the tax system to make if fairer, incentives for businesses to keep jobs in the United States, and investment in the technologies of the future and in our country’s infrastructure. The plan should also include a believable long term strategy that will gradually reduce the national debt to a more manageable level as the economy recovers. The proposals that he has made thus far just are not believable.</Msg><Username>dwb360</Username><Timestamp>1347912072194</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:01:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347912324365-91</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hilarious you think I'm a Mormon....I do wear special underwear though!!! ha hha hahahaha AMERICA WILL VOTE FOR 'ANYONE BUT OBIMBO'....don't have to be a Mormon to vote for Romney...I'm not voting for him to be the pastor of my church....WE NEED A NEW PRESIDENT, not a pastor....the Mormon thing is specious, a distraction....anything so Democrats don't have to talk about jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs... DEMOCRATS FAILING MISERABLY AND MAKING AMERICA MISERABLE!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347912324365</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:05:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347912356256-92</Id><Title>ROMNEY THINKS PEOPLE IN GENERAL ARE IDIOTS !</Title><Msg>I'll run on my great jobs record at the company I owned and ran from 1990-2012 but I'll retroactively retire in 2010 so no one will see all the American jobs I moved to China in 2011 and 2012. I will then of course hide my tax returns for those years. That will totally work right??? What?? That's stupid and only an amateur would try to insult the voters with a stunt like that??? Really??? Hmmmmmm.... Maybe I should keep the my million dollar abortion disposal operation on the DL too then??</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347912356256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347912494470-93</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Glad you shared this with us.</Msg><Username>alixhkn947</Username><Timestamp>1347912494470</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347913362777-94</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DISTRACTIONS DON'T WORK WHEN THE ECONOMY IS TANKING LIKE BIG BERTHA! too bad, little Timmy. OBIMBO IS OUT, GONE, FINISHED, IT'S OVER FOR DEMCORATS...EVERYONE IS aware of their terrible failure..and FAILURE it is!! NO JOBS, NO JOBS, NO JOBS</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347913362777</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347913524336-95</Id><Title>WE NEED HUNDREDS, THOUSANDS, OF ANTI MOHAMMED MOVIES.....</Title><Msg>only way to clear the air. Every Western nation needs to produce sixteen anti-Moslem movies, including Iceland and the Faroe Islands. Not to forget the Falkland Islands. They too need to produce six anti-Mohammed movies LOTS AND LOTS OF THEM, HOW ELSE WILL WE ADDRESS THE 'CRAZY MOSLEM' ISSUE?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347913524336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347914163158-96</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool.</Msg><Username>seritatfh6797</Username><Timestamp>1347914163158</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:36:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347915807849-97</Id><Title>Whitehoues has NO clue whats going on overseas</Title><Msg>Whitehouse claims the internet video is to blame for all the attacks and the murders, but it now is coming out that the libyan attacks happened before that. Whitehouse is CLUELESS</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347915807849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347915930033-98</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for sharing this article.</Msg><Username>carylmqt85807</Username><Timestamp>1347915930033</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:05:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347917547806-99</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>willieivg570620</Username><Timestamp>1347917547806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:32:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347917731287-100</Id><Topic><Title>Whitehoues has NO clue whats going on overseas</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347915807849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On the contrary,Fluteman, I think the White House has a pretty good idea of what happened. Somebody dropped the ball re security and now the coverup is in progress. .</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347917731287</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:35:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347917881009-101</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY THINKS PEOPLE IN GENERAL ARE IDIOTS !</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo6</Username><Timestamp>1347912356256</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Romney reads your posts and thinks many people are like you.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347917881009</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:38:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347918148960-102</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs....see?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347918148960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:42:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347918193633-103</Id><Title>JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS......</Title><Msg>Romney creates them Obimbo takes them away!! VOTE ROMNEY</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347918193633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:43:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347918838406-104</Id><Topic><Title>Whitehoues has NO clue whats going on overseas</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347915807849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just weeks away from the election and Obumbles doesn't want the American people to know he had a terrorist attack on his watch. Let the truth ring out.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347918838406</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:53:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919229210-105</Id><Topic><Title>JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS, JOBS......</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347918193633</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:43:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're WRONG, Obumbles IS creating jobs in China. He outsourced them via the stimulus.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347919229210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919280629-106</Id><Topic><Title>WE NEED HUNDREDS, THOUSANDS, OF ANTI MOHAMMED MOVIES.....</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347913524336</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 16:25:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, birdbrain...you have made many moronic statements Too many to count, but this is a whopper. How dumb can you get you crusty old fart? BTW..it is looking MORE and MORE like a LANDSLIDE for another 4 years of black man in the white house. Or as teabaggers would say. A Shellacking!</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919280629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919404613-107</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mormon or #$%$ Interchangeable, works either way.</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919404613</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347919752531-108</Id><Title>Have a look at projected electoral maps</Title><Msg>links apparently not allowed; google huffington Post electoral map and intrade electoral map and see for yourself wow, very encouraging...a shellacking?</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919752531</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919858350-109</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>weird...yahoo censored the word #$%$</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919858350</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:10:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919925915-110</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is mauron a dirty word?</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919925915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:12:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347919999270-111</Id><Topic><Title>Have a look at projected electoral maps</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919752531</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You people said the same thing prior to the 2010 midterms. Anyone citing the far left rag Huffington post should have their head examined. SHELLACKING 2.0 coming your way, count on it.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347919999270</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:13:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347920033258-112</Id><Topic><Title>walterbirdbrain isa mormon like mittens - they both l'e for the lord'</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347911809788</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 15:56:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, I noticed that. It censors the word $@%#$# too.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347920033258</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:13:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347920512108-113</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>oletazmy5717</Username><Timestamp>1347920512108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:21:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347920626884-114</Id><Topic><Title>Have a look at projected electoral maps</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1347919752531</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:09:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No teleprompter the night of Oct.3rd. Will Barry bring up cops acting stupid,you didn't build that,or Egypt is not our ally again?? It's an adventure when he is not scripted.LOL Of course Romney screws up every now and then too .Who gaffes first loses.LOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347920626884</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347921060590-115</Id><Title>ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION IMO LOL! THOSE SECRET TAPES WILL RUIN ANY CHANCES!</Title><Msg>TOO FUNNY! BUSTED ON TAPES!</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921060590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347921102685-116</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION IMO LOL! THOSE SECRET TAPES WILL RUIN ANY CHANCES!</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921060590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not like he had a chance of winning in the first place!</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921102685</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347921932335-117</Id><Title>REPUBLITARDS LOL! FOLLOW YOUR LEADER ROMNEY!</Title><Msg>GO AAPL!!</Msg><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921932335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347922599107-118</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLITARDS LOL! FOLLOW YOUR LEADER ROMNEY!</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921932335</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:45:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you buy $ 2,000,000, of AAPL again today, dumdumMagoo???LOLOLOLOLOLOL Is Bill Ayers still dead??? Did you go swimming with Michael Phelps again???YOU ARE HILARIOUS!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347922599107</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:56:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347922957928-119</Id><Topic><Title>Whitehoues has NO clue whats going on overseas</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347915807849</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 17:03:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember that Fort Hood wasn't a terrorist act either.It was "workplace violence " This admin.considers Americans really stupid.....maybe they have a point.LOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347922957928</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:02:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347923407203-120</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay cool. Thank you for sharing this.</Msg><Username>mindyure715</Username><Timestamp>1347923407203</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:10:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347924875176-121</Id><Topic><Title>Have You SEEN This?! (CSCO)</Title><Username>shantayvsi904539</Username><Timestamp>1347719602576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-15 10:33:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>cristagyd743</Username><Timestamp>1347924875176</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 19:34:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347928329235-122</Id><Topic><Title>epublicans are failing the central test of electability. Instead of putting together the largest possible coalition of voters, they're relying largely on one slice of America -- middle-aged white men -- and alienating just about everyone else</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347907907759</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 14:51:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats just bribe the public to win their votes. It's easy to win elections by handing out money to the voters.</Msg><Username>bot_feeder</Username><Timestamp>1347928329235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:32:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347928391081-123</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION IMO LOL! THOSE SECRET TAPES WILL RUIN ANY CHANCES!</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921060590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>seems like Mitt is stepping in it on a daily basis now, I think Mitt has one last chance and that is if he hits it out of the park in the debates, other wise turn out the lights on the GOP. (I think Mitt is wrong about having a better chance if his parents were Mexican however, the GOP won't nominate anyone but an old white guy in our lifetime.)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347928391081</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 20:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347931980252-124</Id><Title>good old Mitt</Title><Msg>Republican Mitt Romney confronted a new headache Monday after a video surfaced showing him telling wealthy donors that almost half of all Americans "believe they are victims" entitled to extensive government support. He added that as a candidate for the White House, "my job is not to worry about those people." Yo Mitt, clearly every poor disabled child belongs in your almost half. All the elderly in poverty are in that half. It includes all the veterans that have come home from Bush's wars with no legs and arms, unable to support themselves. No Mitt I think you put your finger on it, you believe your job is to help rich hedge fund managers that donate a lot of money to your campaign. You don't care about poor at all, I would say that answers the question of if you are a Christian.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347931980252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347932081006-125</Id><Topic><Title>good old Mitt</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347931980252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey Mitt did we mention the deaf, dumb and blind are in your half, the mentally ill, and the mentally incompetent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347932081006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:34:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347932249205-126</Id><Title>CNN has Jessie Ventura on</Title><Msg>OMG is he ripping Bush, Cheney and Romney apart!! LOL Says Bush knew about 9-11 and didn't stop it on purpose!!! OMG the guy is on it "Every war is started on a false flag operation!!"</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347932249205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:37:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347933596768-127</Id><Topic><Title>CNN has Jessie Ventura on</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347932249205</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:37:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just made a very interesting point, thanks to the SCOTUS corporations can spend all the money they want to buy their political interest. So what happens when China decides in 2016 it would like to control the Presidential Election so it forms a corporation and donates to a Pac, hey they could put a couple hundred billion into the election. Of course Israel will have to have it's own pac but I think there is more Arab money. Oh yeah and remember people this is the law of the land now, it takes a constitutional amendment to change this. So in 2015 when Iran decides to go loco they could spend like how many trillion. Cool</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347933596768</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347934041589-128</Id><Title>No love for Rasmussen anymore?</Title><Msg>Last week when Rasmussen had Obama ahead liberals here loved Rasmussen.Just posted and posted about it. This week Rasmussen has Romney ahead and libs here are silent. I laugh!!</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347934041589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:07:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347935442894-129</Id><Topic><Title>No love for Rasmussen anymore?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1347934041589</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:07:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I love Rasmussen almost as much as I love SNL, LOL who ever thought you could take a push poll that far!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347935442894</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 22:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937438547-130</Id><Topic><Title>good old Mitt</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347931980252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 21:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GET RID OF O'BLAMMAH!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1347937438547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347937472167-131</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION IMO LOL! THOSE SECRET TAPES WILL RUIN ANY CHANCES!</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921060590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GET RID OF O'BLAMMAH!</Msg><Username>jotrout</Username><Timestamp>1347937472167</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:04:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347938915573-132</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY JUST LOST THE ELECTION IMO LOL! THOSE SECRET TAPES WILL RUIN ANY CHANCES!</Title><Username>greenegggs</Username><Timestamp>1347921060590</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obutthead is a white communist with a tan, birthed and raised by white commies</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1347938915573</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-17 23:28:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>