<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352701431910-1</Id><Topic><Title>RED WORKERS REBELL...TIRED OF CARRYING BLUE PARASITES</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352688877061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Birdshjjjjt, everyone but you knows that the blue states cover the tax hole of the red states. You are too much of a stupid redneck to know it. Read once in a while inbreed.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352701431910</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:23:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352701633953-2</Id><Topic><Title>GOP Clown Circus ONLY Exists as Money Machine for Millionaire$ Rush, Sean, Beck, Coulter, OReilly, etc</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1352690304185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 22:18:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, it's a Frankenstein monster. Funny, now the repukes that created this media machine for political purposes realize they cannot shut it down because the participants are too happy making too much money. Hell let them talk, 2016 is another #$%$ repukes year.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352701633953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:27:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352701688560-3</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA/DIMS STOLE THE ELECTION</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1352694728907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:32:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yaaaaaaaaaaawnnnnn ! Zzzzzzzzzzz, 4 more years inbreed. Suck on it.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352701688560</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:28:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352703443678-4</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA/DIMS STOLE THE ELECTION</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1352694728907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:32:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>except surfergay and junior, of course they are retards and they are experiencing stupefaction</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1352703443678</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 01:57:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352710029846-5</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA/DIMS STOLE THE ELECTION</Title><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1352694728907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 23:32:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you filthy teabags just can't handle the truth you teapigs are done. Back under your rocks</Msg><Username>rationalthought11</Username><Timestamp>1352710029846</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 03:47:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352716685064-6</Id><Topic><Title>tea baggers destroying GOP making this a one party country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352667212933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>For the past twenty years or so, which is as long as some young voters have been on the planet, the current crop of Democrats have, despite their manifest flaws, looked like veritable Founding Fathers when compared to their G-O-P... R-N-C... M-O-U-S-E counterparts. Don"t believe me? Back in July of this year, a veritable Demi-God of the Right, one Richard Posner, Reagan appointee to the 7th Circuit Court of appeals, unflagging conservative voice, reliable conservative vote, once a "short lister" for possible appointment to the Supreme Court,* staunch defender of all things Milty Friedman-y, of The Chicago School in general, and perhaps THE single most visible and well-known judicial proponent of the "Law and Economics" movement, made the following observation in response to a journalist's question: //POSNER, J: There’s been a real deterioration in conservative thinking. And that has to lead people to re-examine and modify their thinking. I’ve become less conservative since the Republican Party started becoming goofy.// Ooooh, SNAP! If it please the court, NO he DID NOT!!! FYI, this sent SEISMIC ripples through the ... tiny ... community ... of people ... who ... knew even vaguely ... who the guy was(?). Ok, maybe "seismic" isn't the right word, maybe something more like "diffuse, but intensely and geekishly focused" might be more accurate. Still, as canaries in coal mines go, Posner had to be among the very biggest and most brightly and densely plumed ... of ... of ... right-wing ... canaries. --------------------------- * That is, until increasing age overtook him -- he turned 50, and so would have been unlikely to cling to the seat for more than another ~30 or 40 years, MAX, putting him right out of the running.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352716685064</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 05:38:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352716752367-7</Id><Title>Tea Party is the reason why....</Title><Msg>Sunday, November 11, 2012 Tea Party Played Key Role in Romney's Defeat By MARC McDONALD Shell-shocked Republicans are continuing to do a post-mortem on why Mitt Romney's bid for the White House was a flop. But in trying to understand their defeat, they really need to point the finger of blame at a section of the GOP itself: the Tea Party. Since it sprang into action a few years ago, the Tea Party has prided itself on "re-energizing" the GOP base and returning the party to its core principles. And indeed, the Tea Party did inspire a lot of Conservatives who had been dismayed by the likes of big-spending George W. Bush (even though the Tea Party only started making a big fuss when President Obama entered the White House). The Tea Party made itself into a force to be reckoned within the GOP. It was a force that could no longer be ignored by party leaders. Which meant that the "moderate" Romney was obligated to pick a Tea Party favorite as his VP selection. Paul Ryan may have delighted the Tea Partiers. But his hard-line extremism scared the hell out of the rest of us. Far from enhancing the Romney ticket, it's clear that Ryan was a liability from Day One. Ryan's presence on the ticket demonstrates that the GOP still hasn't grasped one of the cardinal rules of U.S. politics. That is: you don't screw with Medicare. No matter how much lipstick the GOP tried to put on Ryan's "voucher" pig, most non-Fox News-watching voters saw it for what it was: the first step toward ending Medicare entirely. Frankly, the Tea Party should take much of the blame for Romney's failed White House bid. Yes, the movement did inspire a segment of the GOP. But in doing so, it poisoned the overall GOP brand. In keeping Tea Party figures like Sarah Palin and Michele Bachmann out of the spotlight during the GOP convention, the GOP tried to downplay the extremist crazies in the party that scared middle-of-the-road voters. Oddly, though, the GOP didn't grasp that it'd be a problem if a Tea Party extremist was given the VP nod. Tea Partiers have long claimed that they're working to "save" America and return the GOP to its roots. But really, all the movement has accomplished is to damage the Republican brand and to make average voters wary of an increasingly extreme GOP. Posted by Marc McDonald at 4:32 PM</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352716752367</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 05:39:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719472396-8</Id><Topic><Title>GOP to run RYAN/RUBIO in 2016 ............. (snicker)</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597408489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:30:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOTH PARTIES ARE GUILTY OF DOING NOTHING... SO FAR 2 terms of W. BUSH &amp; 1 term of OBAMA did NOTHING!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719472396</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:24:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719485512-9</Id><Topic><Title>"ANYONE" LOST to OBAMA, REPUBS!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597077092</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:24:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719485512</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719507444-10</Id><Topic><Title>Rhonda_Edelstein- MOST PATHETIC POSTER HERE- believes EVERY LIE FOX NEWS says to her</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597497265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:31:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719507444</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:25:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719518419-11</Id><Topic><Title>YOU REPUBS voted for your LAST choice of GOP PRES. PICK for 2012</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352596980817</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:23:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719518419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:25:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719560143-12</Id><Topic><Title>BUT ROMNEY LOST, why are YOU REPUBLICANS still posting here?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352594762681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 19:46:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719560143</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:26:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352719743188-13</Id><Topic><Title>dumbpainting sticking his fingers in his ears, muting the volume on his tv as he hears election results</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1352222500236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 12:21:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes sir!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352719743188</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352720271926-14</Id><Title>PETREUS RESIGNS BECAUSE OF ADULTERY? WHAT? everyone knows is perfectly all right</Title><Msg>to practice every from of debauchery and perversion and dishonesty in your PERSONAL LIFE. Clinton and the Blue Parasites taught us this. Jon Stewart taught us this. ABC, NBC, CBS teaches that it's OK Why would a Democratically controlled CIA allow the head to resign because of adultery? Jesse Jackson, Charles Rangel, Michelle Obama, President Obimbo, Jesse Jackson Jr, all the rappers, Angelina Jolie, Brad Pitt....EVERYONE, each and all of the Blue Parasites is a liar, schemer, adulterer...what matters? IS THERE SOMETHING ELSE GOING ON....we all know what you do on your own time doesn't matter...wait, Clinton was screwing interns in the oval office....ok, no matter what you do, any time, NOTHING matters if it is all about honesty, truth, or morality. The only thing that really truly matters is YOU MUST KILL BABIES...if you don't KILL BABIES....then you are TERRIBLE. Anyone who REFUSES TO KILL BABIES is despicable...now, on the other hand, if you KILL BABIES, you are the kind of person who truly cares....who is merciful, compassionate, yup... THE BIZZARO WORLD OF THE BLUE PARASITE.....they are here, they live among you and they control the Presidency and the Senate.. DEFEND YOUR SELF AND FAMILY AGAINST THE BLUE PARASITE...but do it very carefully....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352720271926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:37:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352720357318-15</Id><Topic><Title>BUT ROMNEY LOST, why are YOU REPUBLICANS still posting here?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352594762681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 19:46:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Just checking in daily to remind you of plummeting stock prices, unemployment sky rocketing, the 'fiscal cliff' never fixed, politicians mouthing crap, til the next election. Maybe free and honest men, who tell the truth will never get the vote of the blue parasites." Didn't this happen during the last 18 mos of the Chimp's administration? You were'nt checking in with us Communist pigs then, why is that?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352720357318</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:39:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352720420265-16</Id><Topic><Title>RED WORKERS REBELL...TIRED OF CARRYING BLUE PARASITES</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352688877061</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 21:54:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the next three months, more workers will lose their jobs than in the previous year. OBAMACARE is a TSUNAMI of unprecedented proportions and no small business man, like me, has the FEDERAL RESERVE to give me 100 billion every month to cover my overhead!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352720420265</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:40:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352722579476-17</Id><Title>The Cage Cleaners have spoken</Title><Msg>Election day clearly spelled out that America has become an "us vs. them" society. The "them," meaning cage cleaners who are receiving government entitlements, now outnumber the "us" who do not, and the Cage Cleaners outvoted us. Obama ran as Santa Clause again. This time Santa even had free birth control pills, and that's like sixty bucks a month. Thomas Jeffereson once said, "The democracy will cease to exist when you take away from those willing to work and give to those who would not."The election was bought and paid for by Santa Clause and the Cage Cleaners, with our own money. The Cage Cleaners will continue to demonize American capitalism and sell our future to China. And at some point our empty service based economy will most likely collapse. When that happens the US Government will not save you. Precious metals, stockpiles of food and water, firearms and ammo is mandatory for the looming end to the Republic.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352722579476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:16:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352723621195-18</Id><Topic><Title>The Cage Cleaners have spoken</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352722579476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:16:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And our fine president is still Black! and Breitbart is still dead!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352723621195</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:33:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352725225005-19</Id><Topic><Title>The Cage Cleaners have spoken</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352722579476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:16:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is a great, sweeping narrative, describing the fall of our country, but it is simply not true. What you wrote simply summarizes the GOP's defense mechanism that kicked in once they realized they're losing relevancy. I call it denial...</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1352725225005</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:00:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352726637638-20</Id><Topic><Title>The Cage Cleaners have spoken</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352722579476</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 07:16:19 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Denial, what denial. 15 million MORE Americans on food stamps, poverty rate increased dramatically, 23 million unemployed or under employed. Those are FACTS under this President, denial has nothing to do with it.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352726637638</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:23:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352726870179-21</Id><Title>I say We Tax the mega rich EVEN MORE.</Title><Msg>Let's tax those making 10 million a year 85%, you know, pay your fair share kind of thing. Let's see how much CRYING and WHINING we hear from Hollywood and all the sports stars. I bet O'Loser won't look so good when your own pocketbook gets hit.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352726870179</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:27:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352727096933-22</Id><Topic><Title>PETREUS RESIGNS BECAUSE OF ADULTERY? WHAT? everyone knows is perfectly all right</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352720271926</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 06:37:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans are the ones in the Mens Bathroom,,,trying to rape cops</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727096933</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352727177619-23</Id><Topic><Title>Rhonda_Edelstein- MOST PATHETIC POSTER HERE- believes EVERY LIE FOX NEWS says to her</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597497265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:31:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Edelstein is HOT</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727177619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:32:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352727286233-24</Id><Topic><Title>GOP to run RYAN/RUBIO in 2016 ............. (snicker)</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597408489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:30:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Screw so called Legal Europeans who steal the Land and exterminate the Inhabitants You prove how sick white people are</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727286233</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:34:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352727342419-25</Id><Title>WHITE People came from Europe to call us illegals</Title><Msg>#$%$ and go back where you came from</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727342419</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:35:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352727472403-26</Id><Title>Did the Muslims wipe out the Racist Pigs yet ???</Title><Msg>Let me know when the coast is clear...</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727472403</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:37:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352727573826-27</Id><Title>When Whitey was bringing Blacks from Africa,,,Illegal</Title><Msg>Did Not eneter Whiteys mind,,,,only Money</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727573826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:39:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352728294924-28</Id><Topic><Title>GOP to run RYAN/RUBIO in 2016 ............. (snicker)</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597408489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:30:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>building since the 60's?? Guess you don't remember when Reagan gave all illegals amnesty in the 80's.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352728294924</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:51:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352730245997-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOP to run RYAN/RUBIO in 2016 ............. (snicker)</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1352597408489</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-10 20:30:08 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Vete para el Carajo idiota...rasista ,,,pendejo</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352730245997</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:24:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352730750737-30</Id><Title>Obama's socialist country, LOL</Title><Msg>Conservatives blame establishment Boehner: GOP has 'some work to do' Obama's second term agenda Whatever you think of the Obama record, it's worth keeping in mind that by any measure, free enterprise has been winning the game for a long, long time to this point. Compare the United States of 2012 to the United States of 1962. Leave aside the obvious points about segregation and discrimination, and look only at the economy. In 1962, the government regulated the price and route of every airplane, every freight train, every truck and every merchant ship in the United States. The government regulated the price of natural gas. It regulated the interest on every checking account and the commission on every purchase or sale of stock. Owning a gold bar was a serious crime that could be prosecuted under the Trading with the Enemy Act. The top rate of income tax was 91%. It was illegal to own a telephone. Phones had to be rented from the giant government-regulated monopoly that controlled all telecommunications in the United States. All young men were subject to the military draft and could escape only if they entered a government-approved graduate course of study. The great concern of students of American society -- of liberals such as David Riesman, of conservatives such as Russell Kirk, and of radicals such as Dwight Macdonald -- was the country's stultifying, crushing conformity.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352730750737</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:32:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352730994171-31</Id><Topic><Title>When Whitey was bringing Blacks from Africa,,,Illegal</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727573826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:39:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read a history book,fool. Vast majority of Africans sold into slavery were captured by other Africans and then sold to the white man. Money has no prejudice.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352730994171</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:36:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352731207847-32</Id><Title>Former Chief CIA fornicator to be prosecuted under the Uniform Code of Military Justice</Title><Msg>After admitting an extramarital relationship, Cage Cleaner Petraeus will face military prosecution for adultery under the UCMJ. This affair clearly started while he was on active duty. And a FBI investigation was not reported to law makers in a timely fashion, i.e. before the election. Just one more scandal for the twisted Obama Administration. Also a hearing on evidence in the case against fornicator Brig. Gen. Jeffrey Sinclair has opened at Fort Bragg, home to the 82nd Airborne Division. Officials said the Article 32 hearing was expected to last at least two days. Sinclair forced a subordinate to perform oral sex and threatened her life and her family.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352731207847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:40:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352731550013-33</Id><Topic><Title>Former Chief CIA fornicator to be prosecuted under the Uniform Code of Military Justice</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352731207847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I say Petreus deserves all the pssy he can get his hands on. He is the most influential military man since Eisenhower. Just like Clinton, Bush Sr, FDR. These are miserable, lonely jobs. So what if they have to get laid in order to performed them. Just because pukes get psyy once every 5 years does not mean the rest of us have to be subjected to the same regime.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352731550013</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:45:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352731692382-34</Id><Title>HUGE week ahead for Cisco shareholders</Title><Msg>Earnings come out tomorrow after the bell, annual shareholders meeting Thursday, and Option expiration Friday. This could be one of the most volatile weeks in Cisco's history. I wonder how Chambers will EXPLAIN to shareholders how great a job he is doing with PPS sitting at or near multi year lows. Disgraceful.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352731692382</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:48:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352731789235-35</Id><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Msg>This is csco board. Tomorrow is earns will made it .42 cents but stock dowm again !</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352731814915-36</Id><Topic><Title>When Whitey was bringing Blacks from Africa,,,Illegal</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727573826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:39:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whitey is always shopping for People....they dont know any better... I hear Africa was have a Sales on Blacks and white women were desperate</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352731814915</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732101584-37</Id><Topic><Title>When Whitey was bringing Blacks from Africa,,,Illegal</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352727573826</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 08:39:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to have a problem with English. Are you from another country.. or just stupid??</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352732101584</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:55:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352732197935-38</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think Cisco hits or beats its number. The issue is guidance, with the 15% DECLINE in the last 6 weeks I think a boring guidance may already be priced in the stock. We are trading at 8x next years earnings with $6 a share in cash net of debt. With it's free cash flow and net earnings you could BORROW, and buy this company and have it paid off in 6 years. Simply amazing.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352732197935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:56:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352732412156-39</Id><Title>Juniper lowered guidance</Title><Msg>At its October 23rd earnings call and they are trading HIHGER today. Go figure.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352732412156</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:00:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352732812092-40</Id><Title>Did Petraeus or Broadwell Betray The President By Giving Classified Info To Other Repugnant Repubs</Title><Msg>To try to win an election where unemployment was nearly 8%, these repubs would do anything possible. Oh yes, Americans want to know more about what Republican Petraeus and Republican Broadwell were doing and what they may have given to the President's haters in order to TRY to win an election. Always wondered who was the Repub's source for this garbage witch hunt into the Lybia incident. Truly UnAmerican!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352732812092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:06:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352733008621-41</Id><Topic><Title>Did Petraeus or Broadwell Betray The President By Giving Classified Info To Other Repugnant Repubs</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352732812092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you questioning Obama's judgement about appointing Petraeus CIA director??LOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352733008621</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:10:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352733013992-42</Id><Title>Hey CSCO, Austerity is Killing Europe's Economy, Expect Little Growth From Europe. Dead Stock.</Title><Msg>Now, CSCO is also faced with the US fiscal cliff. More government spending cuts. That has got to hurt. $15 soon.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352733013992</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:10:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352733182668-43</Id><Topic><Title>Did Petraeus or Broadwell Betray The President By Giving Classified Info To Other Repugnant Repubs</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352732812092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I always question using Repubs in anything. They are the UnAmerican party. Republicans hate America.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352733182668</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:13:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352733310985-44</Id><Title>Rassy &amp; Gallop Must Be In Deep Depression Mode. How Did He Get It So WRONG!!!!!!</Title><Msg>Even Fauxnews doesn't want them on their station. LOL</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352733310985</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:15:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352733349605-45</Id><Topic><Title>Did Petraeus or Broadwell Betray The President By Giving Classified Info To Other Repugnant Repubs</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352732812092</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:06:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That post is too stupid to even merit a comment . Bye.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352733349605</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:15:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352733513649-46</Id><Title>Gallup &amp; Rassy Are Going Away Like The Literary Digest - Garbage Pollsters. LOL</Title><Msg>Romney Ryan. LOL. LOL. And the idiot Repubs bought it hook line and sinker. LOL</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352733513649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:18:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352733636329-47</Id><Topic><Title>deadpainting obsessed with his own fecal matter</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1350672584256</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 14:49:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is what jrmagoo does all day talks about poo. looks like someone needs a job. pathetic.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352733636329</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:20:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352733644706-48</Id><Title>GOP intellectual political analysis</Title><Msg>“The president was elected on the basis that he was not Romney and that Romney was a poopy-head and you should vote against Romney,” Norquist said on CBS’s “This Morning.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352733644706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:20:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352733812252-49</Id><Title>GOP Clown Circus Determines It Has to Go Even More Right and White</Title><Msg>Only those with roots to the Pilgrims Mayflower and Puritans in Salem Witch Hunt can be in the GOP clown circus.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1352733812252</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:23:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734074674-50</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup &amp; Rassy Are Going Away Like The Literary Digest - Garbage Pollsters. LOL</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352733513649</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:18:33 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only lonely old white GOP clowns would answer the dozens of robocalls and spend 15 minutes doing each poll repeating their Fox indoctrination,</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1352734074674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:27:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352734134028-51</Id><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Msg>Special tax treatment for dividend and capital gains nust end to solve fiscal problems, as must mortgage tax deduction and deduction for employer provided health care. No other way around 16 trillion USA debt.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734323150-52</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Go ahead.Watch what happens to the market when Obama increases dividend and capital gains taxes.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352734323150</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:32:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734379663-53</Id><Topic><Title>dumbpainting sticking his fingers in his ears, muting the volume on his tv as he hears election results</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1352222500236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-11-06 12:21:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP NEOCONS say all they have to do is sharpen their message! LOL!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1352734379663</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:32:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352734806877-54</Id><Title>WHY did REPUBS get it SO WRONG about POLL RESULTS? they though MITT would easily win!</Title><Msg>WHY did REPUBS get it SO WRONG about POLL RESULTS? they though MITT would easily win! TOO FUNNY! SCOTT RASMUSSEN &amp; DORK MORRIS......... TWO BUFFOONS Don't forget senile CHARLES KRAUTHAMMER, another one!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1352734806877</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:40:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352734996604-55</Id><Topic><Title>Former Chief CIA fornicator to be prosecuted under the Uniform Code of Military Justice</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352731207847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I disagree with what you say but I will defend with my life for you to do so.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352734996604</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:43:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735041711-56</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>time for ceo step down maybe at meeting he will resign.</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352735041711</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:44:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735137570-57</Id><Topic><Title>Is changing one's position all the time PRESIDENTIAL MITT ??</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1351020980924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 15:36:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Earth to magoo, Romney lost and will not run again. R U going to talk about Mitt the next 4 years like you've been talking about Bush for the last 8? Please keep showing us what a dopey fool you are.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352735137570</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:45:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352735728920-58</Id><Topic><Title>Is changing one's position all the time PRESIDENTIAL MITT ??</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1351020980924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 15:36:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JuniorMagoo trying desperately to get a conversation going with somebody.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352735728920</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:55:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352735829480-59</Id><Title>Obama Regime, 1454 Days Remain...</Title><Msg>...and counting</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352735829480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:57:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352736263255-60</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime, 1454 Days Remain...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352735829480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:57:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As the number of companies announcing layoffs or going to part time employees increases because of Obama's reelection I hope voters are happy with what they did.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1352736263255</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:04:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352736366186-61</Id><Topic><Title>Is changing one's position all the time PRESIDENTIAL MITT ??</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo8</Username><Timestamp>1351020980924</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-10-23 15:36:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so LOSER PAUL RYAN will in 2016 instead?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo7</Username><Timestamp>1352736366186</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:06:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352737542780-62</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt it, Chambers won't give up his golden ponzi scheme. He will retire in a couple of years, he needs to fleece us shareholders for another 50 - 75 million and then he will leave.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352737542780</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:25:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352737739799-63</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's why the markets have reacted negetively to the Obama win, people will and are SELLING their winners and pay a LOWER cap gains now before it gets hiked. Obots are not real smart but they love their Messiah. I wonder what lie they will suck up next.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352737739799</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:28:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352737804629-64</Id><Title>IF YOU LIKED THE OBAMA DEPRESSION PART ONE</Title><Msg>then you'll really like the coming much deeper, much, much higher unemployment, huge stock market crashing (no investor confidence now) part II!! And rising taxes coupled with socialized inept Obamacare: What's not to like!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352737804629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:30:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352737965990-65</Id><Title>Greetings from My French Riviera Mansion</Title><Msg>To my 48 million voters, keep working faster and harder for less and less before I fire you to make million$ more in China to stuff in my Swiss and Cayman tax-free bank accounts.</Msg><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1352737965990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:32:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352738017730-66</Id><Title>OBAHBAHH GOT NINE MILLION FEWER VOTES THIS TIME</Title><Msg>and that's a FACT JACK! He has no mandate, no confidence in him. He's just a lame duck empty suit now who will show up to the office for an hour once in awhile inbetween vacations, basketball games and golf (and coke snorting sessions!).</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352738017730</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:33:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738251898-67</Id><Topic><Title>Former Chief CIA fornicator to be prosecuted under the Uniform Code of Military Justice</Title><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352731207847</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:40:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but quincy magoo, dumb ivan and surf constantly diddle each other and no one cares!</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352738251898</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:37:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352738478707-68</Id><Title>Obama got millions more votes then Romney</Title><Msg>deal with it, the GOP will never win another white house as it is currently configured, the GOP is turning into a regional party</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352738478707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:41:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738602443-69</Id><Topic><Title>Obama got millions more votes then Romney</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352738478707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:41:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>with voter fraud rampant and black panthers intimidating whites at polls? So not really though huh</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352738602443</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:43:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738649120-70</Id><Topic><Title>GOP intellectual political analysis</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352733644706</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:20:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a poopy-head, now that's some good political analysis, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352738649120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:44:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738777067-71</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>csco post thanks. move on.</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352738777067</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:46:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352738981664-72</Id><Topic><Title>Obama got millions more votes then Romney</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352738478707</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:41:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so does being a racist obama voter who posts on here 24-7 help you then? So your gubment handouts will dry up. Now that he's been re-elected the real, self-centered Obama will come to forefront and he will prove he doesn't actually give a shet about anyone other than himself. I'd say that makes you the gullible retard for voting for him "Jr".</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352738981664</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:49:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352739483262-73</Id><Title>McCain got millions more votes then Romney</Title><Msg>the GOP is in a death spiral</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352739483262</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:58:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352739978921-74</Id><Title>GW Bush never Existed,,Figmant of Imagination</Title><Msg>He never destroyed USA economy,,,you just imagined it,,,,he n ever destroyed the budget process,,,look , best thing to do,,Blame it on Black Guy.....if it does not work Blame the Communist,,,,,if t hat does not work blame it the Muslims...but dont you ever say Whites detroyed America</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352739978921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:06:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740276547-75</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU LIKED THE OBAMA DEPRESSION PART ONE</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1352737804629</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:30:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I still like Barry,regardless of your inaccurate perceptions</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1352740276547</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:11:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740432682-76</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>f.y.i. there is global trouble,especially in Europe. Hard to compete against Asian labor and globalization. I have made $$ in this market since Barry was elected in 2008. Especially after the Bush meltdown</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1352740432682</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:13:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352740841782-77</Id><Topic><Title>tea baggers destroying GOP making this a one party country</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352667212933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 15:53:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumpers</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352740841782</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:20:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352740990743-78</Id><Title>Tsk tsk tsk on Elmo.</Title><Msg>Oh no!!!..Elmo is a gay pedophile!!!!!! Actor who's the voice of Sesames Street's Elmo accused of sex with a 16 year old boy. He admits the affair but says the boy was of consensual age at the time.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352740990743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:23:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741017277-79</Id><Topic><Title>Greetings from My French Riviera Mansion</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1352737965990</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 11:32:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes and we know you always shop around for the highest price. maybe that is why you are not rich because you are too dumb to understand the basics of capitalism. bitter untalented drones like you should move to russia.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352741017277</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:23:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741071925-80</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes Thought Of The Day - September 24, 2012</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348492873292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>pmub bump</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741071925</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:24:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741284753-81</Id><Topic><Title>Tsk tsk tsk on Elmo.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352740990743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior now admitting he had a threesome with Elmo and Big Bird!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352741284753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:28:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741395860-82</Id><Topic><Title>ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352668230474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ump-beh</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741395860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:29:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741409687-83</Id><Title>Tea bagger in Colorado smoking Legal marijuana</Title><Msg>soon they will all be liberals</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352741409687</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741432165-84</Id><Title>Ted has only 5 months to live,</Title><Msg>In April, while speaking at a National Rifle Association convention, Nugent said there are two alternatives for him if the "vile," "evil" and "America-hating" Obama beat Romney. "If Barack Obama becomes the president in November, again, I will be either be dead or in jail by this time next year," said Nugent, who has also defended Romney's "47 percent" comment.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352741432165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741472226-85</Id><Topic><Title>ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352668230474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>KKK ate your mama</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352741472226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:31:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741474763-86</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BpummupB</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741474763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:31:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741514567-87</Id><Topic><Title>NEW RUSH AMNESTY PROGRAM</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486699134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:44:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh yeah</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741514567</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:31:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741537659-88</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rush Limbaugh,,,,forced Obama upon us</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352741537659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:32:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741559935-89</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>csco fail the shareholder.</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352741559935</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:32:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741617932-90</Id><Title>Articles of Marijuana being drafted in Washington and Colorado</Title><Msg>as we speak,,,,,hahahaha...those liberals...always partying and having fun</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352741617932</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:33:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741667628-91</Id><Topic><Title>Ted has only 5 months to live,</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352741432165</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:30:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called sticking your foot in your mouth. Something like all the libs who were going to leave the country if Bush was reelected. They are still here too.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352741667628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:34:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352741699552-92</Id><Title>Marijuana has turned my Conservatives into Bleeding Heart Liberals</Title><Msg>Be careful it dont happen to you</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352741699552</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741791424-93</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>K Street better throw 'em a chew toy... God knows they have no salable skills besides generating right wing froth and influence peddling.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741791424</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:36:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741830278-94</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yep yep</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741830278</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352741878647-95</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Said it once before but it bears repeating now...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352741878647</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:37:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352742071891-96</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Regime, 1454 Days Remain...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352735829480</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:57:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Methinks the 3+ million who didn't vote to make a point and who by omission voted for Obama are probably baby boomers, retired, and are not affected by the layoffs and attrition. Selfish bstards that they are...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352742071891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:41:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352742541342-97</Id><Title>Obama has 1,530 more days in the oval office</Title><Msg>dumb baggers don't do math</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352742541342</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:49:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352743467206-98</Id><Title>If Barry has a lick of sense...</Title><Msg>...he will move closer to the center for the sake of his party and actually turn around the mess he started in his first 4 years when he was doing nothing but campaigning for his next 4 years.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352743467206</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:04:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352743511140-99</Id><Title>Karl Rove Just Called Begging for Million$ More DarkPooled PACash</Title><Msg>Another GOP clown circus peddler of drill baby drill snakeyed oil.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1352743511140</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:05:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352746571080-100</Id><Topic><Title>TURNE THE PAGE WITH ALL THIS #$%$ !</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352731789235</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 09:49:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>where is csco post ?</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352746571080</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 13:56:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352748611601-101</Id><Topic><Title>Tsk tsk tsk on Elmo.</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352740990743</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 12:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior says all those feathers tickle when doing oral on Big Bird.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352748611601</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:30:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749164438-102</Id><Title>the big O's next vacation spot</Title><Msg>not sure where, but that's where i'm going. he has such good taste in luxery stuff</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1352749164438</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:39:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749231289-103</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's probably short the market and that may not be a bad strategy for the next 4 years, unless the market pulls another blulsheeit run like it did in the Clinton heyday, only to crash under Bush(thanks Clinton).</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352749231289</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:40:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749564045-104</Id><Title>market melt up</Title><Msg>bearish sentiment is at 40%, 10% above it's average. If the GOP gets real and agrees to a solution to the fiscal cliff the market is set up for a big leg up. Market's love the DNC.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352749564045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:46:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352749621357-105</Id><Topic><Title>Dividend and capital gains taxes must increase</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352734134028</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 10:28:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have no clue how the world works. that must be why you damand that other take care of you. ask yourself what happens when that happens. liberals have no clue of cause and effect. you should move to russia if you want communism. So many useless americans with their hands out. not enough to go around.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352749621357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:47:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352749990763-106</Id><Title>Obama ended Bush's useless war in IRAQ</Title><Msg>the one that cost us 4 trillion dollars and left hundreds of thousands of our soldiers injured for NOTHING. Just because W had an inferiority complex. (Completely justified).</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352749990763</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:53:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352750087390-107</Id><Title>How many more layoffs this week...</Title><Msg>...under the reelected, jug-eared clown? More attrition on its way...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750087390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:54:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750235619-108</Id><Topic><Title>ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352668230474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>couldn't agree more. The traitor needs to be tried for his treason and run out of town on a rail after a good tar &amp; feathering job!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352750235619</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:57:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352750566825-109</Id><Title>How many more scandals have been suppressed...</Title><Msg>...before the election? So Far: 1. Benghazi 2. General Petraeus 3. ? What's next, anyone?</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750566825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750591454-110</Id><Topic><Title>market melt up</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352749564045</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 14:46:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course they do surf/dumb dumb, that is why they have sold off almost 450 points so far. BRILLIANT</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352750591454</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:03:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750684639-111</Id><Topic><Title>How many more scandals have been suppressed...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750566825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what about that columbian prostitution thing. what about drone shot down by iran not talked about until after elections.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352750684639</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:04:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352750691283-112</Id><Title>ABSOLUTELY!! ALL TAXES MUST INCREASE...THE FEDERAL RESERVE IS RUNNING OUT OF ZERO'S</Title><Msg>to add to the US Treasury's bank account!!!! SO WE MUST RAISE TAXES ON ENTERTAINERS, ACTORS, HEDGE FUND GUYS, AL GORE, WARREN BUFFER, JOBS ESTATE MUST BE CONFISCATED BY THE US SINCE HE IS DEAD AND NEEDS NO MONEY, GET ALL OF HIS ESTATE...EVERY LAST PENNY. TAKE ALL OF BILL GATES MONEY, HE VOTED FOR OBAMA, TAKE JZ'S MONEY, ALL OF IT. No one needs more than 50,000 a year for cigs and malt liquor...the FEds will take care of everything else...your healthcare is paid for, your food, get the card!!!, your rent subsidies will work fine, you don't need to borrow money for your house...NO MORE MORTGAGES..FREDDIE MAC AND FANNIE MAE WILL OWN EVERY HOUSE IN AMERICA AND RENT IT TO YOU IF YOU BE GOOD.... WHAT IS THIS GOING TO COST....everything you have. Why not?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352750691283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:04:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750720272-113</Id><Topic><Title>Forbes Thought Of The Day - September 24, 2012</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1348492873292</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-24 09:21:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see. So in other words you're just another angry, hateful little LibTard parasite. Thanks for clearing that up.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750720272</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:05:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352750790805-114</Id><Topic><Title>How many more scandals have been suppressed...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750566825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks for the reminder... add them to the growing list</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750790805</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:06:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352751001674-115</Id><Title>Time for Congress to investigate Cantor's involvement in the Petraeus Affair!</Title><Msg>Lots of question for the Congressman.</Msg><Username>its_nice_up_here</Username><Timestamp>1352751001674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:10:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352751099879-116</Id><Topic><Title>How many more scandals have been suppressed...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750566825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fast and Furious...Swept under the rug.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352751099879</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:11:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352751422853-117</Id><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Msg>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts By Michael Snyder November 11th, 2012 Barack Obama received more than 99% of the vote in more than 100 precincts in Cuyahoga County, Ohio on election day. In fact, there were a substantial number of precincts where Mitt Romney got exactly zero votes. So how in the world did this happen? Third world dictators don't even get 99% of the vote. Overall, Mitt Romney received 30.12% of the vote in Cuyahoga County. There were even a bunch of precincts in Cuyahoga County that Romney actually won. But everyone certainly expected that Cuyahoga County would be Obama territory. And in most of the precincts that is exactly what we saw - large numbers of votes for both candidates but a definite edge for Obama. However, there are more than 100 precincts in Cuyahoga County where the voting results can only be described as truly bizarre. Yes, we always knew that urban areas would lean very heavily toward Obama, but are we actually expected to believe that Obama got over 99% of the votes in those areas? In more than 50 different precincts, Romney received 2 votes or less. Considering how important the swing state of Ohio was to the national election, one would think that such improbable results would get the attention of somebody out there. Could we be looking at evidence of election fraud hidden in plain sight? Perhaps if there were just one or two precincts where Obama got more than 99% of the vote we could dismiss the results as "statistical anomalies" and ignore them. But there were more than 100 precincts where this happened in the most important swing state in the nation. Maybe there is some rational explanation for the numbers that you are about to see. If there is, I would really love to hear it. What makes all of this even more alarming is that there were reports of voting machine problems during early voting in Ohio. It was being reported that some voters were claiming that they tried to vote for Romney but that the voting machines kept recording their votes as votes for Obama... "I don't know if it happened to anybody else or not, but this is the first time in all the years that we voted that this has ever happened to me," said Marion, Ohio, voter Joan Stevens. Stevens said that when she voted, it took her three tries before the machine accepted her choice to vote for Romney. "I went to vote and I got right in the middle of Romney's name," Stevens told Fox News, saying that she was certain to put her finger directly on her choice for the White House. She said that the first time she pushed "Romney," the machine marked "Obama." So she pushed Romney again. Obama came up again. Then it happened a third time. "Maybe you make a mistake once, but not three times," she told Fox News. The numbers that you are about to see are quite dramatic. They come straight from the website of the Cuyahoga County board of elections. Once again, I am not alleging that election fraud has actually taken place. What I am saying is that these numbers look very, very strange and that somebody needs to start asking some questions. Posted below are voting results from the presidential election from various precincts in Cuyahoga County, Ohio. If you wish to verify these numbers, you can do so right here. In each case, the specific precinct is identified first, followed by the number of votes for Obama and then the number of votes for Romney. In this first set of Cuyahoga County precincts, Mitt Romney received exactly zero votes in each instance... 0154 CLEVELAND -02-Q: 542 - 00192 CLEVELAND -04-L: 388 - 0 0204 CLEVELAND -05-E: 597 - 0 0205 CLEVELAND -05-F: 483 - 0 0206 CLEVELAND -05-G: 257 - 0 0219 CLEVELAND -05-T: 386 - 0 0228 CLEVELAND -06-H: 405 - 0 0232 CLEVELAND -06-L: 70 - 0 0233 CLEVELAND -06-M: 419 - 0 0241 CLEVELAND -06-U: 118 - 0 0248 CLEVELAND -07-F: 361 - 0 0273 CLEVELAND -08-J: 472 - 00280 CLEVELAND -08-Q: 49 - 0 0285 CLEVELAND -09-B: 414 - 0 0288 CLEVELAND -09-E: 478 - 0 0523 EAST CLEVELAND -04-C: 486 - 0Are we actually supposed to believe that not a single person wanted to vote for Mitt Romney in any of those precincts? But wait, there's more. In this next set of results we get to see many of the precincts where Mitt Romney received exactly one vote... 0118 CLEVELAND -01-A: 438 - 1 0144 CLEVELAND -02-G: 532 - 10183 CLEVELAND -04-C: 548 - 10185 CLEVELAND -04-E: 522 - 1 0190 CLEVELAND -04-J: 434 - 1 0200 CLEVELAND -05-A: 364 - 1 0217 CLEVELAND -05-R: 357 - 10240 CLEVELAND -06-T: 148 - 1 0272 CLEVELAND -08-I: 473 - 1 0274 CLEVELAND -08-K: 382 - 10276 CLEVELAND -08-M: 492 - 10279 CLEVELAND -08-P: 378 - 1 0284 CLEVELAND -09-A: 320 - 10287 CLEVELAND -09-D: 394 - 1 0289 CLEVELAND -09-F: 468 - 1 0290 CLEVELAND -09-G: 400 - 1 0303 CLEVELAND -10-C: 471 - 1 0312 CLEVELAND -10-L: 363 - 1 0314 CLEVELAND -10-N: 340 - 1 0315 CLEVELAND -10-O: 473 - 1 0512 EAST CLEVELAND -02-D: 437 - 1 0513 EAST CLEVELAND -02-E: 359 - 1 1040 WARRENSVILLE HTS -02-A: 523 - 1 1041 WARRENSVILLE HTS -02-B: 514 - 1Do these numbers look believable to anyone out there? Now let's look at some of the Cuyahoga County precincts were Mitt Romney received exactly two votes... 0120 CLEVELAND -01-C: 531 - 2 0128 CLEVELAND -01-K: 470 - 2 0136 CLEVELAND -01-S: 635 - 2 0147 CLEVELAND -02-J: 541 - 2 0148 CLEVELAND -02-K: 632 - 2 0149 CLEVELAND -02-L: 531 - 2 0153 CLEVELAND -02-P: 564 - 2 0155 CLEVELAND -02-R: 509 - 20187 CLEVELAND -04-G: 491 - 2 0188 CLEVELAND -04-H: 508 - 2 0194 CLEVELAND -04-N: 520 - 2 0211 CLEVELAND -05-L: 461 - 2 0213 CLEVELAND -05-N: 324 - 2 0222 CLEVELAND -06-B: 637 - 2 0225 CLEVELAND -06-E: 505 - 2 0226 CLEVELAND -06-F: 342 - 2 0234 CLEVELAND -06-N: 244 - 2 0236 CLEVELAND -06-P: 438 - 20249 CLEVELAND -07-G: 446 - 2 0250 CLEVELAND -07-H: 358 - 2 0251 CLEVELAND -07-I: 445 - 2 0253 CLEVELAND -07-K: 429 - 2 0256 CLEVELAND -07-N: 433 - 2 0262 CLEVELAND -07-T: 363 - 20269 CLEVELAND -08-F: 463 - 2 0270 CLEVELAND -08-G: 516 - 2 0278 CLEVELAND -08-O: 405 - 2 0302 CLEVELAND -10-B: 452 - 2 0311 CLEVELAND -10-K: 476 - 2 0511 EAST CLEVELAND -02-C: 319 - 2 0515 EAST CLEVELAND -03-A: 359 - 2 0516 EAST CLEVELAND -03-B: 459 - 2 0519 EAST CLEVELAND -03-E: 293 - 2 0526 EAST CLEVELAND -04-F: 517 - 2 0625 HIGHLAND HILLS -00-A: 377 - 2 These numbers look even more bizarre when you start comparing them with the overall results from the rest of Cuyahoga County that you can find right here. The results from most of the precincts look very much like what you would expect from a competitive national election. But there are more than 100 precincts where the results look incredibly suspicious. Here are some more precincts where Barack Obama won more than 99% of the vote... 0119 CLEVELAND -01-B: 558 - 4 0121 CLEVELAND -01-D: 452 - 3 0122 CLEVELAND -01-E: 671 - 5 0123 CLEVELAND -01-F: 704 - 6 0124 CLEVELAND -01-G: 543 - 3 0126 CLEVELAND -01-I: 674 - 4 0127 CLEVELAND -01-J: 687 - 4 0130 CLEVELAND -01-M: 781 - 4 0132 CLEVELAND -01-O: 615 - 4 0133 CLEVELAND -01-P: 733 - 5 0134 CLEVELAND -01-Q: 753 - 6 0135 CLEVELAND -01-R: 697 - 50142 CLEVELAND -02-E: 434 - 3 0145 CLEVELAND -02-H: 571 - 3 0150 CLEVELAND -02-M: 503 - 4 0151 CLEVELAND -02-N: 601 - 30152 CLEVELAND -02-O: 621 - 3 0156 CLEVELAND -02-S: 471 - 4 0157 CLEVELAND -03-A: 489 - 3 0184 CLEVELAND -04-D: 576 - 30186 CLEVELAND -04-F: 572 - 30189 CLEVELAND -04-I: 503 - 3 0191 CLEVELAND -04-K: 508 - 4 0193 CLEVELAND -04-M: 497 - 4 0195 CLEVELAND -04-O: 599 - 3 0196 CLEVELAND -04-P: 443 - 3 0199 CLEVELAND -04-S: 686 - 5 0203 CLEVELAND -05-D: 569 - 4 0207 CLEVELAND -05-H: 341 - 3 0210 CLEVELAND -05-K: 427 - 3 0212 CLEVELAND -05-M: 340 - 3 0216 CLEVELAND -05-Q: 461 - 4 0218 CLEVELAND -05-S: 515 - 5 0221 CLEVELAND -06-A: 701 - 3 0223 CLEVELAND -06-C: 462 - 4 0227 CLEVELAND -06-G: 401 - 3 0230 CLEVELAND -06-J: 475 - 4 0254 CLEVELAND -07-L: 447 - 4 0261 CLEVELAND -07-S: 449 - 4 0271 CLEVELAND -08-H: 552 - 4 0275 CLEVELAND -08-L: 499 - 3 0282 CLEVELAND -08-S: 517 - 4 0292 CLEVELAND -09-I: 423 - 4 0294 CLEVELAND -09-K: 445 - 40307 CLEVELAND -10-G: 428 - 4 0317 CLEVELAND -10-Q: 446 - 3 0320 CLEVELAND -10-T: 654 - 5 0510 EAST CLEVELAND -02-B: 401 - 4 0518 EAST CLEVELAND -03-D: 374 - 3 0520 EAST CLEVELAND -03-F: 457 - 3 0521 EAST CLEVELAND -04-A: 453 - 4 1045 WARRENSVILLE HTS -04-B: 598 - 4 1049 WARRENSVILLE HTS -06-B: 480 - 4Once again, perhaps there is a rational explanation for all of this. But I find it really hard to believe that one candidate would get more than 99% of the vote in more than 100 precincts in one of the most important counties in the most hotly contested swing state of the 2012 election. Unfortunately, we may never know the truth about these election results. We are just told that we can trust the voting machines and that we can trust whatever results they end up spitting out at us. Look, I don't know what the truth is, but where there is smoke there is usually fire. Voters reported tens of thousands of voting problems on election day, and it will be an absolute disgrace if those complaints are brushed under the rug now that the election is over. Setting aside who won or who lost, the legitimacy of our elections if of the utmost importance. If we cannot even trust the ballot box, what do we have left? I sincerely hope that authorities in Ohio and in the other swing states will investigate some of the voting "irregularities" that are being reported. Millions of Americans are watching, and if all of this just gets swept under the rug there are going to be a whole lot more people that will lose faith in these voting machines. I know that I already have.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352751789596-118</Id><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Msg>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end? BY COACH COLLINS, ON NOVEMBER 12TH, 2012 By Kevin “Coach” Collins It didn’t take long. The layoffs and closings are piling up. The saddest thing about compiling this list is that by the time today is over, the list will probably have grown dramatically. The next saddest part is that at least some of these lay off employees voted for Barack Obama because they didn’t believe this would happen. These are more than just headlines. Every number represents real people who have lost their livelihood. Boeing Announces Big Layoffs in Defense Division cut 30% of workforce Anonymous employer in Los Vegas: “I have 114 employees. I’m firing 22” Momentive Inc. plans 150 “temporary” layoffs – Tyler County West Virginia Wilkes-Barre Pennsylvania “voluntary furloughs” for 300 town workers. Joe Biden’s gift to his old neighborhood Berks County Pennsylvania Exide Technologies to lay off 150 workers Groupon is starting with 80 employee layoffs. But more will certainly follow as the stock price has dropped from $20.00 to $3.85 in the past year TE Connectivity to close Guilford North Carolina plant to lay off 620 50 Layoffs at Anniston Alabama weapons incinerator plant Murray Energy of Steubenville Ohio to layoff 150 Associated Milk Producers of Worthington Minnesota has laid off 130 workers Stanford Brake plant of Lincoln County Kentucky to lay off 75 by Christmas TurboCare, Oce Manchester and East Hartford Connecticut laying off more than 220 workers ATI of North Richland Hills Texas to layoff 172 SpaceX – Rocketdyne Hawthorne California lays off 100 Providence Journal lays off 23 full time employees CVPH of Plattsburgh New York to lay off 17 New Energy of Indiana lays off final 40 workers and closes up 102 East Carbon Utah miners lose jobs – war on coal KIAs U.S. Cellular in Chicago cuts 640 workers Obama fans get what they voted for Career Education cutting 900 jobs across Illinois Vesta Wind Systems cutting 3,000 Oregon getting what THEY voted for! FirstEnergy Akron Ohio cuts 200 Energizer of St. Louis to cut about 1,500 in Vermont and Missouri West Ridge Mine a Utah coal company has laid off 102 miners. Strap yourself in and prepare for this to get much worse before it gets better.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352751880718-119</Id><Topic><Title>How many more scandals have been suppressed...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352750566825</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:02:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>3. Border Patrol Agent Brian Terry mudered by guns purchased by Eric Holder 4. Kathleen Sebelius breaks federal law, keeps her job 5. Obama administration leaks sensitive national security information about UBL raid(for political purposes. 6. Obama administration tells defense contractors to violate federal law. Bonus: Obama administration says it will use taxpayer dollars to pay any government fines incurred. 7.????</Msg><Username>gaga.getty</Username><Timestamp>1352751880718</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:24:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352752087735-120</Id><Title>Democrats had better start Soul Searching</Title><Msg>Democrats Better Start Soul Searching Commentary Magazine ^ | November 11, 2012 | Abe Greenwald Posted on Mon Nov 12 2012 07:28:26 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) by Kaslin Barack Obama ushered in America’s first large-scale experiment in personality-cult politics. The experiment continues apace. Obama got reelected because he enjoys a degree of personal popularity disconnected from his record. No modern president has ever been returned to office with employment figures and right-rack-wrong-track numbers as poor as those Obama has achieved. Obama couldn’t run on his record, which proved to be no problem—Americans didn’t vote on his record. According to exit polls, 77 percent of voters said the economy is bad and only 25 percent said they’re better off than they were four years ago. But since six in ten voters claimed the economy as their number one issue, it’s clear this election wasn’t about issues at all. The president’s reelection is not evidence of a new liberal America, but rather of the illogical and confused experience that is infatuation. For multiple reasons, Americans continue to have a crush on Barack Obama even after his universally panned first term. No longer quite head over heels, they’re at the “I know he’s no good for me, but I can change him” phase. Whatever this means, it surely doesn’t suggest conservatives would be wise to move closer to policies that aren’t even popular among Obama supporters. Why isn’t soul searching underway on the left? When the personality at the center of the cult leaves the stage in four years, Democrats will own his results without the benefit of his appeal. We can’t know quite what a second Obama term will bring, but if his first term is an indication, there’s little reason to expect his party will be crowing. The fiscal cliff is here but a whole landscape of steep drops comes next: the economic cliff (over which lies a possible double-dip recession), the Obamacare cliff (over which lies an unprecedented bureaucratic behemoth), the Iran cliff (over which lies a nuclear bomb), and so on. A precipice in every direction and a president who’s given us no reason to presume he can steer clear. Have Democrats stopped to wonder what initiatives they’ll have to defend when the dust settles in 2016? Already Obama has signaled he’s continuing policies that don’t meet the moment. There’s the assurance of more taxes, of course. But that’s not all. On Friday, citing ecological concerns, the administration closed off 1.6 million acres of federal land in western states from planned oil shale extraction. An American energy boom lies in wait underground and Obama is determined to keep it there. Abroad, the groundwork is being laid to offer Iran a fanciful “grand bargain” in an effort to halt its work on a nuclear weapon. Think “Russian reset” with fanatical theocrats. Perhaps Democrats are confident purely because of their stance on social issues. But as a tactical matter (principle and ideology are a different question), is doesn’t make sense for Republicans to fret over the culture and identity wars that have transfixed the left. Gay marriage as a presidential issue is off the table. The November election showed the future of that question lives at the state level, which is both a popular and conservative approach. Obama himself has said he’ll do nothing about it nationally. Multiple polls taken this year show opposition to abortion is at least as high as it’s been in 15 years. By 2016, the new class war will surely have wound down after Americans see that making the “rich pay their fare share” didn’t solve everyone else’s problems and in fact created new ones. On immigration reform, of course conservatives should act. That was true before Obama’s reelection; it’s now inevitable. In the next four years, serious Republicans will offer policies aiming to give foreign workers a path to citizenship. Leaders like Marco Rubio have already gotten a brilliant head start. It is in the nature of personality cults to fail at most things beyond generating and disseminating propaganda. This inability is the result of two things. First, the personality’s popularity is not results-driven. Since adoration hasn’t been earned by achievement but by the advent of charisma, why kill yourself trying to get results. Second, few people are willing to candidly critique the personality at the center of the cult, so there is little chance of course correction. None of this bodes well for Barack Obama. And for the country’s sake, let’s hope it’s wrong. To effect a revolution in American politics, you have to set parameters that successors will be compelled to heed. FDR implemented programs that at least produced identifiable results before revealing their unsustainable flaws. Bill Clinton had no problem declaring the age of big government over because Ronald Reagan had ushered in a prosperous era in which this was so. What part of the Obama agenda will resonate when isolated from the Obama phenomenon? It’s too soon to say, but not too soon wonder.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352752087735</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:28:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352752473971-121</Id><Title>Rhonda and I still think Mitt can achieve a landslide!!!</Title><Msg>it's not to late for him to pull it off!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352752473971</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:34:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352752500082-122</Id><Topic><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No reason to hire anyone with ObamaCare and incredible Federal regs. At our business our partners are planning to lay off about 20% of the workforce....we anticipate a drop in revenue in 2013 and ObamaCare is a killer for the employer. We do provide health insurance already, but it's gone up and we may just abandon our policy and take the Federal penalty instead, leaving the remaining employees with a lousy policy. OF COURSE, the Feds could write a law REQUIRING THAT WE BUY INSURANCE FOR ALL OUR EMPLOYEES AT VERY HIGH LEVELS...then, of course, we'd lay off more employees. Not many employees actually justify their expense. Some do, we'll keep those. Most are border line.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352752500082</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:35:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352752541834-123</Id><Title>59 philly precincts and not one Romney vote- Russia does touch this fraud</Title><Msg>Worse than a Russian Election Fraud Interactive map: 59 divisions, no Romney votes 1 p.m. chat today: Robert W. Patterson on the GOP/Romney's loss and why Miriam Hill, Andrew Seidman, and John Duchneskie, Inquirer Staff Writers POSTED: Monday, November 12, 2012, 5:30 AM It's one thing for a Democratic presidential candidate to dominate a Democratic city like Philadelphia, but check out this head-spinning figure: In 59 voting divisions in the city, Mitt Romney received not one vote. Zero. Zilch. These are the kind of numbers that send Republicans into paroxysms of voter-fraud angst, but such results may not be so startling after all. "We have always had these dense urban corridors that are extremely Democratic," said Jonathan Rodden, a political science professor at Stanford University. "It's kind of an urban fact, and you are looking at the extreme end of it in Philadelphia." Most big cities are politically homogeneous, with 75 percent to 80 percent of voters identifying as Democrats. Cities are not only bursting with Democrats: They are easier to organize than rural areas where people live far apart from one another, said Sasha Issenberg, author of The Victory Lab: The Secret Science of Winning Campaigns. "One reason Democrats can maximize votes in Philadelphia is that it's very easy to knock on every door," Issenberg said. Still, was there not one contrarian voter in those 59 divisions, where unofficial vote tallies have President Obama outscoring Romney by a combined 19,605 to 0? The unanimous support for Obama in these Philadelphia neighborhoods - clustered in almost exclusively black sections of West and North Philadelphia - fertilizes fears of fraud, despite little hard evidence. Upon hearing the numbers, Steve Miskin, a spokesman for Republicans in the Pennsylvania House of Representatives, brought up his party's voter-identification initiative - which was held off for this election - and said, "We believe we need to continue ensuring the integrity of the ballot." {"I'd be surprised if there weren't a handful of precincts that didn't cast a vote for Romney," he said. But the number of zero precincts in Philadelphia deserves examination, Sabato added. "Not a single vote for Romney or even an error? That's worth looking into," he said.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352752541834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:35:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352752624526-124</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Philly too had this level of fraud</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352752624526</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:37:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352753125854-125</Id><Title>Chastity Bono look alike and Cage Cleaner Janet Napolitano shows up</Title><Msg>in Staten Island for another "pat on the back" photo op. Can the Obama cage cleaners send anybody but do nothing know nothing butch #$%$ Janet No politano? How about non union construction crews for starters with National Guard protection from Union Bosses?</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352753125854</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:45:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352753401657-126</Id><Title>GOP attempts at voter suppression</Title><Msg>backfired and brought out record levels of minorities voting for Obama, baggers largely to blame for Obama reelection</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352753401657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:50:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352754144839-127</Id><Topic><Title>GOP attempts at voter suppression</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352753401657</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:50:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan, we know and you know that you are dumb. Don't you think that in 59 Philadelphia precints, not one vote for Romney is a little suspect.? Wise up. Liberals have broken the election process.</Msg><Username>agolferbogie</Username><Timestamp>1352754144839</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:02:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352754254817-128</Id><Title>S&amp;P closes on support level</Title><Msg>this could get worse if she does not hold.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352754254817</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:04:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352754255413-129</Id><Topic><Title>Why did Republican House leader Eric Cantor know about Petraeus investigation 12 days before Obama - and more than a week before the Election?</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352751948921</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:25:48 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because Repubs HATE America.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352754255413</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352754458527-130</Id><Title>baggers can be thanked for Obama's reelection</Title><Msg>But six to nine months ago, numerous Obama campaign workers were privately expressing concern about the enthusiasm level of black voters, and about whether the massive 2008 turnout could be equaled. They hoped registration efforts and get-out-the-vote drives would kick in at the right time. Re-electing the first black president was clearly a motivating factor for African-Americans, but what also should be noted is the Republican Party's efforts to enact voter suppression laws. Not only were black folks angered and shocked at Republicans' blatant attempts at voter suppression in Ohio, Pennsylvania, Florida, Virginia, Texas and other states, they exacted revenge at the ballot box. Conservatives have valiantly tried to assert that voter ID laws, trimming the early voting days and even eliminating early voting on Sundays was a prudent and practical decision that had nothing to do with black, Hispanic and young voters, or anyone else. But anyone with half a brain could see that the GOP was desperate to upend the coalition that proved so pivotal to Obama in 2008. All over the country GOP-led legislatures and governors rushed to pass voter ID laws, only to see federal courts reject a number of them that clearly weren't thought through properly. In Ohio, the voter suppression tactics were outrageous. After public pressure mounted to stop the practice of extending early voting in GOP-leaning counties and cutting them in Democratic-leaning counties, Ohio Secretary of State Jon Husted had no choice but to equalize early voting periods.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352754458527</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:07:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352754529834-131</Id><Title>sounds like dumb needs a job</Title><Msg>why dont you and your ids go get a job. all day on a csco message board talking about nothing.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352754529834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:08:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352756085860-132</Id><Topic><Title>ABSOLUTELY!! ALL TAXES MUST INCREASE...THE FEDERAL RESERVE IS RUNNING OUT OF ZERO'S</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352750691283</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:04:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, where's the love, Democratic droolers? Hey, we're on your side...RAISE THEM STINKIN' TAXES SO HIGH YOU CAN STEAL ALL THE MONEY IN AMERICA!!! Go for it...... BLUE PARASITES WIN!!! THEY GOT THE PRESIDENCY AND THE SENATE...we got the House.....go down fightin'???? I'M GOOD WITH THAT...BUT I STILL THINK OBIMBO NEEDS TO TAKE A STAND AND RAISE TAXES...as high as he can....just stratospheric...I'm good with that. I'm ready for a break...stay at home once I reach that cap number...why not? let Warren pay my share! let Beyonce pay my share! let Spike Lee pay my share! Let Bill Gates pay my share! let 'the Donald' pay my share! let Jay Z pay my share! hoo boy, we gonna get so MUCH MONEY!!!! from them rich peoples</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352756085860</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:34:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756144909-133</Id><Title>woopsie, looks like Israel will not run our foreign policy</Title><Msg>Nancy HBloomington, IndianaNYT Pick FLAG I hope Israelis are hearing you because this very much summarizes my feelings . As a long time supporter of Israel, I am finding it increasing difficult to justify how I can support behavior which is reprehensible by any civilized standard. I'm not sure what our policy should be toward Israel, but I don't think we should be jumping through hoops to help this country --so filled with talent and leverage--yet unwilling face their own demons and do the right thing. And Netanyahu's attempt to influence our election really really enraged me. I guess he did when he felt was in the best interests of Israel. If so, he had to take the consequences.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352756144909</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:35:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756452244-134</Id><Title>Can the GOP survive?</Title><Msg>You would expect the Republican Party to make a similar lurch to the center. But many Republican leaders still inhabit a bubble. It was stunning how many, from Karl Rove to Newt Gingrich, seemed to expect a Mitt Romney victory. And some of the right-wing postmortems are suggesting that Romney lost because he was too liberal — which constitutes a definition of delusional. Imagine what would have happened if the Republican nominee had been Gingrich or Rick Santorum. We surely would have seen a Democratic landslide. On the other hand, if the Republicans had nominated Jon Huntsman Jr., they might have been the ones celebrating right now. But he had no chance in Republican primaries because primary voters are their party’s worst enemy. Part of the problem, I think, is the profusion of right-wing radio and television programs. Democrats complain furiously that Rush Limbaugh, Glenn Beck and Sean Hannity smear the left, but I wonder if the bigger loser isn’t the Republican Party itself. Those shows whip up a frenzy in their audience, torpedoing Republican moderates and instilling paranoia on issues like immigration.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352756452244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:40:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352756820383-135</Id><Title>Texas soon to be blue state</Title><Msg>“If Republicans do not do better in the Hispanic community, in a few short years Republicans will no longer be the majority party in our state," he said. Cruz added that losing a state like Texas, which carried 38 electoral votes in 2012, would hold national implications. “If that happens, no Republican will ever again win the White House," he said. "New York and California are for the foreseeable future unalterably Democrat. If Texas turns bright blue, the Electoral College math is simple. We won’t be talking about Ohio, we won’t be talking about Florida or Virginia, because it won’t matter. If Texas is bright blue, you can’t get to two-seventy electoral votes. The Republican Party would cease to exist. We would become like the Whig Party." Cruz' words paralleled those of Mitt Romney adviser Carlos Gutierrez, who said on Sunday that Latinos were "scared of the Republican party." The former Commerce Secretary attributed that fear to the presidential primary process, which he said forces candidates "to say outrageous things."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352756820383</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:47:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352757429388-136</Id><Title>dumb has nothing to do all day</Title><Msg>but post useless crap on csco stock board about nothing. this is not a political board...must be why it calls itself dumb.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352757429388</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:57:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352757474484-137</Id><Topic><Title>sounds like dumb needs a job</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352754529834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:08:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Back when dumdum was deepharbor he professed to be a multi-millionaire. He dropped that lie when he became dumdum</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352757474484</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:57:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352757614792-138</Id><Title>gambling in Casablanca?</Title><Msg>Colin Powell's former chief of staff has blasted the Republican Party for being “full of racists.” The biting assessment from retired Army Col. Lawrence Wilkerson came in response to controversy over a comment made by Mitt Romney campaign co-chair John Sununu, who suggested Powell endorsed President Obama because both men are African-American. Wilkerson called Sununu’s comments “an unfortunate slip of words,” but said he believes a larger issue besets the GOP. “My party, unfortunately, is the bastion of those people — not all of them, but most of them — who are still basing their positions on race,” Wilkerson told MSNBC’s Ed Schultz on Friday. “Let me just be candid: My party is full of racists,” he said. Wilkerson also indicated that he believes race is one of the biggest obstacles President Obama faces in the White House. “The real reason a considerable portion of my party wants President Obama out of the White House has nothing to do with the content of his character, nothing to do with his competence as commander-in-chief and president, and everything to do with the color of his skin,” he said. “That's despicable,” he added.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352757614792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:00:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352759702440-139</Id><Topic><Title>gambling in Casablanca?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352757614792</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:00:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>not all tea baggers are racist but all racists are tea baggers</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352759702440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:35:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760173676-140</Id><Title>Repatriation of Cisco cash dies without a Romney Win</Title><Msg>Obama is too anti business to care if these profits were already taxed oversees. With over $1.5 trillion oversees cash bringing Home the Bacon could mean a shot in the arm for the economy yet Obama doesn't care if we stay in recession for 8 Obama years.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352760173676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:42:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760393970-141</Id><Topic><Title>Repatriation of Cisco cash dies without a Romney Win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352760173676</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:42:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda we have talked about this before, your CSCO stock will keep going down, it will bottom only on the day you finally sell your position</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352760393970</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:46:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760464999-142</Id><Title>Repatriation of Romney Money,,He refuses to Pay Taxes</Title><Msg>We need a President like Romney ,,I pay more TaxesThan</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760464999</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:47:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760526116-143</Id><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Msg>Romney keeps money overseas,,Called faith in the USA</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760605018-144</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Instead, can you tells us what Rassy &amp; Gallup were smoking when they had Mittsy up in Ohio and 3 points up overall? Let's not even talk about Pennsylvania. It wasn't even close. Rassy, Gravis, Gallup are Repub Paid pollsters or they are just inept.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352760605018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:50:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760643891-145</Id><Title>Republicans Message Cheat the USA</Title><Msg>Thats the Republican Message,,,let the Wealthy Rob the treasury why do you think Billionaire put Billions into Romneys campaign</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760643891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:50:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352760805234-146</Id><Title>I am shocked that Romney got 1 Vote</Title><Msg>Man was advocating Rape,,,,No Birth Control,,,he wanted to enlarge the military and and start a few wars</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760805234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:53:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760868927-147</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda 95% of blacks voted for Obama, those counties are 100% black it is not surprising he got 100% of the vote. Oh and by the way Obama won the election in a landslide 332 votes, Ohio didn't even matter.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352760868927</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:54:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352760946827-148</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Congress to investigate Cantor's involvement in the Petraeus Affair!</Title><Username>its_nice_up_here</Username><Timestamp>1352751001674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:10:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if the Repubs planned to ask questions about the affair during the House Investigation so that Patraeus would incriminate himself if he denied the relationship. These repubs are #$%$. They are ready to take down their own if they don't parrott the Limbaugh line. So UnAmerican. No wonder Patraeus resigned so quickly. He must have known that this was a setup by the Repugnant Repub House. Investigate Cantor.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352760946827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:55:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352761197231-149</Id><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Msg>Holding The Revelation Of The Affair Over his head. What a dirty trick. Patraeus did the right thing in resigning. Now did Cantor talk to anyone about the affair?</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352761209116-150</Id><Topic><Title>I am shocked that Romney got 1 Vote</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760805234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:53:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that vote was fraudulent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352761209116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:00:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352761264226-151</Id><Title>gonna lose every election until the baggers are thrown out of the GOP</Title><Msg>"I'm not a trained demographer," Walter notes, "but I can say with certainty that: 1) This country is not getting any whiter and 2) older people die." If winning an election depends on appealing to and then turning out a base of old, white people you are going to lose every presidential election from here on out.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352761264226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:01:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352761662961-152</Id><Topic><Title>gonna lose every election until the baggers are thrown out of the GOP</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352761264226</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:01:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That should make you happy, dumdum. Why dont you just shut up about it and let it happen.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352761662961</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:07:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352761818210-153</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Eric Holder knew months before Cantor. Now take your foot out of your mouth.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352761818210</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:10:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352761930093-154</Id><Topic><Title>Can the GOP survive?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352756452244</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 16:40:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Only if the DEMS stop Cheating.... Unlikely</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352761930093</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:12:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352762019661-155</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Message Cheat the USA</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760643891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mean while DEMS Rob the Elections, then Rob the treasury.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352762019661</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:13:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352762091834-156</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CHEATING DEMS need a lesson, DON'T SPEND, DON'T HIRE !!! GIVE THEM A RECESSION !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352762091834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:14:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762835596-157</Id><Title>Lonesome boy at it again</Title><Msg>Poor Lonesome Junior.I've made it very obvious I think his drivel is asinine.Yet he keeps trying to be my pen pal buddy . Not interested.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352762835596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:27:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352762925352-158</Id><Title>Took my lose and sold</Title><Msg>I could not afford watching this to go down further with my hard earned money. Got in at $17.11 and sold today at $17.05, I had few good runs with CSCO buying at low $17 and selling at mid $17 but not this time. Cash is the king, may get in again sometime after earning.</Msg><Username>jasm5</Username><Timestamp>1352762925352</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:28:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352763577631-159</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney is a private citizen again.Why do you care what he does now?</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352763577631</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:39:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352763700100-160</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The affair will now keep Benghazi in the headlines. Bad for Obama.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352763700100</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:41:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352763971185-161</Id><Topic><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When enough DEMS lose their jobs and homes to their precious illegal hispanic voters.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352763971185</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:46:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764074341-162</Id><Topic><Title>I am shocked that Romney got 1 Vote</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760805234</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:53:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try, YOU CHEATS !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352764074341</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:47:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352764267964-163</Id><Title>ROMNEY PAID MORE INCOME TAXES THAN 47% OF USA POPULATION</Title><Msg>Romney paid more income taxes than 47% of usa population. the solution is to get rid of all the tax credits and impose a minimum 15% income tax on the 47% who dont pay their fair share.</Msg><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1352764267964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:51:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764317811-164</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone I know votes only once, But to be fair I don't know any Dems.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352764317811</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:51:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352764880762-165</Id><Topic><Title>Longs? </Title><Username>ingebaorggogos882</Username><Timestamp>1337870176000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-24 10:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cool picks.</Msg><Username>winsentmortin360</Username><Timestamp>1352764880762</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:01:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352765426628-166</Id><Topic><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walt I have a layoff thread, I will update it tomorrow , also, I think that a company and location thread should be started , this is important for the following reason. People didn't take seriously how rotten the economy is and how afraid small business is to hire and they put a lot of hope after 4 years of being bashed by Obama, hit with regulations, taxed up the wazoo. As you said Obamacare will put many out of business. I think its clear that companies are going to restructure to rely on part timers to eliminate having to pay Obamacare expenses. The lies about the recession having ended with 23 million still out of work was election year rose colored glasses. Fact is lots of states cannot pay unemployment insurance any longer.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352765426628</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:10:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352765688720-167</Id><Title>Why does anyone give a rats a z s about this stock?</Title><Msg>Trades between 17 and 20... who gives a ship?! Boring</Msg><Username>smac693</Username><Timestamp>1352765688720</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:14:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352766296818-168</Id><Title>TAX THE RICH AND TAX THE 47% WHO DONT PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE</Title><Msg>TAX THE RICH AND TAX THE 47% WHO DONT PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE LIMIT CHILD TAX CREDIT TO $700 REGARDLESS OF HOW MANY CHILDREN ARE CLAIMED (to end income tax fraud and get rid of loophole).</Msg><Username>spandex_leggings</Username><Timestamp>1352766296818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:24:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766385659-169</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dems want Banghazi in the headlines. We need to know who was the informant that talked to Woodward about the incident. Was it tied to Patraeus' mistress? Was it Cantor? Who was she talking to? Repubs are just mad that they can't back mail Patraeus.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352766385659</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:26:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352766446524-170</Id><Title>47% (ALL DEMOCRATS) PAY ZERO INCOME TAXES, TAX THEM MAKE THEM PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE</Title><Msg>47% (all democrats) pay zero income taxes, tax them make them pay their fair share get rid of tax loophole and source of income tax fraud ( limit child tax credit to $500 regardless of how many children are claimed)</Msg><Username>algore_eats_his_own_boogers</Username><Timestamp>1352766446524</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766590006-171</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY PAID MORE INCOME TAXES THAN 47% OF USA POPULATION</Title><Username>janet_napalitano_is_ugly</Username><Timestamp>1352764267964</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 18:51:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sad but true. 47% of americans pay zero income taxes yet they have a vote on how income tax money is spent. if they pay no income taxes then they should not have a say in how income tax money is spent. it is not fair that the pay zero income taxes. time to levy a minimum 20% income tax on these 47% free loaders.</Msg><Username>algore_eats_his_own_boogers</Username><Timestamp>1352766590006</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:29:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766677247-172</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you are that interested in Petraeus you should learn how to spell his name. Maybe we'd think your posts were more credible.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352766677247</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:31:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766786058-173</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You display your ignorance prominently. Romney pays a lower overall tax rate due to the fact that most of his income is considered capital gain. Favorable capital gain treatment is the cornerstone of a capitalist system. It supports capital formation which is the basis for the stock market. Obama is attempting to undermine the very fundamentals for the American free enterprise system. There will be no reason to invest in the stock market under Obama. There is no reason to invest bonds or bank notes because interest rates are zero. There is no reason to invest in real estate because Obama plans to eliminate tax favored status. In short, stupid Americans who have never been outside the country, have never been taught geography or ignore or never learned history are being led right down the rosy path to socialism. This is un-believable. Obama appeals to the uneducated and government dependent slob parasites that are taking this country down the toilet.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352766786058</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:33:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352766802018-174</Id><Topic><Title>TAX THE RICH AND TAX THE 47% WHO DONT PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE</Title><Username>spandex_leggings</Username><Timestamp>1352766296818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These 47% pay zero income taxes. This is not fair to the 53% who pay all the income taxes. These 47% deadbeats should be forced to pay a minimum 15% income tax regardless of how many bogus tax credits they claim. The tax credits should be limited to $250 no matter how many phony kids these 47% claim that they have.</Msg><Username>raymooondo</Username><Timestamp>1352766802018</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352766913856-175</Id><Title>Rhonda Edelstein Voted for Legitimate Rape</Title><Msg>Republicans are Dumber than you think</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352766913856</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352766951175-176</Id><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Msg>look forward to an astronomical rise in crime rates nationwide: murders, rapes, armed robberies, drug arrests, home invasions, etc. etc. (most of them of course perpetrated by Obutthead voters), not to mention a dive into a depression that will last for decades with a doubling of the unemployement rate. Way to go #$%$, you will regret voting for the piece of excrement when the gubment is forced to cut your food stamps and other entitlement #$%$ back because they are bankrupt and they've milked the U.S. taxpayer dry.</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767092658-177</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You Idiots said the same thing about Slavery,,,,for 100s of Years whites were Parasites who lived off labor of Blacks</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352767092658</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:38:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767242420-178</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone I know Pays more Taxes than Romney</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760526116</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:48:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan said earned income should be taxed at the same rate as investment income, do you think Reagan was wrong?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352767242420</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:40:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767397266-179</Id><Topic><Title>TAX THE RICH AND TAX THE 47% WHO DONT PAY THEIR FAIR SHARE</Title><Username>spandex_leggings</Username><Timestamp>1352766296818</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:24:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The tax credits should be limited to $250 no matter how many phony kids these 47% claim that they have.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1352767397266</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:43:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767453003-180</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I dont believe it was a fraudulent election but we gave an incompetent boob four more years to keep screwing up . Unfortunately the 48 % who voted against will pay him just a big a price as the 50% who voted for him. Companies have already started announcing layoffs.Recession is coming. Hope they enjoy the food stamps and Obama phones.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352767453003</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:44:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352767689648-181</Id><Topic><Title>Time for Congress to investigate Cantor's involvement in the Petraeus Affair!</Title><Username>its_nice_up_here</Username><Timestamp>1352751001674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:10:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cantor got dual citizenship israely and American ,he is a rat ! Him and Bibi are crying river .</Msg><Username>my6peros</Username><Timestamp>1352767689648</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:48:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352768833994-182</Id><Title>Remember when W said he had a mandate. LOL</Title><Msg>In winning re-election, Barack Obama secured more electoral votes than any Republican presidential candidate in the last 24 years wopsie</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352768833994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:07:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769121478-183</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when W said he had a mandate. LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352768833994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:07:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>50 percent of the vote is not a mandate. It was enough to get reelected. And when did you start caring what Bush said?</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352769121478</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:12:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769200091-184</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>are you kidding? The Obama koolaidkids will have an increase in their standard of living just by Obamacare being given to them. They never pay taxes anyway, only those who work for a living are going to be punished.</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352769200091</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:13:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769293012-185</Id><Topic><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Being White is a Full Time Job,,,all that Hate,,,,keeps You Busy....</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352769293012</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:14:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769308986-186</Id><Topic><Title>Longs? </Title><Username>ingebaorggogos882</Username><Timestamp>1337870176000</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-05-24 10:36:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Already a member since 2006, you really know how to pick them.</Msg><Username>winsentmortin360</Username><Timestamp>1352769308986</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:15:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769319260-187</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>btw, there was RAMPANT voter fraud being reported all over, especially in FL and OH, 2 key states, but others as well. He did not win this election, the fraud stole it!</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352769319260</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:15:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352769400569-188</Id><Title>Barrack Obama Record Oil Production....Great President</Title><Msg>USA will be number 1 oil Producer</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352769400569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:16:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769475880-189</Id><Topic><Title>The layoffs have only just begun; when will they end?</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751789596</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:23:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to be the hater,buddy and racist too.You slam "whitey" almost every post.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352769475880</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:17:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352769493698-190</Id><Title>NO Layoffs last 10 Years,,They Only Just Begun,,</Title><Msg>Rhonda is full of #$%$</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352769493698</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:18:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352769766996-191</Id><Topic><Title>Barrack Obama Record Oil Production....Great President</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352769400569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:16:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Takes 3-5 years to get a well from permits to production. So most of what you are talking about began under Bush. You should do a little research before you post.You might not look quite so stupid.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352769766996</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:22:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352770046765-192</Id><Title>Give Billionaires More Money they give u a JOB</Title><Msg>hahahahahaha......Republicans are sick.... So,,,,If I refuse Health Care,,,,Billionaires will hire,,,hey,,,,I treat my Dogs better than that.</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352770046765</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:27:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352770092966-193</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Scrotum In one post you say the leeches will never have it so good,in your next post,you say they will lose it??So which is it??</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352770092966</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352770102994-194</Id><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Msg>.. Secession petitions filed in 20 states President Obama waves to the crowd on election night. (Photo By Chris Carlson, AP) In the wake of last week's presidential election, thousands of Americans have signed petitions seeking permission for their states to peacefully secede from the United States. The petitions were filed on We the People, a government website.</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352770486827-195</Id><Title>THINK FEW IF ANY ARE HIRING TODAY?</Title><Msg>then wait til next year when there's a bread line in every town, just like in Russia and China, waiting hours for a little food, sleeping on the street or in tents with your family and I don't mean on a vacation camping trip either!</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770486827</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:34:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352771362442-196</Id><Topic><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the poor, welfare confederate states decide to secede this time the rich educated northern states will be smart enough to tell them good by. with no colleges better then a community college and no innovation at all the blue states are no better then Haiti.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352771362442</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:49:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352771469477-197</Id><Topic><Title>Republicans Message Cheat the USA</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352760643891</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:50:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They been screwing those wh make under 250K for yrs. , hint abolish unions , no collective bargaining, well the chickens have come home to roost .</Msg><Username>settegast_scholar</Username><Timestamp>1352771469477</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:51:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352772751120-198</Id><Topic><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It happens slowly so you don't even realize it. Pernicious, constant, undermining -- bashing of banks and business due to a financial crisis. Central government control due to crisis. Massive increase in taxes and government welfare due to crisis. Rahm told you. Crisis creates the opportunity for socialist solutions. The fiscal cliff is exactly what Obama wanted to assume control. Lemmings are blind. Worship Dear Leader.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352772751120</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352772800066-199</Id><Topic><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You and your kind are proof that ignorance is bliss.</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1352772800066</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:13:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352772876960-200</Id><Topic><Title>Barrack Obama Record Oil Production....Great President</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352769400569</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:16:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That is the socialist model -- excessive control of business, difficult permits except for the well connected donors, EPA, FDA, NAACP. Black Power Socialism.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352772876960</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:14:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773054525-201</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>2 million fewer people voted for Romney than for McCain 4 years ago. Did people just give up because the lib media told them Romney had no chance -- you betcha. The North Korean lib media propaganda campaign spin machine helped Obama stay in office. Now he is gonna make those TV news readers pay. Used and now ready to be discarded like a used condom.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352773054525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:17:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773122357-202</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Folks on welfare and food stamps don't even know there's a recession -- in fact, life is good.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352773122357</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:18:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773205390-203</Id><Topic><Title>With Obutthead Fraudulently Back in Office, You can</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1352766951175</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 19:35:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Companies have already started announcing layoffs.Recession is coming. Hope they enjoy the food stamps and Obama phones. *** Seems like a cold hard winter is in store for the Northeast libs.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352773205390</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:20:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352773422132-204</Id><Title>WHEN TEXAS SECEDES I'M BECOMING A CITIZEN OF TEXAS AFTERWARDS I DONT GIVE A @#$% IF OBAMA BANKRUPTS THE USA</Title><Msg>WHEN TEXAS SECEDES I'M BECOMING A CITIZEN OF TEXAS AFTERWARDS I DONT GIVE A @#$% IF OBAMA BANKRUPTS THE USA and the USA goes to hell and becomes a 3rd world Greece.</Msg><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1352773422132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:23:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773426414-205</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Petraeus affair is a smokescreen to divert attention during the Benghazi hearings. Paula is a hotter than his wife.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352773426414</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:23:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352773984806-206</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Adam Corolla said tonight what really worries him is the head of the CIA couldn' t keep an affair secret!!!Funny!</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352773984806</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:33:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352774011049-207</Id><Title>USA NO LONGER EXISTS IT BECAME A MUSLIM OBAMAVILLE</Title><Msg>Usa no longer exists it became a muslim communistic obamaville i'm hoping againt hope that all the red states secede and impose border controls to keep democrats out to enforce the borders with deadly force. more importantly red states should have their own currency and goverment to insure we dont have any worthless obamaville dollars.</Msg><Username>hilary_fot_herway2stage_2b_booed</Username><Timestamp>1352774011049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:33:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352774253036-208</Id><Topic><Title>USA NO LONGER EXISTS IT BECAME A MUSLIM OBAMAVILLE</Title><Username>hilary_fot_herway2stage_2b_booed</Username><Timestamp>1352774011049</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:33:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama thought he could buy an election by giving a bunch of goodies to the leeches in this country. . He was right.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352774253036</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:37:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352774782674-209</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN TEXAS SECEDES I'M BECOMING A CITIZEN OF TEXAS AFTERWARDS I DONT GIVE A @#$% IF OBAMA BANKRUPTS THE USA</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1352773422132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:23:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those lazy useless good for nothing lowlife welfare parasites become Obamavilles problem.</Msg><Username>democrat_occupier_wall_of_doodoo</Username><Timestamp>1352774782674</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:46:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776068108-210</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN TEXAS SECEDES I'M BECOMING A CITIZEN OF TEXAS AFTERWARDS I DONT GIVE A @#$% IF OBAMA BANKRUPTS THE USA</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1352773422132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:23:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The remaining patriot states should form an Economic Union of Red States that has no income taxes, no welfare or free hospital(if you dont work you starve to death, if you dont pay for services you dont get any services, if you engage in criminal activity any citizen can shoot you on sight), no ACLU, no stupid left wing activists, no occupiers who will be shot on site to save tax dollars on jail costs, no labor unions or former members of unions, no former left wing public 'school' workers, no liberal sexual deviants like homos no left winger propagandists(journalists), no left winger judges In the new Economic Union of Red States murderers and gang members get executed promptly, criminals have no rights and can be shot dead while comitting a crime and no trial is needed.</Msg><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1352776068108</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:07:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776405543-211</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN TEXAS SECEDES I'M BECOMING A CITIZEN OF TEXAS AFTERWARDS I DONT GIVE A @#$% IF OBAMA BANKRUPTS THE USA</Title><Username>gwbush_is_a_patriot</Username><Timestamp>1352773422132</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 21:23:42 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Red State Govt wants to build a road they must ask people with money for the funds to build the road. Those who contribute funding for the road have a say in how the road is built and where it is built. Those who contribute nothing have NO SAY. Only those people who contribute money have a vote in what is done with their money.</Msg><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1352776405543</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:13:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776605264-212</Id><Topic><Title>Wonder If Cantor &amp; Repub House Were Setting Patraeus Up.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352761197231</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 17:59:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course that is the best you Repubs can come up with. But your buddy Cantor is going down.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1352776605264</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:16:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776814304-213</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that you can see Obama may not have won on the up and up How did Romney get 2 million less votes than McCain?</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352776814304</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:20:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352776957753-214</Id><Topic><Title>59 philly precincts and not one Romney vote- Russia does touch this fraud</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352752541834</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:35:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How did Romney who ran a better campaign than McCain get 2 million less votes than McCain, and why were the polls so wrong. Obama got 9 million less votes than last time, something isn't right here. That is why so many are looking to secede</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352776957753</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 22:22:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352779499208-215</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gawd, you are one scary stream of right wing angry white man sound bytes. Can you tell me where you live so that I don't accidentally drive through that place?</Msg><Username>oil_for_bullets_initiative</Username><Timestamp>1352779499208</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352779682819-216</Id><Topic><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Ted Nugent promised he would either be dead or in jail by now. And Rush Limbaugh promised to move to Costa Rica if Obama won. And the south has been threatening to secede since 1866. So, what is the holdup? Mah Gawd, northerners are salivating at the prospect of getting rid of the fat Jeezus Pony states.</Msg><Username>oil_for_bullets_initiative</Username><Timestamp>1352779682819</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:08:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352779857583-217</Id><Title>Founders said only property owners should have a vote</Title><Msg>Makes sense even more after hundreds of years. Taxpayers sick of paying for the moochers who vote for handouts and those who give them away.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352779857583</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:10:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352780799463-218</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!! Rhoda needs a whaaaaambulance after a particularly starge siesta with dog in the back yard! waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352780799463</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:26:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352780950469-219</Id><Topic><Title>Election Fraud? Obama Won More Than 99 Percent Of The Vote In More Than 100 Ohio Precincts</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352751422853</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 15:17:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You lose Ivan. Now time to go clean your guns, while you still havee them. There will be an agent knocking at your door soon enough. You are being watched. Now go get to the bottom of your bourbon bottle. Crybaby. waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352780950469</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:29:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352781091450-220</Id><Topic><Title>ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352668230474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-11-11 16:10:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!! waaahh!! waahhh!!!! waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352781091450</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:31:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352781240721-221</Id><Topic><Title>MANY READY TO SECEDE FROM THE NOW CORRUPT, PINKO-RULED U.S.A.</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352770102994</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 20:28:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! sore losing teabagging hilljack....GTH LOSER just move out of the country or kill yourself, no one will notice either way LOSER</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352781240721</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-12 23:34:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>