<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-05"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344140218787-1</Id><Title>CiscoBuy Ratings</Title><Msg>Credit Suisse: Outperform The Street: BUY Ford Equity Research: STRONG BUY JAYWALK Consensus: BUY I am not a fast trader, but buy and hold. Besides, CSCO pays a 2% dividend. That's a plus while I wait that this undervalued stock goes up. By the way, I thought that this message board is for financial knowledge exchange. It seems to me like it has become more of a political forum</Msg><Username>velcro1000</Username><Timestamp>1344140218787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 00:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344144929536-2</Id><Topic><Title>August $17 calls, huge volume!</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1344092013506</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 10:53:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>August expiration max-pain is at $17. Looks like we have another 4% in the common near-term, and a lot more than that if you are in the calls. GLTY!</Msg><Username>portguyofva</Username><Timestamp>1344144929536</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 01:35:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344163369625-3</Id><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Msg>AP - WASHINGTON D.C. In a move certain to fuel the debate over Obama's qualifications for the presidency, the group "Americans for Freedom of Information" has Released copies of President Obama's college transcripts from Occidental College ... Released today, the transcript school indicates that Obama, under the name Barry Soetoro, received financial aid as a foreign student from Indonesia as an undergraduate. The transcript was released by Occidental College in compliance with a court order in a suit brought by the group in the Superior Court of California. The transcript shows that Obama (Soetoro) applied for financial aid and was awarded a fellowship for foreign students from the Fulbright Foundation Scholarship program. To qualify, for the scholarship, a student must claim foreign citizenship. This document would seem to provide the smoking gun that many of Obama's detractors have been seeking. Along with the evidence that he was first born in Kenya and there is no record of him ever applying for US citizenship, this is looking pretty grim. The news has created a firestorm at the White House as the release casts increasing doubt about Obama's legitimacy and qualification to serve as President article titled, "Obama Eligibility Questioned," leading some to speculate that the story may overshadow economic issues on Obama's first official visit to the U.K. In a related matter, under growing pressure from several groups, Justice Antonin Scalia announced that the Supreme Court agreed on Tuesday to hear arguments concerning Obama's legal eligibility to serve as President in a case brought by Leo Donofrio of New Jersey . This lawsuit claims Obama's dual c itizenship disqualified him from serving as president.. Donofrio's case is just one of 18 suits brought by citizens demanding proof of Obama's citizenship or qualification to serve as president. Gary Kreep of the United States Justice Foundation has released the results of their investigation of Obama's campaign spending. This study estimates that Obama has spent upwards of $950,000 in campaign funds in the past year with eleven law firms in 12 states for legal resources to block disclosure of any of his personal records. Mr. Kreep indicated that the investigation is still ongoing but that the final report will be provided to the U.S. Attorney general, Eric Holder. Mr. Holder has refused to comment on the matter... LET OTHER FOLKS KNOW THIS NEWS, THE MEDIA WON'T! Subject: RE: Issue of Passport? While I've little interest in getting in the middle of the Obama birth issue, Paul Hollrah over at FSM did so yesterday and believes the issue can be resolved by Obama answering one simple question: What passport did he use when he was shuttling between New York , Jakarta , and Karachi ? So how did a young man who arrived in New York in early June 1981, without the price of a hotel room in his pocket, suddenly come up with the price of a round-the-world trip just a month later? And once he was on a plane, shuttling between New York , Jakarta , and Karachi , what passport was he offering when he passed through Customs and Immigration? The American people not only deserve to have answers to these questions, they must have answers. It makes the debate over Obama's citizenship a rather short and simple one. Q: Did he travel to Pakistan in 1981, at age 20? A : Yes, by his own admission. Q: What passport did he travel under? A: There are only three possibilities. 1) He traveled with a U.S. ... Passport, 2) He traveled with a British passport, or 3) He traveled with an Indonesia passport. Q: Is it possible that Obama traveled with a U.S. Passport in 1981? A: No. It is not possible. Pakistan was on the U.S. . State Department's "no travel" list in 1981. Conclusion: When Obama went to Pakistan in 1981 he was traveling either with a British passport or an Indonesian passport. If he were traveling with a British passport that would provide proof that he was born in Kenya on August 4, 1961, not in Hawaii as he claims.. And if he were traveling with an Indonesian passport that would tend to prove that he relinquished whatever previous citizenship he held, British or American, prior to being adopted by his Indonesian step-father in 1967. Whatever the truth of the matter, the American people need to know how he managed to become a "natural born" American citizen between 1981 and 2008.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344167398130-4</Id><Title>15th ammendment</Title><Msg>voter id...a slick way for disfranchisement of many black voters...skirts the 15th ammendment in a slich and cynical way...we are in trouble as a nation if the courts don't strike down this voter id attempt</Msg><Username>hwardeinhorn</Username><Timestamp>1344167398130</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 07:49:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344179012847-5</Id><Topic><Title>CiscoBuy Ratings</Title><Username>velcro1000</Username><Timestamp>1344140218787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 00:16:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The entire networking group has been hammered down, imo because of changes in Global Enterprise Networking Infrastructure standards. The well positioned co's are emerging as leaders in this sector and the 'anal'ists have had no idea who that would be. Due some serious dd before jumping into any of the networkers, but if u choose well it will be very rewarding...gl.</Msg><Username>two_iron_man</Username><Timestamp>1344179012847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:03:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344181904006-6</Id><Topic><Title>greg and rhonda are ignorant white people</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344080594914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs are ignorant for voting for the dumb guy. Obama show us your grades, Romney got 2 degrees at Harvard at the same time. Romney was an A student in both Doctor of Law, and Masters in Business. Obama we have heard cut classes, got into Harvard via affirmative action. Obama got on Law Review based on affirmative action, and never published a Law Review article. Obama took the bar exam several times and failed. Eventually Obama and his wife both gave up their law licenses. Obama gave his up because he wouldn't prove his citizenship by producing his birth certificate. Obama gave up his license rather than comply with the Illinois Bar Assoc. demand to see his documents.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344181904006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 11:51:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344183469341-7</Id><Title>Obama won Indiana in 2008. Romney's going to win it now</Title><Msg>Four years ago, President Obama became the first Democrat since 1964 to win Indiana. He looks unlikely to repeat that feat. A new Rasmussen Reports telephone survey of Likely Voters in the state finds challenger Mitt Romney picking up 51% of the vote while the president earns just 35%. Three percent (3%) prefer some other candidate, and 11% are undecided.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344183469341</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344183651212-8</Id><Topic><Title>greg and rhonda are ignorant white people</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344080594914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He released them years ago, you know he ran for Senate and was a governor too. If your an A student your not shy about your grades.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344183651212</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:20:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184622541-9</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can you give us the place you found this. I know Yahoo blocks links but I want to verify that this is a genuine story. Also, I understand Obama got rotten grades and cut classes, this was while he was on the BONG.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344184622541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:37:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344184684140-10</Id><Topic><Title>greg and rhonda are ignorant white people</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344080594914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 07:43:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Junior. Still trying to use the race card. Come into the 21st century,buddy.That crap doesn't work anymore.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344184684140</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:38:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344185288000-11</Id><Title>Chambers needs to go and CSCO will thrive</Title><Msg>Chambers is an impediment to CSCO. His old line philosophy has seen better days. Let him take his hundreds of millions and ride off into the sunset. Surely there is some non-profit entity that will listen to his Bullshtt as he plunks down a load of money for the cause. Chambers is like a NFL coach that was good in his prime but the game has passed him by and he needs to move on and allow some younger talent to take CSCO into the future.</Msg><Username>optionwriter101</Username><Timestamp>1344185288000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 12:48:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344187736223-12</Id><Title>ANOTHER SHOOTING IN WISCONSIN,NRA B#^*%$# YAWN!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>GUN CONTROL NOW,STOP THE MADNESS</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344187736223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:28:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188277824-13</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He went to Harvard law and was brilliant (Law Review and all of that).</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344188277824</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:37:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344188948217-14</Id><Topic><Title>Adelson uncovered; Wall Strret Journal</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344118166910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The ties of Adelson to Bugsy Siegle and the Jewish Mafia have been talked about. Bugsy brought serious gambling to Las Vegas. This ties Romney to organized crime and the Jewish/Mormon Mafia.</Msg><Username>comsensea</Username><Timestamp>1344188948217</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 13:49:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344191204640-15</Id><Title>Lousy format</Title><Msg>Does anyone else find this format to be unfriendly to the user and difficult to read when compared to the old format? I find this site is now extremely slow when compared to past formats. I know it is not my computer since Scottrade is lightning fast. Best wishe to all and Good Luck to Yahoo in improving.</Msg><Username>kwhit98</Username><Timestamp>1344191204640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:26:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192205786-16</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: A big Fat LIAR</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344038533513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>About the possible truth of the underlying allegation, for one thing. Or about something (or a whole STRING of somethings) equally heinous showing up if the Romneybot ever actually released his returns. Or about the fact that the charges seem to be sticking. ... Etc. Double up on the Valium dosage. You'll have another shot at the White House in 2016. :D</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344192205786</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:43:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344192805750-17</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: A big Fat LIAR</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344038533513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf is correct that truth of the matter asserted is a complete defense to a claim of slander/libel. (At least here in the U.S. today, and for a very long time, though not at all other times and in all other countries. For example, the legal theory under the older, sovereign-based doctrine of "seditious libel" was that "the greater the truth, the greater the libel/sedition.")</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344192805750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 14:53:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344199311670-18</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: A big Fat LIAR</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344038533513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's only true in the alternate reality that is the GOP now, Reid never claimed fraud or tax evasion, he said he was told that Mitt hadn't paid any taxes for ten years, there are plenty of legal ways for the rich to avoid paying taxes, I have however said it is likely he committed tax fraud, it is the most logical reason he won't release his returns of course the GOP response is never to disprove an accusation, it's another way you know it's true</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344199311670</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:41:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344199847940-19</Id><Title>A Romney victory</Title><Msg>would surely end this investigation now wouldn't it? ZURICH (Reuters) - The Swiss government is bracing itself for protracted negotiations with the United States over undeclared funds stowed by U.S. citizens in Swiss offshore bank accounts, President Eveline Widmer-Schlumpf said. "Constant new demands" made by U.S. justice officials are the main stumbling block, said Widmer-Schlumpf, who is also Switzerland's finance minister, in an interview published in weekend editions of a number of Swiss regional newspapers. The two countries have for years been locked in a conflict over the fact that wealthy Americans are dodging taxes by hiding money in Swiss accounts. Washington is pressuring banks in Switzerland to divulge their names and financial details. "If Switzerland would simply agree to what the United States is asking, a global solution (for all Swiss banks concerned) would be by found tomorrow," Widmer-Schlumpf said without indicating how long it would take to reach such a deal. Eleven Swiss banks including Credit Suisse (CSGN.VX) and Julius Baer (BAER.VX) are under investigation in the United States for aiding U.S. citizens who are suspected of dodging their taxes. Credit Suisse said on Friday that the United States had submitted a fresh request for information on former clients of the bank, after an earlier attempt was blocked by a Swiss court.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344199847940</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 16:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344200684597-20</Id><Topic><Title>Adelson uncovered; Wall Strret Journal</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344118166910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Rhonda remember when you said Israel should murder every man women and child in the Gaza strip, all 1.5 million of them? Guess you felt like Hitler, confining them to the concentration camp of the Gaza strip isn't enough you think they need to be murdered. By the way all Obama said was taxpayers should not foot the bill for boondoggles in Las Vegas, you obviously feel my tax dollars should go to pay for people to go to Vegas, perhaps you should get a job</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344200684597</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:04:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344201015843-21</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the matter you old carcass, you don't know how to google ? Jesus you are totally useless. Just pull the trigger.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344201015843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344201684065-22</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I checked it out the story is an AP story, I'm shocked they are in Obama's back pocket. You make me and others laugh about Obama being smart, he sounds dumb off telepromter. Obama we have heard cut classes, got into Harvard via affirmative action. Obama got on Law Review based on affirmative action, and never published a Law Review article. Obama took the bar exam several times and failed. Eventually Obama and his wife both gave up their law licenses. Obama gave his up because he wouldn't prove his citizenship by producing his birth certificate. Obama gave up his license rather than comply with the Illinois Bar Assoc. demand to see his documents.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344201684065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:21:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344201792245-23</Id><Topic><Title>Adelson uncovered; Wall Strret Journal</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344118166910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-04 18:09:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Its Harry Reid that has Mob Ties.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344201792245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344202926078-24</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh my god he got bad grades and cut classes. Oh lord no ! This is worst than starting 2 wars on false pretenses, allowing WTC attacks, let New Orleans drown and never bother to catch Bin Laden. Oh god help us from a guy that cut classes. IDIOT C)NT</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344202926078</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 17:42:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344205080276-25</Id><Topic><Title>VERY QUIETLY OBAMA'S CITIZENSHIP CASE REACHES THE SUPREME COURT</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1344163369625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 06:42:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL- Rhonda once again proving she is dumber then a tea bagger, LOL Rhonda It was released on April fools day LOL guess the lame stream media is trying to cover it up (I am laughing so hard tears are comming from my eyes) 1) Google any part of it and the first searches displayed are snopes and fact checking both showing this is an outright fabrication, 2) Google it and you will see Obama passed his Bar exam the first time he took it (as did Romney) 3) Rush has been busy saying Obama and Michelle were both disbarred, this is of course completely false, both Obama and his wife asked to have their legal licenses put on inactive status since they were not going to practice law in Ilinois for at least the next four years, maintaining active status requires paying bar asssociation fees, malpractice insurance, being subject to court summons, etc Rhonda proving once again IQ tests should be required if you are allowed to vote, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344205080276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:18:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344206229045-26</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: A big Fat LIAR</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344038533513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-03 20:02:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL Reid and the DNC must be laughing their #$%$ off that Reince Priebus is keeping this issue on the front pages, LOL maybe Reince doesn't want Romney to get elected? LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344206229045</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:37:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344206813855-27</Id><Title>told you this wouldn't go away</Title><Msg>Fight Over Romney's Taxes Escalates the American public won't stand for hiding if you can prove in 10 seconds something is false, Obama was forced to release his B.C. when no one else in history had to do it, what are the chances the American Public isn't going to punish Mitt at the polls if he refuses to release tax records every president in recent history (EXCEPT NIXON) has including his FATHER, LOL let's keep this on the front pages GOPERS LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344206813855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:46:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344209723492-28</Id><Topic><Title>told you this wouldn't go away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344206813855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>JFK and RFK released none, Reagan..one, McCain..two . You keep talking about Romneys taxes while Americans worry about 8.3 UE and remember the" You didn't build that !!!!" gaffe. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344209723492</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 19:35:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344211559845-29</Id><Title>Harry Reid: a Big FAT embarrassment for the libTURDS</Title><Msg>Many Democraps are running from LIAR Harry Reid. Calling it outrageous. Reid is doing obumbles dirty work. I heard from a credible source Obama was still doing Cocaine. Prove he is NOT you stupid ignorant liberals. I think it clearly shows how IGNORANT your agrument is.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344211559845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:05:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344211741841-30</Id><Topic><Title>Harry Reid: a Big FAT embarrassment for the libTURDS</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344211559845</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:05:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sounding pretty desperate there skin flute player, LOL let's keep Romneys reaction on the front page, thanks for the help, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344211741841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:09:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344213267691-31</Id><Title>I heard Obama is doing Cocaine AGAIN.</Title><Msg>He admitted doing coke in college and a CREDIBLE source told me he might be doing coke again in the Whitehouse. Do you want a cokehead in the Whitehouse? He should have to prove he is not. Seems fair.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344213267691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344216339757-32</Id><Title>Romney starting to implode</Title><Msg>just to funny, if he doesn't release his tax returns he is finished, if he releases his tax returns he is finished, LOL - GOP should pick someone else now before they lose the white house and the house</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344216339757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:25:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344216751265-33</Id><Topic><Title>Romney starting to implode</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344216339757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:25:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging by your posts you are extremely worried that Romney will defeat Obama. LOL Your bashing reeks of panic. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344216751265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344216908631-34</Id><Title>The Big Coverup</Title><Msg>Who thinks Obama is hiding something from the public?</Msg><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1344216908631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:35:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217266467-35</Id><Topic><Title>The Big Coverup</Title><Username>sdmiller4747</Username><Timestamp>1344216908631</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:35:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He wasn't able to hide how incompetent he is.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344217266467</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:41:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217331057-36</Id><Topic><Title>told you this wouldn't go away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344206813855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The jobs report was excellent, considering the size of "The Bush Hole". 8.3% up from 8.2%, indicates that more people are looking for jobs, as hope for the USA job market returns. Obama does great work, so the right wing tries to spin it in another direction (WON"T WORK).</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344217331057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:42:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217556447-37</Id><Topic><Title>I heard Obama is doing Cocaine AGAIN.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344213267691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 20:34:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Get lost you fascist, white male, racist creep.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344217556447</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:45:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344217864871-38</Id><Topic><Title>told you this wouldn't go away</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344206813855</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 18:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your weak spin is laughable . 163k is terrible....course thats better than last month's 80k .LOL LOL .Guess you liked than 1.5 GDP too ,right kool-ade chugger??LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344217864871</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 21:51:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344224706000-39</Id><Title>Volume speaks for itself</Title><Msg>GOJO might worth toLook at for better roi IMO</Msg><Username>mystocks24</Username><Timestamp>1344224706000</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-05 23:45:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>