<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-08"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347077467520-1</Id><Title>WILL THE REPUKES EVER FIGURE OUT HOW A VHHAGINA WORKS ?</Title><Msg>Or do they still believe they were delivered by a stork ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347077467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:11:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347111373840-2</Id><Title>GOP= no global warming,,no social security or medicare,no evolution= is that YOU??</Title><Msg>These wackos are scary</Msg><Username>webber3240</Username><Timestamp>1347111373840</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 09:36:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347113351572-3</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE REPUKES EVER FIGURE OUT HOW A VHHAGINA WORKS ?</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347077467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>According to your boyfriend it does pretty much what your mouth does.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347113351572</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:09:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347114794829-4</Id><Title>UE rate drops to 8.1%........How is that Possible</Title><Msg>Fridays jobs report shows employment rose 96k in August. Not a bad number, it's better than losing, BUT it's still not enough to break even with all the new entrants into the job force. So there weren't enough new jobs to make up for the 150k or so jobs needed just to break even, ADD to that the 2 prior months were REVISED DOWN 41k. SO HOW does the rate fall to 8.1%?????? Because 300k PLUS americans have quit looking and are still UNEMPLOYED. Obumbles calls this a victory and all the pundits on the far left eat this up. These people are CLUELESS. O'Loser will tell you that he has 40 months of job growth........WAKE up folks, although he is NOT lying he is NOT telling you the whole truth. If you add 100 new workers per month( JOB GROWTH), but you lose 200 who stop looking or fell off the rolls then you have a broken recovery. There are FEWER American workers today than when Obama took office. Worker participation is at its LOWEST in 31 years. ANOTHER record by the " ONE ". Obumbles is telling you 10% of the truth and leaving the rest out. The far left koolaid chhuggers continue to eat it up and follow their Messiah in spite of ruining the economy. These are not talking points, they are ALL FACTS. Refute them please!!!!!</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347114794829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347115329499-5</Id><Title>And we thought we had nuts in Texas</Title><Msg>The Worst Judge in America? by ThinkProgress September 7, 2012 9:00 pm 2715166119get causes updates Written by Ian Millhiser Last summer, a drunk Arizona police officer named Robb Gary Evans drove himself to a bar, flashed his badge to avoid paying cover at the door, and then walked up behind a woman, put his hand up her skirt, and ran his fingers over her genitals. A jury convicted him of sexual abuse, a felony with a maximum sentence of 2 and a half years in prison, and Evans was fired from the police force after an internal investigation. Nevertheless, Arizona trial Judge Jacqueline Hatch, who was appointed to the bench by Gov. Jan Brewer (R-AZ), decided that Evans’ actions did not warrant jail time — sentencing him probation and 100 hours of community service. Evans also will not have to register as a sex offender. Yet, while Judge Hatch apparently did not view the disgraced former cop’s actions as particularly serious, she had some very harsh words for the woman he assaulted: Bad things can happen in bars, Hatch told the victim, adding that other people might be more intoxicated than she was. “If you wouldn’t have been there that night, none of this would have happened to you,” Hatch said. Hatch told the victim and the defendant that no one would be happy with the sentence she gave, but that finding an appropriate sentence was her duty. “I hope you look at what you’ve been through and try to take something positive out of it,” Hatch said to the victim in court. “You learned a lesson about friendship and you learned a lesson about vulnerability.” Hatch said that the victim was not to blame in the case, but that all women must be vigilant against becoming victims. “When you blame others, you give up your power to change,” Hatch said that her mother used to say. The victim, who has not been identified by the press, called for Judge Hatch to apologize for her offensive comments, adding that if she had not been at the bar to be assaulted by Evans, “it probably would have happened to someone else.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1347115329499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:42:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347115808046-6</Id><Topic><Title>UE rate drops to 8.1%........How is that Possible</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347114794829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there are more private sector jobs now then when Obama took office (even though Bush handed him an economy losing 800,000 a month, surprise the jobs picture didn't turn around for almost 9 months, about how long it took for Obama's policies to kick in) Now it is true there are fewer jobs overall but that's because there have been so many government job losses, So if I understand you right, you are angry that Obama has shrunk the size of the Government?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347115808046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:50:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347116358647-7</Id><Title>Wonder why Rhonda isn't posting</Title><Msg>the latest Rasmussen poll showing Obama leading 46 to 44?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347116358647</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347116575330-8</Id><Title>Explaining the myth of Romney</Title><Msg>Barney Frank: 'Myth Romney' Posted: 07 Sep 2012 07:00 PM PDT I am so going to miss Barney Frank in the House. He is just a fount of quips and great soundbytes and most importantly, an unapologetic liberal advocating for equality. Frank got to speak in the early hours of Thursday's DNC Convention, so unfortunately, I don't think enough people got to hear this great man of the people. Here he is, speaking as a resident of Massachusetts, about how he felt Mitt Romney handled that executive position of governing the state. Now, just recently, Mitt Romney seems to have discovered the middle class. He talks about helping families, even though he made his fortune laying off workers. But that's nothing new for our opponent. He said the same thing when he was running for governor of Massachusetts. So let me tell you about two Romneys: the real Mitt Romney and the myth of Romney. The myth of Romney is that his financial experience means he knows how to create jobs. As governor of Massachusetts, the real Mitt Romney's record on job creation was terrible. During his term, net job growth was less than one percent, about one-fifth the national average, 47th in the country. The myth of Romney is that he never raised our taxes. In fact, the real Mitt Romney called his tax hikes "fees." And in his first year alone, he raised fees more than any other governor in office. Some of those fees? Mitt created a $10 fee for a "certificate of blindness." He increased the cremation inspection fee from $50 to $75. Maybe he didn't call them taxes, but they felt like taxes. The myth of Romney is that he worked hard to bring employment opportunities to Massachusetts. The real Mitt Romney did no such thing. During his time in the governor's office, manufacturing jobs were leaving our state at twice the national rate. Today, the real Mitt Romney has chosen for his vice president one of the most conservative elected officials in Washington. The real Mitt Romney would lower taxes for millionaires and billionaires—which would blow a hole in the deficit. In fact, the Romney-Ryan budget would have made Mitt's total tax rate less than one percent. And that's just the beginning. The Romney-Ryan budget turns Medicare into a voucher program—and then bankrupts it by 2016. It would slash Pell Grants and Head Start. It would pull teachers out of classrooms and cops off the street. And even after all that, the only way Romney and Ryan could pay for their millionaire tax cuts would be to stick the middle class with the bill. That's the real Mitt Romney. The Mitt Romney who declared himself "severely conservative." The Mitt Romney who is no friend of average Americans. And that's a Mitt Romney who has no place as our president. That's why this November we have to re-elect President Barack Obama!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1347116575330</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117479333-9</Id><Topic><Title>And we thought we had nuts in Texas</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1347115329499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:42:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Women that go out without an adult male relative and that aren't wearing their burquas are just asking to be raped. Men can't be held responsible for their natural instincts." Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347117479333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347117510157-10</Id><Title>despair and hard times for 368,000 more Americans Obama won't count as UE</Title><Msg>The administration has a low opinion of American folk. They say UE went down, yet the truth is 368,000 left being counted as UE and only 45,000 net people were hired since last months numbers were as always revised downward. Hey Obama your only interested in lying and making up the numbers to keep your shiny plane. I and most other of the good folks know the despair of not having money and worrying about your family's future. At this months rate that is another 3 million annual people out of the labor force. If they have no jobs they can't pay taxes, the deficit goes up</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347117510157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:18:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117546087-11</Id><Topic><Title>UE rate drops to 8.1%........How is that Possible</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347114794829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Things are going to get worse. The wheels are falling off in his administration. Obama and the Dems will resort to using race card, war on women, and class warfare tactics to distract, distort, and demonize the opposition: If you vote Romney/Ryan you are a bigoted racist, a misogynist, and a homophobe. Voters will be turned off and vote against Obama. His voter base will stay at home. Obama will lose and there will be a week of rioting in major urban centers across the US.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1347117546087</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:19:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117626156-12</Id><Topic><Title>despair and hard times for 368,000 more Americans Obama won't count as UE</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347117510157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they should just borrow money from their parents and start a business</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347117626156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:20:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347117993448-13</Id><Topic><Title>And we thought we had nuts in Texas</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1347115329499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:42:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another week end of your nonsense,Deepharbordumdum? Why aren't you out spending some of your millions??LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347117993448</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347117994625-14</Id><Title>My Tax Cut Secret for Working Americans = Fired Workers Will Have $0 Income and Pay $0 Taxes</Title><Msg>And you can take my tax cut secret to the bank. Hahahahahahaaaaaaaaaaa I laugh all the way to my Cayman and Swiss banks.</Msg><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347117994625</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:26:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347118222298-15</Id><Topic><Title>Pentagon escalates case that former Navy SEAL broke secrecy pledge</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347054487801</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:48:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Israeli commandos were to infiltrate Iran and destroy the nuke sites and Obama leaked the location Israel was using as the staging base for the OP in one on the "stans". This is one of the reasons Obama is distrusted in Israel. He blew their best chance at survival against radical Iran's desire to nuke Israel.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347118222298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:30:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347118828355-16</Id><Title>Ann Romney</Title><Msg>said things were so tight when she and Mitt were in college they had to use a used Mercedes Benz that's why she can relate to the average josephine</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347118828355</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:40:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347119387888-17</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that supposed to be some sort of insult? Mitt the Twit was outspoken in favor of the Vietnam War, but Mitt the Twit scurried away to France like a Republican hypocrit when his chance came to serve in the Vietnam War.</Msg><Username>amazing_aces_wild</Username><Timestamp>1347119387888</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:49:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347119471565-18</Id><Title>palin</Title><Msg>LOL commenting on Kerry mentioning her at the convention. "I think he diminished himself by even mentioning my name," said the 2008 Republican vice presidential candidate appearing on Fox Business Network shortly after Kerry's remarks. "How does he even know my name? I mean, aren't these guys supposed to be these big wig elites who don't waste their time on little people like me-me, representing the average American." Really Sarah, how does he even know your name? Could it be because you were on the ticket for V.P. of the U.S.? LOL you can't make up how stupid this woman is.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119471565</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:51:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347119706053-19</Id><Title>Palin had terrorist on the payroll</Title><Msg>In fact, Palin had longtime ties to the right-wing, anti-government fringes of Alaska politics. Despite her duplicities to the contrary, Palin's husband, Todd, had on three separate occasions registered as a member of the Alaska Independence Party, which called, at the time, for the secession of Alaska from the Union. Palin also produced a glowing video on behalf of the AIP welcoming them to Fairbanks for their statewide convention earlier that year. In 2009, for my book, The Lies of Sarah Palin: The Untold Story Behind her Relentless Quest for Power, I interviewed Mark Chryson, chairman of the AIP from 1995 to 2002, who talked about the various ways his movement supported Palin during her tenure as mayor of Wasilla (he claims Palin attended the AIP convention in 1994.) One former militia member I interviewed in Talkeetna with direct links to Cox said that the Palins -- "especially Todd" -- were "sympathetic to our cause." That Palin and her minions would associate with Cox -- and seek out his counsel for political "strategy" at a time when she was being considered as a potential vice-presidential nominee -- is further reflection not only of her fringe political views but also of her warped political judgment.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119706053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120717610-20</Id><Topic><Title>REPUKES MEDICARE PLAN...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347074694442</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:24:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347120717610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120739735-21</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE REPUKES EVER FIGURE OUT HOW A VHHAGINA WORKS ?</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347077467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347120739735</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:12:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347120764304-22</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LEAKS 'CLASSIFIED' INFORMATION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347074333603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hello !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347120764304</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347120859809-23</Id><Title>Rasmussen has Obama ahead by 2 a 5 point swing did you see that Rhonda LOL</Title><Msg>The three national tracking polls that were published on Friday all moved toward President Obama, probably reflecting momentum from the Democratic convention. In the Gallup national tracking poll, Mr. Obama moved into a three-point lead over Mitt Romney, up from one point on Thursday. What’s a bit more worrisome for Mr. Romney is that Gallup’s reporting of the head-to-head results in its poll occurs over a lengthy seven-day window, meaning that only a minority of the interviews in the poll were conducted after the major speeches at the Democratic convention. In fact, most of the interviews in the poll were conducted just after the Republican convention in Tampa, Fla., a period in which Mr. Romney should have been enjoying a convention bounce of his own. Gallup’s approval ratings, however, are published over a three-day window, meaning that they will be quicker to respond to shifts in opinion. Mr. Obama’s approval ratings shot up to 52 percent in the version of poll published on Friday, while his disapproval ratings declined to 43 percent. The FiveThirtyEight forecast model does not use approval ratings directly, but this is a sign that there could be more good news for Mr. Obama in the head-to-head portion of the poll in the days ahead.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347120859809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121219159-24</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LEAKS 'CLASSIFIED' INFORMATION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347074333603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I don't know where bin Laden is. I have no idea and really don't care. It's not that important. It's not our priority." - G.W. Bush, 3/13/02 "I am truly not that concerned about him." - G.W. Bush, repsonding to a question about bin Laden's whereabouts, 3/13/02 (The New American, 4/8/02)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347121219159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:20:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347121302679-25</Id><Title>GOP wreck hard to reverse; the direction is correct, but more has to be done; Bernanke to the rescue</Title><Msg>New jobs need to be created, We are no longer losing jobs (800, 000 a month due to GOP policies), but we need to create jobs at about 300, 000 a month. It looks like the FED will help, since we are only creating jobs at about 100, 000 a month.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1347121302679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:21:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121326434-26</Id><Topic><Title>despair and hard times for 368,000 more Americans Obama won't count as UE</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347117510157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wham bang, thank yoiu mam !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347121326434</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121789531-27</Id><Topic><Title>despair and hard times for 368,000 more Americans Obama won't count as UE</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347117510157</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:18:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ann knows the despair of not having money and worrying about her family's future, when she and Mitt were in college they had to sell some of their stock portfolio to pay for school. If they hadn't had that stock they might have been forced to borrow money from either her rich parents or his rich parents. Talk about operating without a safety net.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347121789531</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:29:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347121810692-28</Id><Title>MITT ORDERING NEW SHIRTS FOR HIS SUPPORTERS...</Title><Msg>BROWN SHIRTS !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347121810692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347121922990-29</Id><Topic><Title>GOP wreck hard to reverse; the direction is correct, but more has to be done; Bernanke to the rescue</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1347121302679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(New jobs need to be created, We are no longer losing jobs) That is because the House no longer has Nasty Pelosi throwing money away, we now have adults controlling the spending. Private job creation is happening in Republican controlled states. That part really upsets you liberal pecker-woods!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347121922990</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:32:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122002640-30</Id><Topic><Title>GOP wreck hard to reverse; the direction is correct, but more has to be done; Bernanke to the rescue</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1347121302679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we need to rely on the fed for now but after Obama is reelected he will be able to get his jobs bill passed. Now the GOP wants the country to fail but after the election they will be ready to compromise.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347122002640</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:33:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347122350518-31</Id><Topic><Title>Palin had terrorist on the payroll</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119706053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Terrorist??? How about Bill Ayers?? Wasn't he Obama's good buddy?? You really are dumb.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347122350518</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123092960-32</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And when were you there,amazing? I was there 1966-67. So I walked the walk,buddy. Clinton,Cheney,Biden are just a few of the famous who hid out.But the worst of all was John Kerry. A backstabbing so.b.who used the war to further his career. And slandered some true heroes who never made it back. You cant get any lower than John Kerry!!</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347123092960</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:51:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123311799-33</Id><Topic><Title>Palin had terrorist on the payroll</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119706053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior, how many times have you brought up Bush's drunk driving from 35 years ago?Oooooooopsie!!!!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347123311799</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347123648868-34</Id><Topic><Title>Palin had terrorist on the payroll</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119706053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonk, Junior is really good at sticking his foot in his mouth...no matter which id he uses .LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347123648868</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124408771-35</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(John Kerry. A backstabbing so.b.who used the war to further his career. And slandered some true heroes who never made it back. You cant get any lower than John Kerry!!) When he came on the other night, I turned the breaker switch off and told my family they would get much more information from the dark than they would from a traitor! Kerry, Fonda help the enemy, John Kerry, Bill Clinton, Obama, Kennedy and Edwards are all roll models for a sick bunch of self centered, greedy power hunger Pecker-woods! These people care nothing about you your family, you are just a means to their greed! Don't be stupid, none have anything to give you, unless it is taken from you then they want their cut. No different than that drug dealer down the street!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347124408771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:13:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124582999-36</Id><Topic><Title>Palin had terrorist on the payroll</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347119706053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 11:55:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More futile distraction, distortion, and demagoguery.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1347124582999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347124863777-37</Id><Topic><Title>GOP wreck hard to reverse; the direction is correct, but more has to be done; Bernanke to the rescue</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1347121302679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:21:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's called creative destruction. Obama loss will mean a week or two or riots.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1347124863777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:21:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347125211335-38</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LEAKS 'CLASSIFIED' INFORMATION</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347074333603</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 23:18:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Obama Administration has ties to the Muslin Brotherhood with an anti-israeli agenda.</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1347125211335</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:26:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347125496336-39</Id><Topic><Title>Intel CUTS Q3 revenue guidance</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347053857038</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 17:37:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>INTC is getting caught in the PC destruction. They didn't approach the wireless and tablet market and now they are getting hit. Same for DELL and HPQ. There is a SHIFT on the way (not a slow down). INTC loses in my view is someone else's gain. If BRCM QCOM ARMH and SKWS put out warnings, THEN you'll have reason to worry.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347125496336</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 13:31:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347127315599-40</Id><Title>SURF SIGNED UP AS "DONOR ORGAN" ACCORDING TO HIS</Title><Msg>facebook page. His specicially says at death his body will be used to make multiple new awholes for people who need a new one. All because dems have worn out their other ones whenever Obama comes around and has them grab their ankles. Of course, quincymagoo, dumb.ivan and jasonbaby have worn out surf's and each others.</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1347127315599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:01:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127436787-41</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Agree completely, Capt. The sight of Kerry makes me want to vomit. And yet there are #$%$ on this board who defend that piece of garbage.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347127436787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127476435-42</Id><Topic><Title>SURF SIGNED UP AS "DONOR ORGAN" ACCORDING TO HIS</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1347127315599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:01:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ahhh, disappointing. Work on your succinctness</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347127476435</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:04:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127672257-43</Id><Topic><Title>SURF SIGNED UP AS "DONOR ORGAN" ACCORDING TO HIS</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1347127315599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:01:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>whatever dood. Hey just remember to use condoms the next time you guys "get together" in the limo, people don't want their new awhole all torn up and diseased. thanks!</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1347127672257</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127816731-44</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ORDERING NEW SHIRTS FOR HIS SUPPORTERS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347121810692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hear he got a good deal on them.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347127816731</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:10:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347127819046-45</Id><Topic><Title>SURF SIGNED UP AS "DONOR ORGAN" ACCORDING TO HIS</Title><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1347127315599</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:01:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There are typos and then there is wrong. It is DUDE</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347127819046</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:10:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128004540-46</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, how dare Kerry save the lives of his fellow fighters by trying to shut down the war. Bad boy Kerry, bad boy.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347128004540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:13:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347128099006-47</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE REPUKES EVER FIGURE OUT HOW A VHHAGINA WORKS ?</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347077467520</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 00:11:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ReCONs can't help it - most of them don't have empirical evidence to ground their theories. (Autrement dit: They ain't had poosie since poosie had them.)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347128099006</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 14:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347131979169-48</Id><Title>bounce</Title><Msg>rhonda how come you're not out posting the latest polls?? Mitt Romney got what you call a dead-cat bounce coming out of the 2012 Republican Convention in Tampa Bay. According to the folks at Gallup, Barack Obama has done a whole lot better. His job approval number now stands at 52 percent, a nine-point jump since late August. Nothing in the news cycle — other than the convention — could account for an improvement that significant. The same is true of the head-to-head contest with Romney, where Obama has transformed a two-point deficit into a four-point advantage.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347131979169</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347132321273-49</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What continues to confound me is how many people who were staunchly against the Vietnam War still have not confronted the brutal reality of what our leaving that conflict wrought. The death camps, the millions of refugees who barely made it out alive, the horrors perpetrated on the people by Ho Chi Minh once he was victorious...</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347132321273</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:25:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347133333103-50</Id><Title>I see the pennis state boys from gay valley ( I mean happy vally) blew another one today. Coaches are blaming the tight ends for not hokding on to the balls properly. The gay coach sandusky must have recruited the quaterback, name magroin, and the kicker named Ficken.</Title><Msg>Careful Michigan, the nitwitny lions will try to blow you out of the stadium. GO WOLVERINES!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133333103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133753674-51</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup: Obama Approval Jumps After DNC</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347133075930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your point, Pecker-wood? Most con-men are likable, lest they wouldn't be able to con anyone!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347133753674</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133812271-52</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ORDERING NEW SHIRTS FOR HIS SUPPORTERS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347121810692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 12:30:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Actually, he ordered the brown shirts (yellow in the front) to give to the obama folks so their shirts match their underware.</Msg><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133812271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:50:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347133883245-53</Id><Topic><Title>I see the pennis state boys from gay valley ( I mean happy vally) blew another one today. Coaches are blaming the tight ends for not hokding on to the balls properly. The gay coach sandusky must have recruited the quaterback, name magroin, and the kicker named Ficken.</Title><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133333103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The kids on that team have absolutely nothing to do with what pervert Sandusky did. Use your vitriol on Sandusky. He deserves it. The football team doesn't.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347133883245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347134306160-54</Id><Topic><Title>Gallup: Obama Approval Jumps After DNC</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347133075930</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:37:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney getting ready to spend the millions in campaign money he has on ads. Lets see what the polls say in a couple of weeks.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347134306160</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:58:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347134424040-55</Id><Topic><Title>I see the pennis state boys from gay valley ( I mean happy vally) blew another one today. Coaches are blaming the tight ends for not hokding on to the balls properly. The gay coach sandusky must have recruited the quaterback, name magroin, and the kicker named Ficken.</Title><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133333103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't just Sandusky. Paterno knew, the AD knew, the whole community knew. The smart players have already transferred out in protest. The remaining players are condoning the actions by staying. They should all leave if they actually don't condone what happened. Hell, Illinois and Indiana will take them.</Msg><Username>kmhapy</Username><Timestamp>1347134424040</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:00:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347135126766-56</Id><Topic><Title>I see the pennis state boys from gay valley ( I mean happy vally) blew another one today. Coaches are blaming the tight ends for not hokding on to the balls properly. The gay coach sandusky must have recruited the quaterback, name magroin, and the kicker named Ficken.</Title><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133333103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole community didn't know .And the players on this team certainly didn't. Did the schools that took those "smart"players condone what happened by taking those players? Some off the things Sandusky did happened before these players were even born. You got some pretty high standards, pal. Must be tough for you to live by them.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347135126766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:12:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347135733084-57</Id><Topic><Title>I see the pennis state boys from gay valley ( I mean happy vally) blew another one today. Coaches are blaming the tight ends for not hokding on to the balls properly. The gay coach sandusky must have recruited the quaterback, name magroin, and the kicker named Ficken.</Title><Username>soletraine</Username><Timestamp>1347133333103</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 15:42:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Player transfers had little to do with protesting Sandusky. Sanctions imposed on Penn State means this team will be second rate for years. These players want to play in bowl games and increase chances for the NFL.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347135733084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:22:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347136358851-58</Id><Topic><Title>IS ROMNEY THE BEST THE REPUBS HAVE? I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO CRY</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1346447081968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you still want to kill 1.5 million women and children Rhonda? How does that make you any different then Hitler?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347136358851</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347136883610-59</Id><Topic><Title>During the Vietnam War, I Toured France and Had to Fight for Good Seats at Cafes</Title><Username>roboromney_version_2012</Username><Timestamp>1347065914420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-09-07 20:58:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>over 2 million people died in vietnam before the brave people, Kerry, Fonda etc had the courage to stand up and demand an end to the war. I understand why those that fought in the war are so upset at Kerry and Fonda. They made America understand that our fighting in Vietnam was not only useless but it was immoral. The only true heroes were the ones like Kerry who came home and tried to stop the war and the men who had the moral courage to go to Canada instead of becoming murderers.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347136883610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:41:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347137026360-60</Id><Title>hey Rhonda have you seen the polls? LOL</Title><Msg>President Obama’s post-convention “bounce” continued to grow Saturday, as new polls showed him widening a lead over Republican nominee Mitt Romney. Obama’s lead over Romney among registered voters grew to 49%-45% in Gallup’s tracking poll. The 49% for Obama was his highest point in the survey since late April. It represented an increase of 1 point since Friday and a 5-point swing from Romney’s 47%-46% lead in the Gallup survey just before the Republican convention began. The poll combines small samples taken each night to present a seven-day average. Since three of the nights of the survey period preceded the Democratic convention, Obama’s lead in the survey is likely to grow further. Gallup’s measure of job approval also continued to improve for Obama, with 52% of adults surveyed saying they approved of his performance in office, compared with 42% disapproving. That survey uses a three-day average.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347137026360</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347137273972-61</Id><Title>Obama's lead will continue to grow</Title><Msg>As it becomes clear to the voters that Mitt Romney wants to give big tax cuts to the rich, big tax increases to the middle class and wants to throw the elderly out of nursing homes if they don't have $100,000 a year to pay his corporate friends. KISSIMMEE, Fla. -- A political group supporting the re-election of President Barack Obama is airing a new ad that criticizes challenger Mitt Romney for advocating tax policies that would increase the tax burden on middle-income families. The ad by Priorities USA Action, a so-called super political action committee, uses an analysis by the independent Tax Policy Center and declares that Romney's plan would raise taxes on an average family by up to $2,000 while giving tax breaks of $250,000 to multimillionaires. The ad is airing in Colorado, Florida, Iowa, Ohio, Virginia and Wisconsin.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347137273972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:47:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347137441365-62</Id><Title>Mitt admits he is not a Christian</Title><Msg>Obama increased his lead over Romney in certain favorable characteristics. Asked who was more "eloquent," 50 percent of the 1,720 registered voters questioned in the poll favored Obama, compared to 25 percent for Romney. Asked about being "smart enough for the job," 46 percent sided with Obama compared to 37 percent for Romney. In fact, Obama led Romney in a dozen such favorable characteristics, such as "represents America" or "has the right values." The only such category in which Romney had an advantage was being "a man of faith," as 44 percent picked Romney, who is Mormon, compared to 31 percent for Obama, who is Christian.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347137441365</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 16:50:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347138069999-63</Id><Title>WAR</Title><Msg>Women Against Romney- check it out on Facebook!! “House Republicans have voted repeatedly for legislation that would be harmful to women’s health and women’s rights,” said Rep. Waxman. “I have worked for decades to promote equality for women, but the bipartisan support for women’s programs that used to exist in Congress has been shattered by tea party extremism. The Republican-controlled House has become the most anti-women House in modern history.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347138069999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:01:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347138246370-64</Id><Title>GOP war on Woman</Title><Msg>actually means the number of abortions will go up, if you are against abortion you should vote Obama In February 2012 the state of Texas decided to cut off reproductive and preventative health services to 130,000 low-income women. The staggering move caps what has been an escalating war on women’s health in state legislatures and in the U.S. Capitol since Tea Party-backed Republican majorities took control of the U.S. House and the majority of statehouses and took a determined minority in the U.S. Senate. While anti-woman rhetoric has been a mainstay of right-wing politics for decades, in the past two years that rhetoric has been turned into a record number of laws – and hurt a record number of women. Texas’s move is extreme, but it’s not unusual. In fact, when it comes to women’s health, Republicans in the U.S. Congress and in the race for the presidency are trying to remake America in Texas’s image. In refusing funding for its women’s health programs, Texas has jeopardized women’s health – putting the burden especially on low-income women – and increased the risk of unwanted pregnancies, the main reason for abortions. Eliminating the entire federal family- planning program – a step supported by every Republican in the U.S. House and both major GOP presidential contenders – would do the same on a national scale, all while costing taxpayers billions of dollars in increased health–care expenses resulting from the lack of preventative care. One year ago, People For the American Way issued a report on the unprecedented barrage of antichoice bills being unleashed by newly empowered state legislatures. In the year since, perhaps sensing that their window of opportunity might be drawing to a close, far-right national and state lawmakers, in coordination with Religious Right activists, have expanded their attacks. They are targeting not just abortion rights, but also access to birth control and preventative care, as well as contemporary views of women’s roles in the workplace, the family and the halls of power. What follows are dispatches from the varied fronts in the growing War on Women. The Battle Against Birth Control Texas’s decision to take away preventative health care from 130,000 women overnight is the product of a decades-long struggle against women’s health care that advanced dramatically with the Right’s political victories in 2010. It is also a case study of what the Tea Party’s anti-woman rhetoric looks like when it becomes law and is applied to millions of people. Texas has actually done what right-wing activists and politicians around the country say they want to do – and it’s not pretty. The Texas legislature started chipping away at women’s health care when it voted to cut family planning funding by two-thirds in October 2011. The state’s Republican leaders then became locked in a battle with Washington over funding for Planned Parenthood. Texas’s Women’s Health Program is largely financed by $35 million in federal funds, which the federal government will not let the state withhold from qualified providers – including Planned Parenthood. In response, Texas’s legislature and Gov. Rick Perry have decided to refuse those federal funds, thus leaving tens of thousands of Texas women on the line.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347138246370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:04:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347139970344-65</Id><Title>just like Ann Romney Gina Rinehart</Title><Msg>had a grandfather that was a coal miner! The world's richest woman, Australian mining tycoon Gina Rinehart, drew international scorn recently after saying that people who are jealous of the wealthy should drink less and work harder. And now she's back with some more helpful advice. Speaking at the Sydney Mining Club, Rinehart said her country's mining industry couldn't compete with nations that are willing to pay workers less than $2 a day for their sweat and labor. The implicit suggestion: Employers should be free to pay workers whatever they please. This echoes Rinehart's earlier to-do list, in which she urged Aussie lawmakers to cut the minimum wage so that, well, she wouldn't have to spend so much money on things like workers' salaries and benefits. "The evidence is inarguable that Australia is becoming too expensive and too uncompetitive to do export-oriented business," Rinehart said at the Sydney Mining Club. "Africans want to work, and its workers are willing to work for less than $2 per day. Such statistics make me worry for this country's future."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347139970344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:32:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347141080775-66</Id><Topic><Title>just like Ann Romney Gina Rinehart</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347139970344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DumdumIvan who used to be multimillionaire Deepharbor is spending another weekend all alone typing #$%$ on the net.Wonder why he's not in the British Virgin Islands or Mach Picchu today.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL Not even at one of the golf courses he owns. LOLOLOLOLOL What a pathetic loser this guy is!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347141080775</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:51:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347141607556-67</Id><Topic><Title>just like Ann Romney Gina Rinehart</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347139970344</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 17:32:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another one of Magoo's ids. He should be pitied. Obviously lonesome.Understandable since he is about as obnoxious as you can get.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347141607556</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347142021316-68</Id><Title>headed out to dinner at the club</Title><Msg>have to use up some more of our minimum, that's the problem with belonging to so many clubs you constantly have to go out to dinner, see you folks later, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347142021316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347144267848-69</Id><Topic><Title>headed out to dinner at the club</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347142021316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo heading down to the Salvation Army for din-din.LOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347144267848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 18:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347145215064-70</Id><Title>You must see the film "2016 Obama's America</Title><Msg>I thought I had read all about Obama, but this movie was filmed and researched all over the world, and they interviewed people that I never read about before. We endorse this as the most researched piece on Obama ever assembled. Don't think you know Obama until you hear him on the assembled clips, his friends, his mentors, his writings, his own family. We still don't really know this man Like Brokaw and Charlie Rose have said, but this movie will help close the circle. Its a must see in order to really be informed.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347145215064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347148125256-71</Id><Topic><Title>You must see the film "2016 Obama's America</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347145215064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the gay turd who ripped off my id ("juniorSclassmate") doesn't know shyt! 2016 IS a GREAT movie exposing Obama as the worthless mongrel that he is and a HUGE socialist--mentored and schooled in socialism for an early age!! The card-carrying commie Frank Marshall Davis and Bill Ayers the anarchist indoctriated him well! He is a threat to our nation and needs to be removed in the election...get out and VOTE him out people! In four more years he'll finish off our country if he remains as POTUS! Great post Rhonda!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1347148125256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:48:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347148333994-72</Id><Topic><Title>You must see the film "2016 Obama's America</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347145215064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The way it was put together, anyone watching and still voting for Obama has to be a simple minded Pecker-wood. No one in their right mind would support this unknown! Maybe someone like Dumb-Ivan with a morbid mind, one that celebrates the genocide of people we pledged to help.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347148333994</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347151106965-73</Id><Topic><Title>UE rate drops to 8.1%........How is that Possible</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347114794829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 10:33:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles RAMPED up the government employees his first 2 years and the bloated system couldn't take it. He is finally just getting rid of them. BOTTOM line, there are FEWER Americans working today than when your Messiah took office, FACT. A worker is a worker no matter what sector they are in. Why don't you respond to the NEW RECORD that Obumbles holds, LOWEST worker participation rate in 31YEARS. How's that for hope and change. Now go ahead and try to spin that MISERY.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347151106965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:38:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347151413744-74</Id><Title>"2016 obama's America": A "documentary" with over 100 credited Actors!</Title><Msg>A documentary with actors? Based on a book entitled "The Roots of Obama's Rage". Rage? Seriously, is rage a word you'd use to describe Obama? Rush yes. Obama no. So Obama is an Anti Colonialist? So were Washington, Jefferson, Madison, Franklin et al. In fact this country was founded by Anti Colonialist.</Msg><Username>t_bag_d_bags</Username><Timestamp>1347151413744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 20:43:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156080371-75</Id><Topic><Title>You must see the film "2016 Obama's America</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347145215064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 19:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wish we could get some billionaire like Trump, Adelman , Wynn to pay for free tickets and get a few million more people to see the movie 2016 Obama's America. Professional actors? they are all libs. Libs your next to lose your job if this Commie gets re elected. And then when your laid off they won't count you either. There are 23 million unemployed Americans, and Obama lets in millions of Mexicans to take your jobs, so he can have voters for the Commie Democrat party.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347156080371</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347156583400-76</Id><Title>Romney winning 11 swing states poll</Title><Msg>In the 11 swing states, Mitt Romney now attracts 46% of the vote, while President Obama earns 45%. Four percent (4%) prefer some other candidate, and five percent (5%) are undecided. In 2008, Obama won these states by a combined margin of 53% to 46%, virtually identical to his national margin. Due to the Democratic leanings of these states, a Romney lead in the 11 swing states would almost certainly result in victory for the GOP. However, Obama is likely to enjoy a bounce from his convention this week, and the results could shift significantly.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347156583400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156756338-77</Id><Topic><Title>Romney winning 11 swing states poll</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347156583400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda very entertaining for you to post last weeks Rasmussen poll, LOL do you still want to murder 1.5 million people, simple question? a yes or no will do</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347156756338</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347156831748-78</Id><Topic><Title>Romney winning 11 swing states poll</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347156583400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the polls, despite every effort by main stream media will continue to shift to Romney....Obimbo has shot his wad, he's got nothing left to show....its over. No jobs, no jobs, no jobs....if this shoe was on the other foot right now, the useless, drooling main stream media would be trumpeting the failure of this administration. They'd be SCREAMING ABOUT THE 350,000 UNEMPLOYED WHO dropped out of the unemployment pool, they'd be yelling about the 96,000 new jobs....pathetic!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347156831748</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:13:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347158673455-79</Id><Topic><Title>Romney winning 11 swing states poll</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347156583400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:09:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That 96k job creation will likely be revised down 45k like every report in the last year. See when liars in BLS are Democrats the margin of error only happens in Obama's favor for the Obama lapdog media to Trumpet, the correction a month later is never told to the people. See the media is a propaganda machine for the Democrap party. Same with the 368k that lost their jobs and can't find one. They no longer count like the few net 41k new hires. But lets do the math and get it correct 368k minus 41k is still a monthly loss of 327k worker from those working and being counted. And Obama can't explain that as being GW Bush's fault.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1347158673455</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-08 22:44:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>