<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-14"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344916890284-1</Id><Topic><Title>Romney paid just 13% in taxes last year</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1344905101468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>First off 50 percent of you Lib freeloaders pay only SS taxes that pay for your retirement benefits. You freeloaders don't pay FED income taxes. Romney paid in millions more last year than half the country and he is retired. Romney pays Cap Gains income tax on his stocks etc. Just like us Cisco shareholders. If Romney is dishonest for getting dividends on his equities then so are you. Romney paid the same amount as any other taxpayer on his Cap Gains. Your just jealous, and that is a bad trait. If you were capable of getting a Doctors of Law degree and a Masters in Busness from Harvard simultaneously like Romney did and few are smart enough to do that then maybe you could head a corporation for 20 years and save 200 million like Romney. But I am sure Romney wouldn't waste his time being envious and Biatching about it on the Cisco board.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344916890284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344917129382-2</Id><Topic><Title>Just wondering how many jobs could have</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344907190458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 21:19:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the silly one, repeating every Liberal Tree Hugging Pecker-woods lies -- repeating it 1000 times it is still a lie. Drink that cool aid and don't take time to think for yourself. More gas less price and more taxes and the paper pushers can figure like crazy and they are not going to change that.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344917129382</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:05:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344917556185-3</Id><Topic><Title>Just wondering how many jobs could have</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344907190458</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 21:19:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Specifically, Exxon holds that it paid “total taxes and duties to the US” of $9.8 billion, but its SEC filings show that it paid just $1.3 billion in federal income tax, Note this is for the last tax year. Also, since Exxon pays lots of other vendors, employees, and station operator, the taxes they pay and the taxes on the dividends paid by Exxon shareholder are probably billions more. I am sure Exxon will be paying President Romney a lot for Oil leases when we finally like Cappy says start using our valuable natural fuel resources. Libs know nothing about economics.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1344917556185</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344918913236-4</Id><Topic><Title>HERE IS WHO PAUL RYAN REALLY IS...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344905581667</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 20:53:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump this baby PS Colorado Mountain High !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344918913236</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:35:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344919786642-5</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Ronmey AFRAID to show his taxes??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344249834000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 06:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who cares? Why is Obama afraid to mention he is owned by goldman sachs?</Msg><Username>billwilly749</Username><Timestamp>1344919786642</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:49:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344919882777-6</Id><Title>ULTIMATE SWEET JUSTICE WOULD BE....</Title><Msg>Romney/Ryan get elected, and all the teabags that were parading themselves with Medicare Obama Hitler signs get fked in the ahzz. Oh please let it be so. I changed my mind. I want Romney/Dickhole to win</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344919882777</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 00:51:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344920740819-7</Id><Topic><Title>Romney paid just 13% in taxes last year</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1344905101468</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 20:45:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No, Fruitloop, in point of fact Romney does not: FICA tax is not assessed on income from capital gains. Nor (as of this writing) is Medicare tax assessed on income from capital gains. (Even if they WERE assessed on capital gains INCOME, this would no doubt be limited to "realized" capital gains income, which for the Romneys of the world can often be limited to a teeny, tiny fraction of their TOTAL capital gains INCOME.) Only wage slaves have traditionally been expected to pay these, which combined equal 15.3% for the vast majority of Americans (and on the very first dollar earned), as I previously noted. And 15.3% is (still, as of this writing) LARGER than 14%. You're just so #$%$ stupid, I lose IQ points every time I read one of your posts. Hard to believe you remember to breathe.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344920740819</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 01:05:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344921021789-8</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Wasserman Shultz: I didn't know that?????</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344910121291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 22:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jesus Christ Greg, lay a few more sheet rocks and get yourself some good vodka. That cheap Popoff sjht is really eating your brain. PS Hey Greg I hooked 1 brown and 2 rainbows today. I smoked them suckers with the girlfriend and had them over crustini and some aioli. It brought back memories when your wife use to tell me "I am so hungry. Let me have your one eyed trouser trout baby".</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1344921021789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 01:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344922212501-9</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Ronmey AFRAID to show his taxes??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344249834000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 06:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In addition to shockingly low effective tax rates (possibly approaching ZERO in certain years) paid on his vast sums of lucre, you mean? I heard somebody earlier today (ex-Mormon) say it's also possible that doing so could reveal that he did not comply with all the LDS church's tithing guidelines (which incidentally run to nearly 78000 pages, and over 40 bound volumes in their most recent 2008 edition). And THAT could not only put him on the church's terrestrial shytlist, making get-togethers with other high church officials AWK-WARD, but could also fair bollox up all his plans for that cushy afterlife. (cf. afterbirth)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344922212501</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 01:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344931369433-10</Id><Title>The AGE of Nigras is OVER</Title><Msg>NBC would have you believe that nigras own the planet. Nothing could be furder from de truff. Da last whitey election is about to take place, and the mud people will be running fo cover.</Msg><Username>fatass_michelle</Username><Timestamp>1344931369433</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 04:02:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344931462790-11</Id><Title>IM SO TIRED OF MY OWN #$%$</Title><Msg>and I still cant believe you dipschits are swallowing it</Msg><Username>fatass_michelle</Username><Timestamp>1344931462790</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 04:04:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344937498512-12</Id><Topic><Title>Why is Ronmey AFRAID to show his taxes??</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344249834000</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-06 06:43:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>transparency does work in USA.LoL!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1344937498512</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 05:44:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344943206695-13</Id><Title>WHY IS OBOZO AFRAID TO RELEASE HIS COLLEGE RECORDS?</Title><Msg>We all know why, dont we?</Msg><Username>downgoesobama</Username><Timestamp>1344943206695</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344943394353-14</Id><Title>18</Title><Msg>Today is a good day</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344943394353</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:23:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344943607865-15</Id><Topic><Title>tax cuts for the rich, tax increases for the middle class</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344887898031</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 15:58:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP Strategist Jon Sununu was asked if it's necessary to reform social security &amp; medicare, shouldn't it start immediately for everyone, and not just those under age 55. He didn't have an answer to that one. LOL</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344943607865</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:26:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344943759086-16</Id><Topic><Title>I saw news interviews in Janesville, WI -where r the black people at?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1344861029581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 08:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does the GOP REFUSE to run a black or intelligent female as Pres. or VP ? Why two white guys again?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344943759086</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:29:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344943842404-17</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN a positive force for Democrats</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344869998515</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 10:59:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Helps crystalize the ROMNEY campaign as being against the middle-class, minorities, the poor &amp; women</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344943842404</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344943882826-18</Id><Topic><Title>MITT ROMNEY'S VP pick not to go after moderates</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1344859609440</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 08:06:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>EGGADS!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344943882826</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:31:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344944712032-19</Id><Title>chmabers hope someone shoot kil u</Title><Msg>wat a crook ceo</Msg><Username>ericmedina2000</Username><Timestamp>1344944712032</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344945127074-20</Id><Title>Obumbles=Show USA your records. You CROOK</Title><Msg>Why are you paying lawyers millions to hide your past. What are you hiding?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344945127074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:52:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344945309540-21</Id><Title>Idiots equate mandatory submission of tax returns to optional college transcripts</Title><Msg>YOU REPUKES ARE JUST TOO FUNNY!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344945309540</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344945859259-22</Id><Title>John SUNUNU PUT in HIS PLACE BY CHRIS MATTHEWS !</Title><Msg>John SUNUNU PUT in HIS PLACE BY CHRIS MATTHEWS ! 3 minutes ago “He likes Ryan without the plan,” Matthews pressed. Sununu answered that, while Romney appreciates the Ryan budget reform proposals, Romney has his own budget that he is running on. “So he’s a cafeteria Catholic on this,” Matthews said, suggesting that Romney was picking and choosing what Ryan advocates that he would support. When Sununu argued that the government was going to have to reform Medicare or it would go bankrupt eventually, Matthews agreed. “Are you still with Ryan,” Matthews asked again. “No, I’m with Romney,” Sununu protested. “Forget Ryan’s plan.” LMAO!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344945859259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344946543148-23</Id><Topic><Title>I saw news interviews in Janesville, WI -where r the black people at?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1344861029581</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 08:30:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Republicans DID have a black man run in the primaries, the far left dragged his good name through the mud with personal attacks and FAKE accusations. You people are the real racist who hate REAL black men.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344946543148</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:15:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344946578489-24</Id><Title>I like how Ryan's plan</Title><Msg>cuts veteran's benefits!!! Baggers should be proud.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946578489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344946645899-25</Id><Topic><Title>I like how Ryan's plan</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946578489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:16:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cut's pell grants, we need to get dumber to compete with other nations</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946645899</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344947044007-26</Id><Title>why is Mitt different then every other candidate?</Title><Msg>"This whole issue is not about me," Reid said in his home state of Nevada on Monday. "Mitt Romney's the first presidential candidate since his dad ran not to release his income tax returns. He's released one income tax return, and that points toward the Bahamas, Switzerland and a few other foreign countries. This whole controversy will end very quickly if he releases his income tax returns, like everybody else has done." Romney has released his tax return from 2010 and an estimate from 2011. He has vowed to release his full 2011 return once it's completed, but he will not release past years', as previous presidential candidates have done. Meanwhile, Reid chief of staff David Krone insisted Monday, again, that he knows who Reid's source is -- and that the source is credible. "I know who this person is, and if I thought this person was not credible, I would say something to Sen. Reid. I would try to shut it down. This person is credible," Krone said. "This person has asked Reid to protect the confidentiality of this person, but it's real," he continued. "This person told him this. This person said it to Sen. Reid."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344947044007</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:24:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344947379482-27</Id><Title>American Taliban</Title><Msg>"Our rights come from God, not from government". Really? Did the right to bear arms come from God? No, it is in that document of government called the Constitution. Did the right for African Americans and women to vote come from God? No, it is in the Constitution. If a woman is raped and gets pregnant with that rapist's baby, does the right for that woman to get an abortion come from God? No, it is legal due to a Supreme Court decision upholding the constitutional right to obtain such a procedure. On this one, Mitt Romney supports the resolution that would take away that right. And finally, does the right to avoid paying income taxes in this country by stuffing your money in a Swiss bank account come form God? Related Ryan, Romney embrace a hyper-individualistic view of America's past and future Romney selection of Paul Ryan Why should Romney release his tax returns if Obama won't release his college records? With Paul Ryan, Romney bets on the wrong vision for America Romney could easily defuse critics by releasing his tax returns Paul Ryan in that short statement, makes it clear where Mitt Romney and the Republicans want to take this country. They want to take it toward a government of an "American Taliban" guided by some interpretation of the "inalienable rights" that "their" god has bestowed upon us. We should think long and hard of the implications of that statement.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344947379482</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344947712107-28</Id><Topic><Title>American Taliban</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344947379482</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:29:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush did not acquit John Walker Lindh</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1344947712107</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:35:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344947781565-29</Id><Title>the obvious solution from a republican</Title><Msg>STOCKMAN: The Ryan budget is a ‘fairy tale,’ not a serious vision. ”Paul D. Ryan is the most articulate and intellectually imposing Republican of the moment, but that doesn’t alter the fact that this earnest congressman from Wisconsin is preaching the same empty conservative sermon…A true agenda to reform the welfare state would require a sweeping, income-based eligibility test, which would reduce or eliminate social insurance benefits for millions of affluent retirees. Without it, there is no math that can avoid giant tax increases or vast new borrowing. Yet the supposedly courageous Ryan plan would not cut one dime over the next decade from the $1.3 trillion-per-year cost of Social Security and Medicare. Instead, it shreds the measly means-tested safety net for the vulnerable…In short, Mr. Ryan’s plan is devoid of credible math or hard policy choices.” David A. Stockman in The New York Times.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344947781565</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:36:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344949795850-30</Id><Topic><Title>I like how Ryan's plan</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946578489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:16:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunately dumb rednecks like yourself don't get the big picture. Something has to go, but since you libTURDS have turned our country into a nanny state it will be painful for many who have come to rely on the government for their well being. Free stuff for your vote, it's the libturd way.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344949795850</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:09:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344950039478-31</Id><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Msg>Somebody call the boys in white and get the straight jacket. Somebody has gone off his meds. Call the mothership......</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344950489028-32</Id><Topic><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>anyone notice the baggers never respond to policy issues, all they have is personal attacks? It's clear the Ryan pick was a desperate move that is backfiring, even David Stockman rips him apart today, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344950489028</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:21:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344950680215-33</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Wasserman Shultz: I didn't know that?????</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344910121291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 22:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you daydreaming at your janitor job again today BOYsurfer? BTW, did you ever learn how to spell the company that you claimed you sold. LMMFAO at the BOY janitor. he he</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950680215</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:24:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344950697687-34</Id><Topic><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Judging by how upset the loons like dumb ivan are, Ryan must have been a good choice. Funny to read their rants!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1344950697687</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:24:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344950724142-35</Id><Topic><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mr Ryan has no serious plan to create jobs. David A. Stockman</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344950724142</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:25:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344950907856-36</Id><Topic><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IvanMagoo mentions policy issues. How about 1.5 GDP and 8.3 UE. Want to talk about that, Magoo???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344950907856</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344951088034-37</Id><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Msg>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign? 2 minutes ago Name ONE SINGLE demographic that Ryan ADDS to the GOP.... Minorities...Nope Women....Nope...His attacks of female healthcare will give more female votes to Obama (he already had 68%) Under-35...Nope Seniors...Nope...His attacks on SS and Medicare give more to Obama... The GOP already gets the majority of the OLD WHITE MALE vote...So Ryan ADDS NOTHING, and in fact he loses female and senior voters!!! Obama can't believe his good luck...</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344951259373-38</Id><Title>Negative articles about csco</Title><Msg>A lot of negative articles right before earnings. It could be a hedge fund manipulation play. Chambers is going to drive it down to 16 on thursday</Msg><Username>smathan75</Username><Timestamp>1344951259373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:34:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344951316283-39</Id><Topic><Title>Negative articles about csco</Title><Username>smathan75</Username><Timestamp>1344951259373</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:34:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WAT A PIGGGGGGGGGGGGGG</Msg><Username>ericmedina2000</Username><Timestamp>1344951316283</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:35:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952018307-40</Id><Topic><Title>GOP PROS FUME: Romney Ceded Election With Ryan Pick</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344951684936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt nominated an extremist the baggers love him but everyone else hates him there is no compromise with Ryan just a fiscal cliff Representative Paul Ryan was a pivotal figure in killing the 2010 Bowles-Simpson agreement, which Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney now holds out as a model for putting America’s fiscal house in order. The 18-member panel needed 14 votes to send a 10-year plan to trim the debt to Congress for a vote. As his party’s then- ranking member on the House Budget Committee, Ryan led a bloc of three House Republicans who denied the additional votes needed. All three Senate Republicans on the panel backed the plan and one of them, former New Hampshire Senator Judd Gregg, said he believes the House Republicans who rejected it were beholden to an argument by anti-tax advocate Grover Norquist that the measure was tantamount to a tax increase.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344952018307</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:46:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952098242-41</Id><Topic><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan is going to cost Romney more votes then Palin cost McCain</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344952098242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:48:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952199005-42</Id><Topic><Title>GOP PROS FUME: Romney Ceded Election With Ryan Pick</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344951684936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep on bashing.... makes it more obvious Ryan was a good choice.LOL Squirm,libbies,squirm.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344952199005</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:49:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952251927-43</Id><Topic><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan on FULL TILT wacko attack</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344950039478</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:13:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And the Presidents plan is what????? Oh wait, after 3 1/2 years we STILL have UE above 8% and less Americans working than when he took office. Laughable gomer.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344952251927</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952410462-44</Id><Topic><Title>GOP PROS FUME: Romney Ceded Election With Ryan Pick</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344951684936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonka, If you recall it was the same tired rhetoric we heard going into the 2010 midterms. Same thing we heard going into the Scott Walker election in Wisconsin. How is it all working out for the big mouth libTURDS? Kind of makes me laugh.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344952410462</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:53:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344952761691-45</Id><Title>I said sell Cisco at $17.65</Title><Msg>Whenever the wall street criminals come out and upgrade after a 14% move it is a tell tale sign they need you to buy so they can sell. Sold all my remaining shares and said we would see a slow bleed going into earnings. If we get a decent drop I will grab a few shares for a trade. Otherwise no harm in waiting to see if Chambers dumps on the shareholders AGAIN.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344952761691</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344952762389-46</Id><Title>A lesson in irony:</Title><Msg>The Food Stamp Program, administered by the U.S. Department of Agriculture, is proud to be distributing the greatest amount of free meals and food stamps ever to 46 million people. Meanwhile, the National Park Service, administered by the U.S. Department of the Interior, asks us "Please Do Not Feed the animals." Their stated reason for the policy is because the animals will grow dependent on handouts and will not learn to take care of themselves. This ends today's lesson.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344952762389</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:59:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344952807689-47</Id><Topic><Title>GOP PROS FUME: Romney Ceded Election With Ryan Pick</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1344951684936</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:41:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Ryan pick was a smart move. It will help Mitt gain support among conservatives and the Tea party. Plus Ryan is one smart dude. Just wait until he debates Biden.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344952807689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:00:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344953082904-48</Id><Topic><Title>Debbie Wasserman Shultz: I didn't know that?????</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344910121291</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-08-13 22:08:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ANOTHER libTURD caught in a blatant lie. How does the DNC Chair not know that Superpac Priorities USA is not a Democratic backer since its leader ran Obama's 2008 campaign. What a stupid ignorant LIAR. She gives the entire Democratic party a BAD name. Anybody else notice that it seems every Democrat who goes in front of a micro-phone LIES. What gives with these people.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344953082904</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:04:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344953221922-49</Id><Title>another Dan Quayle, LOL</Title><Msg>yeah that Ryan was a great pick, a great pick if you are Obama, LOL Ryan's ratings were less positive than those for any other vice presidential pick part of Gallup since 2000, including Sarah Palin, Joe Biden and Dick Cheney. The only other recent vice presidential selection to gain net negative ratings was Dan Quayle in 1988.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344953221922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344953370377-50</Id><Topic><Title>another Dan Quayle, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344953221922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>let's see Romney has net negative ratings and Ryan has net negative ratings, LOL talk about dropping the ball, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344953370377</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:09:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344953871632-51</Id><Title>Where is Obama's PLAN?</Title><Msg>After 3 1/2 years of his social engineering of America we have had the LONGEST running stretch of UE above 8% since the great depression. Gotta love that record libTURDS. 300k - 500k LESS Americans working today than when he took office. How can any intelligent person vote for this character again. His Hope and Change has FAILED America.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344953871632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:17:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344954588242-52</Id><Title>Goldmans' conviction buy upgrade to $24</Title><Msg>How can they come a week before earnings and be so sure?</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344954588242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344954744614-53</Id><Topic><Title>Where is Obama's PLAN?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344953871632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Please explain in your own redneck fashion the lie you are referring to? I await your ignorant response.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344954744614</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:32:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344954780042-54</Id><Title>biden may be running the country SOON !!</Title><Msg>obammy born in kenya and claiming dual citizenship for a scholarship !!! In a move certain to fuel the debate over Obama's qualifications for the presidency, the group "Americans for Freedom of Information" has Released copies of President Obama's college transcripts from Occidental College ... Released today, the transcript school indicates that Obama, under the name Barry Soetoro, received financial aid as a foreign student from Indonesia as an undergraduate. The transcript was released by Occidental College in compliance with a court order in a suit brought by the group in the Superior Court of California. The transcript shows that Obama (Soetoro) applied for financial aid and was awarded a fellowship for foreign students from the Fulbright Foundation Scholarship program. To qualify, for the scholarship, a student must claim foreign citizenship. This document would seem to provide the smoking gun that many of Obama's detractors have been seeking. Along with the evidence that he was first born in Kenya and there is no record of him ever applying for US citizenship, this is looking pretty grim. The news has created a firestorm at the White House as the release casts increasing doubt about Obama's legitimacy and qualification to serve as President article titled, "Obama Eligibility Questioned," leading some to speculate that the story may overshadow</Msg><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1344954780042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:33:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344954842019-55</Id><Topic><Title>Where is Obama's PLAN?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344953871632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Private employment is at record highs, your job losses are all government job losses, Obama is the best GOP president since Clinton Perhaps the GOP could pass Obama's job bill, or at least vote on it</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344954842019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:34:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344955024329-56</Id><Topic><Title>Goldmans' conviction buy upgrade to $24</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344954588242</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:29:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because they needed to unload all the shares they bought at $15 just 7 days before. People need to start looking at when and why you see these upgrades, just a week or so before Cisco was trading at $15 and the world was coming to an end. After a 14% increase in share price to $17.10 over the next week or so GS decides to FINALLY upgrade. REALLY...... That just smells of CRIMINAL behavior. Think about it.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344955024329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:37:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344955422411-57</Id><Topic><Title>Where is Obama's PLAN?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344953871632</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:17:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The federal government payroll has increased by about 120k under Obama. State and local govt. payrolls have declined due to budgetary problems. Never trust anything dumb.ivan posts.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344955422411</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344955585484-58</Id><Topic><Title>biden may be running the country SOON !!</Title><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1344954780042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL that Hoax again, the one released on April Fools Day, LOL The only real question is are you stupid enough to believe that or are you so stupid you think everyone else is a #$%$</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344955585484</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:46:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344955657865-59</Id><Topic><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ROMNEY JUST FORFEITED the votes of WOMEN &amp; THE MIDDLE CLASS. MAGOO is NOW SATISFIED THAT, barring a total disaster, OBAMA gets REELECTED!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1344955657865</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:47:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344955911818-60</Id><Topic><Title>biden may be running the country SOON !!</Title><Username>hoe.inthewall</Username><Timestamp>1344954780042</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:33:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Q: Has a “smoking gun” been found to prove Obama was not born a U.S. citizen? Did he attend Occidental College on a scholarship for foreign students? A: This chain e-mail is a transparent April Fools’ Day hoax. It fabricates an AP news story about an nonexistent group, and makes false claims about Obama and the Fulbright program. Transparent to everyone but morons, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344955911818</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:51:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344956095792-61</Id><Topic><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your ignorance and bias are showing again,dumb. Pros say Palin kept Mccains defeat from being even worse.He was a poor candidate who ran a poor campaign. That will get you beat regardless of who the veep is.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344956095792</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:54:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344956324455-62</Id><Topic><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, you are STUPID! HINT: IF McCAIN PICKED A COMPETENT VP, we might be talking about President McCain's RE ELECTION now!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1344956324455</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:58:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344956490657-63</Id><Title>Mitt messed up big time</Title><Msg>after 10 years of running for President you would think he would have learned something about politics by now, LOL This year, an incumbent even more embattled than George H.W. Bush has his own preferred election theme. He doesn't want to debate his own record, which is pretty dismal. He wants to debate the record of the congressional Republicans elected in 2010, a bunch radically less popular even than the president himself. You'd imagine that Romney's job was to refuse the Democratic invitation, to choose his own ground for the election, and to keep his distance from the congressional GOP. You'd imagine, but you'd be wrong. Romney has instead chosen to bolt himself to the House Republicans. He has chosen as his running mate Paul Ryan, the House Republican leader -- not their formal leader, but their intellectual leader, the person who set their agenda. He has effectively adopted Paul Ryan's agenda as his own: big immediate cuts in spending, a dramatic cut in the top rate of income tax to 28% and a bold reform of Medicare for those 55 and under. Obama's message in 2012: "Forget the economy. It's Medicare, stupid!" The Romney-Ryan response? "We agree. Medicare it is."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344956490657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:01:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344956638558-64</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt messed up big time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344956490657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John Sununu claims that they are going by ROMNEY'S HEALTH PLAN and not RYANS ! Chris Matthews nailed Sununu yesterday! LOL!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1344956638558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344956728476-65</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt messed up big time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344956490657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's pretty telling that Mitt would be running from his own V.P. choice less then 24 hours after nominating him, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344956728476</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344956936258-66</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt messed up big time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344956490657</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:01:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is really funny is the dems having a vice president like Joe Biden and then making fun of the repub choice. Now that is HILARIOUS!!!!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344956936258</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:08:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344957145647-67</Id><Topic><Title>What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1344951088034</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 09:31:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(What Does Paul Ryan Bring to Mitten's Campaign? 2 minutes ago Name ONE SINGLE demographic that Ryan ADDS to the GOP....) My vote in Florida, and many more like me!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344957145647</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344957767123-68</Id><Title>Romney/Ryan---Women &amp; Farmers (no clue)</Title><Msg>The GOP must have a "death wish". These two are extreme right on women's issues, and are behind about 20% with women voters. Also, Ryan and the GOP, are witholding dought relief for the farmers, in an effort to make BHO look bad. It is all backfiring, and the GOP is being buried in the dust.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344957767123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344958259401-69</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan---Women &amp; Farmers (no clue)</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344957767123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan voted for drought relief earlier this month. The bill was killed in the dem senate. Get your facts straight.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344958259401</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:30:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344959052245-70</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan---Women &amp; Farmers (no clue)</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344957767123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A new five-year Farm Bill including programs providing a safety net for farmers is stalled in the U.S. House of Representatives. The Senate passed one version of the bill but the House has failed to vote on its version. And the current bill expires in September. South Dakota Senator John Thune believes there will be pressure to pass it when Congress returns to Washington after Labor Day. "I think after having been out in the month of August a lot of members of Congress are going to have heard from their constituents about the drought conditions, how important it is that they get a new Farm Bill and hopefully that will change the political dynamic when we get back in September and there will be more votes for it," Thune said. Once the House passes its version, leaders from the House and the Senate need to come together to hammer out a final bill.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344959052245</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:44:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344960144877-71</Id><Topic><Title>Obumbles=Show USA your records. You CROOK</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344945127074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 07:52:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>elhcq</Username><Timestamp>1344960144877</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:02:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344960326914-72</Id><Title>Obama released his tax records, Mitt and Paul refuse</Title><Msg>what are they hiding? don't worry though Mitt's will leak out proving he cheated on his taxes.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344960326914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:05:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344960673558-73</Id><Topic><Title>I like how Ryan's plan</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946578489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:16:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something has to go, but we can never ever EVER touch the military budget. Let's streamline the rest of government, put the poor and unemployed on the streets, destroy public education, and give tax cuts to the rich so we can bomb some more countries.</Msg><Username>lefthandedgraffiti</Username><Timestamp>1344960673558</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344961041639-74</Id><Topic><Title>I like how Ryan's plan</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344946578489</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 08:16:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Something has to go, but we can never ever EVER touch the military budget. Let's streamline the rest of government, put the poor and unemployed on the streets, destroy public education, and give tax cuts to the rich so we can bomb some more countries. that is the GOPER plan, they are owned by the rich and the military industrial complex, Bush had to start two wars to justify the spending, Congress is busy voting for military spending the pentagon says is a waste, I can live with sequestration, go ahead and cut military spending in half, still leaves us plenty of military to destroy the rest of the world</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344961041639</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:17:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344961181976-75</Id><Topic><Title>Obama released his tax records, Mitt and Paul refuse</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344960326914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:05:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>release your returns Mitt, we want to know about your felony record before we don't vote for you</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344961181976</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:19:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344962089922-76</Id><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Msg>the elderly aren't as stupid as the GOP thinks Mitt Romney’s selection of Paul Ryan provides an opening for a fundamental debate over entitlements and health care policy. But is Romney ready for that debate? Campaigning this week, the former Massachusetts governor is already downplaying the one thing that made Ryan famous: His plan to severely cut health care and social spending. On Monday, Romney didn’t bring his new running mate to Florida, an elderly swing state where Medicare is about as popular as sunlight. (A whopping 74% of seniors oppose Ryan’s cuts to the program, according to CNN polling.) Instead, Romney brought chutzpah, telling Floridians that if they look at his health care plan and the Ryan budget, both actually enlarge Medicare. Who knew? “My plan, like [Ryan’s], really expands Medicare Advantage,” Romney said. It’s one thing to run on cutting health care for seniors because the debt and deficit are large. It’s another thing to run on the opposite pledge — expanding care — with the same plan to cut health care once in office. (At least Paul Ryan is direct.) We’ll come back to this campaign pitch in a moment. But first, why is Romney even talking about expanding government health care? It is because he’s now stuck between two inexorable laws in today’s politics: You can’t sell Medicare cuts to seniors, and you can’t beat President Obama without them.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344962533019-77</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL! Your name is perfect, dummy. The turd in the WH is cutting 700 billion from medicare. All seniors know that. See you at the turd flushing.</Msg><Username>downgoesobama</Username><Timestamp>1344962533019</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:42:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344962644127-78</Id><Topic><Title>another Dan Quayle, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344953221922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BWWAAAHAAA! I got 2 words for you, numbnuts. Joe, the clueless idiot, Biden. LOL! Too funny.</Msg><Username>downgoesobama</Username><Timestamp>1344962644127</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:44:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344963692456-79</Id><Title>FACT:Obama raises middle class taxes</Title><Msg>HC bill is a new tax. food HC and gas more expensive than ever. americans lost 40% of total wealth under dumb dumb. liberals get all wet because he keeps saying he will get the rich...hahahahahahahahahahaha hows that working out you dumb suckers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963692456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344963837262-80</Id><Topic><Title>another Dan Quayle, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344953221922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 10:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the CONs think if you multiply a negative # by another negative #, you get a positive #? Naaah, that would mistakenly imply that CONs know basic arithmetic...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344963837262</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344963948617-81</Id><Title>BUSH lowered middle class taxes.</Title><Msg>liberals are to busy smelling their own farts to realize results. words words words. idiots are getting clobbered by the guy they think is "going to help them" hahahahahahahahahahaha. they deserve what is coming to them. what tax rate did obama pay? hahahahahahahahaha idiots.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963948617</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:05:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344964236074-82</Id><Topic><Title>FACT:Obama raises middle class taxes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963692456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>libTURDS have no answer because they won't tell you the ENTIRE truth. They tell you REP. gave tax breaks to the rich but they FAIL to tell the whole truth. EVERYONE got a tax break with the middle and lower getting the larger percentage. That is fact.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344964236074</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:10:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344964274743-83</Id><Title>what does obama plan to do in his</Title><Msg>second term? anyone? attack people?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344964274743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:11:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344965063021-84</Id><Topic><Title>Obama released his tax records, Mitt and Paul refuse</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344960326914</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:05:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>your not better then everyone else Mitt, you're going to have to play by the same rules</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344965063021</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:24:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344965245603-85</Id><Topic><Title>what does obama plan to do in his</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344964274743</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:11:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm glad you have accepted the fact that Obama is going to be reelected, expect a lot to be accomplished in his second term, the GOP won't have as its agenda trying to destroy the economy so they can blame it on Obama,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344965245603</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344965551189-86</Id><Title>I thought this was a Cisco stock info board ...</Title><Msg>not a damned political propaganda forum! Grow up !</Msg><Username>dr_p1</Username><Timestamp>1344965551189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:32:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344965779615-87</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No cuts to Medicare enrollee services, though. Ask ANY senior about that. In fact, because of Obamacare: (1) seniors now have no deductible/copay for most screening and preventive care services; (2) the much-discussed "donut hole" in Medicare Part D, which required many seniors - about 4 million souls, and especially those needing multiple medications - to pay thousands of dollars out of pocket each year, has been ~50% closed under Obamacare so far, and will be closed further each year, disappearing entirely in 2020; (3) seniors (and the rest of us) can no longer be denied coverage due to "pre-existing conditions"; (4) seniors (and the rest of us) can no longer be subject to annual or lifetime coverage caps that leave them suddenly without coverage during a major illness; (5) seniors (and the rest of us) can no longer suddenly have coverage canceled for contrived, bullshyt reasons when insurance company death panels and accountants determine that costs of future coverage are likely to exceed premium payments; (6) seniors (and the rest of us) now have a guaranteed right of appeal when insurance company death panels and accountants make arbitrary and/or factually incorrect/unsupported denials of coverage for specific treatments and procedures. The "cuts" (so-called) to which you refer came overwhelmingly from: (a) eliminating the windfall subsidy to insurance companies offering "Medicare Advantage" plans, which provided them with a large guaranteed government-subsidized profit (~15% on average, year after year after year) for every such plan subscription sold; and (b) eliminating unnecessary/ duplicative services/ procedures, double-billing, up-coding, code-jamming, unbundling and other shady (fraudulent or bordering on fraudulent) provider practices (... you know, all that "waste, fraud and abuse" you CONs always complain about, but are often found at the center of ...).</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344965779615</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:36:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344965935171-88</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>-- ... you know, all that "waste, fraud and abuse" you CONs always complain about, but are often found at the center of ... -- I'm talking to YOU, Rick Scott (Gov. Florida). =P</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1344965935171</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344965935395-89</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>compare that to Ryan's plans Therein lies the rub. Ryan’s budget isn’t courageous — it’s just cruel. Three-fifths of the cuts he wants would hit those with low incomes, while those who have the most would continue getting more. It’s no wonder the former altar boy has had his knuckles rapped by a group of nuns for peddling a budget that “rejects church teaching about solidarity, inequality, the choice for the poor, and the common good.” Ryan’s claim to courage — beating up on the poor notwithstanding — lies in his supposed willingness to tackle tough fiscal issues without obfuscation or sugar-coating. This would be admirable – if it were not utter nonsense. He preaches the need for austerity while refusing to touch defense spending. He doesn’t specify which tax loopholes would be eliminated to pay for massive tax cuts. He voted against stimulus to help the whole country, but for the auto bailout to help his own congressional district. Still, it’s true that on pages 44-47 of Ryan’s so-called “Path to Prosperity” plan, you can read exactly what he intends to do with Medicare. Pages 50-54 explain his plans for tax reform. There are giant gimmicks and plenty is left unsaid, of course. But, yes, technically it is a plan, outlined in black and white and illustrated with colorful graphs and charts. Is that courageous? Not on the level of, say, our returning veterans, for whom Ryan’s budget would slash support by 13 percent. No, he is remarkable only because — unlike the man at the top of the ticket, who is a shameless cipher — Ryan isn’t hiding the ball. Instead, he#$%$ struggling Americans in the face with it.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344965935395</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:38:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344966655473-90</Id><Title>Reagan Budget Director: Paul Ryan’s Plan Is A “Fairy Tale”</Title><Msg>and a nightmare to the elderly, what was Mitt thinking? It's almost like he chose Ryan because he wanted to lose.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344966655473</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:50:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344966760045-91</Id><Title>The Paul Ryan &amp; Ayn Rand connection</Title><Msg>The Paul Ryan &amp; Ayn Rand connection Ryan likes to spout off how he's such an admirer of Rand's "philosophy"...In fact Rand was an anti-Catholic, pro-choice, atheist....Now tell me how that jibes with anything that the right-wing nuts like Ryan and the GOP stand for today?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1344966760045</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:52:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344967045219-92</Id><Topic><Title>Romney/Ryan---Women &amp; Farmers (no clue)</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1344957767123</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 11:22:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ryan, the House Budget Committee chairman, is the architect of a fiscal plan that includes steep spending cuts and the eventual transformation of Medicare into a federal subsidy for private coverage. Ryan’s plan wouldn’t affect current recipients or those 55 years and older. Future Generations Democrats say Ryan’s proposal would amount to scrapping Medicare for future generations, and that it would increase costs or reduce benefits for many seniors</Msg><Username>comsensea</Username><Timestamp>1344967045219</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:57:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344968641983-93</Id><Title>in 2008 REPUBS bragged about VP candidate Sarah Palin's EXEC. EXPERIENCE; but VP Paul Ryan</Title><Msg>HAS ABSOLUTELY NO EXECUTIVE EXPERIENCE WHATSOEVER !!!! So why the flip-flop by REPUKES HERE?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1344968641983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344969822688-94</Id><Title>the baggers are very good</Title><Msg>at picking on the poor and disabled, Romney intends to get his henchmen to hold them down while he cuts their hair off, but it's all in good fun Ryan’s proposal to cut Medicaid, the health-care program for the poor, would hit many seniors now. The program provides care to poor children, pregnant women, the disabled -- and some 6 million seniors who rely on it for nursing-home care, home health aides and other services. Medicaid Proposal Ryan’s budget would cut the program beginning next year, with the reductions totaling about $800 billion over the next decade. That’s about one-third of projected spending on the program. There’s a double standard when it comes to protecting Medicare and Medicaid beneficiaries from cuts, said Howard Gleckman, a resident fellow at the Washington-based Urban Institute. That’s because Medicaid beneficiaries are much poorer, and the program tends to be less well understood, he said. “The very poor, frail elderly aren’t very good at lobbying for themselves, and neither are their family members, and it’s very easy to forget about these people,” Gleckman said.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344969822688</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:43:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344970183740-95</Id><Topic><Title>in 2008 REPUBS bragged about VP candidate Sarah Palin's EXEC. EXPERIENCE; but VP Paul Ryan</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1344968641983</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:24:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because Ryan is so brilliant! He is smarter than Obimbo who BECAME PRESIDENT with no executive experience!!! Wow!!!! Aren't you more impressed with Ryan than Obimbo? Obozo had affirmative action on his side and DECEIT, COVER UP, HIDING RECORDS AND PURE D LYING TO HELP HIM...Ryan got nothing!! No body helping Ryan but Ryan, the way America became strong... YOU DID IT ALL BY YOURSELF!!!!! WOW, OLD SCHOOL, EH?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970183740</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:49:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344970204673-96</Id><Title>Mitt doubles down on his bet</Title><Msg>that all americans are as stupid as tea baggers, LOL he thinks if you lie over and over again it will become the truth, LOL Romney rolls out ad promising to protect Medicare (AP) – 13 minutes ago WASHINGTON (AP) — Mitt Romney's presidential campaign is airing a television ad promising to strengthen Medicare and protect the program for seniors.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344970204673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:50:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344970305555-97</Id><Title>RYAN....OLD SCHOOL...HE DID IT BY HIMSELF...OBIMBO....NEW SCHOOL, SOMEBODY ELSE PUT HIM IN OFFICE</Title><Msg>he sure didn't do it by himself, the way Ryan built his life. Obozo had affirmative action, lying main stream media, hidden college records, no history anywhere about his life that didn't fit the Soros Pattern and ONE BILLLLLLIIIIOOOOONNNNN DOLLARS from Saudi Arabia to help get the first Moslem American President....wow! RYAN BUILT IT ALL BY HIMSELF...OLD SCHOOL!!! Obimbo....new school...all drooling all the time.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970305555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:51:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344970342432-98</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt doubles down on his bet</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344970204673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb you may be, ivan you is not!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970342432</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344970377443-99</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN....OLD SCHOOL...HE DID IT BY HIMSELF...OBIMBO....NEW SCHOOL, SOMEBODY ELSE PUT HIM IN OFFICE</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970305555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:51:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Walt, you hit a home run again...Ryan is amazing, Obimbo is drooler.</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1344970377443</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344970545183-100</Id><Title>Smokescreens wont fool Americans</Title><Msg>After all the bashing and whining by the board libs one fact remains...after 3 1/2 years of Obama GDP is 1.5, UE is 8.3, 47 million people are on foodstamps, 23 million people underemployed or just plain unemployed.Yeah,I can see why the loons would rather talk about Ryan.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1344970545183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:55:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344970546208-101</Id><Title>RYAN/ROMENY LEADING POLLS IN FLORIDA? HUH? FLORIDA VOTERS PREFER RYAN/ROMNEY TO 'DROOLER'.....</Title><Msg>wow, isn't that a big kick in the cajones for Democrats!!! i love it!!!! Florida, home of the old, land of the feeble, MEDICARE MONSTER and they all love Ryan. Guess they've lived long enough to have a very good #$%$ detector!!!! They can tell Drooling Biden and Teleprompter Obimbo don't have a clue what they are talking about, except MediScare crap, and Ryan has his ducks in a row!!! Wow!!! Go Florida, give Biden a hot fudge enema....over and over again!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970546208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344970650849-102</Id><Topic><Title>Smokescreens wont fool Americans</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1344970545183</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:55:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You can say that again!!! and please do...OVER AND OVER AND OVER...the facts don't favor Obimbo the Drooler, do they? Are you better off??? IT'S THE ECONOMY STUPID..... It feels good to say that...the only better feeling will be telling Obimbo good bye in November!!! BUH BYE!!!!</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1344970650849</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344970883715-103</Id><Title>FACT: obama raised midle and lower class tax rates</Title><Msg>bush did not. remember when obama said we "haf ta" lower middle and lower class tax rates and costs of HC. well he raised all of them for those people.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344970883715</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344971038205-104</Id><Topic><Title>FACT:Obama raises middle class taxes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963692456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>will joe biden say we have to raise their taxes to lower them....hahahahahahaha I am sure nancy might say somthing like that.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971038205</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:03:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344971153357-105</Id><Title>remember when obama raised taxes on middle and lower classes</Title><Msg>Supream court verified this.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971153357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:05:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344971361664-106</Id><Topic><Title>remember when obama raised taxes on middle and lower classes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971153357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Supream - you morons crack me up, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344971361664</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344971420094-107</Id><Title>Obama raises HC costs for middle and lower class</Title><Msg>and you thought he was "looking out for you". hahahahahahaha idiots get what they deserve.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971420094</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:10:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344971486805-108</Id><Title>Real Clear Politics polls</Title><Msg>No toss up electoral map Obama 332 Romney 206 LOL shows Obama taking FLA, PA and OH, only in birdbrains alternate reality world is Mitt winning in FLA, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344971486805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344971602403-109</Id><Topic><Title>FACT:Obama raises middle class taxes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963692456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump...hope and change hahahahahahahahaha</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971602403</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344971991026-110</Id><Title>Playing the race card</Title><Msg>Joe Biden told a largely black audience today " The GOP wants to put you back in chains". What kind of stupid racist rhetoric is that?? From the vice president no less!!!! Just when you think the dems can't get any dirtier or sink any lower..........they do.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344971991026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344972192555-111</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Give me your address. I have a bridge I want to sell you.</Msg><Username>downgoesobama</Username><Timestamp>1344972192555</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:23:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344972332329-112</Id><Topic><Title>FACT:Obama raises middle class taxes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344963692456</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 13:01:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nancy Piglosi has her own answer, UE benefits create jobs. FUNNY STUFF These people are totally out of their mind. THINK</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344972332329</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:25:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344972612198-113</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Campaigning this week, the former Massachusetts governor is already downplaying the one thing that made Ryan famous: His plan to severely cut health care and social spending. On Monday, Romney didn’t bring his new running mate to Florida, an elderly swing state where Medicare is about as popular as sunlight. (A whopping 74% of seniors oppose Ryan’s cuts to the program, according to CNN polling.) Instead, Romney brought chutzpah, telling Floridians that if they look at his health care plan and the Ryan budget, both actually enlarge Medicare. Who knew? “My plan, like [Ryan’s], really expands Medicare Advantage,” Romney said. It’s one thing to run on cutting health care for seniors because the debt and deficit are large. It’s another thing to run on the opposite pledge — expanding care — with the same plan to cut health care once in office. (At least Paul Ryan is direct.) The WH didn't cut a penny from medicare enrollees, he is cutting 700 billion in fraud and insurance waste which he reinvests into healthcare programs. Ryan's budget calls for the exact same 700 billion in fraud and insurance waste cuts but in his case the savings go for tax cuts for millionaires. I know voters are stupid but I don't think they are as stupid as Romney is playing them. Sure there are some like you that are stupid enough to believe Romney but those of us not in the alternate reality teabagger rabbit hole know better</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344972612198</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:30:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973041087-114</Id><Topic><Title>Playing the race card</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344971991026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds more like something Sharpton or Farrakhan would say . No wonder they call Biden a gaffe machine. Although I think idiot might be a better description.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1344973041087</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:37:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973122429-115</Id><Topic><Title>Real Clear Politics polls</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344971486805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same old song and dance we heard from you O-bots prior to the 2010 midterms. SHELLACKING 2.0 coming your way.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973122429</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:38:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344973144845-116</Id><Title>ER will be bad</Title><Msg>Judging from today's price action, ER will be bad. You read it here first.</Msg><Username>cruisemercedez</Username><Timestamp>1344973144845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973161838-117</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama cost the middle and lower class more in taxes.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344973161838</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973499967-118</Id><Topic><Title>ER will be bad</Title><Username>cruisemercedez</Username><Timestamp>1344973144845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where do you people come from, REALLY, you know what earnings will be based on todays price action? You dingbats kill me. Geeez</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973499967</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973515559-119</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's true only in the alternate reality tea bagger rabbit hole, here in the real world Obama has cut taxes on all middle and lower income people unemployment for college educated is 4.6% it's just the baggers who never graduated from high school that can't find work. Reality is you idiots could go get a job picking vegetables but you're to lazy.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344973515559</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:45:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344973671041-120</Id><Title>1.5% GDP, 8.3% UE</Title><Msg>Those are REAL economic facts and those are REAL facts that effect the every day middle class American. Obumbles is a failure.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973671041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:47:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973727155-121</Id><Topic><Title>Playing the race card</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344971991026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes and the liberals chain them by de-valuing their dollar and raising their taxes and costs for HC.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344973727155</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:48:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344973795267-122</Id><Title>Where is Obama's plan to fix Medicare</Title><Msg>HE doesn't have one, he doesn't have a budget, he doesn't have a plan for jobs. Hasn't met with his jobs council for 6 months. He has NO plan. We are tired of his Hope and Change.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973795267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973833557-123</Id><Topic><Title>remember when obama raised taxes on middle and lower classes</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344971153357</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:05:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>magoo has a new ID how cute. to bad spelling wont lower middle class tax increase under obama :(.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1344973833557</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:50:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344973906225-124</Id><Topic><Title>ER will be bad</Title><Username>cruisemercedez</Username><Timestamp>1344973144845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>kiddie... look at 5 days price chart, and you see it gaps up, then straight line down 3 days including today. no EOD rally either, it is plainly written.</Msg><Username>cruisemercedez</Username><Timestamp>1344973906225</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:51:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344974111939-125</Id><Topic><Title>ER will be bad</Title><Username>cruisemercedez</Username><Timestamp>1344973144845</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:39:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said based on TODAYS ACTION. Now you bring up 5 day chart and 3 day. I ridiculed you based on YOUR post, not something else. FYI, I sold everything at $17.65 and will wait for CC guidance.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344974111939</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344974216844-126</Id><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Msg>I think the worst is behind...</Msg><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344975197578-127</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Until CHAMBERS opens his pie hole?</Msg><Username>casualj7</Username><Timestamp>1344975197578</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:13:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344975467515-128</Id><Topic><Title>1.5% GDP, 8.3% UE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973671041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you for saying again! It cannot be said too much! The media sees the nation burning to ashes but keeps their fat mouth shut! The love Obimbo more than this lovely nation, hope of the free and land of the brave!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344975467515</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:17:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344975605406-129</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN/ROMENY LEADING POLLS IN FLORIDA? HUH? FLORIDA VOTERS PREFER RYAN/ROMNEY TO 'DROOLER'.....</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970546208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:55:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the Dems both deserve and need to be abused frequently and often! It's fun! Push a Dem downstairs, under the bus and in front of the train!!!! The crushing, crunching sound of shattered bones makes a lovely back drop to the misery they have caused America</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1344975605406</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:20:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344976113711-130</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rumor has it that all of Chambers's holes have been plugged solid until after the conference call tomorrow.</Msg><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1344976113711</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:28:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344976642460-131</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep trying, my child (isn't that what your name - Balak - means?). I agree with you and apparently so do the 40 or so analysts but a stock trades where buyers and sellers find equilibrium, and apparently, there are sellers out there at these absurdly low prices. Hopefully, tomorrow's earnings report and call provide the catalyst to disturb that equilibrium (in the right direction) so we can make some money. I have lost my shirt on this stock following recent earnings reports and I am now extremely weary. Staying long all the same. Please, please, Mr. Chambers, could you say something nice, for a change?</Msg><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1344976642460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:37:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344977868453-132</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN/ROMENY LEADING POLLS IN FLORIDA? HUH? FLORIDA VOTERS PREFER RYAN/ROMNEY TO 'DROOLER'.....</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344970546208</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:55:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it is fun to abuse Democrats. They need lots and lots and lots of abuse to even part way make up for the severe damage they've done to our nation. RINO'S need almost the same amount of abuse, but less intense!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344977868453</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:57:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344977958596-133</Id><Title>OBIMBO PROMISES RELIEF FROM THE DROUGHT........</Title><Msg>he's gonna #$%$ all over America..while flying Air Force One. If you think that's rain, you're a real Democrat.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344977958596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344978081450-134</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan costs Mitt FLA and the election</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344962089922</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 12:34:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>more evidence you're an elitist Democrat...who wants black Americans to stay on the Ghetto Plantation provided by Demoratic Entitlements......saves you money since the kill each other off with homicide and drug overdose. Democrats are counting on those casualties to lower their Welfare Costs.....that and the abortion of black babies...Democrats are so cruel.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344978081450</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:01:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344978186618-135</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO PROMISES RELIEF FROM THE DROUGHT........</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344977958596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess I should have used the word...'he's gonna URINATE all over America..." Or maybe I should have said..."he's gonna pizz all over America..." Or maybe just '...he's gonna WHIZZ all over America...."</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344978186618</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:03:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344978332460-136</Id><Topic><Title>Playing the race card</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1344971991026</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:19:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing is too low when dealing with rich republican #$%$</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1344978332460</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:05:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344979019279-137</Id><Topic><Title>Where is Obama's plan to fix Medicare</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973795267</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:49:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Since he is such a socialist - hang all the rich on TV - advertising rates would be very high - take their stolen cash (what they stole from the middle class) - free health care for all - two birds with one stone - romney can be first.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1344979019279</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344979298474-138</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>killl him</Msg><Username>ericmedina2000</Username><Timestamp>1344979298474</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:21:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344979648292-139</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perhaps if done before he pulled the co off-course, but now it probably is too late.</Msg><Username>two_iron_man</Username><Timestamp>1344979648292</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:27:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344980121465-140</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will see tomorrow that Chamber’s warning last Q was a figment of his negative warped mind. They will easily beat the numbers and he once again destroyed the stock PPS for the entire qtr by shooting his stupid mouth off. The BOD needs to SHUT HIM UP permanently by firing his behind!</Msg><Username>st8_shooter</Username><Timestamp>1344980121465</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344980265189-141</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt doubles down on his bet</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344970204673</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 14:50:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>death vouchers for all</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1344980265189</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 17:37:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344982246430-142</Id><Title>Obama care's future?</Title><Msg>Tuesday, 14 August 2012 15:40 Auto Bailout Now Forecast to Lose $25 Billion — and Counting</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344982246430</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:10:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344983228334-143</Id><Title>Medicare terminators, Mitt and Paul, Romney-hood members!</Title><Msg>Butchers of medicare and social security think they can push Florida off in a wheelchair into the sea, but they are underestimating grey power! Mitt and Paul will both be neutered!</Msg><Username>dawnofreality</Username><Timestamp>1344983228334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344983987141-144</Id><Topic><Title>Medicare terminators, Mitt and Paul, Romney-hood members!</Title><Username>dawnofreality</Username><Timestamp>1344983228334</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:27:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama pulling over 700 billion out of Medicare over the next ten years and yet you loons keep saying Ryan is the one who wants to destroy Medicare. Has all that kool-ade eaten up your braincells??</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1344983987141</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:39:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344984188815-145</Id><Title>IF YOU BULLDOZED ALL DEMOCRATS INTO A SWAMP, WOULD IT HURT THE GATORS?</Title><Msg>YES, it might, which is why keeping them on ghetto plantations is the Democratic way of population control and crowd control. In Democratic ghetto's in big cities, the Democrat is out of the way of hard working people and they actually over time, reduce their population by homicide, over dosing and other forms of mayhem. Democrats smile when their ghetto people show up to vote and get the pack of cigs and the 2 liter bottle of Thunderbird. It's called 'trading your birthright for a mess of pottage'....or Marlborough's and 'the wine of the century, 20/20'</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344984188815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:43:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344984299519-146</Id><Title>WHY DOES OBIMBO HATE AMERICA? AND 'IS BIDEN AN ACTUAL HUMAN'?</Title><Msg>Two questions that only the culprit can answer. The perpetrators of this massive hoax are now running for cover. The demise of the Biden-Obimbo comedy show will bring shock waves around the ethos, that and relieved laughter</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344984299519</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:44:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344985310596-147</Id><Title>"Pop! Goes the Weasel's"</Title><Msg>The Democrat had earlier declared that he wouldn't be running for re-election in 2012. First elected to serve the 18th Congressional District in 2002, Cardoza would have faced the prospect of a bruising primary against strong Democratic candidates in order to prolong his political career. In announcing his resignation plans last year, he blasted the Obama administration for its "failure to understand and effectively address the current housing foreclosure crisis." Cardoza's seat will be vacated effective midnight on Wednesday, but no special election will be held due to the timing of his resignation.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1344985310596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:01:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344985458310-148</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It will hit 20 next year, just be patient. It regresses to the mean periodically; it will start going up out of no where, like usual. This time I am out.</Msg><Username>sirishauf</Username><Timestamp>1344985458310</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:04:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344985487975-149</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU BULLDOZED ALL DEMOCRATS INTO A SWAMP, WOULD IT HURT THE GATORS?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344984188815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats should be bulldozed into a large heap, and left for buzzards. But they insist on voting, so all of them should be given 'cocaine ballots'....paper soaked in heavy cocaine residue so that they all 'smoke' their ballots and reduce the damage they do electorally to the rest of us! Go Democrats!!! Go to Venezuela and help elect Chavez. Leave this nation.......soon!</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1344985487975</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:04:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344985557424-150</Id><Topic><Title>OBIMBO PROMISES RELIEF FROM THE DROUGHT........</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344977958596</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obimbo 'pizzled' all over America!!! HE ALREADY HAS!!! HE'S 'PIZZLED' US INTO A FUNK AND NOW WE SUFFER JOB LOSS AND MISERY...THE PIZZER!!!!!</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1344985557424</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:05:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344985954232-151</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU BULLDOZED ALL DEMOCRATS INTO A SWAMP, WOULD IT HURT THE GATORS?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1344984188815</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:43:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You people want to kill our ecosystem! Keep the garbage out of the swamp!!!!!</Msg><Username>jog49</Username><Timestamp>1344985954232</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:12:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344986172941-152</Id><Topic><Title>Buy CSCO now</Title><Username>balak_joshi</Username><Timestamp>1344974216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:56:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It was 21 just last Q before Chambers started his usual stupidity. It can be 20 in one day if they fire his behind!</Msg><Username>st8_shooter</Username><Timestamp>1344986172941</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344987474470-153</Id><Topic><Title>GOP= war against women,,war on middle class,,,,just puppets for filthy rich</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1344983964712</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 18:39:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bingo - not much better than hitler</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1344987474470</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 19:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344989997900-154</Id><Title>williard will push grannies over a cliff in their wheelchairs!!!! he already killed a guys wife!!</Title><Msg>so he could stash cash in off shore accts</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344989997900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:19:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344990103253-155</Id><Topic><Title>williard will push grannies over a cliff in their wheelchairs!!!! he already killed a guys wife!!</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344989997900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Congratulations!!!!!! Stupidest post of the year!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1344990103253</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:21:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344990215048-156</Id><Title>teaBAGGERS please answer yes or no,$ off shore is wrong@ is tax evasion...</Title><Msg>specially 4 a presidential candidate</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344990215048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344990309816-157</Id><Topic><Title>williard will push grannies over a cliff in their wheelchairs!!!! he already killed a guys wife!!</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344989997900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>u got money in the caymans too?</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344990309816</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:25:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344990838344-158</Id><Topic><Title>williard will push grannies over a cliff in their wheelchairs!!!! he already killed a guys wife!!</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344989997900</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well howdy-doody Magoo! Created yet ANOther ID I see. How many does that make now? Give up already, LOSER!</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1344990838344</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:33:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344991939084-159</Id><Title>what kind of man ties his dog to the roof of a car?</Title><Msg>willard</Msg><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344991939084</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:52:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344994314154-160</Id><Title>What kind of man EATS dog?</Title><Msg>Obama</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344994314154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 21:31:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344994484828-161</Id><Topic><Title>teaBAGGERS please answer yes or no,$ off shore is wrong@ is tax evasion...</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344990215048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could you please get your GED and learn the english language. TIA</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344994484828</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 21:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344994705256-162</Id><Topic><Title>What kind of man EATS dog?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344994314154</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 21:31:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you referring to a real canine or Michelle??</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1344994705256</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 21:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344996145861-163</Id><Topic><Title>1.5% GDP, 8.3% UE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344973671041</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:47:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Let's talk about the real issues facing Americans. Democrats want to talk about anything BUT the issues. Obama is the ONLY person who is CUTTING medicare to the tune of 740 BILLION dollars to fund his Obamacare fiasco. True story.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1344996145861</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1344996417538-164</Id><Title>CSCO Shareholders!</Title><Msg>CSCO’s stock performance has been pathetic for many years. It should be in the high 20s right now. The financial performance over the last year has actually been improving. The last several Qs they have actually beat the Wall Street numbers. Note tomorrow, they will again beat the numbers easily. What’s the problem? IT is JOHN CHAMBERS. The man is worthless; he is so negative and has instilled no confidence in investors. Note the performance tomorrow, the numbers will be once again stellar but Chambers can’t keep his negative mouth shut. He will destroy the performance of all of the hard work of all of the CSCO employees again by his stupidity. Time for hid #$%$ to go!</Msg><Username>csco_kid</Username><Timestamp>1344996417538</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:06:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1344996821643-165</Id><Topic><Title>teaBAGGERS please answer yes or no,$ off shore is wrong@ is tax evasion...</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344990215048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nothing but #$%$ - supported by #$%$.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1344996821643</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 22:13:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345000334564-166</Id><Topic><Title>Real Clear Politics polls</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1344971486805</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 15:11:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL. GOP refused to let a Hispanic on the ticket. Bye Bye Rubio. You are now a token boy no matter what the GOP tell you now. BTW bye bye Florida. Romney to Rubio: You go and play the background now. We will throw you a bone and let you introduce me at the convention.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1345000334564</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:12:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345000496054-167</Id><Title>Rubio wasn't White enough for the GOP</Title><Msg>Play your position Rubio and introduce Romney (your master) when he demands you to.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1345000496054</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:14:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345000860012-168</Id><Topic><Title>teaBAGGERS please answer yes or no,$ off shore is wrong@ is tax evasion...</Title><Username>cdmovado</Username><Timestamp>1344990215048</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 20:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is wrong is having a community organizer leading the largest most complex economy in the world.</Msg><Username>buckibrown2</Username><Timestamp>1345000860012</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-08-14 23:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>