<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-11-09"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352437267440-1</Id><Topic><Title>So what do you celebrating libs think?</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352327693729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 17:34:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that there aren't many Gracious repub losers....but a lot of deluded angry Haters.</Msg><Username>alex510_4ever</Username><Timestamp>1352437267440</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:01:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352437425114-2</Id><Topic><Title>Diick Morris video today goes into detail why polls are off. Predicts Romney win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352164239525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-05 20:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dick is always right, lol</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352437425114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:03:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352438765815-3</Id><Topic><Title>Rhonda_Edelstein likes to believe hack political analysts like DORK MORRIS</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352424500032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:28:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhoda hearts dog. She finds solace in the back yard with her beast, in a most unnatural way.</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352438765815</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:26:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352439259112-4</Id><Topic><Title>So what do you celebrating libs think?</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352327693729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 17:34:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg># 1 you are a loser as are any of the people yu voted for...they stand for nothing and believe in nothing except for power and duping losers like you # 2 The great Barack Obama, without havng to run again, will preside over another rennaissance of American capitalism. Like Clinton did. He will not start a war. He will bring money back into ordinary people's pockets, and it will make even the 1% MUCH richer. Theey will do way better than the alternative would have been. You lost...now try and put up with prosperity, it is on the way. BTW the top 1% will pay more and will not feel a thing.</Msg><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352439259112</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 00:34:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352442647668-5</Id><Topic><Title>So what do you celebrating libs think?</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352327693729</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 17:34:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean Happy Warrior Joe, the guy that kicked Gilligan in the balls and sent him back to debate school, THAT Biden ? BWWWAAHAHAHAAHAHAHAAHAHAH ! Suck it loser !</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442647668</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:30:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352442808094-6</Id><Topic><Title>Would you pet a rabid dog?</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352429241061</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:47:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes ponder that deep though DORKemifa85, then lick his ahzzz before you belch it !</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442808094</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:33:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352442998144-7</Id><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Msg>Will you cheer him on as you did with Mitt when we said he would bomb the crap out of them, or will you call him a warmonger ? The mike is open...</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352445218266-8</Id><Title>RYAN EASILY RE-ELECTED TO HOUSE IN WI AND WILL CONTINUE</Title><Msg>to help block the lame duck Hussein Obama. Anything that Hussein Obama "passes" by doing and end run around congress will easily be undone when the new conservative president is elected. Hussein might as well go on vacation for 4 years and smoke his coke....that and play baskerball and golf...that's all that drugged up socialist chimp really wants out of life.</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352445218266</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:13:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352445429936-9</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN EASILY RE-ELECTED TO HOUSE IN WI AND WILL CONTINUE</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352445218266</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:13:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The 'smartest' guy in congress was exposed for what he was... A DUMB AhZZ. He won't be there long, the emperor has no clothes. Now get back to blowing your daddy LOOOOOOSAH !</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352445429936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352445590356-10</Id><Title>SECOND NIGHT OF REPUBLICAN SUICIDE WATCH !</Title><Msg>BWWWWAHAHAHAHAAHAHAHAAHAHAH. Good night pukes !!! Enjoy the next four years.</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352445590356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:19:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352446308970-11</Id><Topic><Title>RYAN EASILY RE-ELECTED TO HOUSE IN WI AND WILL CONTINUE</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352445218266</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:13:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why did obama take his state and romney's state during the election?</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1352446308970</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:31:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352448537309-12</Id><Title>Obama won! Sell all your stock and run :--))</Title><Msg>Living oversea is cheaper and you don't have to work to pay TAX!</Msg><Username>m13monkeys</Username><Timestamp>1352448537309</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 03:08:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352461446660-13</Id><Topic><Title>Special Dividend ?</Title><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1352396037994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:33:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone needs to preserve cash right now. The crash is coming. A house of cards can be held up only so long. Those with cash will be able to buy assets for pennies on the dollar after the dust settles.</Msg><Username>secretary_whitewater</Username><Timestamp>1352461446660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 06:44:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352464946211-14</Id><Topic><Title>$== 13 INDICATOR CSCO BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT ==$</Title><Username>danwilliam291</Username><Timestamp>1351177026980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long</Msg><Username>jacoblee982</Username><Timestamp>1352464946211</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 07:42:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352465738748-15</Id><Title>Latest poll results</Title><Msg>Latest Poll Says Black American Mormons would have Voted for Romney if only there were Any Black American Mormons Written by Asheville Jack Topics: Barack Obama, Mitt Romney, 2012 Presidential Election, FOX News, Mormon Thursday, 8 November 2012 Ann and Mitt Romney boogie off the stage after concession speech A new Fox News poll out today shows African American Mormons would have likely voted for Presidential candidate Mitt Romney in large numbers, if only there were any Black Mormons. Romney, reached during a vacation stop in Asheville North Carolina, said he was 'beyond ecstatic" at the news. "What this means," said Romney, "is that the Republican party can look forward to the day when African Americans might actually vote for a Republican." Romney said he regretted that Mormons once had a rich history of being highly prejudiced against Black folks, telling a small group of wealthy Mormon donors "how were we to know that one day they would be allowed to vote?" The ex-Presidential candidate went on to say that he held out hope that someday Mormons might actually attempt converting African American to the Mormon faith. Romney noted that as a young man he helped spread the Mormon faith while living in a castle in France but that he would have gladly worked with inner city Blacks too. "Even the forth-seven percent of Americans who live on the public dole need to be saved in Jesus' name. Fox News commentators were apparently equally thrilled with the poll results. Bill O'Reilly lauded the poll as further proof that Black American Mormons, if there were any, would have happily cast aside "that pinhead Obama," while Sean Hannity just chuckled softly at the mere though of Black Mormons. Meanwhile, republican strategist Carl Rove told Fox News's anchor Chris Wallace that he is still holding out hope that the nonexistent Black American Mormons votes would be tabulated soon. "It's not too late," said Rove, "for those ballots to give Ohio to Romney. Ohio's the key, don't you see?"</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352465738748</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 07:55:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352465739409-16</Id><Title>Ann Romney is a Mannequin like Laura Bush</Title><Msg>They live in the Valley of the Dolls</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352465739409</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 07:55:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352465812899-17</Id><Title>Fiscal cliff is how you fix 50 years of debt capitalism</Title><Msg>Too much debt for world economy to service. Wall Street wants another year extension of Bush tax cuts, which will add about 1.5 trillion more to already unserviceable national debt.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352465812899</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 07:56:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352465913450-18</Id><Title>Fox News Owners Arrested for Inventing News</Title><Msg>in Europe,,,they just Fabricate News,,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352465913450</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 07:58:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352466003291-19</Id><Title>Sara Palin and Bullwinkle will win in 2016</Title><Msg>She will become our next President....and we will all become Taliban Bornagains</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352466003291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:00:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352466765816-20</Id><Topic><Title>Sara Palin and Bullwinkle will win in 2016</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352466003291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:00:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is no one more irrelevant in politics than Simple Sarah</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352466765816</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:12:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467009650-21</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Around 90 employees are being laid off from the Teco Coal Corporation. Director of Personnel, Paul Matney, says no mines are shutting down but they are reducing their manpower and staffing, which will reduce some production. Matney said that the layoffs are at several locations and are the result of the economic conditions of the coal market. He says more information will be released Friday.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467009650</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:16:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467105024-22</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wilkes-Barre city employees will know by the end of the week if their jobs are safe from furloughs during the final six weeks of the year, city officials said Wednesday. In October, the city asked its nearly 300 employees to take voluntary furloughs to patch a $2 million deficit. But the number of employees who accepted them by last Friday's deadline was not enough to solve the city's budget woes, forcing the city to resort to mandatory furloughs, city spokesman Drew McLaughlin said. McLaughlin said officials are still determining how they can reduce the work force without diminishing services. The... 600 Layoffs At Groupon</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467105024</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:18:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467150347-23</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Groupon is firing some employees today. A source familiar with the situation puts the number at 80. This is a significant number of people, obviously, but it's also a very small percentage of Groupon's 10,000+ global employees. Groupon is reporting Q3 earnings this evening. Management will presumably describe the details of these layoffs on the call. The source familiar with the situation suggests the cuts are part of a sales and marketing "optimization" effort that Groupon management alluded to on the last earnings call. UPDATE: Groupon disclosed that it has cut more than 600 jobs from its salesforce</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467150347</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:19:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467544033-24</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TurboCare, Oce laying off more than 220 workers Thu Nov 08 2012 23:58:36 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 8 replies Republic American Newspaper ^ | 11/9/12 More than 220 workers in Manchester and East Hartford face layoffs in the coming weeks, according to notices filed with the state. TurboCare Inc., which makes parts for gas and steam turbines, plans to close its Manchester plant and lay off all 88 of its employees, a notice filed with the state Labor Department says. The plant, at 80 Sheldon Road opposite the Manchester post office, will close on Dec. 31, according to the filing, known as a Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notice, or WARN notice. The work is being moved to a company plant in Massachusetts</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467544033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:25:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467570240-25</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Pratt &amp; Whitney expects to make "significant" additional layoffs this year, the head of the United Technologies Corp (UTX.N) jet-engine unit said on Thursday. Its parent company plans about new 1,500 job cuts in Connecticut this year, which will be spread between Pratt and Hamilton Sundstrand, which makes aviation components, said Pratt &amp; Whitney President David Hess."</Msg><Username>commishfree1</Username><Timestamp>1352467570240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:26:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467601914-26</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ATI plans to lay off 172 workers in North Richland Hills Thu Nov 08 2012 23:56:36 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache Star Telegram ^ | 11/9/12 NORTH RICHLAND HILLS -- ATI Schools &amp; Colleges plans to lay off 172 employees by Dec. 31, according to notices sent to the Texas Workforce Commission last week. ATI is laying off 122 people at its home office at 6331 Boulevard 26 in North Richland Hills, according to an Oct. 31 letter citing the Worker Adjustment and Retraining Notification Act of 1988. That notice explains that ATI has decided to reduce its workforce at that location. An additional 50 people are expected to be laid off from ATI Career Training Center</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467601914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:26:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467714377-27</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Energy Lays Off 40 Employees Thu Nov 08 2012 23:42:54 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 2 replies The Farmers Exchange ^ | 11/9/12 Published: Friday, November 9, 2012 Indiana's oldest ethanol plant has shut down indefinitely. New Energy Corp. President Russ Abarr said the plant shut down last week, resulting in the layoff of 40 employees. "We've been looking at what we can do and trying to avoid it," Abarr said. "The decision to lay off long-standing, dedicated employees of New Energy was extremely difficult. Abarr says an undetermined number of workers will stay on the job as the plant that opened in 1984 prepares to remain idle for at least several months.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467714377</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:28:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352467780661-28</Id><Title>Banana Republic of America</Title><Msg>Obama was re-elected by Africans, Mexicans and welfare hos. In less than 4 years, America has been transformed into a banana republic. Enjoy the misery. 4 more years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352467780661</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352467813484-29</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>.S. Cellular drops Chicago, cuts 640 local jobs Thu Nov 08 2012 23:18:20 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 13 replies Chicago Business ^ | 11/9/12 U.S. Cellular will sell markets including Chicago to units of Sprint Nextel Corp. for $480 million. The move will result in 980 job cuts at U.S. Cellular, with 640 in the Chicago area, according to a spokeswoman. The cuts are slightly under 12 percent of the approximately 8,400 total employees U.S. Cellular had at the end of the third quarter. The company plans to keep its headquarters in Chicago, President and CEO Mary Dillon said on a conference call this morning, according to a transcript. The Chicago White Sox also will continue to play at U.S. Cellular Field. "Our naming... Career Education to cut 900 jobs, close 23 campuses (Illinois) Thu Nov 08 2012 23:11:10 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 7 replies Daily Herald ^ | 11/9/12 Career Education announced Thursday that it is cutting 900 jobs and closing 23 campuses as it continues to battle with declining enrollment. The Schaumburg-based for-profit education provider reported the cuts when it released its third-quarter loss of $33.1 million. Last year the company posted a $10.6 million profit during the same quarter. Third-quarter revenue dropped 22 percent to $332.8 million from $428.4 million. Advertisement “We are taking the difficult step of closing campuses and reducing our workforce because these measures are essential to advancing the turnaround of Career Education,” chairman, president and CEO Steven H. Lesnik said in a release.... Vestas to cut 3,000 more jobs Thu Nov 08 2012 23:08:01 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 4 replies Oregon Live ^ | 11/9/12 Vestas Wind Systems is aiming to sell a stake of as much as 20 percent and shed another 3,000 off its headcount, more than doubling the number of jobs it plans to eliminate by 2013. The announcement came as the Danish company reported disappointing financial results that sent its shares tumbling 13 percent. The world's biggest wind turbine-maker said Wednesday that its third-quarter loss widened to 175 million euros ($225 million), compared with a loss of 60 million euros in the year-ago period. Analysts had forecast net income of 20 million euros, according to a Bloomberg survey. Revenue increased 49... FirstEnergy to cut 400 jobs by 2016, cites lower prices, competition Thu Nov 08 2012 23:05:40 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 3 replies Cleveland Plain Dealer ^ | 11/9/12 AKRON, Ohio -- FirstEnergy expects to cut up to 400 jobs by 2016 as it struggles to stay profitable in a lackluster economy that has led to continued low demand and low power prices. Anthony Alexander, chief executive officer, revealed the coming job cuts Thursday during a public teleconference with financial analysts about the company's third quarter financial results. He said the reductions would be made through "normal attrition" beginning next year. FirstEnergy issued pink slips a week ago to 142 employees, but the actual number of positions eliminated was 200. The 58 other were open spots. Headquartered in Akron,...</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352467813484</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:30:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352467837449-30</Id><Title>Champion Spinner</Title><Msg>KARL ROVE TRIES TO SPIN LOSS - Watching the former Bush strategist learn of the results Tuesday night was like watching a child learn that Santa Claus doesn't exist. Amanda Terkel: "No one lost as much on election night as Karl Rove. Although he wasn't running for office, his Crossroads organizations spent more than$300 million on Republican candidates in the 2012 election, with some of the biggest spenders in the conservative movement putting their hopes -- and dollars -- in the care of Rove. Combined, his groups were the largest single outside force of the 2012 election. The results were bleak. According to the Sunlight Foundation, American Crossroads, Rove's super PAC, saw just a 1 percent return on its investments. Crossroads GPS, the political nonprofit arm, saw a 14 percent return.... Rove was back on Fox News Wednesday morning after his election night meltdown. He didn't address his reaction to the Ohio call or Crossroads' failures but instead argued that Republicans need to do a better job in reaching out to the Latino community. "Obama kept the coalition that he had in 2008, only it was a little bit smaller," he said. Underlying Rove's comments is the belief that while Obama won, he did not win by as large a margin as he would have without all the money and support from conservative outside groups."</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352467837449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:30:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352468288958-31</Id><Topic><Title>Champion Spinner</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352467837449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:30:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Karl Rove George W. Bush's former political guru wasn't convinced that Ohio had gone for Obama, so on Tuesday night, he explained his reasoning. But Fox News anchor Megan Kelly was dubious about the math, asking if it was something he "does as a Republican to make himself feel better, or is this real?" Kelly's zinger hardly settled the matter. The Fox News host then got involved in moderating the awkward and contentious debate between Rove and the Fox News "decision desk." Rove believed they had called Ohio for Obama too soon. Ultimately, though, and after some on-air consultation with the behind-the-scenes crew, Kelly wasn't buying it. "They are not listening to Karl," she said. "They don't care what Karl said."</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352468288958</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:38:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352468714370-32</Id><Topic><Title>why IS THE CEO STILL HERE?</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352391819873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:23:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>election is over turn the page post csco</Msg><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352468714370</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:45:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352468883996-33</Id><Title>JPMorgan Downgrade</Title><Msg>There are so few people on this board who actually belong here that I am probably talking to myself. However, CSCO is down in premarket because the JPM downgraded them this morning to hold with a $17 target. At this point, if you ignor tax concequences, CSCO could buy themselves in less than 4 years. If they could buy their stock off shore witht he cash they have sitting around (where they made the money) and then buy additional stock with future cash flow, I would own the company in less than 4 years- because I am not selling. I would sure like to hear from someone who actually has something worthwhile to say about where I am going wrong Too bad there isn't another site somewhere that was not populated by socialists, where we could discuss CSCO.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352468883996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:48:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352468885296-34</Id><Title>Urgent, help wanted on layoff thread</Title><Msg>So many post election layoffs, its too big a job for just one person. So many bosses, you know the one percent are trying to keep their businesses viable despite the taxation Obama is promissing to bury them with So many bosses can't afford the Obamacare cost increases, that were supposed to save money per employee, but now will cost thousands per headcount. Can you guys just post new Obama layoffs to my Official Layoff Thread. I just want to show how Obama is NOT the little guy, collecting a paycheck's friend. Socialism has failed everytime its been tried, why don't the Obama voters see the pain coming our way.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352468885296</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:48:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352469197919-35</Id><Topic><Title>Both wives looked stricken, and Ryan himself seemed grim. They all were thrust on that stage without understanding what had just happened. "He was shellshocked," one adviser said of Romney.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352425763580</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:49:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Turnout was lower than 2008. Over 80% of the counties in America voted Red again. Obama won due to nggrs, spix and gays in Chicago, Cleveland, Philadelphia, New York and LA. Obama won by 2 million in the popular vote. 900,000 of that plurality came from Chicago. Obama won because all the blacks voted for him because he was black. The blacks voted for Jesse Jackson Jr. even though he did nothing, didn't even show up to work. He partied on campaign contributions and taxpayers money. The Latinos voted for Obama because he's going to rewards illegal aliens with citizenship after they committed crimes of stealing American jobs. The gays, young impressionable students, ho's and socialists filled in the rest. Obama is the President of the easily swayed lemmings. Romney was exactly what America needed. Now we will have a repeat of the last 4 years or worse.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352469197919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:53:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352469431174-36</Id><Topic><Title>JPMorgan Downgrade</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352468883996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:48:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IMHO this is a result of Obama being reelected. Let me make this clear it isn't sour Grapes that the ZeroZebraDouche is re elected. Its just that Chambers and most other multination CEO wanted a special tax to let them repariate what now is about a trillion and a half dollars back into the USA. This would be the cheapest stimulus package but once again Obama want none of it. Obama doesn't want the private sector to lead us out of our financial mess. Government must be seen as the Messiah. Phone companies, Internet carriers, businesses with video and other heavy data loads only see more expenses and taxes from Obama and they won't to an upgrade (long overdue) until they know how bad these expenses will be and how much they will be able to invest. Just like layoffs here too ELECTIONS HAVE CONSEQUENCES</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352469431174</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352469457912-37</Id><Title>VCE is the secret that the analysts don't understand.</Title><Msg>VCE: Short History Of A Big IT Experiment What a long, strange trip it's been for VCE, the joint-venture developer of Vblock converged infrastructure solutions set up by VMware, Cisco and EMC. Set up originally in June of 2009 as a way to build reference architectures based on the three partners' storage, server, networking, and virtualization technologies, it eventually morphed into an independent builder of integrated solutions which are shipped to customers only after being fully bundled and tested in VCE's own facilities. VCE is already experiencing a billion-dollar annual run rate. Take a trip back in time to look at how VCE got its start long before it was officially formed. For a closer look at VCE's future prospects, see a preview of our exclusive report, "The VCE Gamble: You Got To Know When To Hold 'Em, Know When To Fold 'Em." The full article is available exclusively in the CRN Tech News app.</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469457912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352469530523-38</Id><Topic><Title>why IS THE CEO STILL HERE?</Title><Username>jckyhrs</Username><Timestamp>1352391819873</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 11:23:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>VCE i one of the reasons... Read ....</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469530523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:58:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352469913855-39</Id><Title>Hey, youse guys, remember Alan West?</Title><Msg>Allen West v. Reality November 8, 2012 By mario piperni No one has painted an uglier picture of Republican obstructionism, partisanship and insanity over the last two years than Tea Party favorite, Allen West. Well, except maybe for Michele Bachmann. So, forgive me if I take some pleasure in watching West desperately flail about in Rovian election night fashion as he reluctantly watches his political career come to an abrupt end in Florida. U.S. Rep. Allen West was poised for a legal fight in his closely watched race Wednesday even as Democratic opponent Patrick Murphy declared a razor-thin victory. The conservative congressman has refused to concede, but Murphy seized on the projections of several news organizations, declaring himself the victor after a long and often vicious campaign. It was unclear what effect West’s actions could have on Murphy’s 2,456-vote lead in the unofficial count, but the Republican’s hopes appeared to be fading. No doubt, West will do well for himself in his new post-political career. There’s always room for another Palin kook on Fox or on the conservative radio clown circuit. Whatever. All that matters is that in the battle of teabagger vs. reality, chalk up another victory for reality.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352469913855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:05:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352469975933-40</Id><Topic><Title>VCE is the secret that the analysts don't understand.</Title><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469457912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>July, 2007: Cisco And Intel Invest In VMware Intel in July, 2007 invested $218.5 million in VMware to acquire a 2.5-percent share in that company. That news was followed a couple weeks later with word that Cisco invested $150 million for a 1.6-percent stake in VMware. The foundation of VCE was in place with EMC, Cisco and Intel now all owners of VMware.</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469975933</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:06:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352470043864-41</Id><Topic><Title>VCE is the secret that the analysts don't understand.</Title><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469457912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>March, 2009: Cisco Introduces UCS Server Line Cisco, historically one of the biggest networking vendors in the industry, stunned the IT world by unveiling the Cisco Unified Computing System (UCS) blade server line. Cisco said its UCS servers were designed primarily to optimize the performance of VMware environments. Despite attempts by other more established server vendors to dismiss the potential competitiveness of the upstart, Cisco's UCS servers are currently integrated in the converged infrastructure offerings of storage vendors EMC, NetApp and Hitachi Data Systems.</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352470043864</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:07:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352470210523-42</Id><Title>Amarantus Bioscience Inc. AMBS @ 0.03 treatment for PARKINSON's and ALZHEIMER's + Michael j Fox Foundation</Title><Msg>AMGEN Co Founder just joined the company last week and Michael J Fox Foundation . Treatment for this disease is a billion dollar drugs. Big Pharma will acquire AMBS. Check it out before the big boys come in. AMBS is a bargain.</Msg><Username>johnjohn5200</Username><Timestamp>1352470210523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352470236863-43</Id><Topic><Title>VCE is the secret that the analysts don't understand.</Title><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469457912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>June, 2009: V+C+E, Not Quite Yet VCE The last block fell in place in building the VCE foundation when VMware, Cisco and EMC held a joint press event at EMC World 2009 to unveil a partnership between the three companies and how they would develop cloud computing platforms. This wasn't VCE yet. It was originally called the VMware-Cisco-EMC alliance. Later, it would be called VCE, which was short for "Virtual Computing Environment." Eventually, it was just VCE. Pictured: Chuck Hollis (left), EMC's vice president and CTO of global marketing; Ed Bugnion (center), Cisco CTO; and Parag Patal, VMware's vice president of alliances</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352470236863</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352470388475-44</Id><Topic><Title>VCE is the secret that the analysts don't understand.</Title><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352469457912</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:57:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>January, 2010: Cisco Signs With NetApp Cisco wanted to prove that, despite its close relationship with EMC, it was an independent server vendor, and did so in a spectacular fashion by unveiling a relationship with NetApp, EMC's top storage rival. This new Cisco/NetApp relationship, which also included VMware, promised to deliver new architectures based on their technologies for data center efficiency with a joint customer support framework. Cisco in late 2012 signed a similar relationship with EMC rival Hitachi Data Systems.</Msg><Username>exgeae</Username><Timestamp>1352470388475</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:13:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352470965249-45</Id><Title>Iran shoots at Obama drone</Title><Msg>in international air space Syrians refugees fleeing economic distress in Iran created by Obama is fomenting conflict</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352470965249</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:22:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471028419-46</Id><Topic><Title>IN DEPTH CSCO ANALYST REPORT</Title><Username>danwilliam291</Username><Timestamp>1350653652093</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-10-19 09:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Informational report</Msg><Username>raymartini607</Username><Timestamp>1352471028419</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:23:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352471092027-47</Id><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Msg>Everyone is hoping for just a shallow double dip. We have become Japan. 0% interest rates for 20 years with recessions every couple years.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471280953-48</Id><Topic><Title>JPMorgan Downgrade</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352468883996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:48:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>being as the stock never goes over 20 , they could buy it all including all of ours sub $20 .. i wouldnt put it past the jerk ceo to be planning such a crooked move .. so if thats their intention , they will continue to make moves that hold the stock in the teens for the next 4 yrs. They certainly have done an excellent job of doing just that . just wait until the next earnings report when chambers opens his stupid crook mouth .. we will probably see 15 again . all going according to plan .</Msg><Username>composerx1</Username><Timestamp>1352471280953</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:28:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352471282705-49</Id><Title>How many Coffins did GW Bush use up?</Title><Msg>Bush and the Republicans use up Americans like they are Toilet Paper</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352471282705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:28:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471375989-50</Id><Topic><Title>JPMorgan Downgrade</Title><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352468883996</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:48:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know why CSCO is being punished more than other companies. I am a U.S. citizen, but would like to see CSCO permanently invest that cash off shore. Just holding temperary investments causes the money to be taxed a third time. That money is never coming back here. If a candidate as good as Romney can't be elected against someone as bad as Omaba, there is no hope for this place. We are going the way fo Euroe. A good place to invest the cash would actually be Mexico. Maybe CSCO could become a Mexican corporation. Mexico is educating twice as many engineers as us per capita. They have good growth, low unemployment, less regulation. If we legalized drugs, their crime problem would disappear. Maybe I could imigrate there!!! CSCO is worth twice the current price. Their business is mostly off shore and will not b hurt by Obama as much as other companies. Unfortunately, they have the double wammy of CA and governor Moon Beam. Chambers, come to Nevada- low taxes and low regulation. We also have lots of empty, low-cost houses.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352471375989</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:29:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471380572-51</Id><Topic><Title>Sara Palin and Bullwinkle will win in 2016</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352466003291</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 08:00:03 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that cant be because the stupid #$%$ would blow bullwinkle away from a helicopter first .</Msg><Username>composerx1</Username><Timestamp>1352471380572</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:29:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352471391737-52</Id><Title>no need to sell. no preannouncement. don't sweat the qtr it will just be an ok one.....</Title><Msg>hold</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352471391737</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:29:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471416946-53</Id><Topic><Title>How many Coffins did GW Bush use up?</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352471282705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:28:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dem LBJ used up 58,200 coffins...or did you forget????</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352471416946</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:30:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471750681-54</Id><Topic><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We will get what we deserve.</Msg><Username>eurekapeak</Username><Timestamp>1352471750681</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:35:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352471787672-55</Id><Title>Green</Title><Msg>A lot of people must have decided this morning that if JPMorgan wants you to sell your shares, they must be worth a lot- to the buyer (JPM).</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352471787672</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:36:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352471881498-56</Id><Title>I Think CSCO</Title><Msg>is dead money (or worse). It's in a very competitive spot. It's not as nimble as competitors. A price target of $17 from JPM tells you that this is a sell. Yeah, they have cash, and they used it to juice the dividend to put a floor under the price. I don't see that happening again.</Msg><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352471881498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:38:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471936158-57</Id><Topic><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tuesday America voted for more food stamps and free cell phones. Yes,we will get what we deserve.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352471936158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:38:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352471992062-58</Id><Topic><Title>Special Dividend ?</Title><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1352396037994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:33:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe this is more than a rumor.</Msg><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1352471992062</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:39:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352472027058-59</Id><Title>End of Mayan calendar</Title><Msg>End of the world on December 21, 2012. Re-election of Obama plays right into that prediction. Get out now unless you want to be a bagholder. Obama suk balz. Germany and France in recession along with rest of world. USA too. Iran shooting at drones and Obama's sanctions are fomenting the winds or war in Iran. Just what the world needs now.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472027058</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:40:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352472378324-60</Id><Title>Gas rationing in New York and New Jersey</Title><Msg>Obama has re-created the 1970's. He thinks this is the worst recession since the Great Depression because Obama wasn't in the country during the early 70's. Obama is going to show us what a Jimmy Carter re-election would have looked like. Romney was the next Reagan. Unfortunately, America's affirmative action agenda has turned over the country to uneducated welfare dependent lemmings that are easily manipulated.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472378324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:46:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352472404994-61</Id><Topic><Title>I Think CSCO</Title><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352471881498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They didn't use any of their cash to "juice the divident". They pay a dividend out of current cash flow and bank the rest. Cash on the balance sheet is going up every quarter. Cash has increase $4 billion in the last year. They are kicking the stuffing out of their competitors. Their market share has increased in the last year.</Msg><Username>dewey_duhawk</Username><Timestamp>1352472404994</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:46:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352472548397-62</Id><Title>Greece runs out of cash next week</Title><Msg>Oopsie! Is Obama going to bail them out? Greece has gotten 2 bailouts worth 240 billion euro, voluntary haircuts, etc. and things keep getting worse. Bailouts aren't working and now contagion is everywhere. Default is the only option.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472548397</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:49:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352472623923-63</Id><Topic><Title>I Think CSCO</Title><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352471881498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wait for $11 or $13 by March. Might get there sooner.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472623923</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:50:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352472683839-64</Id><Topic><Title>I Think CSCO</Title><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352471881498</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:38:01 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too many Obama voters at CSCO means CSCO stock is doomed. Chambers needs to go.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472683839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:51:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352472703031-65</Id><Topic><Title>Gas rationing in New York and New Jersey</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472378324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:46:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is going to take all those lemmings right down the tube. Only problem is the rest of us are going too,LOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352472703031</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:51:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352472796591-66</Id><Title>Looks Like A Morning Pump And Dump</Title><Msg>as a hedge fund exits after JPM downgrade.</Msg><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352472796591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:53:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352472816232-67</Id><Topic><Title>Special Dividend ?</Title><Username>grantuphill</Username><Timestamp>1352396037994</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 12:33:57 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is going to tax the sheet out of dividends and stocks. Wait for the special dividend in December and then get out before December 21, 2012.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472816232</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:53:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352473279629-68</Id><Title>Congressional Priorities, 1)congressional paychk, 2) personal benefits, 3) non stop reelection campaigning</Title><Msg>4)cronies needs and wants, 5)lobbyists needs ands wants, 6) partys needs and wants...Country comes last.</Msg><Username>gliderpilot7777</Username><Timestamp>1352473279629</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:01:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352473457087-69</Id><Topic><Title>Looks Like A Morning Pump And Dump</Title><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352472796591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:53:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when stock market peaked inventories are building Sell CSCO and buy Groupon -- they have great Brazilian Wax deals. CSCO coupons suk balz.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352473457087</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:04:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352473555473-70</Id><Topic><Title>How many Coffins did GW Bush use up?</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352471282705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:28:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is this George Boosh that Obama blames for everything? Does George Boosh run the country?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352473555473</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:05:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352473862764-71</Id><Topic><Title>How many Coffins did GW Bush use up?</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352471282705</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:28:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama just got reelected. Libs should be happy. Yet here they are still posting and bashing Bush. Silly and juvenile.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352473862764</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:11:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352473864551-72</Id><Title>start with a budget obama.</Title><Msg>then cuts in congress salerys and benifits. they work part time and travel on our dime. also check yourself about airforce 1 use.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352473864551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:11:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352473931272-73</Id><Title>CSCO DOWNGRADED TO</Title><Msg>Neutral from overweight price target 17</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1352473931272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:12:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352474151097-74</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO DOWNGRADED TO</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1352473931272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>missing a decimal point?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352474151097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:15:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352474263628-75</Id><Title>telco's rolling out LTE to new markets. csco providing the infrastructure.....</Title><Msg>pt $22</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352474263628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:17:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352474321880-76</Id><Topic><Title>start with a budget obama.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352473864551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:11:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama don't do budget. Obama all bullsheet all the time. Obama has no plan man. Romney had a good 52 point plan. Obama will adopt Romney's plan because it's exactly what America needs. Obama bashed Romney's plan and said Romney is stupid just to get elected. Obama released a comic book for creating jobs.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352474321880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:18:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352474457146-77</Id><Topic><Title>Gas rationing in New York and New Jersey</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352472378324</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:46:18 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Those celebrating Obama's victory wont be so happy in a year or so when they open their 401ks.You judge people by their performance. His handling of the economy so far gives you an indication of what to expect in the future.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352474457146</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:20:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352474772631-78</Id><Title>We need a national debt tax of 5% on all purchases...</Title><Msg>Then extend the Bush tax rate for the next 4 years. Install a national debt sales tax of 5% on all purchases. By doing this, you collect from ALL AMERICANS! This would end all the class warfare #$%$ and get us to act as one nation instead of all this divisiness. Small and large business could then plan ahead knowing they won't be burdened by increased taxes. Then look at the corporate tax rate and get corporations like GE to pay their fair share. And finally, through attrition, cut every gov dept by 10%.</Msg><Username>mkymantle07</Username><Timestamp>1352474772631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:26:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475035116-79</Id><Topic><Title>Let the Layoffs begin: OFFICIAL LAYOFF THREAD</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352405610331</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 15:13:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>xide to lay off 150 workers Thu Nov 08 2012 22:45:00 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 5 replies Reading Eagles News Daily ^ | 11/9/12 Exide Technologies announced Thursday that it will be idling its lead-recycling operations in Laureldale and laying off 150 workers, effective no later than March 31. Idling means that all of the permits and approvals will be kept up to date and the plant will be maintained in case Exide wants to reopen it later, said Susan Jaramillo, spokeswoman for Exide. The plant has been operating since the 1930s, Exide said. The company will continue to operate its plastics-recycling business with about 25 employees. TE Connectivity to close Guilford plant, lay off 620 Thu Nov 08 2012 22:41:49 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 3 replies Biz Journal ^ | 11/9/12 TE Connectivity, which makes electrical connectors for appliances and other devices, will close its factory in north High Point and eliminate 620 jobs, according to a company official. The closure and layoffs will happen in phases through the end of 2013, said Tom Peacock, a spokesman for the Pennsylvania-based firm said. TE Connectivity (NYSE: TEL) was known as Tyco Electronics until a name-change in 2011. Peacock said the closure of the facility will not impact the company’s other Triad facilities, and 50 employees from the closing factory will be transferred locally. More Layoffs for Major Wind Company (3,000 Jobs Cut) Thu Nov 08 2012 22:38:17 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 3 replies Oregon Public Broadcasting ^ | 11/9/12 A global wind company with offices in the Pacific Northwest has announced more layoffs. Vestas says it will cut an additional 3,000 jobs by the end of 2013. That nearly doubles the number of jobs the wind turbine company had planned to eliminate. Most recently Vestas it would layoff 3,700 people by the end of 2012. Vestas has not said where jobs will be cut from its global workforce, though some of the job eliminations happen as the company sells off some manufacturing facilities. That means workers will be employed through a different company. Vestas’ North American sales and service... Cigna to Lay Off 1,300 Workers Worldwide Thu Nov 08 2012 22:34:50 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 6 replies KTEN-TV ^ | 11/9/12 DENISON,TX--- One international company with local offices will be eliminating jobs. Cigna announced November 1st that 1,300 jobs will be cut worldwide now through June 2013. A cigna rep says only a small number of these jobs will in Denison. He says most of the layoffs will occur in Europe. "The largest impact in the United States is going to be in our home state, where our headquarters is, in Connecticut of about 200 people. Then all the other actions are going to be smaller and spread throughout all of our offices and operations throughout the United States," Cigna Corporation's. Ameridose to lay off hundreds of workers Thu Nov 08 2012 22:32:23 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 4 replies Boston Herald ^ | 11/9/12 The shuttered sister company of the Framingham pharmacy at the center of the nation’s deadly meningitis outbreak is laying off hundreds of workers, including many permanently, as it struggles under a temporary closing order issued last month amid questions about its sterility process. Westboro-based Ameridose LLC notified workers in a letter that it would begin a “mass layoff” starting tomorrow, a process that will affect roughly 650 workers at the company and another 140 at the marketing company, Medical Sales Management, with which it works directly. The companies have the same owners as New England Compounding Center, the Framingham company... Energizer to Slash Workforce by 10% – Or About 1,500 Jobs Thu Nov 08 2012 22:27:06 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time) · by My Favorite Headache · 12 replies Gateway Pundit ^ | 11/9/12 Energizer announced today it will layoff 10% of its workforce. 1,500 will be affected. Plants in Missouri and Vermont are slated for closure. StL Today reported: Energizer Holdings Inc. will reduce its global workforce by more than 10 percent — or about 1,500 employees — as the company closes three manufacturing plants and streamlines other operations. The moves are part of a companywide restructuring plan for the maker of batteries and personal care items such as Schick razors and Playtex tampons. Energizer said Thursday it plans to save about $200 million in annual pre-tax savings through the changes</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352475035116</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:30:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475212797-80</Id><Topic><Title>We need a national debt tax of 5% on all purchases...</Title><Username>mkymantle07</Username><Timestamp>1352474772631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:26:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your plan makes more sense than what we are getting out of Washington.However the Obama voters like things just the way they are. Half of us supporting the other half.....their half.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352475212797</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:33:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475493158-81</Id><Topic><Title>start with a budget obama.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352473864551</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:11:04 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's holds all the cards , tax the rich or sequester Jan. 1st,one or the other will happen,.Boehner has nothing to negotiate with,it's over before it starts.Sequester originated with the Obama administration,then submitted to the Senate,then congress,Boehiner &amp; congress passed the sequester playing right into Obama's hands,Boehiner has been out played.,best and only option tax the rich,once they get hammered they can join the crowd in socialist wagon,let the other guy pull</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1352475493158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:38:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475585320-82</Id><Topic><Title>You can't beat Santa Claus , Obama bribed the 49% with presents</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352414996715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:49:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A lot of people are losing their jobs for Christmas, coal in their stocking instead of gold.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352475585320</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:39:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475712213-83</Id><Topic><Title>telco's rolling out LTE to new markets. csco providing the infrastructure.....</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352474263628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just saw a story that said Telcos weren't going to spend. Please tell me the title of your story so I can search it out, Or copy and paste it here.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352475712213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:41:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352475928261-84</Id><Topic><Title>telco's rolling out LTE to new markets. csco providing the infrastructure.....</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352474263628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda, AT &amp; T just announced a couple days ago they were increasing CAPEX spending 16% to 22 billion next year.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352475928261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:45:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352475954631-85</Id><Title>Chambers to Resign</Title><Msg>Chambers needs to retire leaving any golden chute with the company! Over the last 3 years he has demonstrated that he has lost the magic touch in leading CSCO to a bright and prosper future. His 5 billion dollar acquisition of NDS Group that's a provider of video software is his latest mistake @ shareholders expense. Think back to the half billion dollar blunder purchase he made with the Flip phone camera from Pure Digital for a cool $590 million. Let's stanch the flow of losses and secure his resignation immediately!</Msg><Username>timber103</Username><Timestamp>1352475954631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:45:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352476585915-86</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO DOWNGRADED TO</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1352473931272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont you just love these criminals who have their overweight rating ON until the stock FALLS 15% and then they lower it. Criminals at work, sad fact for the retail investor. J.P. Morgan analyst Rod Hall this morning cut his rating on Cisco Systems shares to Neutral from Overweight, chopping his target on the stock to $17, from $21. The stock closed Thursday at $16.83. Hall asserted that 2013 is likely to be a difficult year for Cisco due to weak enterprise IT spending, software government spending and the ongoing economic issues in Europe. He also sees long-term competitive risks from the rise of soft-defined networks. Hall asserted that January quarter guidance could disappoint the Street. He advised investors to swap into Ciena or Qualcomm.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352476585915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352476763042-87</Id><Topic><Title>Chambers to Resign</Title><Username>timber103</Username><Timestamp>1352475954631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:45:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>everyone on here has been bringing up the fact the jerk needs to go asap to no avail . they need him there because he is the best reason the stock goes nowhere and it seems that is what the bod wants .</Msg><Username>composerx1</Username><Timestamp>1352476763042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:59:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352476765885-88</Id><Topic><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The BUSH RECESSION ended almost 4 years ago. By definition there would be no 'double dip'. the last double dip recession was under REAGAN.</Msg><Username>melissa99999999999999</Username><Timestamp>1352476765885</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:59:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352477250965-89</Id><Topic><Title>Chambers to Resign</Title><Username>timber103</Username><Timestamp>1352475954631</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:45:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Internally they don't want to stock to go up. They count on the share buyback to make their numbers. They also need lower price to issue MORE options and then they temporarily get a little bullish so they can UNLOAD. The ponzi scheme continues.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352477250965</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:07:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352477272250-90</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO DOWNGRADED TO</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1352473931272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's a big chop - from 21 to 17.</Msg><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352477272250</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:07:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352477598240-91</Id><Title>Simpson-Bowles super committee</Title><Msg>you know why Obama never acted on Simpson-Bowles,because he had his sequester,that's what Obama wants SEQUESTER everybody pay.New tax revenue will not go to reduce deficit.he's a screwed socialist.FEAR ALL POLITICIANS</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1352477598240</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:13:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352477644640-92</Id><Title>Ya think we'll see a budget...</Title><Msg>...sometime in the next 4 years? Or is the jug-eared clown going to talk about bipartisanship until his lame duck term ends?</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352477644640</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:14:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352477683462-93</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO DOWNGRADED TO</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1352473931272</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:12:11 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We just had a month long HAIRCUT from $19.75 to $16.83 and this BOZO comes out after the 15% dive and then downgrades. I think more of these guys should be going to jail. Do you honestly think they waited UNTIL NOW to tell their clients to SELL????? No wonder the retail investor has left the market.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352477683462</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:14:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352478486148-94</Id><Title>Cisco Has A Leaker</Title><Msg>and an ex-CIA guy is trying to find out who it is.</Msg><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352478486148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:28:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352479596028-95</Id><Topic><Title>all the inbreds have crawled back under their rocks</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352478960525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:36:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dont you have a job? fn loser.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352479596028</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:46:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480021339-96</Id><Topic><Title>I LOVE THE WHINE OF CASTRATED TEABILLYS IN THE MORNING</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352472622466</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:50:22 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is a great thing. And to think they will suffer for 4 years. What a gift !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352480021339</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:53:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480051011-97</Id><Topic><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fiscal cliff is a bunch of crap. acually if you look back in history when the government shuts down the economy does well. washington is out of the way and greedy politicians cant get in the way of business. Obama better watch out because GOP wants gov to shut down...and yes you will get your SS checks dont let obama lie to you. this market is a result of headwinds ahead. higher taxes debt gov in the way, obamas robinhood policies...does not help the economy. even benny cant prit his way out. so the talking heads on TV are full of it. fiscal cliff is good for markets. when gov cant do anything to business and people.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480051011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:54:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480110990-98</Id><Topic><Title>Solving fiscal cliff does not stop the recession</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352471092027</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 09:24:52 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>double dip coming look for a 40% correction at least...see japan.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480110990</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:55:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480448845-99</Id><Topic><Title>all the inbreds have crawled back under their rocks</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352478960525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:36:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am embarrassed for you since you are too dumb to see how dumb you really sound. get a job idiot. what a waste of a human life.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480448845</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:00:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352480449770-100</Id><Title>Lonesome boy still pleading</Title><Msg>Poor Junior still crying out for companionship!! HILARIOUS!!! TOOOOOOOOOO FUNNNEEEEEEEEE!! Will somebody please just post and tell him what a butthead he is!! He'll love it LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352480449770</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:00:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480569562-101</Id><Topic><Title>You can't beat Santa Claus , Obama bribed the 49% with presents</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352414996715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:49:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda since you have never worked a day in your life, or paid a penny in income taxes I find it offensive you should think you have any say in how my tax dollars are spent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352480569562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:02:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480853604-102</Id><Topic><Title>You can't beat Santa Claus , Obama bribed the 49% with presents</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352414996715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:49:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well said.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480853604</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:07:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480867932-103</Id><Topic><Title>all the inbreds have crawled back under their rocks</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352478960525</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:36:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney people on this board have shown more class in losing than Surf,Junior,Magoo,and others have in winning.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352480867932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:07:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480880446-104</Id><Topic><Title>You can't beat Santa Claus , Obama bribed the 49% with presents</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352414996715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:49:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no obama shut down coal this year it will be IOUs</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480880446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:08:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352480970758-105</Id><Topic><Title>You can't beat Santa Claus , Obama bribed the 49% with presents</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352414996715</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 17:49:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so these are facts you made up in your head? dumb knows what rhonda pays in taxes hahahahahahahahahahaha like to see sarah the condom begging ho paid in taxes.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352480970758</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:09:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352481329925-106</Id><Topic><Title>4 more years</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352426541828</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:02:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the tragedy is neither party will act civil towards one another. Both seem to be in each others face. We have run defeciets for yrs. but the magnitude has grown under each president. The basic problem is that no one wants there pork program cut or their benefit cut--everyone from food stamp people to military mfrs......i.m.o.f.w.i.w.</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1352481329925</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352481689932-107</Id><Title>Romney outspent Obama 40 to 1,,,Buying Election??</Title><Msg>and He failed.....totally...miserably,,,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352481689932</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:21:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352481769125-108</Id><Title>Notice, Republicans just Don't Evolve</Title><Msg>Edelstein still mimicking Fox News</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352481769125</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:22:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352481928354-109</Id><Topic><Title>What about Benghazi?</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352428442139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but was it Obama or someone else who was negligent? That is the purpose of the hearing am I not correct? So, the point is why put the finger on him until the facts are in?</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1352481928354</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:25:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482125449-110</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352482125449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:28:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482214482-111</Id><Topic><Title>SECOND NIGHT OF REPUBLICAN SUICIDE WATCH !</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352445590356</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 02:19:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like we lost Flutie !!! Walter go next door and check Flutie's trailer. BWWWWWWAHAHAHAHAHAHAAHAHAHAH</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352482214482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:30:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352482251153-112</Id><Title>Dont let us down again</Title><Msg>I was hoping Obama would lose.But he won and now I wish him success.Not for him,for me and my family.I think he's been a terrible president and will continue to be. But if he continues to fail that hurts everybody. So I'm hoping he surprises me and finally gets a clue as to what a president should do. If the country is doing good, chances are my family is doing good. And thats what its all about.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352482251153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:30:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482302500-113</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you have to understand pukes, they don't know if they agree to it or not yet. First it has to happen (doesn't matter what it is) then pukes will KNOW Obama did the wrong thing. Then they will tune into Rush and find out why they outraged.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352482302500</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:31:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482451556-114</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Beachkahuna and Surf are the same poster....dumbivan probably is too.Really phony and childish.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352482451556</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352482480053-115</Id><Title>I voted 4 Obama because I hate whites, and don't care about America</Title><Msg>Nor anything else.</Msg><Username>beaner9576</Username><Timestamp>1352482480053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482573895-116</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Waiting for you whining HYPOCRITES who called Bush a warmonger to call O'Loser a warmonger for his WARS. Let's start from the beginning.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352482573895</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:36:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482719901-117</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb Dumb and BOYsurfer ARE the same poster. Surf forgot he was posting under the Dumb Dumb ID and told everyone to vote for Gary Johnson. Surf has been backing Johnson for awhile now. These kids are as dumb as a doorknob.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352482719901</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:38:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352482826936-118</Id><Topic><Title>Dont let us down again</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352482251153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:30:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree Carey and I hope you are right.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352482826936</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:40:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352483012955-119</Id><Topic><Title>What about Benghazi?</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352428442139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So you are condoning the government LYING to the AMerican people when it suits them politically. Is that what you are saying? I don't have a problem with making mistakes, I don't like them, but everyone is guilty of that. I WON'T condone lying to the American people. PERIOD</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352483012955</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:43:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352483056488-120</Id><Topic><Title>Dont let us down again</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352482251153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:30:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good post,Carey. Family before politics</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352483056488</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:44:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352483309880-121</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only in your alternate reality are we the same poster, but I did encourage voters, who didn't support Obama, to vote for Johnson, if the vote was for Johnson or Romney I would have voted for the guy who didn't want to start another middle east war (Johnson)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352483309880</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:48:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352483614114-122</Id><Topic><Title>telco's rolling out LTE to new markets. csco providing the infrastructure.....</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352474263628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I must have been concentrating too much on the elections and missed that. Thanks, your post is much more helpful because it has at least a citation of who, what, when and how much, The original post lacked any specifics. I wish Yahoo would allow links to stories, so people could gather more facts. I try to post pastes of articles. Sometimes its tough getting rid of advertising.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352483614114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:53:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352483629282-123</Id><Topic><Title>OK REPUKES GET ON THE RECORD: IF OBAMA BOMBS IRAN AFTER THIS DRONE ATTACK...</Title><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1352442998144</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 01:36:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So now Surf,dumdum,and Rational all supported Johnson?? Wonder how many other Magoo ids feel that way.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352483629282</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:53:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352484107310-124</Id><Topic><Title>Dont let us down again</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352482251153</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:30:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior continues to show why no one wants anything to do with him.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352484107310</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:01:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352484733613-125</Id><Title>Sell Obama speech!!!!!</Title><Msg>SELL!!!</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352484733613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:12:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352484811233-126</Id><Topic><Title>telco's rolling out LTE to new markets. csco providing the infrastructure.....</Title><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1352474263628</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 10:17:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By Sinead Carew (Reuters) - AT&amp;T Inc will boost capital spending by about 16 percent to $22 billion a year for the next three years to upgrade its wireless and wireline networks, the company said on Wednesday. Its shares fell more than 3 percent after the news. Rival Verizon Communications Inc is ahead in high-speed mobile services, and AT&amp;T also must improve rural phone lines, comprised of outdated copper technology. The company said it hopes the investments will boost revenue growth by allowing it to chase new opportunities such as adding wireless connections to cars and home security. AT&amp;T said upgrading its wireline network was more attractive than carving off the business or divesting parts of the network. Previously, it said it was considering selling some rural phone lines. "This gives us the opportunity to improve our top-line growth and change our cost structure," Chief Executive Randall Stephenson told analysts at an AT&amp;T event in New York. Investors worried about the spending hike from AT&amp;T's 2012 capital budget for $19 billion to $20 billion, although the company vowed to come in at the low end of the range this year. "It's a big number and it's not just for one year," Hudson Square Research analyst Todd Rethemeier said.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352484811233</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:13:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352485013979-127</Id><Topic><Title>Sell Obama speech!!!!!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352484733613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:12:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama didn't waste any time telling everyone it's his way or the highway. America voted, and we have to live with ANOTHER 4 years of DIVIDED government. WOW</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352485013979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:16:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352485281621-128</Id><Title>Obama Regime, 1457 Days Left...</Title><Msg>...and counting</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352485281621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:21:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352485576591-129</Id><Title>Markets ROLLING OVER</Title><Msg>After Obama's speech. Nobody in the business world has any faith in this man. The dumb people RULE. Good job AMerica.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352485576591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:26:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352485743382-130</Id><Topic><Title>What about Benghazi?</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1352428442139</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 21:34:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This mess wasn't started by Obama. It was his underlings at the State Dept.namely Charlene Lamb. She was the one who denied increased security at Benghazi. But as this fiasco worked its way up the ladder more and more people got involved. Does this include Obama?? He wont say anything so we dont know.That only leads to suspicion. An investigation is the only way of finding out what really happened.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352485743382</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:29:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486045800-131</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ROLLING OVER</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352485576591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:26:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gonna be a big run on food stamps and free cellphones.Better sign up now.lol</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352486045800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:34:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352486062851-132</Id><Title>Obama Spoke CSCO is up!</Title><Msg>Close $18++++</Msg><Username>fixedforlife</Username><Timestamp>1352486062851</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:34:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486097491-133</Id><Topic><Title>Sell Obama speech!!!!!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352484733613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:12:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP House members must never allow Obama tax hike on top earners; instead,tax everyone in a fair, equal way. Taxing top 2% will solve nothing in itself.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352486097491</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:34:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486173947-134</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ROLLING OVER</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352485576591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:26:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the spending is what needs cut and both sides will never agree to some types of cuts. Looks grim, IMHO.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352486173947</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:36:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352486198836-135</Id><Title>SEALs Punished for Leaking Secrets</Title><Msg>only the white house can do that! they know better who is expendable like Brian Terry, Glen Doherty, Christopher Stevens, Sean Smith and others! Who will be the next sacrificial lamb to the master? Who knows what evil lurks in the hearts of men? The Shadow knows!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1352486198836</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:36:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486264926-136</Id><Topic><Title>Sell Obama speech!!!!!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352484733613</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:12:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>His tax the rich is ideology only. Its a drop in the ocean compared to our debt.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352486264926</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:37:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486537177-137</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Has A Leaker</Title><Username>porkypiggins</Username><Timestamp>1352478486148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 11:28:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come on now ! Everyone knows cisco is the Southern border of the internet and has more back doors then A Chinese maker of Cisco equipment telephone book has people by the last name of Chin in it. But it's possible as well that the Leaker is an Illegal hire in San "JOSE" named jose and the ex-CIA person is former illegal MOOOOSLIME MOLE spy.</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486537177</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:42:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352486629697-138</Id><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Msg>Hope and Change Chapter 2 coming to all you people who voted for the great divider. He hasn't learner a thing. SAD</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352486699134-139</Id><Title>NEW RUSH AMNESTY PROGRAM</Title><Msg>Instant amnesty but you can't vote for 25 years. If dems don't call that RACIST, then DEMS are NUTS and have something wrong with them. But then again, The dems are for and care about illegals right....???</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486699134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:44:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486889914-140</Id><Topic><Title>Markets ROLLING OVER</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352485576591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:26:16 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama now has the repubs by the short hairs.They'll make a lot of noise but as the deadline approaches they'll cave and Obama will get pretty much what he wants. And the market wont like that</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352486889914</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:48:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352486933817-141</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>middle class drones who bought his promises are going to get pinched. what a shame. more blame and hate less compromise. children will be burning our metro areas down when it is all said and done.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352486933817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:48:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352486991859-142</Id><Title>rich leaving the country</Title><Msg>mass exodus. already happening and corps following.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352486991859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:49:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487158447-143</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The sheit ALWAYS rolls downhill folks. When the rich get hurt and the middle class work for the rich, GUESS WHAT HAPPENS. People will never learn, the snakeoil salesman wins again. SIGH</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352487158447</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:52:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487175225-144</Id><Topic><Title>I voted 4 Obama because I hate whites, and don't care about America</Title><Username>beaner9576</Username><Timestamp>1352482480053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you need to get a job loser.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487175225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:52:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352487289163-145</Id><Title>Because of Obama's reelection scores of companies laying off employees</Title><Msg>Over the days following President Obama's re-election, the US stock market has undergone a two day sell-off resulting in a loss of over 400 points. On Wednesday, immediately following the election, the market suffered it greatest single day loss of the year. While numerous experts point to the Europe debt crisis or an approaching fiscal cliff in the US as the culprit, many business owners have indicated Obama's re-election as a direct cause of the faltering business climate and loss of confidence. One Las Vegas business owner, after having warned his employees of a certain lay-off if Obama were re-elected, followed through with his ominous threat dropping one fifth of his work force in anticipation of a worsening environment. The following is a list of companies which have announced layoffs directly as a result of President Obama's re-election. Many contracting businesses have indicated that the impending implementation of Obamacare, a looming threat of tax increases, and an overall anti-business environment will now prevail and perhaps even get worse, over the next four years prompting a defensive stance. List of layoffs and closings courtesy of the website The Blaze: Westinghouse - Research in Motion Limited - Lightyear Network Solutions - • Providence Journal - • Hawker Beechcraft - • Boeing (30% of their management staff) - • CVPH Medical Center - • US Cellular - • Momentive Performance Materials - • Rocketdyne - • Brake Parts - • Vestas Wind Systems - • Husqvarna - • Center for Hospice New York - • Bristol-Meyers - • OCE North America - • Darden Restaurants - • United Blood Services Gulf Various Offices which will be closing as a result of re-election: Caterpillar Inc. will close its plant in Owatonna Minn. Mount Pleasant’s Albrecht Sentry Foods The Target store at Manassas Mall Va. Millennium Academy in Wake Forest NC Target Closing Kissimmee FL Location The Andover Gift Shop in Andover MA Grand Union Family Markets Closing Storrs Location CT Movie Scene Milford Location NH Update: TE Connectivity Closing Greensboro Plant – 620 Layoffs Expected Gomer’s Fried Chicken in South Kansas City Kmart in Homer Glen Fresh Market on Pine Street in Burlington AGC Glass North America to permanently close its Blue Ridge Plant in Kingsport Tenn. The Target store at Platte and Academy in Colorado Springs The Roses store on Reynold Road in Winston-Salem NC Meanders Kitchen losing its West Seattle location at 6032 California Ave Bost Harley-Davidson at 46th Avenue North and Delaware Ave. in West Nashville TN Townsend Booksellers in Oakland The Kmart store in Parkway Plaza off University Drive in Durham NC Elections have consequences. Obama has demonized business, passed regulations that make earning a profit hard, and his planned taxes and mandates have business going out of business. People get the Government they deserve.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487289163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:54:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352487385564-146</Id><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Msg>SAN FRANCISCO (AP) — San Francisco is preparing to become the first U.S. city to provide and cover the cost of sex reassignment surgeries for uninsured transgender residents.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487545095-147</Id><Topic><Title>I voted 4 Obama because I hate whites, and don't care about America</Title><Username>beaner9576</Username><Timestamp>1352482480053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As long as the 51% pay your way you can mooch and post here. But what if the Doctors retire, the businesses retrench, the rich move their money to gold, silver and bank in Singapore where the money is safe? You spoke like an Obama Patriot, you want to kill the Golden Goose and when you eat the Goose's carcass you will starve because all the food will be gone.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487545095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:59:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487579011-148</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior had his tonsils removed to keep from getting pregnant.....dummy.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352487579011</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:59:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487624591-149</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He still won't get laid, you have to look good and have a personality to get laid</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487624591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:00:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487847142-150</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior has an 8 x10 glossy of Obama and a strong right hand. Says his sex life is great.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1352487847142</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:04:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487859596-151</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>makes sense why it needs so many ids. It is not sure what it is.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487859596</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:04:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352487953957-152</Id><Topic><Title>rich leaving the country</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352486991859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Deadman , they might leave but before that happens they will convert their USD to some currency that will not be devalued or they will go to metals, diamonds etc. Money will be sent overseas and their investments will be made through shells so that the rich won't pay Obama's Tax hikes. If you think the rich got that way by not knowing how to protect their assets from governmental theft. And if they get tired of the Obama administration raiding their wallet they will sell their houses and move to Australia or Singapore</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487953957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:05:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352488011846-153</Id><Topic><Title>I voted 4 Obama because I hate whites, and don't care about America</Title><Username>beaner9576</Username><Timestamp>1352482480053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well said. they will learn. even shorting the market after 2012 wont make sense. huge sell off is coming before year end.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352488011846</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:06:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352488049473-154</Id><Topic><Title>Because of Obama's reelection scores of companies laying off employees</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487289163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nobody is hiring, and 23 million are already out of a job.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352488049473</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:07:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352488127972-155</Id><Topic><Title>rich leaving the country</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352486991859</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:49:51 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>already are. I have been trying to sell the business to avoid cap gaind tax hikes next year.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352488127972</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:08:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352488599513-156</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior has a terrible anal leakage problem due to his many weekends spent at Maurices Bathhouse. Wonder if insurance will pay for surgery to " tighten "him up a little.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352488599513</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:16:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352489087432-157</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And what about his alter ego Goo?</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352489087432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:24:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352489126969-158</Id><Topic><Title>$== 13 INDICATOR CSCO BUY/SELL/HOLD REPORT ==$</Title><Username>danwilliam291</Username><Timestamp>1351177026980</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-10-25 10:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great picks</Msg><Username>milleramando</Username><Timestamp>1352489126969</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:25:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352489194869-159</Id><Title>Didn't Nugent say he'd be dead or in jail if Obama wins?</Title><Msg>We're waiting nugent.</Msg><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1352489194869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:26:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352489406366-160</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it will be fun to watch what happens in the wake of it getting what it wanted. the next four years will be miserable for americans. higher taxes and a fed doing everything it can to de-value the dollar spells doom and gloom for the quality of life. this is why we have to take care of them because they dont understand cause and effect. they hear free ice cream and are all for it. still waiting for that free ice cream they are.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352489406366</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352489649676-161</Id><Title>riots in socialist Argentina</Title><Msg>President Fernando De la Rua resigned and fled the government palace in a helicopter, driven from office by a devastating economic crisis and days of rioting that left 22 people dead and homes and supermarkets across Argentina ransacked. De la Rua's sudden downfall yesterday came amid Argentina's worst unrest in a decade. Screeching tear gas canisters arced across the capital and police fired rubber bullets at thousands of anti-government protesters in the runup to his fall. socialist USA will be next</Msg><Username>obvaccdismf</Username><Timestamp>1352489649676</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:34:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352489679120-162</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What about the 3 million+ fools who decided not to vote, they STILL VOTED for Obama... The buggers chose not to vote on some kind of principle, that they were going to teach the Republican Party something - Yeeeeeeeeeeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah, riiiiIIIIIIIIiiiiiiiiight. Now we're stuck for another 1,457 days with the worse president in U.S. history...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352489679120</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:34:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352490544431-163</Id><Topic><Title>Mormon Harry Reid Attacking Romneys religion.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1348597176061</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-25 14:19:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Buuuuuuuuuuuuuuuurp</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352490544431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:49:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352490555817-164</Id><Topic><Title>Didn't Nugent say he'd be dead or in jail if Obama wins?</Title><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1352489194869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:26:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Ted is with all those stars who said they'd leave if Bush was elected again.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352490555817</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:49:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352490782141-165</Id><Topic><Title>AAAAAAAAAHAAAAHAHAHAHAHA ...</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352302250558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:30:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once you go Barack, you never go back. :D</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352490782141</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:53:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352490902839-166</Id><Topic><Title>I voted 4 Obama because I hate whites, and don't care about America</Title><Username>beaner9576</Username><Timestamp>1352482480053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 12:34:40 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah,,Put Whites on Reservations and give then Casinos</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352490902839</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:55:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352491021616-167</Id><Topic><Title>NEW RUSH AMNESTY PROGRAM</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486699134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:44:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White People are the Immigrant Haters,,,,you would Think whitey is from this part of the World,,,but they are NOT</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1352491021616</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:57:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352491036160-168</Id><Topic><Title>Parallels between Clinton/Gore '92 and Romney/Ryan '12</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1346707019418</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-09-03 17:16:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now to do sumthin about Skinflute and the other right-wing SOCIOPATHS lurking on this hyere board...</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352491036160</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:57:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491103808-169</Id><Title>There's a reason Jimmy Carter only served ONE TERM</Title><Msg>And it doesn't explain why the jug-eared clown deserves two</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352491103808</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:58:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352491203520-170</Id><Topic><Title>AAAAAAAAAHAAAAHAHAHAHAHA ...</Title><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352302250558</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-11-07 10:30:50 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks you're really enjoying that long butt plug surferboy gave you last night</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352491203520</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:00:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491493229-171</Id><Title>Where is the guy Pribius from Wisconsin</Title><Msg>Somebody shut mouth of the little pervert.</Msg><Username>doctor_hardon</Username><Timestamp>1352491493229</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:04:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352491576693-172</Id><Topic><Title>Dead pig wearing Romney shirt left outside California GOP office</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352491094441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you ever think about how people see you by what you post? Do you have any respect for yourself?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352491576693</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:06:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491610540-173</Id><Title>He has nothing more to say, no more "cool" factor, and....</Title><Msg>his looks are tired and worn out. The jug-eared clown will soon not want to be watched, listened to, and taken seriously by fewer and fewer(anyone really take him seriously now?). As his second term grinds on, he will become even more of an annoyance if that's possible, then the media will turn on him. All of this will happen imperceptibly slow, but it WILL happen. Can't wait.. :-)</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352491610540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:06:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352491703287-174</Id><Topic><Title>Didn't Nugent say he'd be dead or in jail if Obama wins?</Title><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1352489194869</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:26:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're also still waiting for the closing of Gitmo, how's about you?</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352491703287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:08:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491741476-175</Id><Title>BIGGEST LOSERS - Election Day 2012</Title><Msg>#1 - Myth Robbedme - Ain"t never, ever, EVER gonna be Prez, no way, no how. #2 - Lyin' Ryan - Ditto (see #1). He's just lucky he'll have a gubmint pension to fall back on in his later years. #3 - Karl "Miss Piggy" Rove - (Koch Brothers, in an ominous, raspy, metallic baritone duet (but w/ a probounced southern drawl)). "You have failed me for the last time..." Heh.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352491741476</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:09:01 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491835225-176</Id><Title>Final hour should be interesting</Title><Msg>Shorts are filled up and thinking we end with another LOSS on Friday. Any kind of buying spurt could send the shorts scurring and give the market a pretty good close. Ifs and buts</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352491835225</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:10:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352491994033-177</Id><Title>Obama's CIA director has affair, resigns!</Title><Msg>Did he have the affair with a foreign national (spy)???</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352491994033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:13:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352492129215-178</Id><Title>Petraeus, snapshot of a liberal</Title><Msg>Making staff females have all the sex the boss says</Msg><Username>gaga.getty</Username><Timestamp>1352492129215</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:15:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352492313529-179</Id><Title>Obama's CIA director RESIGNS</Title><Msg>Are the dominos beginning to tumble? CIA Director Petraeus resigns, says he had an affair, maybe it's Benghazi related instead. WHO knows, nobody in this administration tells the truth.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352492313529</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:18:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492349646-180</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Huge signal to the middle class to STOP working "for" the rich, and start working for THEMSELVES. Most of the "rich" I've had the displeasure of coming into contact with over the years couldn't so much as inflate their own tires without professional assistance. (Alas, alackaday, the same doesn't hold for inflating their own EGOs...)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352492349646</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:19:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492383040-181</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's CIA director has affair, resigns!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352491994033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:13:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was busy doinking and didn't have time for people DYING in Benghazi.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352492383040</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:19:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492504941-182</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's CIA director has affair, resigns!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352491994033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:13:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not General BeTrayus? He's a solid Repuke</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1352492504941</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:21:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492558724-183</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOBODY in the middle class WILL EVER get rich under Obumbles. He is making it so NO ONE will want to take a risk with their capital only to have the government just STEAL it away. You people will never learn.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352492558724</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:22:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492688957-184</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Very likely the Ron Paulites who got kicked to the curb by Robbedme/Lyan at the RNC Convention. OH SWEET, SWEET IRONY! (Eh Fergferg? HIGH FIVE!!!)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352492688957</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:24:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492839224-185</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why so glum, Skinfwute? Aaaaahaaaaaa</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352492839224</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:27:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492850562-186</Id><Topic><Title>Dead pig wearing Romney shirt left outside California GOP office</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352491094441</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 14:58:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just another "class act" by some liberal punk. Notice it was done at night with no one around. Real brave!!!</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352492850562</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:27:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492882571-187</Id><Topic><Title>Because of Obama's reelection scores of companies laying off employees</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487289163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When the 911 tax cuts that affect every tax class go up, when Obamacare raise medical coverage by 2,000 buck, when gas climbs because Iran attacks Israel with Nukes or Israel protects herself from attack. When Obama raise the taxes When the layoff raise the deficit And when we get another Obama downgrade You moocher will have to pay your fair share. There is a saying you peckwoods "there is no free lunch" When we go broke like Greece you will be getting religion] at a Salvation Army Soup Kitchen.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352492882571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:28:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352492969691-188</Id><Topic><Title>Dow up 60, Obama speaks, Dow DOWN 20</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352486629697</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:43:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why so *gwum*, Skinfwute?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352492969691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:29:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352493202530-189</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's CIA director has affair, resigns!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352491994033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:13:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He was Obama's CIA director, not Bush's. He also resigned when getting caught dipping his wick in the wrong place. Clinton just lied to us and kept on going.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1352493202530</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352493386818-190</Id><Topic><Title>Because of Obama's reelection scores of companies laying off employees</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352487289163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:54:49 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>//blah blah blah ... at a Salvation Army soup kitchen...// Will Lyan Ryan be (re)washing the pots &amp; pans afterward?</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352493386818</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:36:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352493564362-191</Id><Title>Love is in the air</Title><Msg>This constant flirting Junior is trying to get going with Deadpainting is disgusting!!!!Just because Dead is the only one responding to him Junior has fallen in love!!!! Just plain sickening!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352493564362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:39:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352493816620-192</Id><Title>Cage cleaners will be working overtime this weekend</Title><Msg>As scandalous sex perpetrators ravage our government, the libdem cage cleaners will be creating facades that are unprecedented even as our government has been hijacked by numerous " acceptnâ-pazirs". . Piling on our State Department martyrs it should not be a shock that these perps hidden agendas will be supporting the president who himself is in contempt of the U.S. constitution. Stand by for the imploding left wing media elitist that will continue to present the liar in chief with his hidden agenda to downsize the free world in favor of the Islamist death squads.</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1352493816620</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:43:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352493830287-193</Id><Topic><Title>POLLS: Romney UP 6 in Florida</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1351955898465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AAAAAAAAAAAHAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAAAAAAAAAA!!!!</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352493830287</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:43:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352493941030-194</Id><Title>Westgate CEO who threatened to fire workers if Obama was elected</Title><Msg>instead gave everyone a raise, LOL just to funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352493941030</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:45:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352493947029-195</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You wish. In two years there will be another eruption. You can count on it. The Senate will be GOP.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352493947029</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:45:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352493967128-196</Id><Topic><Title>Love is in the air</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352493564362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will make you equal. He won't raise income taxes. Instead, he's going to do a wealth tax. If you have worked hard and saved money, he's is going to confiscate it so you below equal. A world without jealousy. There is no reason to covet thy neighbors stuff cause it's the same as yours. You are just a gear in the big machine.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352493967128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:46:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494017042-197</Id><Topic><Title>Love is in the air</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352493564362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:39:24 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOPSIE!!! Somebody gave me a thumbs down. Wonder who???LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352494017042</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:46:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494047458-198</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know several former Tea Party politicians who might disagree... (But they're too busy looking for a job just now.)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352494047458</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:47:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352494075872-199</Id><Title>David Siegel, just another racist</Title><Msg>admitted on CNBC that he is better off today than 4 years ago. I think Obama is the first President that everybody knows what he is thinking.</Msg><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352494075872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:47:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494095406-200</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's campaign has been a disaster, worse run than Romney</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1348411491763</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-09-23 10:44:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea baggers like Rhonda still think Romney can pull off a victory, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352494095406</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:48:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494097095-201</Id><Topic><Title>POLLS: Romney UP 6 in Florida</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1351955898465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are still counting votes in Florida -- 10% of the vote is still outstanding. Are they going through the hanging chads? Romney looks to be a couple votes behind Obama.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352494097095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:48:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494184792-202</Id><Topic><Title>NEW RUSH AMNESTY PROGRAM</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486699134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:44:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice try RACE CARD-IST ! My parents were immigrants, legal ones, YOUR COWARD CRIMINAL KIND NOT WANTED OR RESPECTED !!! Todays immigrants don't fool me, maybe several generations of Americans, but NOT me ! GO BUILD YOUR OWN INFRASTRUCTURE THIEF !!! And besides HIPANICS came from South America !!! Liver Alone, Cheese mine !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352494184792</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:49:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494209527-203</Id><Topic><Title>POLLS: Romney UP 6 in Florida</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1351955898465</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-11-03 11:18:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you probably bought CSCO at 60, and still have it. you doppy republican</Msg><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352494209527</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:50:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494214835-204</Id><Topic><Title>Obama's CIA director has affair, resigns!</Title><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352491994033</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:13:14 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this is just another example of why government spending must get cut. This CIA guy and those Secret Service guys spend their time chasing #$%$ on the taxpayer's dime.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1352494214835</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352494457882-205</Id><Title>Libs and dems were right years ago, he did Petraeus !</Title><Msg>Probably with a illegal or moooooslime prostitute ! ha ha !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352494457882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:54:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494694079-206</Id><Topic><Title>NEW RUSH AMNESTY PROGRAM</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352486699134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:44:59 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"[REPUBLICONS ON NATIVE AMERICANS:] i say we put em to work filling in the Bering Strait, then charge em ten bucks a head to walk home." - The Late, Great George Carlin (paraphrased)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352494694079</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494947534-207</Id><Topic><Title>Obama asks Congress to make tax cuts permanent for 98% of Americans and small business</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352494598193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:56:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP is owned by the 1%, unfortunately the baggers are to stupid to realize it</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352494947534</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:02:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352494991824-208</Id><Topic><Title>The Tea Party Experiment Has failed. Badly.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352493466020</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:37:46 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh huh, mos def. (I hope and pray you little numbnuggets keep telling yourselves this shyyt!!!) NAH NAH NAH NAH NAH NAH HEY HEY HEY GOODBYE</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352494991824</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:03:11 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352495253553-209</Id><Topic><Title>Obama asks Congress to make tax cuts permanent for 98% of Americans and small business</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1352494598193</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:56:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama won 8 of the10 wealthiest counties in the U.S. Wonder why the one percenters like him so much??? Maybe you're the stupid one,Magoo. Obama has to be doing SOMETHING for them.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352495253553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:07:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352495306449-210</Id><Topic><Title>David Siegel, just another racist</Title><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352494075872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can say with 100% certainty that Gov. Romney is better off today than, possibly ever! Why? because most of Romneys income comes from dividends, and they are the highest ever.</Msg><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352495306449</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:08:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352495445412-211</Id><Topic><Title>David Siegel, just another racist</Title><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352494075872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:47:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And I say, good for Romney. Wish it was me!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352495445412</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:10:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352495543363-212</Id><Topic><Title>Libs and dems were right years ago, he did Petraeus !</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352494457882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:54:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>RUMOR IS :GOP got wind of the affair and were threating to blackmail the General @ the White Housre if they didn't knuckle under on the "Benbhazi Story"</Msg><Username>rfourdnask</Username><Timestamp>1352495543363</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:12:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352495684205-213</Id><Title>Another day, more market cap lost.</Title><Msg>Dear John Chambers, You are killing the shareholders and YES, it's your fault. You are not selling the street on Cisco's value, in the absence of information, the sell side will OWN you. We can't afford you anymore.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352495684205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:14:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352495795097-214</Id><Topic><Title>DIICK MORRIS expains why Obama will lose bigtime</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1351727722686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:55:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A hopeless alcoholic</Msg><Username>kaptnkirk53</Username><Timestamp>1352495795097</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:16:35 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352496606921-215</Id><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Msg>So Petraeus is resigning, GUESS what that means? He WILL NOT be testifying next week on Benghazi. This has been known and hidden by the Whitehouse all along. My guess is there is NO AFFAIR, he is being forced out and using this as a cover so he doesn't have to testify. The American people have been screwed AGAIN. So the Director of the CIA does not have to testify before congress about a possible Whitehouse coverup because he RESIGNS just days before the hearings. Unbelievable.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352497267785-216</Id><Title>Economy is crushing young people</Title><Msg>And blacks and Latinos. That's the Spanish economy Obama wanted. And this is during the recovery. The next recession has already started. Great job Obama. Prolong the misery 4 more years. Time for another porkulus package. Socialism works great until you run out of other people's money. Obama said he will veto any bill that extends tax cuts for the rich. He wants a recession. No compromise. Obama is going cliff diving. Lean forward and bend over the fiscal cliff. Wheee!!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352497267785</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:41:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352497282878-217</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm not a lawyer, but I thought if you were ordered by congress to testify, you had to show up?? Anybody know for sure???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1352497282878</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:41:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352497755775-218</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There will still be a paper trail regardless of Petraeus.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1352497755775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:49:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352497822710-219</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you are subpoenaed. flute must be on LSD he is so far from reality,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352497822710</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:50:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352497935386-220</Id><Title>The most likely outcome? Eight GOP takeaways and two giveaways for a net gain of six. A 53-47 Senate, just like we have now, only opposite. Barack Obama’s parting gift to the Democratic Party.</Title><Msg>good call Rhonda, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352497935386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:52:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352497966077-221</Id><Topic><Title>The most likely outcome? Eight GOP takeaways and two giveaways for a net gain of six. A 53-47 Senate, just like we have now, only opposite. Barack Obama’s parting gift to the Democratic Party.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352497935386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:52:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like the parting gift part the best, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352497966077</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:52:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352498027515-222</Id><Topic><Title>Libs and dems were right years ago, he did Petraeus !</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352494457882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 15:54:17 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>blackmail seems to be the only policy the GOP has these days</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352498027515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:53:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352498276872-223</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Affair is probably true. If Petraeus was trying to avoid testifying he wouldn't have ruined his reputation and career with a sordid story of cheating. He'd have used ill health or some other excuse. Some reporter probably getting ready to out him and he had to fess up.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352498276872</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:57:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352498504163-224</Id><Title>Obama Resigns Prior to Benghazi Hearings.</Title><Msg>he knows his impeachment is coming you see...</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352498504163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:01:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352498677788-225</Id><Title>Obama threatens veto</Title><Msg>Election is over. Back to the nasty Obama. You got fooled again, sukkas.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352498677788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:04:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352498683523-226</Id><Topic><Title>The most likely outcome? Eight GOP takeaways and two giveaways for a net gain of six. A 53-47 Senate, just like we have now, only opposite. Barack Obama’s parting gift to the Democratic Party.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352497935386</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:52:15 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Long as repubs put up candidates like Angle and ODonnell in 2010 and Akin and Mourdock this time,they wont control the senate. I dont like it but thats the way it is. Sometimes you have to learn the hard way.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352498683523</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:04:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352499192246-227</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Resigns Prior to Benghazi Hearings.</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352498504163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:01:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary and Geithner are leaving. Rats are jumping off the sinking ship. Who else wants out?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352499192246</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:13:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352499245432-228</Id><Topic><Title>Obama threatens veto</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352498677788</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:04:37 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They weren't fooled. They like all the free stuff Obama gives them. You can now get by decently being on the dole. They voted for the guy who'll keep giving it to them.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352499245432</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:14:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352499503012-229</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Resigns Prior to Benghazi Hearings.</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352498504163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:01:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hillary will be replaced by John Kerry. The guy is pure #$%$. As a Nam vet, I hate his guts.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1352499503012</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:18:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352502516800-230</Id><Topic><Title>DIICK MORRIS expains why Obama will lose bigtime</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1351727722686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-10-31 19:55:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>YOU STUPID COW ...BWAAAAAAAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352502516800</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:08:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352502647007-231</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Resigns Prior to Benghazi Hearings.</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352498504163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:01:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see the treatment for delusion is not working. Never stop posting, you amuse me.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352502647007</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:10:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352502673641-232</Id><Title>I LET BARBARA STREISAND AND SEAN PENN DECIDE WHO I VOTE FOR</Title><Msg>I LET BARBARA STREISAND AND SEAN PENN DECIDE WHO I VOTE FOR You can never go wrong with Barbara Streisand or Sean Penn because these celebrities are 1000 times smarter than the average person. Chris Matthews is another sage voting guide.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352502673641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:11:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352502711420-233</Id><Topic><Title>Another day, more market cap lost.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352495684205</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:14:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you going to blame Bush for high unemployment after 8 years of Obama?</Msg><Username>scott4usa</Username><Timestamp>1352502711420</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:11:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352502751332-234</Id><Title>WONDER HOW LONG IT WILL TAKE FOR AMERICANS TO SAY..."JEEESH! WHAT DID I DO?..OBIMBO? WHAT WAS I THINKING</Title><Msg>I hope it only takes about two years, so that when the Senate and House have their round of elections, Tea Party can take more seats. No doubt misery stretches as far as the eye can see....and never fear little Demmies...old Walter, the aging brilliant visionary that helps you drooling dotards see the truth will be right here to point out your misery!! he he he he... Wonder what's going to happen to UnEmployment..UE....well, it's gonna go higher and higher, because Obimbo has no clue how to manage an economy.. OH YEAH, one last point...HIGHER TAXES ON EVERYONE...TAX THE RICH, TAX THE MIDDLE CLASS, TAX THE POOR, BECAUSE WE MUST SEND MORE GOVERNMENT CHECKS TO THE DROOLERS I'm good with that. Tax the crap out of everyone...Democrats! GO FOR IT. Raise taxes so high that no one, especially Brad Pitt, Jon Stewart, and lots of those other goobers can make over 250,000 a year. Boehner will make sure to help Obimbo raised taxes to 100% on everything over 250,000. Go get Spike Lee and Micheal Moore. Those rich guys just have too much money!!! RAISE TAXES!!!! ON THE FILTHY RICH....good. good good good.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352502751332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:12:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352502774931-235</Id><Topic><Title>I LET BARBARA STREISAND AND SEAN PENN DECIDE WHO I VOTE FOR</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352502673641</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:11:13 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You must have voted for Hugo Chavez then.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1352502774931</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:12:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352502829975-236</Id><Title>FROM NOW ON DEMOCRATS WILL WIN EVERY ELECTION BECAUSE GOP = RICH NUTTY WHITE RACIST OLD CODGERS</Title><Msg>From now on democrats will win every election because gop = rich nutty white racist old codgers who are also dumb as rocks.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352502829975</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:13:49 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352502846095-237</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Of course you have to ! But Flutie as usual is clueless. He started hitting the Popoff on Nov 6th at 11:30PM and hasn't stopped drinking. BWWWWWAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAAHAHAAH.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1352502846095</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:14:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352503040854-238</Id><Topic><Title>MORE Whitehouse coverups</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1352496606921</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 16:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CONGRESS has more power than anyone. Even the US President. Boehner has incredible power. He can impeach and fire the President of the United States. Best get along with Cantor and Boehner. Let's watch how this plays out. Even Issa has amazing power. He's running the useless, dangerous Attorney General out of office. What a joke, a dangerous joke Eric Holder has been.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352503040854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:17:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352503103691-239</Id><Title>DICK MORRIS IS NOW A LAUGHING STOCK DUE FOR PREDICTING ROMNEY LANDSLIDE</Title><Msg>Dick morris is now a laughing stock due for predicting romney landslide obama landslide = buffoon morris has no credibility.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352503103691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:18:23 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352503246228-240</Id><Topic><Title>DICK MORRIS IS NOW A LAUGHING STOCK DUE FOR PREDICTING ROMNEY LANDSLIDE</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352503103691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:18:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morris was totally wrong. Guess you can make fun of him because you've never been wrong your whole life, right??</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1352503246228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:20:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352503361337-241</Id><Title>REPUBLICANS WILL CO-OPT HISPANIC VOTE. STARTING WITH RUBIO AND CRUZ....</Title><Msg>its all starting. A good sound whipping will get your attention. Thanks Democrats...you awakened a sleeping giant. 60 million droolers against 57.5 million hard working, smart, insightful, roaring to fight back folks. Worried yet? Unemployment Trillion dollars a year of debt...EVERY FRICKING YEAR...even that senile old Jon Stewart is going to get tired of that, especially when Democrats limit everyone's income to 250,000 a year. I think the House will reluctantly agree to Obama's plan to confiscate all income over 250,000 a year from every American in America...EVERY ONE! Corzine, Stewart, Spike Lee, Edie Murphy, Angelina Jolie, Lady Gaga, all the hedge fund boys...EVERYONE IN AMERICA MAKES NO MORE THAN 250,000 a year until the national is debt is paid down to zero....I'll betcha it'll get paid down quick. THANKS PRESIDENT OBAMA....that's thinking like an American!!!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352503361337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:22:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352503658781-242</Id><Topic><Title>REPUBLICANS WILL CO-OPT HISPANIC VOTE. STARTING WITH RUBIO AND CRUZ....</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352503361337</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:22:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>People with the really big money know how to protect that money. Obama will score some points with the peons who think he's socking it to the big guys but they'll get around it.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352503658781</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:27:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352503725505-243</Id><Topic><Title>DICK MORRIS IS NOW A LAUGHING STOCK DUE FOR PREDICTING ROMNEY LANDSLIDE</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352503103691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:18:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Correctamundo! (But in case you hadn't noticed, Dick Morris had been a laughing stock since circa 1995...)</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1352503725505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:28:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352503951486-244</Id><Title>CHRIS CHRISTIE SAW THE GOODNESS OF OBAMA, SNUBBED ROMNEY AND SHOULD JOIN DEMOCCRAT PARTY</Title><Msg>CHRIS CHRISTIE SAW THE GOODNESS OF OBAMA, SNUBBED ROMNEY AND SHOULD JOIN DEMOCCRAT PARTY to make America a true utopia and paradise.</Msg><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352503951486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:32:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352503983351-245</Id><Topic><Title>DICK MORRIS IS NOW A LAUGHING STOCK DUE FOR PREDICTING ROMNEY LANDSLIDE</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352503103691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:18:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who do you think has done better since 1995, you or Morris? How many ids do you use??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352503983351</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:33:03 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352504072254-246</Id><Topic><Title>CHRIS CHRISTIE SAW THE GOODNESS OF OBAMA, SNUBBED ROMNEY AND SHOULD JOIN DEMOCCRAT PARTY</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352503951486</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:32:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you eat those "special"mushrooms??</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352504072254</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:34:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352504502446-247</Id><Topic><Title>DICK MORRIS IS NOW A LAUGHING STOCK DUE FOR PREDICTING ROMNEY LANDSLIDE</Title><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352503103691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:18:23 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BUT OUR JOBS ISN'T TO PREDICT ELECTION WINNERS, that's what DORK MORRIS CLAIMS HIS JOB IS! HE STAKES HIS REPUTATION ON IT, you idiot!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352504502446</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:41:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352504598293-248</Id><Topic><Title>Rhonda_Edelstein likes to believe hack political analysts like DORK MORRIS</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352424500032</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:28:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>now loser REPUKES will whine like little biiatches for the next 4 yrs. about OBAMA!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352504598293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:43:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352504636134-249</Id><Topic><Title>Diick Morris video today goes into detail why polls are off. Predicts Romney win</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1352164239525</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2012-11-05 20:10:39 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who??? only every republican on this board? Really?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352504636134</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:43:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352504677915-250</Id><Topic><Title>doremi, careyh - like to vote for LOSERS all the time</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352424190564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>REPUBS here all products of broken homes?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352504677915</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:44:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352504785896-251</Id><Title>Hannity has ROMNESIA backpeddles on Immigration Reform, Calls for AMNESTY!!!</Title><Msg>Apparently he realized your party, now comprised of Old White Racists, ain't sufficient to win ANYTHING going forward! LOL!! Fox "News" Sean Hannity told his radio listeners Thursday that he’s “evolved” on immigration and thinks undocumented immigrants without criminal records should have a “pathway to citizenship.” Noting that Hispanic voters overwhelmingly backed President Obama in Tuesday’s election (as the white racist vote declined), Hannity said that the stooooopid party could only compete for Latino voters if they took immigration off the table. Ain't Reality a beeeeeyotch, REPUBS? SEASONS BEATINGS!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352504785896</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352505245148-252</Id><Title>Petraeus bad news for Obama</Title><Msg>Now that sex has been added to the Benghazi story the MSM will show more interest and the public too. Funny the drone story and Petraeus come out just after the election is over????? Some transparency.lol</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352505245148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:54:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352505362154-253</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Resigns Prior to Benghazi Hearings.</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352498504163</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 17:01:44 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everyone knows he is going down, why be around him?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1352505362154</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352505369954-254</Id><Topic><Title>doremi, careyh - like to vote for LOSERS all the time</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1352424190564</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-08 20:23:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why do they post here when all then can do is predict LOSERS?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352505369954</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:56:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352505494359-255</Id><Title>maxedout333 will never see another REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT in his lifetime now!</Title><Msg>GOP is DONE!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352505494359</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352505505678-256</Id><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Msg>IN 2016 GOP HAS NOTHING BUT LOSER CANDIDATES THAT EVERYBODY DESPISES. On the other hand DEMS have the following adored possible Presidential candidates: MICHELLE OBAMA, JOE BIDEN, HILLARY CLINTON, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN, GRAY DAVIS, ROM EMANUAL, ANTHONY WEINER, GLORIA ALRED, ALEC BALDWIN, ELIZABETH WARREN JOHN KERRY, AL GORE</Msg><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352505633844-257</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hope we see all of them in a series of debates.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352505633844</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:00:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352505966809-258</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you can watch how winners debate!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352505966809</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:06:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352506056854-259</Id><Title>REPUBS YOU LOST! and you still post here? WHY?!</Title><Msg>Explain!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506056854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:07:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352506138814-260</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont Forget John Edwards and Tom Daschle.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352506138814</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:08:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352506174917-261</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and John McCain and Mitt Romney</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506174917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:09:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352506196917-262</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And Alvin Greene</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352506196917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:09:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352506483319-263</Id><Title>It's a great day for america = Obama is President, and bigots are angry. Those are two great things.</Title><Msg>No cure for GOPtarded bigoted stupid, none. Four more years. VICTORY!!!!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506483319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:14:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352506540118-264</Id><Title>TOP GOP STRATEGIST - "HOW DO YOU EXPAND A SHRINKING DYING DEMOGRAPHIC" ?</Title><Msg>GOOD F'ING QUESTION...</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506540118</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:15:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352506559866-265</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Also dont forget Debbie Wasserman Schultz, Nancy Pelosi and Harry Reid</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1352506559866</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:15:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352506629319-266</Id><Title>MORE GOP FAMILY VALUES ON PARADE - TOP CIA BETRAYUS BETRAYS OWN WIFE</Title><Msg>OMFG -- RESIGNS IN DISGRACE!! And the national Republican Hypocrisy continues to know no bounds...</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506629319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:17:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352506659540-267</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>who??</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506659540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:17:39 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352507322025-268</Id><Topic><Title>IN 2016 GOP NO CANDIDATES, DEMS HAVE JOE BIDEN, HILLARY, ANTONIO VILLARAGOISA, JERRY BROWN</Title><Username>mad_as_hell_democrat_watchdog</Username><Timestamp>1352505505678</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:58:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxine Waters and Jesse Jackson Jr. I was going to mention Gov.Blagojevich but I don' t know if they'll let him out of the slammer to debate.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352507322025</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:28:42 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352507406798-269</Id><Title>SEAN HANNITY AND DICK MORRIS SHOULD GO CRAWL UNDER A HOLE</Title><Msg>SEAN HANNITY AND DICK MORRIS SHOULD GO CRAWL UNDER A HOLE the are wrong on everything. If they had any pride they would go hide under a hole in shame.</Msg><Username>only_democrats_luv_children</Username><Timestamp>1352507406798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:30:06 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352507699621-270</Id><Topic><Title>Petraeus bad news for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352505245148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:54:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's OUR Homer Obama ! Doh ! doh ! doh !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352507699621</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:34:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352507759362-271</Id><Topic><Title>Petraeus bad news for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1352505245148</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:54:05 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad a distinguished career ends like this. But he did it himself</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352507759362</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:35:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352507858425-272</Id><Title>JUAN WILLIAMS CORRECTLY PREDICTED OBAMA LANDSLIDE VICTORY</Title><Msg>JUAN WILLIAMS CORRECTLY PREDICTED OBAMA LANDSLIDE VICTORY while Sean Hannity got egg all over his face. Those are the facts.</Msg><Username>only_democrats_luv_children</Username><Timestamp>1352507858425</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:37:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352507871992-273</Id><Topic><Title>MORE GOP FAMILY VALUES ON PARADE - TOP CIA BETRAYUS BETRAYS OWN WIFE</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506629319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:17:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe Barry should of shared Larry with him ??? Once you turn your back, you always give back... just ask Barry</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352507871992</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:37:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352507980873-274</Id><Topic><Title>MORE GOP FAMILY VALUES ON PARADE - TOP CIA BETRAYUS BETRAYS OWN WIFE</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506629319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:17:09 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Barry says Larry gave great reacharounds.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352507980873</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:39:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352508113735-275</Id><Topic><Title>WONDER HOW LONG IT WILL TAKE FOR AMERICANS TO SAY..."JEEESH! WHAT DID I DO?..OBIMBO? WHAT WAS I THINKING</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352502751332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:12:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama refused to make a deal on the fiscal cliff last year (which resulted in a credit downgrade of the U.S.) for strategic reasons. If Obama had made a deal a year ago, the negative impact of government spending cuts would have already hit the economy by now and made it worse. Now that he's successfully secured a second term, he can stop trying to postpone reality to American voters about taxes, budget cuts and the truly weak economy. A real economy that has hit bottom would not need to have tough budget decisions postponed or constant QE interventions by the Federal Reserve. Obama and the lib media portrayed the illusion that all was well. You can't trust Nobama.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352508113735</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:41:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352508373184-276</Id><Title>Warren Buffet just fixed the fiscal cliff</Title><Msg>“You just pass a law that says that any time there's a deficit of more than 3 percent of GDP, all sitting members of Congress are ineligible for re-election,” he said.“Yeah, yeah, now you've got the incentives in the right place, right?”</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352508373184</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:46:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352508528050-277</Id><Topic><Title>SEAN HANNITY AND DICK MORRIS SHOULD GO CRAWL UNDER A HOLE</Title><Username>only_democrats_luv_children</Username><Timestamp>1352507406798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What HOLE ? MexiHOLE ???</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352508528050</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:48:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352508552114-278</Id><Title>Proud Dem Quincymagoo Has Called His Congressman repeatedly asking for a new Law</Title><Msg>legalizing human-sheep marriage. When asked why he says "it's to advocate for a friend".</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352508552114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:49:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352508669245-279</Id><Title>OBAMA STOLE THE ELECTION THROUGH VOTER FRAUD</Title><Msg>we all know it. Why else would those #$%$-lib states make such a big deal on fighting a need for voter id. Worthless bums!</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352508669245</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:51:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352508748388-280</Id><Title>what is likely to happen</Title><Msg>the DNC introduces a bill that keeps everyones tax rates at the same rate they are now except those making more then 500k a year, and lets the GOP vote no</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352508748388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352508832876-281</Id><Topic><Title>WONDER HOW LONG IT WILL TAKE FOR AMERICANS TO SAY..."JEEESH! WHAT DID I DO?..OBIMBO? WHAT WAS I THINKING</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1352502751332</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 18:12:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Higher UE, foreclosures, bank fees, gas prices, State bailouts, practically free college education only to illegals, more hostile countries patrolling off our shores, no more affirmative action or freebies to minorities AFTER Whites officially become the minority, BLACK RAP music 24x7 on buses, trains, planes and elevators, illegals rather learn Ebonics before English, etc...</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352508832876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:53:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352509120088-282</Id><Topic><Title>good news for JRmagoo</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1352487385564</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 13:56:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bumped just for JuniorMagoo in case he hadn't heard about S.F. news</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352509120088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:58:40 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352509527636-283</Id><Title>Remember East Coast SANDY Victims, illegals get to jump to front of the line</Title><Msg>After all they were here before the White man... In Public schools history starts with mexican American war and slavery... Every thing before that are just rumors and fairy tales, no one before conquered other lands or people, slavery was just fiction, gold and resources was a invention of the White man post 1600-1800's ... right ??????</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352509527636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:05:27 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352509541034-284</Id><Title>Dumbivan and Junior sitting in a tree...</Title><Msg>k-i-s-s-i-n-g...</Msg><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352509541034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:05:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352509606828-285</Id><Topic><Title>Remember East Coast SANDY Victims, illegals get to jump to front of the line</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352509527636</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:05:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Almost forgot, RACISM wasn't even a word prior to MLK... right ????</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1352509606828</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:06:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352509758625-286</Id><Title>BREAKING: OBAMA THREATENS IRAN AFTER ATTACK ON OUR DRONE!</Title><Msg>he says if it happens again he will cancel their NY Times subscription</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352509758625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:09:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352509836510-287</Id><Topic><Title>Dumbivan and Junior sitting in a tree...</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352509541034</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:05:41 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but more like #$%$</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352509836510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:10:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352509964494-288</Id><Topic><Title>Proud Dem Quincymagoo Has Called His Congressman repeatedly asking for a new Law</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352508552114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:49:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>magoo especially like the smaller ones who don't cry out as much</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352509964494</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:12:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352510156213-289</Id><Title>HUSSEIN OBAMA: NO MANDATE, STOLEN ELECTION, NO COOPERATION</Title><Msg>From congress and nowhere to go in 4 years. Just a lame duck joke.</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352510156213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:15:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352510476086-290</Id><Title>This is what we're up against...</Title><Msg>New book by Professor Barbara Thompson, see description below: Looking for something to read as Thanksgiving approaches? Or a unique take on what has made President Barack Obama such a successful politician? Or perhaps an explanation of Obama as an apostle and his “politics as religion?” You could check out “The Gospel According to Apostle Barack” by Barbara Thompson (AuthorHouse 2012). The mouthful of the book’s subtitle is: “In Search of a More Perfect Political Union as Heaven Here on Earth.” The book’s thesis is that Obama is not just the 43rd president of the United States. Much more than that, he’s an apostle akin to Martin Luther King, Jr. or even Jesus Christ. ****************************************************************************************************************************** I heard this FREAK woman interviewed today on a local talk station. This is what conservatives are up against. The almost ancient fetish for a messiah or a god figure on earth, a mystic or religious experience - and many have chosen the jug-eared clown as their messianic leader. Truly twisted, but this is what is happening to this country. It's scary to think this woman is teaching as a professor and shaping young minds in our schools and universities. VERY SCARY</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352510476086</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:21:16 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352510718518-291</Id><Topic><Title>Proud Dem Quincymagoo Has Called His Congressman repeatedly asking for a new Law</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1352508552114</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:49:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo always throws them on their back for sex. Says it 's easier to kiss them that way.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1352510718518</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:25:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352511304571-292</Id><Topic><Title>SEAN HANNITY AND DICK MORRIS SHOULD GO CRAWL UNDER A HOLE</Title><Username>only_democrats_luv_children</Username><Timestamp>1352507406798</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:30:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't you mean, crawl INTO a whole, or crawl UNDER a rock? How do you crawl under a hole? You'd better go back and start again from 3rd grade from where you dropped out of school.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352511304571</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:35:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352511451186-293</Id><Title>Let's see if Bammy does something REALLY STUPID</Title><Msg>in the next 4 years to get himself IMPEACHED. Chances are pretty good the jug-eared clown will...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352511451186</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:37:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352512098313-294</Id><Title>What's with Petraeus</Title><Msg>FBI is investigating Paula Broadwell [girlfriend].....Ironically, FBI only investigates crime related incidents. Hmmmm</Msg><Username>rfourdnask</Username><Timestamp>1352512098313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:48:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352515014701-295</Id><Title>JEB BUSH</Title><Msg>In spite of his brother, romney should have picked him for his v p. He is the most talented bush and will remain a power in his party.</Msg><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1352515014701</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:36:54 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352515267165-296</Id><Title>Stop liberalism in America</Title><Msg>Boycott all union made products and services</Msg><Username>whatdoidonow3</Username><Timestamp>1352515267165</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:41:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352515398111-297</Id><Topic><Title>It's a great day for america = Obama is President, and bigots are angry. Those are two great things.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506483319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:14:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean like the religious bigots on your side who bash Romney for his religion? Bigots are bigots, and hypocrites are hypocrites.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352515398111</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:43:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352515498367-298</Id><Topic><Title>HUSSEIN OBAMA: NO MANDATE, STOLEN ELECTION, NO COOPERATION</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1352510156213</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 20:15:56 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You forgot, jug-eared...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352515498367</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:44:58 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352515913043-299</Id><Title>Bammy broke an interesting barrier with his reelection...</Title><Msg>Becoming the first president in the history of the republic to win a second term with less support in both the popular vote and the Electoral College than he received the first time he ran.</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352515913043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:51:53 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352516249669-300</Id><Topic><Title>It's a great day for america = Obama is President, and bigots are angry. Those are two great things.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506483319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:14:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The United States has a massive debt problem, which now stands at about $16 trillion and is expected to grow by about $1 trillion annually in Obama's second term. The average American seems to be in the dark or in denial about this debt, just as many Spaniards and Greeks were a couple of years ago. If we continue to vote in politicians who will promise to give us more and not take away what we have now, the debts will grow and eventually spiral out of control. We need an adult to tell us we can't have any more candy, but we are not electing "adult leaders" that tell us what we don't want to hear. Until true reforms and solutions are found to cut the debt and bring solvency to essentially bankrupt programs like Social Security, Medicare, student loans, and even the post office, there is little chance for a robust and secular economic rebound in this country. Romney provided solutions - he provided a 52 point plan. Obama is now asking people for ideas because he has none except tax the rich. What a joke!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352516249669</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:57:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352517638421-301</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy broke an interesting barrier with his reelection...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352515913043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:51:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are still counting votes in Ohio and Florida. Electoral College has not voted. Final count won't be in for 10 days. Re-counts in 7 states possible.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352517638421</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:20:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352518288756-302</Id><Title>Obama, Petraeus and Hillary in The Benghazi Bungle</Title><Msg>Petraeus, a former Army general who led the surge into Iraq under former President Bush and also led U.S. troops in Afghanistan before taking over the CIA, is one of the most respected and influential generals of his time. His wife, Holly, has worked with the Obama administration to help military families. He was scheduled to testify next week on Capitol Hill behind closed doors about the death of four Americans, including two working for the CIA. They died at the U.S. consulate in Benghazi, Libya, Sept. 11. Holes in security at the consulate have been the subject of an internal government investigation at the State Department and a congressional inquiry. *** Hillary is getting out too before the sheet hits the fan. Benghazi is going to blow!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352518288756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:31:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352518389950-303</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy broke an interesting barrier with his reelection...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1352515913043</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 21:51:53 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Could many early votes for Obama be invalid because they voted twice? Early and again on Election Day.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352518389950</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:33:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352518460555-304</Id><Topic><Title>It's a great day for america = Obama is President, and bigots are angry. Those are two great things.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1352506483319</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:14:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How dare the majority of the electorate, the Senate, most of the House and the President make me pay the same tax on my income as my driver! I'm a "job creator!" Benghazi! Benghazi! Benghazi?????</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1352518460555</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:34:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352518565164-305</Id><Title>Petraeus quits before Benghazi testimony</Title><Msg>All the bad news is popping out just a couple days after the election while the votes are still being counted. Holy smoking gun! OBAMA = NIXON</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352518565164</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:36:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352518637909-306</Id><Topic><Title>Obama, Petraeus and Hillary in The Benghazi Bungle</Title><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352518288756</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:31:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget about chem trails and the grassy knoll! Wake up people!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! hahahaha</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1352518637909</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:37:17 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352518800652-307</Id><Title>Benghazi- the first time that scared old white guys have tried to spell an African word...</Title><Msg>I am SO PROUD! Couldn't be PROUDER!</Msg><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1352518800652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:40:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352519360065-308</Id><Title>Time to fire Eric Holder</Title><Msg>He still hasn't done jack about the Somali pirates, or the Fort Hood Mooslim terrorist or the Gitmo 9/11 terrorists. He's been a do nothing except for running guns to Mexico.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352519360065</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:49:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352519548752-309</Id><Topic><Title>Benghazi- the first time that scared old white guys have tried to spell an African word...</Title><Username>belongsinamuseum</Username><Timestamp>1352518800652</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:40:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gadaffi was killed with a bayonet. All U.S. Marines are issued a bayonet. Clown Commander in Chief does not know what weapons his military have at their disposal???</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352519548752</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:52:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352519712126-310</Id><Title>The illusion that all is well</Title><Msg>This economy has been held together by unsustainable government spending and Federal Reserve manipulation. If a true bottom had been reached in this economy, the Federal Reserve would not need to be intervening again and again. While some hopeful signs have emerged in housing and in other areas due to the stimulus and QE3 programs, that is likely to unravel in 2013. The real Obama economy (not the one that has been artificially propped up to win an election) and austerity is coming to America, whether it is induced by politicians or by the markets.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352519712126</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 22:55:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1352520119574-311</Id><Topic><Title>what is likely to happen</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1352508748388</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 19:52:28 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who's going to be in a buying mood on 12/26/12, 12/27/12 or 12/28/12?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1352520119574</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:01:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1352521829053-312</Id><Title>Now that is interesting</Title><Msg>Toyota Camry that featured the “Star Spangled Banner” and the Japanese car company’s proud declaration that the Camry was just named the “Most American-Made Car” on the road for the third year in a row: GM could have entered bankruptcy and voided its absurd union contracts, which paid workers $70 an hour. That would have preserved the rule of law, the rights of bondholders, shareholders and nonunion workers equally. Instead, taxpayers will lose money, and GM may once again go bankrupt without necessary changes being made — thanks to its embrace of Big Government. There's an old saying that covers this: Lie down with dogs and wake up with fleas. It seems Government Motors is scratching.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1352521829053</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-11-09 23:30:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>