<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-25"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345869695814-1</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I might not be able to DO anything about it. But I will MAKE 480K in the first 2 years thanks to Willard. I have never voted my wallet, so I am going to let you vote for me. Thanks sucker.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345869695814</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 00:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345869761358-2</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can always count on you to correct my typo. Thanks spell-checker</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345869761358</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 00:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345876759216-3</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHRISTIAN RIGHT TRADED JESUS FOR JOSEPH SMITH...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345856558376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody the other day told me he refers to it as ' Heaven". Pretty crazy stuff for sure.</Msg><Username>i_got_cool_id</Username><Timestamp>1345876759216</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 02:39:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345897350752-4</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHRISTIAN RIGHT TRADED JESUS FOR JOSEPH SMITH...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345856558376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's an imaginary white guy with a white beard and is republican, his righthand man is the archangel Bony Morony.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345897350752</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 08:22:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345897514011-5</Id><Title>GOP offers solid tips....</Title><Msg>G.O.P. Offers Delegates Tips on Pretending to Like Romney Posted by Andy Borowitz TAMPA (The Borowitz Report)—The Republican National Committee has issued the following confidential memo to delegates attending its 2012 national convention: Welcome Republicans! By now, you should have received your credentials, your mask of Obama in Joker makeup, and the number to call if you see Sarah Palin anywhere on the premises. As a delegate to the 2012 Republican National Convention, the eyes of the world are upon you. More specifically, the eyes of the liberal-dominated media, who will be eager to exploit any signs of less than total enthusiasm for our nominee—that is, when they’re not trying to trick you into talking about rape. The point of this memo is not to convince you to like Mitt Romney. We know that ship sailed long, long ago. The point is to win in November and protect the American values that our forefathers fought so hard for, such as mandatory transvaginal ultrasounds. Here, then, is a list of helpful tips on how to pretend to like Mitt Romney: 1. In previous regional practice sessions, there has been a ten to fifteen second lag time between a speaker saying the name “Mitt Romney” and any audible applause or cheering on the part of session participants. To tighten up this “silence hole,” try to get in the habit of clapping/hooting/stomping whenever anyone says anything. 2. Here’s a simple exercise you can do in your hotel room, car, or anywhere. Say the name “Mitt Romney,” then try to visualize something that you love: a family member, for example, or your favorite Fox host. 3. Starting Monday morning at the Tampa Marriott there will be intensive thirty-minute coaching seminars on fake smiling and squealing led by Flo, of Progressive insurance fame! There will be light refreshments and amphetamines. 4. Some of you have expressed concern that no matter how hard you try, even after listening to the Kid Rock “Romney Rocks” CD we provided, every time you hear the name Mitt Romney you can’t help but frown and find yourselves on the edge of tears. To you, we say: “Go for it!” TV viewers are sure to misinterpret a delegate’s full-on sobbing as a sign of being overwhelmed by love for Mitt (LOL). To hone your weeping skills, we’ve included in your Convention Welcome Bag a DVD of Michael Phelps’s mom, Debbie, at the London Olympics and footage of Kim Jong-il’s funeral. 5. Close your eyes and think of Santorum.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345897514011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 08:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345901618600-6</Id><Title>British Archives found Barak's Birth Certificate</Title><Msg>Obama bribed Kenya with $ 4 billion dollars of tax money to hush up his birth place. But now the British Official Archives where a thousand years of records are kept has found records of a Son being born to Barak Sr. on Aug 4 of the year Hussein claims he was born in Hawaii. Since the last BC was found to be a photoshop knock-off, maybe we got the only copy Hussein hasn't destroyed. And yes he was according to the Brits a British Kenyan born Son of the Empire. The Empire strikes back. I guess this makes the United Kingdom the birther Kingdom for you libs.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345901618600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 09:33:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345903496463-7</Id><Topic><Title>Why hasn't Mitt released his</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345849848645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 19:10:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WHO DOES MITT ROMNEY THINK HE IS? TREASURY SECRETARY? - Ba dum cha. Because he doesn't pay his taxes. Anyway: "Tax experts who have begun to examine the Bain Capital documents released Thursday by Gawker are raising questions as to whether presumptive GOP presidential nominee Mitt Romney has paid all the taxes he owed. At issue are two tax-avoidance techniques employed by Bain Capital, the firm founded by Romney, which have been commonly used in the private equity world but have come under increasing legal scrutiny." The New York Times is getting skeptical. NYT: "Mr. Romney said last week that he had paid an effective federal tax rate of at least 13 percent over the past decade, but he declined -- as he has over months of speculation and attacks -- to release returns before 2010. 'My view is I've paid all the taxes required by law,' Mr. Romney said. Bain private equity funds in which the Romney family's trusts are invested appear to have used an aggressive tax approach, which some tax lawyers believe is not legal, to save Bain partners more than $200 million in income taxes and more than $20 million in Medicare taxes. Annual reports for four Bain Capital funds indicate that the funds converted $1.05 billion in accumulated fees that otherwise would have been ordinary income for Bain partners into capital gains, which are taxed at a much lower rate." [NYT]</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345903496463</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:04:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345904209999-8</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It isn't a typo when you misspell it the same way 4 or 5 times,fool.LOLOLOLOLOL.BTW,Thurs. you said you were putting me on ignore. But you fell right into my little trap. I rattle your cage and you start barking!!!!!!HILARIOUS!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345904209999</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345906637750-9</Id><Title>Questions that need to be asked</Title><Msg>What Is God Telling Todd Akin? by Charles Selden on August 23, 2012 in Newsmakers And what’s the medium? I Hear You So far no reporter has asked Congressman Todd Akin for details about what God has been saying or the medium He has been using. This week the question opportunities were as abundant as life in Eden before Eve bit the apple. Akin assures everyone that God has been giving him advice, but no reporter follows up? Professional reporters usually seek corroboration or confirmation of statements from candidates for high office. Except for spiritual stuff. Perhaps because Bob Woodward unwittingly established the precedent for giving the faithful a pass when Woodward asked President Bush Junior if he ever asks Bush Senior for advice about invading Iraq: Bush, smiling beatifically, answered “I consult the Higher Father.” Woodward missed the scoop of the decade by not pursuing with, “And what did the Higher Father say?” Akin exceeds Bush Junior and dozens of other members of the GOP who claim to consult higher powers for guidance. Akin says he is in non-stop, 7/24 contact with God. Yet the press does not press him, as if it would be impolite to ask questions like With all respect, sir, would you give us details about the last time and topic on which God guided you? Did you take notes? Was your comment about “legitimate rape” completely your idea and not His? Has He commented on that yet? How does He usually communicate with you? Do you hear His voice or see a message from Him on your e-mail? Would you like the GOP to be renamed “God’s Own Party”? The next time you speak with God, would you ask Him how you could be more pro-consumer?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345906637750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:57:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345906684617-10</Id><Title>deny women cancer screenings</Title><Msg>the war on women continues is Mitt so stupid he doesn't realize that Planned Parenthood has saved millions of women's lives? is Mitt so stupid he will continue to move to the right trying to shore up his base while ostracizing the swing voters? Does the #$%$ really think swing voters believe in the birthers? His comments just cost him a lot of votes! LOL The support from women’s groups can boost those efforts. Their advertising offensive comes months after Romney pledged to “get rid of” Planned Parenthood. "Of course you get rid of ‘ObamaCare,’ that's the easy one, but there are others," he said in March. "Planned Parenthood, we're going to get rid of that."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345906684617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:58:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345906884836-11</Id><Topic><Title>Questions that need to be asked</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345906637750</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 10:57:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>many of the GOP are mentally unbalanced, believing God speaks to them, LOL, most psychiatrist would have them committed if they came up for review remember when Sarah was speaking in tongues?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345906884836</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:01:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345907022676-12</Id><Title>Oh no, they're going to reverse engineer his tax returns</Title><Msg>Last Call Posted by Zandar And the giant pile-on on Mitt Romney's really awful month continues as John Cook over at Gawker has gotten his hands on nearly 1,000 pages of Bain Capital documents, detailing Mitt's mysterious quarter-billion dollar fortune. Today, we are publishing more than 950 pages of internal audits, financial statements, and private investor letters for 21 cryptically named entities in which Romney had invested—at minimum—more than $10 million as of 2011 (that number is based on the low end of ranges he has disclosed—the true number is almost certainly significantly higher). Almost all of them are affiliated with Bain Capital, the secretive private equity firm Romney co-founded in 1984 and ran until his departure in 1999 (or 2002, depending on whom you ask). Many of them are offshore funds based in the Cayman Islands. Together, they reveal the mind-numbing, maze-like, and deeply opaque complexity with which Romney has handled his wealth, the exotic tax-avoidance schemes available only to the preposterously wealthy that benefit him, the unlikely (for a right-wing religious Mormon) places that his money has ended up, and the deeply hypocritical distance between his own criticisms of Obama's fiscal approach and his money managers' embrace of those same policies. They also show that some of the investments that Romney has always described as part of his retirement package at Bain weren't made until years after he left the company. Fortune magazine's Dan Primack is already calling the documents "worthless" (really, they read all 950 pages, they promise!) but as the New Yorker's Amy Davidson points out: Here is reason number one thousand and forty for releasing your tax returns if you’re running for President of the United States: if you don’t, someone will try to reverse engineer them, using whatever scraps of paper are available, until they have built some sort of structure that may, in your mind, look like a clumsy papier-mâché version of your well-ordered financial house—and you will have no cause to complain; they will be performing a public service. Mitt Romney took too long to define himself on his own terms because he couldn't do so, as the whole Todd Akin meltdown proves. Details destroy Romney. He counted on being an unknown, a Rorschach test to everyone, so that everyone would see what they wanted to in him. That's what makes the Obama team counterattack so powerful: it doesn't have to be the absolute truth, just enough of it to be politically useful to Obama. The only thing Romney can do at this point is release more details...and the devil in those details are far worse than anything that his opponent can come up with. His opponent and the media have now done so for him. It only gets worse for him here. All he can do is continue to lie about Obama weakening welfare requirements and supporting infanticide. That's literally all he has left with 75 days to go.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345907022676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:03:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345907088135-13</Id><Title>Check into Mitt the twit's 2002 tax returns!</Title><Msg>eom...</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1345907088135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:04:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345907156801-14</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no, they're going to reverse engineer his tax returns</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1345907022676</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:03:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's good to see Mitt is "one of us".</Msg><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345907156801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345907763151-15</Id><Title>God is sending a hurricane to punish</Title><Msg>the GOP for nominating a cultist, if you are a christian and you vote for Romney you will go to hell. The next day Moses said to the people, "You have committed a serious sin. Now I will go up the mountain to the LORD. Maybe I will be able to make a payment for your sin and make peace with the LORD for your sin." 31So Moses went back to the LORD and said, "These people have committed such a serious sin! They made gods out of gold for themselves. 32But will you forgive their sin? If not, please wipe me out of the book you have written." 33The LORD answered Moses, "I will wipe out of my book whoever sins against me. 34Now, go! Lead the people to the place I told you about. My Messenger will go ahead of you. But when I punish, I will punish them for their sin." 35So the LORD killed people because they had Aaron make the calf.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345907763151</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:16:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345908126025-16</Id><Title>the know nothing party</Title><Msg>(this is an interesting historical illusion that will be lost on all baggers who are to stupid to know about the real know-nothing party) A handful of Republicans have tried to fight the know-nothings. “I believe in evolution and trust scientists on global warming,” said Jon Huntsman, the former Utah governor, during his ill-fated run for his party’s presidential nomination. “Call me crazy.” And in an on-air plea for sanity, Joe Scarborough, the former G.O.P. congressman and MSNBC host, said, “I’m just tired of the Republican Party being the stupid party.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345908126025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:22:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345908283823-17</Id><Topic><Title>the know nothing party</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345908126025</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:22:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today's (8/25) Non-Sequitur explains it honestly. Enjoy!</Msg><Username>jdanielman</Username><Timestamp>1345908283823</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:24:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345908409617-18</Id><Topic><Title>THE CHRISTIAN RIGHT TRADED JESUS FOR JOSEPH SMITH...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345856558376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:02:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Kolob. That's where Mitt's tax returns are.</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1345908409617</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:26:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345909380587-19</Id><Title>this is gonna stick</Title><Msg>Mitt will see a lot of ads about this, if there was any question about a war on women this answers it, how can you consider yourself a christian and deny women basic healthcare, is the GOP the Taliban? Their advertising offensive comes months after Romney pledged to “get rid of” Planned Parenthood. "Of course you get rid of ‘ObamaCare,’ that's the easy one, but there are others," he said in March. "Planned Parenthood, we're going to get rid of that."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345909380587</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 11:43:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345911373917-20</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf. Carey didn't bust you, I did. I saw you misspelled CERENT first time I read it. But I let you do it a few more times to be sure. So no typo,buddy. I nailed you for being a big phony liar . You cant make millions and still call the company CERANT. We all laugh at you!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1345911373917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345911804482-21</Id><Title>so what Mitt just misspoke</Title><Msg>Romney caused another stir earlier in the week by declaring that big business was "doing fine" in the current economy in part because companies get advantages from offshore tax havens. What he meant to say is he was doing fine because of offshore tax havens</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345911804482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345911894405-22</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that I care but anybody can search it and know you are lying. Anyways bud, you seem to be obsessed with it you you keep thinking about it. 1st sunny day in a week on Sullivan's Island. Going sailing in a few. You have a nice day, OK ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345911894405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:24:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345912400694-23</Id><Topic><Title>UNEMPLOYMENT IS ONLY 4% !!!</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345754192762</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-08-23 16:36:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Repukes, skinning squirrels does not count as a #$%$ in Biology. ? Back to college pukes ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345912400694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:33:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345912407879-24</Id><Topic><Title>so what Mitt just misspoke</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345911804482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:23:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>AGAIN?</Msg><Username>av8lover</Username><Timestamp>1345912407879</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:33:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345912685698-25</Id><Title>JESUS IS VERY SAD...</Title><Msg>The evangelicals threw Jesus under the bus and have embrace the false prophet con man that directed the Mountain Meadows massacre. How sweeeeeet it is ! PS I am having a lot of fun down in SC pointing this out to my repuke friends. The moment I do, all of them reacts as if they are swallowing a box of screws. Oh the humanity of it all !!!</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345912685698</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:38:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345913051791-26</Id><Title>ASSANGE is a real hero !</Title><Msg>USA and UK police states want him in jail. They want to keep their dirty laundry and how they control the masses under wraps.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345913051791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 12:44:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345915384787-27</Id><Title>Mitt can take us back to the good old days</Title><Msg>where if you were a women and you got raped it was your own fault for tempting the man!!! perhaps Mitt can require all women to wear burkas</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345915384787</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345916056144-28</Id><Title>WILL THE ALMIGHTY SEND AN EARTHQUAKE TO DESTROY THE DEM</Title><Msg>convention? After all, there will never be a larger gathering of baby butchering sodomites and perverts for another 4 years! Just sayin!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916056144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345916274702-29</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE ALMIGHTY SEND AN EARTHQUAKE TO DESTROY THE DEM</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916056144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know birdbrain but he is clearly sending sending a hurricane to Tampa cause he is angry the GOP is nominating the first non-christian for President in history. Will the evengelical hatred of minorities (including women) be stronger then their professed love of Jesus?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345916274702</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:37:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345916599916-30</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE ALMIGHTY SEND AN EARTHQUAKE TO DESTROY THE DEM</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916056144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh haven't you heard dumbo, the weather channel says now that will merely be downgraded to a storm when it comes ashore! LOL! The Almighty has once again made dumbos like you look DUMB and DUMBER! Btw, why do you corrupt bassturds want to murder UNBORN Women!??</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916599916</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:43:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345916860973-31</Id><Title>The movie "2016" is a must see.</Title><Msg>It shows the "why" and "how" Obama will destroy America. Tell everyone you know to see it. It will open their eyes to how un-American and evil Obama and his inner circle are.</Msg><Username>csco_forever</Username><Timestamp>1345916860973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:47:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345917084657-32</Id><Topic><Title>MITT TO PAY 0.82% IN TAXES, AND SO WILL I</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345785817352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mitt's 0.82% will be more than 90% of Obama supporters who live off the taxpayer. Give me a break. Obama is the leader of criminals, perverts, welfare queens, and other Liberal parasites.</Msg><Username>buy_and_hold</Username><Timestamp>1345917084657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:51:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345917745937-33</Id><Topic><Title>MITT TO PAY 0.82% IN TAXES, AND SO WILL I</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345785817352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>crank The proposal would eliminate capital gains taxes for couples making 200k or less or singles making 100k or less. It certainly would not apply to those in Romney's tax bracket. Be careful what you read from libs like Surf. yes that was Romeny's origional proposal (although he would lower the rate on rich taxpayers also) however Ryan's budget eliminates capital gains taxes on all income levels and Romney says he supports Ryan's budget and WOULD SIGN IT INTO LAW</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345917745937</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:02:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345917961252-34</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE ALMIGHTY SEND AN EARTHQUAKE TO DESTROY THE DEM</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916056144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>we can only hope and pray that He does--I can't think of a more deserving group of sickos! maybe it will rain down fire and brimstone?</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1345917961252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:06:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345917992951-35</Id><Title>hey MO</Title><Msg>For them -- and for the rural communities that depend on their incomes -- the drought is far more than a news item. It's an earth-shattering event, one they worry could lead the dairy communities of southern Missouri to unravel. And, perhaps saddest of all, farmers say the sell-offs could have been avoided. "We didn't fail. We did everything right," said Argall's wife, Jeanette. "It was the system that failed us." Hey Jeanette that is the capitalist system!!! The House GOP has blocked farm aid that might have saved you. LOL but vote for Mitt cause if his taxes are cut to 0% all that money will trickle down on you, LOL just cracks me up how these redneck morons can be convinced to vote for tax cuts to the wealthy to balance the budget, while cutting their own throats!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345917992951</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345918111685-36</Id><Topic><Title>MITT TO PAY 0.82% IN TAXES, AND SO WILL I</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345785817352</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 01:23:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah surf I think I messed up, sold off one of my businesses this year and realized a quarter million gain, figured taxes were going up, should have waited for Mitt so I wouldn't have owned any taxes all.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345918111685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345918381010-37</Id><Topic><Title>British Archives found Barak's Birth Certificate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345901618600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 09:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doesn't surprise me, the guy has paid lawyers MILLIONS to hide his entire past. WHY is that?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1345918381010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:13:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345918755256-38</Id><Topic><Title>British Archives found Barak's Birth Certificate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345901618600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 09:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks Rhonda, it is important to keep the loony tunes birther movement alive!! All polls show it loses the GOP a lot of votes. People by and large just don't want to vote for crazy, all your postings help tie Mitt in with crazy!! Let's hope TRUMPS big surprise is some type of birther crazy</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345918755256</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:19:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345918887170-39</Id><Topic><Title>The movie "2016" is a must see.</Title><Username>csco_forever</Username><Timestamp>1345916860973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In 2008 I saw the GOP movie 2012 that said the world would end by now if Obama was elected, I've doubled my money since then, keep selling scared the weak and stupid are big buyers.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345918887170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345918962097-40</Id><Topic><Title>9-11 happened under Obama's administration</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345857616750</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:20:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>come on people 9-11 happened under Obama and then Bush got Osama bin Laden right? baggers redefine stupid!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345918962097</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:22:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345919368681-41</Id><Title>Rhonda you should go</Title><Msg>keep crazy alive!!! It's being called a "star-studded event," but really that's only if you consider dying entertainers from yesteryear "stars." Pat Boone's gonna be there. Remember him? Didn't think so! Basically this is an event for old bigots who hate the fact that the current President of the United States is black and from a colorful family background. That includes one man who isn't necessarily verging on the geriatric side, but he's a war criminal who refused to deploy even though he was a member of the military—which he willingly signed up for in the first place. His reason—because of his idiotic ideals. What's funny is how this is being billed as a "Tea Party Patriots Event," clearly connecting the tea party to the movement known for being the craziest of the right wing groups. It seems that conservative voters are being inundated with this ideology in a way that makes every one of them either look insane or clueless about their own voting platforms. Have fun with that, guys!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345919368681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345919859958-42</Id><Title>Obama aims to shift campaign focus back to Medicare</Title><Msg>meanwhile the Romney camp is attempting to shift the focus back to the crazy birther movement, LOL just to funny how stupid these people are</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345919859958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:37:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345920912558-43</Id><Title>Where are they Mitt?</Title><Msg>Are you going to release them or are they going to be leaked in front of the election? Why would Romney have a Swiss bank account? “Most presidential candidates don’t think it appropriate to bet that the U.S. dollar will lose value by speculating in Swiss Francs, which is basically the rationale offered by the trustee of Romney’s ‘blind’ trust for opening this account,” they wrote. And “you don’t need a Swiss bank account” to speculate in foreign currencies, they note. Then they focused on the tax-compliance questions the Swiss account raises. “The account seems to have been closed early in 2010, but was the income in fact reported on earlier tax returns?” they asked. And did the Romneys file, on time, the necessary disclosure forms to the Treasury? Then there is Romney’s sizable IRA. “Even under the most generous assumptions,” wrote Kleinbard and Canellos, “Romney would have been restricted to annual contributions of $30,000 while he worked at Bain. How does this grow to $100 million?” Plausible explanations exist, they said, including that “a truly mighty oak sprang up virtually overnight from relatively tiny annual acorns because of the unprecedented prescience of every one of Romney’s investment choices.” But it’s also possible, they said, that Romney may have “stuffed far more into his retirement plans each year than the maximum allowed by law by claiming that the stock of the Bain company deals that the retirement plan acquired had only a nominal value.” Of course, we don’t know without seeing Romney’s tax paperwork. Kleinbard and Canellos said the vast amounts in Romney’s family trusts raise a parallel question: “Did Romney report and pay gift tax on the funding of these trusts,” or might he have claimed “unreasonable valuations” that “would have exposed him to serious penalties if all the facts were known?” The “complexity of Romney’s one publicly released tax return, with all its foreign accounts, trusts, corporations and partnerships, leaves even experts (including us) scratching their heads. Disclosure of multiple years’ tax returns is part of the answer here, but in this case it isn’t sufficient. Romney’s financial affairs are so arcane, so opaque and so tied up in his continuing income from Bain Capital that more is needed, including an explanation of the $100 million IRA.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345920912558</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 14:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345924658604-44</Id><Topic><Title>IT IS TIME TO GET ANOTHER 2 ASSAULT RIFLES...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345857442191</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-24 21:17:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When Surf used to be Rationalthought he was a Vietnam war hero.When he got busted on that Rational went away.LOLOLOLOLOL .Now that his CERENT story blew up on him, wonder what he'll be next!!LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL .How about astronaut, Surf??LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345924658604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 15:57:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345925806265-45</Id><Title>Surfandski And Jasonbaby Planned their Wedding for the Dem Con-vention</Title><Msg>and the also plan to "consumate" their union as a "surprise" on primetime just after Obama takes the podium they will stand up in the aisle, catch the network camera's attention and then quickly drop their drawers as surf bends over and grabs his ankles while jason "rear-ends" him..Yes, they will be the talk of the town.</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1345925806265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345926008919-46</Id><Topic><Title>WILL THE ALMIGHTY SEND AN EARTHQUAKE TO DESTROY THE DEM</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1345916056144</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:34:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes! the filthy beasts will be "toasted" by lightning and then swallowed alive by an earthquake</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1345926008919</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:20:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345927163791-47</Id><Title>under the Romney plan</Title><Msg>the middle class pays more in taxes while the rich get big tax breaks, education is cut leaving the country even further behind other countries in preparing our country for the future, women are denied healthcare the same way they are in taliban countries the elderly are thrown to the mercy of the insurance companies who will maximize profits by minimizing care</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345927163791</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:39:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345927315311-48</Id><Title>how many times does God have to do this</Title><Msg>to the GOP before they realize they are offending him? Convention officials said they have contingency plans, but would not discuss them publicly. Monday's events could be easily shifted to Tuesday - the storm is expected to move away from the area early Tuesday morning. The main Monday attraction, a speech by Mitt Romney's wife Ann, has already been moved to Tuesday night so that broadcast networks would televise it. Those networks had scheduled no coverage Monday. In 2008, Republicans dramatically altered their Monday program, which was to feature speeches by President George W. Bush, Vice President Dick Cheney and the governors of Louisiana and Florida. But as two hurricanes were heading for their states, the governors headed home, and the convention attended to routine business and corporate sponsors were urged to tone down their events and help raise money for possible hurricane victims. Romney and President Barack Obama continued to spar Saturday in the hours leading up to the convention.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345927315311</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:41:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345927478514-49</Id><Title>share price</Title><Msg>where do you see share price in 6mos.?</Msg><Username>howellkk</Username><Timestamp>1345927478514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:44:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345927528327-50</Id><Topic><Title>Surfandski And Jasonbaby Planned their Wedding for the Dem Con-vention</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1345925806265</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:16:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf says Linda Lovelace is a rank amateur compared to him!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345927528327</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:45:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345930452700-51</Id><Title>woopsie</Title><Msg>ad hominem don't seem to be getting the votes for Mitt, the GOP should spend more time insulting women, hispanics, blacks, the poor and anyone with a college education that believes in science, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345930452700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:34:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345930484379-52</Id><Topic><Title>woopsie</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345930452700</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:34:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This shift away from a fossil-fueled future is highlighted by a new USA Today/Gallup poll that finds Obama leading Mitt Romney by 13 points on energy issues. Respondents were asked which candidate they thought was better equipped to handle energy, and Obama received 53 percent of support, compared to just 40 percent for Romney.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345930484379</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 17:34:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345932421419-53</Id><Title>Nothee, Barry!!</Title><Msg>Univ. of Virginia tells Obama to do his speechifying somewhere else....not on their campus. Now thats funny.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1345932421419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 18:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345932584618-54</Id><Topic><Title>Nothee, Barry!!</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1345932421419</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 18:07:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would that be a woopsie or an oopsie for the president.LOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345932584618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 18:09:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345933493383-55</Id><Title>America will prosper</Title><Msg>once Obama is reelected the GOP will stop trying to destroy the economy to make Obama look bad, Obama will be able to reach out across the aisle without worrying about alienating his liberal base, if the GOP is willing to compromise we can be great again, if Mitt gets elected and the GOP policy of trying to tear down the country for political gain works you can expect the DNC to adopt the same policies the GOP did and prevent any legislation from passing. They will take the same position the GOP took, their only goal will be to vote out Romney.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345933493383</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 18:24:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345936226546-56</Id><Topic><Title>share price</Title><Username>howellkk</Username><Timestamp>1345927478514</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 16:44:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>With one more good qtr in a row, CSCO shall be around $27-29 by November. If just a so-so qtr, CSCO will stay around $20. Lets hope for the best, and Chambers has to deliver great news!</Msg><Username>yourdaddy3980</Username><Timestamp>1345936226546</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:10:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345936812785-57</Id><Topic><Title>British Archives found Barak's Birth Certificate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345901618600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 09:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I wonder if Trump knows about this and has this as his surprise?</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345936812785</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:20:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345937138658-58</Id><Topic><Title>The movie "2016" is a must see.</Title><Username>csco_forever</Username><Timestamp>1345916860973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just read that per movie theater venue its #1, in revenue per screen. Its just that as a political movie it doesn't have the wide release and Batman, Bourne, or the Expendables the big summer action movies. Obama is the worst, and yet there are idiots who like 12% unemployment, bankruptcies, homes under water, $4,000 shrinkage in yearly net income, foreclosures, kids graduating College and unable to find there first professional job. I can't wait for his defeat.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345937138658</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 19:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345940898694-59</Id><Topic><Title>British Archives found Barak's Birth Certificate</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345901618600</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 09:33:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey Rhonda, we both hope Trump brings up crazy at the nomination, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345940898694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 20:28:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345941550895-60</Id><Title>Let's hope Rhonda is right!!</Title><Msg>and Turmp brings up the birther thing at the convention!! After all 8% of the GOP are supporters, the other 92% think he is a crazy, hopefully he can tie Mitt to the birthers WASHINGTON – Donald Trump’s popularity among Republican voters has taken a huge dive in the wake of President Barack Obama releasing his birth certificate, according to a new poll. Just eight percent of GOP primary voters supported him in a Public Policy Polling survey released Tuesday</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345941550895</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 20:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345942192062-61</Id><Title>More bagger lies</Title><Msg>Obama executive orders so far 134 W's executive orders 291 NOT 600 executive orders, LOL baggers are so stupid they believe anything and are to lazy to do a simple google search to see they are being played as fools</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345942192062</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 20:49:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345943179913-62</Id><Title>Obama executive orders so far 134</Title><Msg>baggers claim 600, LOL is it because they are stupid and believe whatever hatred they are told?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345943179913</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:06:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345943817920-63</Id><Title>Funny how tommaxgreg</Title><Msg>shut his stupid lying mouth as soon as it was pointed out what a liar he is</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345943817920</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345944141889-64</Id><Title>chicken bagger bullies</Title><Msg>spew their lies and like the cowards they are don't even try and defend what they have said, they have no truth or honor.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345944141889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:22:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345944284070-65</Id><Topic><Title>The movie "2016" is a must see.</Title><Username>csco_forever</Username><Timestamp>1345916860973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 13:47:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market is up 100%, the auto industry saved, Bin Laden killed, Iraq troops reduced, no attacks on american soil, women covered with basic health care, renewable energy usage up 500%. Foreign investors willing to take 1.8% interest on 10 year bonds. Yep, the man is destroying the country. LMAO ! LOL! AAAAHAHAHAHAHAHAAHA. LOL ! GOP= Party of IDIOTS.</Msg><Username>thebeachkahuna</Username><Timestamp>1345944284070</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345944386557-66</Id><Topic><Title>chicken bagger bullies</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345944141889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>they run like the little vermin they are, don't even try and defend their lies, they are the lying dishonest folks pulling the country down, can you imagine the founding fathers spewing outright lies like they do? there not Americans</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345944386557</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345945475441-67</Id><Topic><Title>chicken bagger bullies</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345944141889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dumb.ivan formerly known as Deepharbor the board multimillionaire spending another weekend alone in mommy's basement posting trash.....some millionaire.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345945475441</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:44:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345951353402-68</Id><Title>dumb.ivan - incessant #$%$</Title><Msg>Hey dumbschtt....would you please shut the pfck up, you babbling dimwitted POS? Thank you.</Msg><Username>sentry85az</Username><Timestamp>1345951353402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 23:22:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345951671236-69</Id><Topic><Title>chicken bagger bullies</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345944141889</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 21:22:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's a far left libpoozie who wets his bed every night after jacking himself off looking at a filthy picture of Hussein Obama, his communist idol. What a miserable little jerk.</Msg><Username>sentry85az</Username><Timestamp>1345951671236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 23:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345952956480-70</Id><Title>The GOP Clown Circus MUST Go On</Title><Msg>Tampa swamming with GOP clowns and family value STRIPPERS.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345952956480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-25 23:49:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message></Date>