<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346472107672-1</Id><Topic><Title>How many Obamanurists on this Board????</Title><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346459217725</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:26:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The count is 1!</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346472107672</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346473576633-2</Id><Title>Akin leading by 3</Title><Msg>People hate Clair and Rove more than Todd. Biden makes a racist dumb remark libs are silent, but when a Gop sticks his foot in mouth and unlike Biden apologizes, Rove throws a knife at him and the press piles on. The people know the man is a good guy and are giving him a second chance accepting his apology and favoring him over Clair. Maybe the GOP can give him some money so they gain a much needed Senate seat. Harry Reid is the Senior Sen. from Nevada, that won't change, but we can get rid of his other title Majority leader. He can't even pass a budget.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346473576633</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:26:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346473821487-3</Id><Topic><Title>9-9-9</Title><Username>zhuodanya</Username><Timestamp>1346442160401</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 15:42:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think its better than Romney's plan, so was Newts plan also a flat tax. At least Romney is adopting Newt's energy plan.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346473821487</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:30:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346474125576-4</Id><Topic><Title>IS ROMNEY THE BEST THE REPUBS HAVE? I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO CRY</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1346447081968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come Nov 6 Obama will be a crying loser. Obama wasted 100,000,000 on ads that Romney is a heartless felon. Now we know Romney has quietly spent his life helping others. Ryan took care of a senile Granny and adores his mom. This dog won't hunt, Obama keep wasting your time and the money you have on ads nobody will believe</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346474125576</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:35:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346475368740-5</Id><Topic><Title>2016 Obama's America the Movie</Title><Username>swami.chemist</Username><Timestamp>1346456251482</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 19:37:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama 2016 -- explains so much! Being an Independent and brought to this movie by a Conservative friend -- I has some eye rolling going on -- as I entered the theater and expected a big slam... but it was not... it was a very good" birth to today", in-depth examination of what has made our President who he is. Pretty clear when it was over... my mind is changed, I'm done with hoping with this president. He is purpose built to destroy the good parts of America and enhance the bad. Haiti and the Dominican Republic are the same island but are worlds apart... our President wants the same policies as Haiti... and I just don't get it. This movie was fair enough that I would require everyone in America to watch it before the election, just so they can get the same background information that I didn't have... and see if it affects your decision... it affected mine. You should go</Msg><Username>saytira</Username><Timestamp>1346475368740</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 00:56:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346478651980-6</Id><Title>Arpiao says a lot about Obamanurists!</Title><Msg>Obamanurists are just idiots. "It is a miscarriage of justice that the federal government is dropping its case against Sheriff Arpaio and to make such an announcement on the Friday night before the Democratic National Convention can only be politically motivated to shield the administration from criticism," Pablo Alvarado, director of the National Day Laborer Organizing Network, said in a statement."</Msg><Username>obadidos1</Username><Timestamp>1346478651980</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 01:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346489476461-7</Id><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Msg>Check it out on Youtube! Wow!!</Msg><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346489476461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:51:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346503355603-8</Id><Title>Another victory for voters rights</Title><Msg>Ohio Judge Upholds Early Voting Rights For All Citizens August 31st, 2012 4:48 pm Axel Tonconogy A federal judge has ordered Ohio to restore in-person voting rights on the weekend before election day, in the second major victory for voting rights advocates in two days. In July, the Obama campaign filed a lawsuit stating that Ohio’s new election law “arbitrarily eliminates early voting during the three days prior to Election Day for most Ohio voters, a right previously available to all Ohio voters.” The recently enacted law gave preferential treatment to members of the military, who were allowed to vote at a board of elections up through the Monday before Election Day, while civilians had an earlier voting deadline of 6 p.m. on the Friday before Election Day. The Obama campaign argued that the law was politically motivated and designed to suppress Democratic voters, who are most likely to utilize early-voting options. Additionally, the campaign disputed the legality of instituting unequal voting rights for UOCAVA (“Uniformed and Overseas Citizens Absentee Voter Act) and non-UOCAVA voters. In his opinion, Judge Peter C. Economus agreed with the Obama campaign’s complaint. “A citizen has a constitutionally protected right to participate in elections on an equal basis with other citizens in the jurisdiction.” Dunn v. Blumstein, 405 U.S. 330, 336 (1972). In Ohio, that right to participate equally has been abridged by Ohio Revised Code ‘ 3509.03 and the Ohio Secretary of State’s further interpretation of that statute with regard to in-person early voting. In 2005, Ohio expanded participation in absentee balloting and in-person early voting to include all registered Ohio voters. Now, “in-person early voting” has been redefined by the Ohio legislature to limit Plaintiffs’ access to the polls. This Court must determine whether preliminary injunctive relief should be granted to Plaintiffs on their claim that Ohio’s restriction of in-person early voting deprives them of their fundamental right to vote. Following Supreme Court precedent, this Court concludes that Plaintiffs have stated a constitutional claim that is likely to succeed on the merits. As a result—and as explained below—this Court grants Plaintiffs’ motion for preliminary injunction. Just hours after the decision, Ohio Attorney General Mike DeWine announced that he will appeal to the Sixth Circuit U.S. Court of Appeals. As election law expert Rick Hasen notes, the Sixth Circuit has been “bitterly divided in election law disputes in the past”, and the case “could get very ugly very quickly.” So while the Obama campaign won a victory today, the battle for voting rights in Ohio is far from over.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346503355603</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:42:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346504001528-9</Id><Topic><Title>IS ROMNEY THE BEST THE REPUBS HAVE? I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO CRY</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1346447081968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rhonda, Are we as Americans, allow to tar and feather him when he holds the office no longer? I think I know a couple Navy Seals and Border Agents that will hold and tie him to the rail!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346504001528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 08:53:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346504942934-10</Id><Title>Samsung: Apple trying to limit consumer choice</Title><Msg>Yr freedom of choices is limited. capitalism going to stay.</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1346504942934</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:09:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346505360780-11</Id><Title>GOP runs from Romney/Ryan Plan</Title><Msg>In a flier distributed to constituents, Representative David McKinley, Republican of West Virginia, who voted against the plan, said that it “would privatize Medicare for future retirees, raise the retirement age and keep in place the Medicare cuts included in last year’s health care bill.” The flier added, “The Congressional Budget Office determined the plan would nearly double out-of-pocket health care costs for future retirees.” Ricky Gill, a 25-year-old Republican challenging Representative Jerry McNerney in California’s Central Valley, said he “commended the fact that there’s a mature conversation about the national debt.” But, he added, “it would be very difficult for me to endorse any specific plan without having a seat at the table.” This week, Speaker John A. Boehner of Ohio repeatedly declined to say that a Republican election victory in November would be a mandate to pass a Ryan-style Medicare overhaul, instead pointing to energy, tax reform and more generalized deficit reduction. One Republican political consultant working on House and Senate races admitted “the Ryan budget is well under water,” hurting Republican House candidates in California, Florida, Illinois, New Jersey and Virginia, as well as Representative Rick Berg of North Dakota, once considered a shoo-in for the Senate. Republicans can effectively counter the Medicare attacks by going after Democrats on the president’s health care law, the consultant said, but every moment tussling over health care is a diversion from the issue that Republicans say can win the race — the economy. Democrats are now pouring on the Medicare attack. A recent advertisement by the party attacked Representative Dan Benishek of Michigan, a freshman, saying that he had voted to “essentially end Medicare and raise costs on seniors by over $6,000,” the amount the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office estimated the Ryan plan would shift annually to Medicare beneficiaries.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346505360780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:16:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346505428337-12</Id><Title>Making the rounds</Title><Msg>Eastwooding’ makes the rounds on the Web By Claudine Zap Claudine Zap PostsEmailBy Claudine Zap | The Sideshow – 19 hrs agoShare53EmailPrint Clint Eastwood was the surprise speaker at the Republican convention. And the "Dirty Harry" actor's rambling speech didn't make everybody's day. The 82-year-old gave an ad-libbed talk to an empty chair on stage that was supposed to be President Obama—or where he was sitting—or something. It didn't take long for Obama's furniture stand-in to take on a life of its own. Cue the "Eastwooding" Web meme. Game of Thrones "Eastwooding" from @Column55 on twitter.Immediately, Clint Eastwood became a trending topic on Twitter as commenters poured out their thoughts—and let their imaginations run wild. From Brent Spiner ‏@BrentSpiner, "After watching Clint Eastwood's speech last night at the RNC, I'm voting for the chair. " Chris Rock (yes, that Chris Rock) ‏@chrisrockoz posted, "Clint Eastwood on the phone with Obama now: 'It all went according to plan,sir.'" @BorowitzReport wrote, "A new poll reveals that Romney trails Clint Eastwood's empty chair after convention." Mr Eastwood addresses chair, at the Republican National Convention in Tampa, August 30, 2012. (Photo by Mark Wilson/Getty … Ken Jennings ‏@KenJennings added, "An LA cop friend tells me Clint Eastwood has been driving alone in the HOV lane 'with the President' for YEARS. " Funny Or Die jumped in with a gallery of some of the best images, noting that Eastwood gave "a stern lecture to a chair," and picking up on some of the best chair memes, many of which involved the Eastwood/Chair ticket for 2012. A fake Simpsons cartoon image shows Grandpa Simpson in a newspaper clipping with the headline, "Old man yells at chair." And a Shepard Fairey version of the 2008 "Hope" poster was circulating with an image of a chair instead of Obama. Suzanne Munshower ‏@expatina asked, "I have one question: Was the mystery guest Clint Eastwood or the Invisible Obama?" Simon Pegg ‏@simonpegg posted, "Woken up to excited chatter in the US. Apparently Clint Eastwood had an argument with an empty chair regarding its political standpoint. " FastLaugh ‏@FastLaugh tweeted, "Give Clint Eastwood a break... The RNC asked him to speak about ObamaCare and he thought they said ObamaChair..." Obama's Twitter feed, @BarackObama responded with the post: "This seat's taken " and a photo of the commander-in-chief in a chair with the plaque "The President." It's been retweeted more than 40,000 times. Get full coverage of the Republican National Convention here »</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346505428337</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 09:17:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346509285235-13</Id><Topic><Title>Romney loses cool with reporter that catches him in a lie</Title><Username>shapingtechnologies</Username><Timestamp>1346489476461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 04:51:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney Adviser: Ryan 'Didn't Talk About Obama Closing the Plant' Posted: 31 Aug 2012 03:00 PM PDT Click here to view this media Eric Fehrnstrom, Mitt Romney's senior campaign adviser, is denying that Republican vice presidential nominee Paul Ryan suggested that President Barack Obama was to blame for a GM plant that was shut down while President George W. Bush was still in office. Ryan's Wednesday night convention speech has been blasted by fact checkers at The Associated Press, USA Today and CNN (just to name a few) for what one Fox News contributor called "misrepresentations" and Salon's Joan Walsh said were just "nastiness and lies." One of those misleading statements had to do with a Janesville plant that GM decided to close in June of 2008, but Ryan has repeatedly said that the president "broke his promise" by failing to keep it open after taking office in 2009. "What Paul Ryan said there was clearly misleading," CNN host John Berman pointed out to Fehrnstrom on Thursday. "Well, no," Fehrnstrom replied. "He didn't talk about Obama closing the plant. He said that candidate Obama went there in 2008, and what he said was with government assistance, we can keep this plant open for another 100 years." The adviser continued: "Here we are four years into his administration. That plant is still closed. I think it's a symbol of a recovery that hasn't materialized for the people of Janesville, Wisconsin, just as it hasn't materialized for Americans everywhere." "He left the impression that President Obama shut that plant down," Berman pressed. "Well, I would encourage people to go back and look at what candidate Obama said in 2008," Fehrnstrom insisted. "What he said was with his recovery program, with government assistance, we can keep that plant open for 100 years. Four years later, it's still shuttered. I think it's a symbol of a broken economy under this president." Earlier this year, Fehrnstrom was widely mocked after he said that Romney could shake up his campaign "like an Etch A Sketch" and "start over again" after spending the primary season pandering to conservative voters. As the general election campaign was underway in June, the adviser tried to deflect attention from the candidate's extreme positions on contraception and abortion rights by saying that women's issues were just "shiny objects" being used to distract voters.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346509285235</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346510045316-14</Id><Title>Even the GOP convention goers</Title><Msg>aren't voting for Romney/Ryan He may have appeared onstage at the Republican National Convention on Thursday night, but teacher Sean Duffy of Austin, Texas, isn’t necessarily voting for GOP nominee Mitt Romney come November. “I lean more toward Obama, but I think I’m going to vote for someone who’s going to be a strong supporter of education and education reform,” Duffy, 26, told POLITICO in an interview. Duffy teaches 11th grade English at Del Valle High School near the Texas capital. He’s also, as POLITICO reported yesterday, the co-star of a save-the-date video inspired by Wes Anderson’s “Rushmore” that went viral in 2010.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346510045316</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:34:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346511171793-15</Id><Title>Will Romney increase the minimum wage?</Title><Msg>CONVENTION WORKERS EARNING LESS THAN MINIMUM WAGE - Jason Cherkis: "Carolyn Walker said she has been cleaning the convention center for 13 years. She had been making $8 per hour until a few years ago, when the cleaning contract went to another company, Cleanevent USA. The new company meant a new, downsized paycheck. She's now making minimum wage -- $7.67 per hour. But that wasn't the only hit to her wallet. Walker said the company charges her $6 per week for uniforms. 'It stinks to tell you the truth,' she said. 'We work very hard.' It effectively means she's making less than Florida's minimum wage. Larry Gilmore, 32, and Jean Baptiste, 27, recounted similar hits to their paychecks by Cleanevent. Baptiste said he's charged $11 per week for uniforms -- a thin blue short-sleeve shirt and dark pants...Baptiste's rent in Tampa is $575. His electric bill can be as high as $160 per month. If he wants to park near the convention center for work, he -- and the others -- said they would be charged for the privilege. Baptiste said he does not use that parking garage."</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346511171793</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 10:52:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346511804218-16</Id><Title>Making the rounds</Title><Msg>The following is making the rounds on the internets. It’s a piece from the Tikkun Daily and a column called “The Not-So-Social-Gospel.” It imagines what the New Testament would be like if Jesus was a modern day Republican. It’s a good read. The Lazy Paralytic 1. When Jesus returned to Capernaum after some days, it was reported that he was at his home. 2. So many gathered around that there was no longer room for them, not even in front of the door; and he was speaking the word to them. 3. Then some people came, bringing to him a paralyzed man, carried by four of them. 4. And when they could not bring him to Jesus because of the crowd, they removed the roof above him; and after having dug through it, they let down the mat on which the paralytic lay. 5. When Jesus saw this he grew angry, “Why did you wreck my roof? Do you have any idea how much that cost to install? Do you know how many tables and chairs I had to make in my carpentry shop to pay for that roof? The reeds alone cost five talents. I had them carted in from Bethany.” 6. The disciples had never seen Jesus so angry about his possessions. He continued, “This house is my life. And the roof is the best part.” The disciples fell silent. 7. “It’s bad enough that you trash my private property, now you want me to heal you?” said Jesus, “And did you not see the stone walls around this house?” “Yes,” said the man’s friends. “Are these not the stone walls common to the towns and villages of Galilee?” 8. “No,” Jesus answered. “This is a gated community. How did you get in?” The man’s friends grew silent. 9. Then Jesus turned and said to the paralytic, “Besides, can’t you take care of your own health problems? I’m sure that your family can care for you, or maybe the synagogue can help out.” 10. “No, Lord,” answered the man’s friends. “There is no one. His injuries are too severe. To whom else can we go?” 11. “Well, not me,” said Jesus. “What would happen if I provided access to free health care for everyone? That would mean that people would not only get lazy and entitled, but they would take advantage of the system. 12. Besides, look at me: I’m healthy. And you know why? Because I worked hard for my money, and took care of myself.” The paralyzed man then grew sad and he addressed Jesus. “But I did work, Lord,” said the paralytic. “Until an accident rendered me paralyzed.” “Yes,” said the man’s friends. “He worked very hard.” 13. “Well,” said Jesus, “That’s just part of life, isn’t it?” “Then what am I to do, Lord?” said the paralytic. “I don’t know. Why don’t you sell your mat?” 14. All in the crowd then grew sad. “Actually, you know what you can do?” said Jesus. “You can reimburse me for my roof. Or I’ll sue you.” And all were amazed. 15. “We have never seen anything like this,” said the crowd.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346511804218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:03:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346512426760-17</Id><Topic><Title>Making the rounds</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346511804218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:03:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Very Poorly Prepared Crowd 1. The day was drawing to a close, and the twelve apostles came to Jesus and said, “Send the crowd away, so that they may go into the surrounding villages and countryside, to lodge and get provisions; for we are here in a deserted place.” 2 But Jesus said to them, “Why not give them something to eat?” They said, “We have no more than five loaves and two fish – unless we are to go and buy food for all these people.” 3 For there were about five thousand men. And Jesus said to his disciples, “You know what? You’re right. Don’t waste your time and shekels. It would be positively immoral for you to spend any of your hard-earned money for these people. They knew full well that they were coming to a deserted place, and should have relied on themselves and brought more food. As far as I’m concerned, it’s every five thousand men for themselves.” 4. The disciples were astonished by this teaching. “But Lord,” said Thomas. “The crowd will surely go hungry.” Jesus was amazed at his hard-headedness. “That’s not my problem, Thomas. Better that their stomachs are empty than they become overly dependent on someone in authority to provide loaves and fishes for them on a regular basis. Where will it end? Will I have to feed them everyday?” “No, Lord,” said Thomas, “Just today. When they are without food. After they have eaten their fill, they will be healthy, and so better able to listen to your word and learn from you.” Jesus was grieved at Thomas’s answer. Jesus answered, “It is written: There’s no such thing as a free lunch.” So taking the five loaves and the two fish, he looked up to heaven, and took one loaf and one fish for himself, and gave the rest to the twelve, based on their previously agreed-upon contractual per diem. But he distributed none to the crowd, because they needed to be taught a lesson. So Jesus ate and he was satisfied. The disciples somewhat less so. “Delicious,” said Jesus. What was left over was gathered up and saved for Jesus, should he grow hungry in a few hours. The very poorly prepared crowd soon dispersed</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1346512426760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346512619611-18</Id><Title>So you are a middle class guy</Title><Msg>trying to get by and trying to decide if you are going to vote Romney or Obama you kind of know what you're getting with Obama but you wish it was a lot more, so your thinking of voting Romney but he made that comment about having your parents come up with all the money for a kid in college, he wants to raise the rates on student loans from 3.4% to 6.5%, and he wants to take away your kids pell grant, so your a little unsure if you can afford to have your kid going to college under Romney. Course you know the current entitlement program is unsustainable but you also know the Ryan "medicaid" proposal will eliminate funding IMMEDIATELY (not in 10 years) for nursing home care and you're pretty sure you can't afford the 75k a year to keep your mother in law in the nursing home, on the other hand she needs full time care and you can't afford to have your wife give up her job to take care of her at home. Your father and mother are in pretty good health but are scrapping by on their little social security check, you help them with what ever extra money you can come up with but with the Ryan plan putting back the donut hole in the prescription drug program you're sure your parents won't be able to come up with the extra $6,400 a year for their medicine, but without your Dad's diabetes medicine he isn't going to live long and then who will take care of Mom? You know the rich are taxed to death! Didn't Mitt have to pay almost 14% in taxes! You surely can't support this Obama class warfare attacking the rich. While you are willing to fight to make sure the rich don't pay anymore in taxes you're wondering why it is Ryan's plan increases your taxes by over $2,000 a year? Your 20 year old drop out daughter is working at Starbucks and living with that toothless redneck, you're not happy about that but at least you know she is getting inexpensive contraceptives and STD screening at the local Planned Parenthood. God knows what you will do if Romney eliminates funding and she get's pregnant with that retards child. Likely she will have to move back home, course now that your wife has to stay at home to take care of her mother you probably lost your home to the bank. So your daughter and your new grandson will have to share the one bedroom apartment with your mother in law and your recently widowed mother. No you're not happy with Obama at all.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346512619611</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346512952681-19</Id><Title>at least Bush kept us safe</Title><Msg>Well not so much really. What people mean when they say he kept is safe seems to be that there wasn't another terrorist attack like 9/11. By that standard, he kept us no safer than Jimmy Carter, George H.W. Bush, Bill Clinton, or Barack Obama. And even leaving out 9/11, for reasons that are never explained, Bush was president during the anthrax attacks, the Beltway sniper incident, the Los Angeles airport shooting, the Mohammed Reza SUV incident, the Seattle Jewish Federation shooting, and the bungled response to Hurricane Katrina. Again, I don't blame Bush for the victims of those incidents, but to harken back to his tenure as a time when the president kept America safe is ahistorical. There are, in addition, many of us who think that the War in Iraq made Americans less safe in various ways -- it certainly made the 4,488 Americans who died fighting there less safe, and with uncertain at best safety benefits to those of us back in the United States. The more you look at the evidence, the more you realize that, measured in total citizens killed, keeping Americans safe wasn't Bush's strength. My guess is that the talking point keeps getting trotted out as a vestige of the rally-around-the-president impulse that took hold after 9/11, and because conservatives still feel as though they have to say something positive about George W. Bush's tenure.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346512952681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346513498312-20</Id><Title>Somewhere in Kenya</Title><Msg>A village is missing it's idiot...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1346513498312</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:31:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346513892262-21</Id><Title>Aristotle, pretty bright guy</Title><Msg>However, people are concerned about rising income inequality, surveys indicate. Average inflation-adjusted, after-tax incomes of the richest 1% of U.S. households ballooned 275% from 1979 to 2007, according to an October report by the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office. That was more than four times the 65% growth for the rest of the top 20%. The middle-income tier, the next 60% of wage earners, had a far more modest 40% rise in household income, while the poorest one-fifth of the population averaged an 18% gain. Those numbers have the public's attention. Almost two-thirds of Americans believe the income gap is widening, and 57% said that's negative for society, according to the Pew Research Center poll. Nearly the same percentage, 58%, said the wealthy pay too little in taxes. "The real difference between democracy and oligarchy is poverty and wealth. Wherever men rule by reason of their wealth, whether they be few of many, that is an oligarchy, and where the poor rule, that is democracy". Aristotle</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346513892262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:38:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514552972-22</Id><Topic><Title>Aristotle, pretty bright guy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346513892262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:38:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"We can have democracy in this country, or we can have great wealth concentrated in the hands of a few, but we can't have both." Louis D. Brandeis (Supreme Court Judge)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346514552972</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:49:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346514823181-23</Id><Topic><Title>at least Bush kept us safe</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346512952681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>4488 Americans died in Iraq...that was Bush's war. Absolutely terrible. 58206 Americans died in Vietnam....that was democrat LBJ's war. And you libs never mention that.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346514823181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346515601801-24</Id><Topic><Title>at least Bush kept us safe</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346512952681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I've made it very clear I believe the Vietnam war was a colossal mistake. Course there is plenty of blame to go around on that one. Not sure why that makes Bush's war good? More GOPER fuzzy logic. Among the released tapes are conversations between Nixon and national security adviser Henry Kissinger in early December of 1972 in which they discuss how and why they will escalate the deeply unpopular war in Vietnam. Weeks later, Nixon would begin a bombing campaign in North Vietnam on Christmas day. "Let's look at the action. We can't have any doubts about it," Nixon said to Kissinger. Throughout the discussions, Nixon and Kissinger never use the phrase "bombing," but instead refer to campaign as "the action." The conversations also reveal that Nixon was aware that he was undertaking a huge gamble by escalating the war. He feared that Congress might cut his funding for the war. "Blame the Democrats," Kissinger suggested. According to historian Luke A. Nichter, the newly released items show that Nixon had a personal hand in the details of the Vietnam war planning the war's escalation. "President Nixon was more involved in the minutia of the Vietnam War than we previously thought, at least during the Christmas bombing period," Nichter said.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346515601801</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:06:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517658499-25</Id><Topic><Title>at least Bush kept us safe</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346512952681</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 11:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush tenure was very positive if your goal is to destroy the American safety net. break up unions, lower the wages for American workers and put more money in the hands of the elite. You need to consider the goals when you judge.</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1346517658499</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:40:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517790096-26</Id><Topic><Title>"SURF" OBSSESSED WITH EASTWOOD!</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346459941376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so if I hear you right you are saying: 'gay is as gay does', i.e. surf once again as a dem has proven his gayness in a big way. Yep, ditto that.</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346517790096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:43:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346517874642-27</Id><Topic><Title>"SURF" OBSSESSED WITH EASTWOOD!</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346459941376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yep. I heard his local ER doctor had to call in a specialist to reattach it to his scrotum because he ripped it out by the roots!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346517874642</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 12:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346522244749-28</Id><Title>Today's Poll Romney up 3%, Tomorrow it will be 5%</Title><Msg>Due to the nature of 5 day moving averages todays polling is only one day for the Romney/Eastwood convention night. Romney was likeable and a good speaker. Eastwood will move the senior and undecided vote for Romney. Tomorrow Romney will take the lead 5% and maybe monday even more. Then Romney will start his TV ads and his friends Pac ads will dominate Obama who has failed to be ahead with his negative, nasty and lying ads. All Obama's ads refuted during the RNC. Game over for Obama. Move up the moving trucks, haul the garbage out.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346522244749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346522382535-29</Id><Title>Ryan admits he lies about everything</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan's campaign walked back comments the VP nominee made about running a marathon. "I had a two hour and fifty-something" marathon, Ryan said last week an interview. "I hurt a disc in my back, so I don’t run marathons anymore." But the Ryan campaign confirmed to Runner's World that he has only run one marathon, the 1990 Grandma’s Marathon in Duluth, Minnesota, which he finished in just over 4 hours. The admission comes after wide speculation that Ryan had exaggerated his marathon time. Running a sub-3 hour marathon means averaging under 7 minutes per mile for the entire race, a possible but extremely impressive feat. As the New Yorker's Nicholas Thompson put it, "It’s the difference between racing and running." This isn't the first time Ryan has come under fire this week for stretching the truth. His RNC speech was chastised for misleading claims about Medicare and the 2008 closing of a Wisconsin plant. Yeah he isn't going to cut your medicare, you can trust him he doesn't lie.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346522382535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346522727847-30</Id><Title>OBAMA TO GET LIAR OF THE YEAR AWARD</Title><Msg>he LIED: -about Bin laden's death a recent seal team member's book says -about an economic recovery -about the jobs picture improving--it's much WORSE -he lied and covered up FAST AND FURIOUS YOU NAME IT--HE LIES ABOUT IT!!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346522727847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346523155962-31</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan admits he lies about everything</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346522382535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why would he lie about this, it's stupid, isn't he smart enough to see he would get caught in the lie. Is he so far out of touch that he thinks the truth can be whatever he says it is? Is he completely devoid of reality?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346523155962</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346523547691-32</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA TO GET LIAR OF THE YEAR AWARD</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346522727847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no shet! he's a huge lying criminal--he should be arrested and jailed asap by the feds</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346523547691</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:19:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346523590966-33</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA TO GET LIAR OF THE YEAR AWARD</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346522727847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>only one person dumber than Obama, that is the person that votes this second time for him, after what they have seen. He will get a few votes, part of his family (only part) a few drug dealers, a couple of illegal immigrants that slip though the voting place, dumb-ivan, and a few other sissy. No real American could vote for this tree hugging pecker-wood!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346523590966</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:19:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346523676896-34</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA TO GET LIAR OF THE YEAR AWARD</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346522727847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>totally agree</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346523676896</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:21:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346523758306-35</Id><Topic><Title>IS ROMNEY THE BEST THE REPUBS HAVE? I THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TO CRY</Title><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1346447081968</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 17:04:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh Ryan adores his mom, oh my God, what a great steps for the repukes, a son that loves his mother. I guess it is an exception in repuke land and the sheep are just in awe of it! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346523758306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346524036991-36</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY MOVING TO BRAZIL !!!!</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346446405882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So no more drill baby drill ? Make up your mind gerbil</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346524036991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:27:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346524161106-37</Id><Title>If Romney doesn't get elected</Title><Msg>will the GOP decide that it's because he wasn't conservative enough to get the independent voter? will the GOP just hand the keys over to the Tea Baggers?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346524161106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346524527298-38</Id><Title>Running on Empty</Title><Msg>If you drank the Kool Aid for the last four years, it's okay because you can drink responsibly again.We have been running on empty as a country. We can continue on this path of empty wallets, empty 401K's, and empty homes or we can just let him go and vote for a leader who has the qualifications and experience to create jobs and rebuild the economy. The choice is clear!</Msg><Username>gavinsox</Username><Timestamp>1346524527298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:35:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346524639777-39</Id><Topic><Title>Running on Empty</Title><Username>gavinsox</Username><Timestamp>1346524527298</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't know about your 401k but mine has doubled</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346524639777</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346527865997-40</Id><Title>If you will lie about your marathon time</Title><Msg>and lie throughout your national speech, it's a fairly safe bet you lied about this too. Ryan said he did not know about the two requests he made for stimulus money for companies in his district WHILE HE WAS VILIFYING THE STIMULUS ACT. Ryan said a staff person handled the matters. How could anyone believe that Ryan did not meet with the owners of the companies he was trying to help. One of these requests was for $20 million that would reap 7,600 new jobs in his district. And he didn't know about the matter? A staff person handled it without his knowledge? Besides being uncommonly dishonest, Romney and Ryan insult our intelligence. There has never been a candidacy as utterly dishonest as Romney-Ryan's. They look you directly in the eye- they look America directly in the eye- and tell the most bald-faced lies.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346527865997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346528016161-41</Id><Topic><Title>If you will lie about your marathon time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346527865997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought the baggers all claimed the high moral ground, truth, justice and the American way? How do you baggers reconcile the clear fact that Ryan is a lying sack of Missouri pipe tobacco with your moral and Christian values? How is it when the catholic church says his budget is immoral and unchristian you back him?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346528016161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:33:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346528582988-42</Id><Title>RICO act:</Title><Msg>That should give Obama, Pelosi, Reid and Holder anywhere from 30 to life! plus strip them of their above our health benefits and pensions.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346528582988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346534678944-43</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY MOVING TO BRAZIL !!!!</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346446405882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SurfingMagoo What does drill,baby,drill have to do with Brazil? That 2 billion should have been spent here to give our oil workers jobs and help a little on being us being energy independent. Do you ever put any thought into your posts??? And knock off the Surf id. It fools nobody.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346534678944</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:24:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535204644-44</Id><Topic><Title>If you will lie about your marathon time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346527865997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who said Guantanamo will be closed on Jan.20,2010? Not a Ryan lie. Who said they would cut the deficit in half their first term? Not a Ryan lie Who said the stimulus would hold unemployment under 8.0. Not a Ryan lie. There are more examples but you get the drift. Your messiah can lie with the best of them.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346535204644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535254359-45</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY MOVING TO BRAZIL !!!!</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346446405882</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 16:53:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so are you telling us this because you're following his every move like you do Clint Eastwood? Whoa...back-off GAY dude!</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346535254359</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346535407655-46</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA TO GET LIAR OF THE YEAR AWARD</Title><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346522727847</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 14:05:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah both Obama and dumbivan are little sissies. Maybe they should get together with Surf and have a pink panties sissy party sleepover?</Msg><Username>donkeydouchebags</Username><Timestamp>1346535407655</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:36:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346536449941-47</Id><Topic><Title>If you will lie about your marathon time</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346527865997</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:31:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP blocked closing of gitmo, GOP blocked all legislation that would have reduced the deficit insisting on tax breaks for the wealthy Obama NEVER SAID THE STIMULUS WOULD hold unemployment under 8%, never happened, another GOP lie</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346536449941</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:54:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346536686145-48</Id><Topic><Title>Ryan admits he lies about everything</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346522382535</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:59:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he admits it was an outright lie about his marathon time, why would he tell the truth about anything?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346536686145</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 17:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346536998060-49</Id><Title>the GOP 8% lie</Title><Msg>First, we have never found an instance of anyone in the administration making a public pledge to keep unemployment below 8 percent. The source for Romney’s and the others’ statements is a Jan. 9, 2009, report called "The Job Impact of the American Recovery and Reinvestment Plan" from Christina Romer, then chairwoman of the president's Council of Economic Advisers, and Jared Bernstein, the vice president's top economic adviser. Their report projected that the stimulus plan would create 3 to 4 million jobs by the end of 2010. The report also included a chart predicting unemployment rates with and without the stimulus. Without the stimulus (the baseline), unemployment was projected to hit about 8.5 percent in 2009 and then continue rising to a peak of about 9 percent in 2010. With the stimulus, they predicted the unemployment rate would peak at just under 8 percent in 2009. The important word here is projection. The economic analysis wasn’t a promise, it was an educated assessment of how events might unfold. And it came with heavy disclaimers. "It should be understood that all of the estimates presented in this memo are subject to significant margins of error," the report states. "There is the more fundamental uncertainty that comes with any estimate of the effects of a program. Our estimates of economic relationships and rules of thumb are derived from historical experience and so will not apply exactly in any given episode. Furthermore, the uncertainty is surely higher than normal now because the current recession is unusual both in its fundamental causes and its severity."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346536998060</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346537311906-50</Id><Title>the disbarment GOP lie</Title><Msg>In an email in response to a public inquiry the ARDC replied: Michelle Obama holds a valid license to practice law in Illinois, has never been disciplined or the subject of a disciplinary proceeding in Illinois and is on voluntary inactive status as an Illinois lawyer. Voluntary inactive status is simply a lawyer registration category for lawyers who are not currently practicing law. Attorneys on voluntary inactive status may resume active status at any time as a matter of course. Now why would she go on "voluntary inactive status" instead of just paying malpractice insurance, bond insurance and be subject to every tom dick and harry that wanted to call her in front of a court room without cause? Come on baggers spin more lies. Or are you really stupid enough to believe this crap fat limpcheese sells you</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346537311906</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:08:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346537839726-51</Id><Title>The 23 million on welfare lie,</Title><Msg>More than 4.4 million people are on welfare, an 18% increase during the recession. The program has grown slower than others, causing Brookings Institution expert Ron Haskins to question its effectiveness in the recession. just another GOP lie, one has to wonder if the baggers are so stupid they won't figure out they are being lied to so much?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346537839726</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:17:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346537948945-52</Id><Title>lies, damn lies and</Title><Msg>republicans</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346537948945</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346538660728-53</Id><Title>when I was a Republican</Title><Msg>it was in part because they were the moral party, they told the truth, now they seem to take pride in the fact that their base is so stupid they can just be lied to, LOL Presidential campaigns and political conventions are supposed to help voters understand how a candidate would govern. If the past few weeks are any indication, Americans can expect two things from a Mitt Romney presidency: lies and attempts to further divide a nation that already is too polarized. Romney is running a series of ads criticizing President Barack Obama’s decision to waive some requirements of the 1996 welfare reform law. The waivers give states more flexibility in how they meet the goal of getting welfare recipients back to work. But the Romney ads claim that under “Obama’s plan, you wouldn’t have to work and you wouldn’t have to train for a job. They just send you your welfare check.” This is the opposite of the truth. The waivers were requested by five governors, including two Republicans, to increase the effectiveness of welfare-to-work programs. The Romney ads have been tagged with four Pinocchios from Washington Post fact checker Glenn Kessler and a “pants-on-fire” rating from PolitiFact. Yet the lies keep coming. Wow 4 pinocchios, that is a lie that proves if you believe it you're a retard.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346538660728</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539060385-54</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Poll Romney up 3%, Tomorrow it will be 5%</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346522244749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:57:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but Rhonda we still want to know, you posted a while back that Israel should murder every man, women and child on the Gaza strip, all 1.5 million of them, If you don't respond we will have to assume you still support this genocide. Do you think your opinion is a reflection of the American jewish opinion? by the way how is Harv, if you need me to I can still post your address if you need help, it was smart for you to delist your phone number however,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1346539060385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346539419187-55</Id><Topic><Title>Today's Poll Romney up 3%, Tomorrow it will be 5%</Title><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1346522244749</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 13:57:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumdum You made that threat to Rhonda away back when you were DeepHarbor .Or did you forget ?? I didnt. Bottom line,Magoo,you aren't near as smart as you think you are and the rest of us aren't as dumb as you like to think.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1346539419187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 18:43:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346543771770-56</Id><Title>AS CLINT SAID THE OTHER NIGHT, OBAMA IS NOTHING BUT</Title><Msg>an "empty chair", AWOL, derelict of duty...nothing but an empty seat and empty suit. Well-said Mr. Eastwood.</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1346543771770</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:56:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346543882907-57</Id><Topic><Title>"SURF" OBSSESSED WITH EASTWOOD!</Title><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346459941376</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2012-08-31 20:39:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well what do you expect from a gay effeminate dude like surf? LOL</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1346543882907</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 19:58:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346546083269-58</Id><Title>PENN STATE GETS FKED BY OHIO...</Title><Msg>That stadium should have been empty. ESPN is a disgrace for having televised that game.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346546083269</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:34:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346547003057-59</Id><Title>NO LIMIT TO THEIR GREED...</Title><Msg>Not only do they get tax breaks, they don't want to pay what is left. Oh look, surprise surprise, Bain involved. ****************************************** The New York attorney general is investigating whether some of the nation’s biggest private equity firms have abused a tax strategy in order to slice hundreds of millions of dollars from their tax bills, according to executives with direct knowledge of the inquiry. The attorney general, Eric T. Schneiderman, has in recent weeks subpoenaed more than a dozen firms seeking documents that would reveal whether they converted certain management fees collected from their investors into fund investments, which are taxed at a far lower rate than ordinary income. Among the firms to receive subpoenas are Kohlberg Kravis Roberts [KKR 14.25 0.02 (+0.14%) ], TPG Capital, Sun Capital Partners, Apollo Global Management, Silver Lake Partners and Bain Capital, which was founded by Mitt Romney, the Republican nominee for president. Representatives for the firms declined to comment on the inquiry</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346547003057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346549484721-60</Id><Topic><Title>RICO act:</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346528582988</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 15:43:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ever notice how gays have a tough talk, always calling someone retard or idiot? what they think they are going to try to slap us? Silly Pecker-woods are funny!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346549484721</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346551173149-61</Id><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Msg>No problem, repukes will swallow he coomshot as if it were steak and lobster! *********************************************************** The Huffington Post reported that in 1999 the GOP presidential candidate had been part of an investment group that invested $75 million in Stericycle, a medical-waste disposal firm that has been attacked by anti-abortion groups for disposing aborted fetuses collected from family planning clinics. Coming during the heat of the GOP primaries, as Romney tried to sell South Carolina Republicans on his pro-life bona fides, the revelation had the potential to damage the candidate's reputation among values voters already suspicious of his shifting position on abortion. But Bain Capital, the private equity firm Romney founded, tamped down the controversy. The company said Romney left the firm in February 1999 to run the troubled 2002 Winter Olympics in Salt Lake City and likely had nothing to with the deal. The matter never became a campaign issue. But documents filed by Bain and Stericycle with the Securities and Exchange Commission—and obtained by Mother Jones—list Romney as an active participant in the investment.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551307398-62</Id><Topic><Title>When I was a Democrat I was an Idiot but I am better now</Title><Username>gregjanetommax</Username><Timestamp>1346547344694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:55:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, from your writing it looks like you are doing 'great'. LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551307398</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346551653591-63</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You usually post articles like this under your dumb.ivan id. Why the change today ?</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346551653591</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:07:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346551958119-64</Id><Title>The folks aint happy with Obama</Title><Msg>Upon arriving at Sioux City, Iowa today Obama saw this banner draped from a hangar: " OBAMA welcome to SUX.....WE DID BUILD THIS!! "</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346551958119</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:12:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552159922-65</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You found me out ! Me and ivan are the only ones that cut/paste articles. You fools make up facts on the fly ! LMAO ! Go away gramps, I don't like to beat up senior citizens.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346552159922</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552477783-66</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm probably younger than you,Magoo. And yes I know you will say you aren't him like you deny all your other ids.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1346552477783</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:21:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552944977-67</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not denying it. I am telling you that you found me out crankie old man ! Didn't I ? LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346552944977</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:29:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346552957780-68</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well, well, well. More anti-Romney lies posted by you (LOL with the lin "Mother Jones" rag as your source no less!) and gay language of "swallowing". Don't project your lewd conduct on to the rest of you POS. You are one pathetically sad, desperate case.</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1346552957780</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346553960240-69</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY INVESTED IN ABORTED FETUSES ...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346551173149</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 21:59:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut the phf*ck up you babbling communist jacgoff.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1346553960240</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:46:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346554109328-70</Id><Topic><Title>NO LIMIT TO THEIR GREED...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346547003057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crawl back into your miserable communist schytt hole you miserable little twaht.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1346554109328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 22:48:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1346557411106-71</Id><Topic><Title>NO LIMIT TO THEIR GREED...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1346547003057</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 20:50:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Schneiderman is a former Chairman of the Democratic Senate Campaign Committee.</Msg><Username>fallis.1942</Username><Timestamp>1346557411106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1346557767110-72</Id><Title>A Football Question</Title><Msg>Last year.....after the Packers / Bills game, Buffalo released quarterback Trent Edwards. During the Packers / Eagles game, the Packers injured Philadelphia quarterback Kevin Kolb. Philadelphia then had to play backup quarterback Michael Vick. During a playoff game against the Eagles, the Packers injured Michael Vick and another backup was needed. After the Packers / Cowboys game, Dallas fired Wade Phillips and most of his staff . After the Packers / Vikings game, Minnesota fired Brad Childress and most of his staff. Four weeks after losing to the Packers, the 49er's coach Mike Singletary and most of his staff were fired and replaced. During the Bears Playoff game, the Packers injured Jay Cutler and backup Todd Collins forcing the Bears to go with 3rd string quarterback Caleb Hanie. So here's the question..... ............. Is it just me, or did the Packers create more jobs last year than Obama?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1346557767110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-09-01 23:49:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>