<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-09-12"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347447724163-1</Id><Title>rotten capitalism going to stay</Title><Msg>Ur living standard goes down, mi living standard will go up.LoL need mi stupid explanation. can U figure out with Ur academic reasoning.</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1347447724163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:02:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347447996963-2</Id><Topic><Title>rotten capitalism going to stay</Title><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1347447724163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:02:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ur stupid logics is Eistein's theroy of relativity.</Msg><Username>lkoncri0998</Username><Timestamp>1347447996963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:06:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347448288258-3</Id><Topic><Title>Revealed: How Bush was given SEVEN direct warnings about threat from Bin Laden in months before 9/11 attacks On the eleventh anniversary of the atrocity, it has emerged that the White House received multiple briefs between May and August that year about an attack with explosives and numerous casualties.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347390660675</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 15:11:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>U confirmed Bin Laden had nothing to do with 9/11. he was US scapegoat.LoL!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1347448288258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:11:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347449591036-4</Id><Title>Poll: Obama holds 10-point lead over Romney among Catholic voters</Title><Msg>Poll: Obama holds 10-point lead over Romney among Catholic voters A new poll by a Catholic advocacy group shows President Barack Obama has a slight lead over Gov. Mitt Romney among non-Hispanic Catholics, despite the stalled economy and his 2012 establishment of church regulations requiring them to fund contraception and abortion-related services that they abhor. The poll of 2,629 likely Catholic voters, an unusually large sample, showed that 46.5 percent of non-Hispanic Catholics support Obama, while 45.6 percent support Romney.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347449591036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347450210883-5</Id><Title>FOR ALL YOU RACIST &amp; HOMOPHOBIC REPUKB: if you were in ENGLAND you could be PROSECUTED! Juror says he’s too homophobic and racist to serve, now faces prosecution</Title><Msg>FOR ALL YOU RACIST &amp; HOMOPHOBIC REPUKB: if you were in ENGLAND you could be PROSECUTED! Juror says he’s too homophobic and racist to serve, now faces prosecution Juror says he’s too homophobic and racist to serve, now faces prosecution Judge Gary Burrell dismissed a potential juror who said he was too racist to serve. (Southampton Crown Court) A British man who said his "extreme homophobic and racist views" should make him ineligible for jury duty now faces prosecution over the claim. The Daily Echo reports that the man's identity is being kept anonymous for now but that Judge Gary Burrell QC read the leader in open court. In the letter, the man writes: "I strongly believe that it would be a serious injustice to the legal system to select me for jury service. "I hold extreme prejudices against homosexuals and black/foreign people and couldn't possibly be impartial if either appeared in court. Therefore it would not be in the court's interest to have me a juror." In addition, the man said that if he were selected, he also would not pay attention to the case and would simply vote with the majority. The man had been selected to serve on a jury in the case of a man on trial for assault and reckless driving. And while Burrell questioned the authenticity of the man's claim, he nonetheless dismissed him from jury duty. Though he escaped jury duty, the man could soon find himself on trial. The prosecutor and defense attorneys in the case, barristers Rebecca Austin and Robert Bryan, stepped outside their traditional role of legal combatants to lodge a joint complaint against the man. Under Britain's Contempt of Courts Act, he could face prison time or a fine for failing to serve on jury duty. "The Attorney General's Office is aware of this case, and we await more information from Judge Burrell," said a spokesman for the Attorney General's Office.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347450210883</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:43:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347450594376-6</Id><Title>AMERICA DOESN'T LIKE HATE: The Greater Phoenix Tea Party Patriots group has pulled the plug on Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe Arpaio, cancelling their Sept. 22 "Birther" bash at the city's Celebrity Theatre "due to inadequate ticket sales</Title><Msg>AMERICA DOESN'T LIKE HATE: The Greater Phoenix Tea Party Patriots group has pulled the plug on Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe Arpaio, cancelling their Sept. 22 "Birther" bash at the city's Celebrity Theatre "due to inadequate ticket sales." Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe's Arizona 'Birther' Party Scrapped The Greater Phoenix Tea Party Patriots group has pulled the plug on Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe Arpaio, cancelling their Sept. 22 "Birther" bash at the city's Celebrity Theatre "due to inadequate ticket sales." The venue's website touts an "intimate atmosphere of this 2,650-seat theater in the round" with an "extremely rare revolving stage." Prices of entry ranged from $10, for tickets purchased in advance, to $25 if you wanted a "Meet and Greet" with the Maricopa County sheriff, who is pushing for a "Congressional investigation into the fraudulent documents produced by the [Obama] administration." The group's website has posted a blog entry confirming the decision to nix the show. "We apologize for any inconivienience (sic)," organizer Chris Rossiter wrote, promising that further probes into the validity of President Obama's birth certificate "will be pursued in earnest." When contacted by ABC News, Tea Party Patriots co-founder Jenny Beth Martin said she had no idea that Arpaio, Boone, or Lt. Col. Terry Lakin, a doctor who spent five months in prison after he refused deployment to Afghanistan, were scheduled to headline the affiliate's gathering. "I didn't know about it about until you told me 120 seconds ago," Martin, who, along with Sarah Palin, was named to Time magazine's 2010 "Most Influential" leaders list, told ABC News today. Tea Party Patriots Group leaders in Arizona did not respond to requests for comment. It's been an eventful summer for Arpaio, "America's Toughest Sheriff." On July 19, the same day he first appeared in court to face accusations he engaged in a systematic campaign of racial profiling, Arpaio convened a press conference in Phoenix, promising to unveil a big break in his "independent investigation" into the validity of the president's birth certificate. But supporters were to be disappointed. With no substantial revelations to report, he launched into a tirade against the White House. "Show us the microfilm," he said, dismissing the electronic birth certificate released last year by President Obama. "I said it a while back. Show us the microfilm and we'll all go back home and forget this. "We wanted to clear the President of the United States. That was my mission, but it hasn't happened that way." Since then, the racial profiling suit has been dismissed and the feds have dropped a separate abuse-of-power investigation. But Arpaio still faces damaging charges that his office failed to pursue more than 400 sex crimes cases between 2004 and 2007.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347450594376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:49:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347453221074-7</Id><Title>how about some details Mitt?</Title><Msg>Now, with polls showing that Obama has taken a slight lead in the race after the Republican and Democratic national conventions, increasingly anxious conservatives are calling on Romney to spell out more of his plans - even if it risks alienating some undecided voters. The calls for a change in strategy have become particularly loud since Sunday, when Romney struggled during an interview on NBC's "Meet the Press" program to explain what income tax loopholes he might close to help offset the cost of his tax cuts, or whether he would keep portions of Obama's healthcare overhaul, including a requirement of insurance coverage for those with pre-existing medical conditions. "Mr. Romney's pre-existing political calculation seems to be that he can win the election without having to explain the economic moment or even his own policies," said an editorial published Tuesday in the Wall Street Journal, which often is a barometer of the thinking of leading conservatives. "Such vagueness carries its own political risks," the Journal editorial said. It isn't the first time that conservatives in his party have raised doubts about Romney's campaign strategy, but with the Nov. 6 election less than two months away, the calls for the former Massachusetts governor to be bolder and more explicit have become increasingly urgent. William Kristol, editor of the conservative Weekly Standard, said that Romney could be setting a course to lose the election despite the factors working in the Republican's favor - such as the nation's 8.1 percent unemployment rate. "When a challenger merely appeals to disappointment with the incumbent and tries to reassure voters he's not too bad an alternative," Kristol wrote, "that isn't generally a formula for victory." Romney's advisers say they are sticking</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347453221074</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:33:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347453570447-8</Id><Title>Where is O'Losers PLAN?</Title><Msg>Far left extremists are asking where his plan is. They want to know why he is silent on not backing Unions and screwing the kids in Chicago. Obumbles home town of Chicago run by his past right hand man Rahm Emanual isa pile of chit going down the toilet. Give O'Loser another 4 years and Obumbles will finish turning the country into his own little personal Chicago. Hope and change folks.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347453570447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:39:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347454099510-9</Id><Title>Democratic Platform.............</Title><Msg>Blame Bush and promise the moon to the poor and less fortunate to buy their vote. Attack the rich and blame everyone else. Maybe it's time to call a spade a spade, O'Losers policies are killing the economy. Hard to argue with facts.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347454099510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:48:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347454334564-10</Id><Title>23 million unemployed Americans.............</Title><Msg>This is occuring under O'Losers watch. Who's to blame for this? 3 1/2 years after libTURDS took over the country, there are fewer Americans working than when they took office. They have NOT CREATED a single job folks. That is FACT.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347454334564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:52:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347454481758-11</Id><Title>liberals are so angry</Title><Msg>why do they judge attack and condem other people's beliefs? I thought they were the party that was all about equal rights and warm fuzzy songs around the camp fire?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1347454481758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:54:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347454490374-12</Id><Topic><Title>Where is O'Losers PLAN?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347453570447</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:39:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HIS PLAN is to WIN !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347454490374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:54:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347454543090-13</Id><Title>WHY aren't far left extremists slamming Dem. Rahm Emanual in Chicago</Title><Msg>like they did Scott Walker in Wisconsin? The far left have no principles, all they have is HATE and Division. The truth is coming out folks, all you have to do is pay attention to their actions.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347454543090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:55:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347455192879-14</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICA DOESN'T LIKE HATE: The Greater Phoenix Tea Party Patriots group has pulled the plug on Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe Arpaio, cancelling their Sept. 22 "Birther" bash at the city's Celebrity Theatre "due to inadequate ticket sales</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347450594376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why is the right-wing so hateful &amp; intolerant?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347455192879</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:06:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347455369383-15</Id><Topic><Title>liberals are so angry</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1347454481758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They are unless you are a conservative black or a woman, then they attack you and spread their hatred. What's that word that describes their actions.....................................OH yea, HYPOCRITE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347455369383</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:09:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347455510065-16</Id><Topic><Title>liberals are so angry</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1347454481758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>psychiatrist have a term for people that do what you are doing, it is called projection</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347455510065</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:11:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347455624629-17</Id><Title>increasingly anxious conservatives are calling on Romney to spell out more of his plans - even if it risks alienating some undecided voters.</Title><Msg>increasingly anxious conservatives are calling on Romney to spell out more of his plans - even if it risks alienating some undecided voters. Now, with polls showing that Obama has taken a slight lead in the race after the Republican and Democratic national conventions, increasingly anxious conservatives are calling on Romney to spell out more of his plans - even if it risks alienating some undecided voters. The calls for a change in strategy have become particularly loud since Sunday, when Romney struggled during an interview on NBC's "Meet the Press" program to explain what income tax loopholes he might close to help offset the cost of his tax cuts, or whether he would keep portions of Obama's healthcare overhaul, including a requirement of insurance coverage for those with pre-existing medical conditions. "Mr. Romney's pre-existing political calculation seems to be that he can win the election without having to explain the economic moment or even his own policies," said an editorial published Tuesday in the Wall Street Journal, which often is a barometer of the thinking of leading conservatives. "Such vagueness carries its own political risks," the Journal editorial said. It isn't the first time that conservatives in his party have raised doubts about Romney's campaign strategy, but with the Nov. 6 election less than two months away, the calls for the former Massachusetts governor to be bolder and more explicit have become increasingly urgent. William Kristol, editor of the conservative Weekly Standard, said that Romney could be setting a course to lose the election despite the factors working in the Republican's favor - such as the nation's 8.1 percent unemployment rate. "When a challenger merely appeals to disappointment with the incumbent and tries to reassure voters he's not too bad an alternative," Kristol wrote, "that isn't generally a formula for victory." Romney's advisers say they are sticking</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347455624629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:13:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347455705746-18</Id><Title>"If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," -George Will &amp; Ann Coulter If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," declared George Will on ABC's "This Week With George Stephanopoulos" Sunday.</Title><Msg>"If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," -George Will &amp; Ann Coulter If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," declared George Will on ABC's "This Week With George Stephanopoulos" Sunday.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347455705746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347455991557-19</Id><Topic><Title>liberals are so angry</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1347454481758</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 08:54:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So when you talk about actual FACTS, according to you its " projection ". Interesting comment, did you take your pills today?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347455991557</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:19:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347456434411-20</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt thinks you should be able to beat your "wives."</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347408199351</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:03:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So tell us about Bill Ayers dying, Magoo!! LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347456434411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:27:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347456550037-21</Id><Topic><Title>Where is dumb.ivan?/</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347411186584</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:53:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon,dumb.ivan,talk about calling me dumb and then you say Bill Ayers died when Obama was 15.LOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347456550037</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:29:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347456705657-22</Id><Topic><Title>Bill wil be shocked</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347410913988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:48:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooooooopsie, Magoo!!!!!!So tell us aboutBill Ayers funeral LOLOLOLOLOL Did you go?? LLOLOL Man,are you stupid!!!!LOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347456705657</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:31:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347457296878-23</Id><Title>perhaps you would like to read a little</Title><Msg>press release that came from our U.S. State Department …. OBAMA’S State Department … on the anniversary of the 9/11 Muslim attacks on America. Here it is … please be sitting down: The Embassy of the United States in Cairo condemns the continuing efforts by misguided individuals to hurt the religious feelings of Muslims – as we condemn efforts to offend believers of all religions. Today, the 11th anniversary of the September 11, 2001 terrorist attacks on the United States, Americans are honoring our patriots and those who serve our nation as the fitting response to the enemies of democracy. Respect for religious beliefs is a cornerstone of American democracy. We firmly reject the actions by those who abuse the universal right of free speech to hurt the religious beliefs of others Well isn’t that just so sweet. They’re attacking our Embassy in Cairo. They’re killing our Ambassador in Libya … and the State Department issues a press release telling us to be careful not to hurt their feelings. Are you FREAKING KIDDING ME? OH … maybe you don’t believe me. Well … just click here and read the press release for yourself. Is it any wonder that the world sees America as a nation in decline? A WEAKENING nation in decline? Apparently the Obama campaign figured out that this wasn’t going to go over too well, so they have now disavowed the State Department’s press release.</Msg><Username>gogbpacker91</Username><Timestamp>1347457296878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347457346737-24</Id><Title>Truly … this one is hard to believe.</Title><Msg>Joe Biden was present yesterday to honor the memory of the people on Flight 93, the 9/11 flight brought down by passengers before the Muslim hijackers could fly it into the Capitol or the White House. Have you heard what he said? Again … sit down. Biden said that the 9/11 memorial services were a “bittersweet moment for all Americans.” Excuse me ….. Bittersweet? I looked it up … here’s the definition: bittersweet |ˈbitərˌswēt| adjective • arousing pleasure tinged with sadness or pain: the room, with all its bittersweet memories. Pleasure tinged with sadness? Thanks, Joe</Msg><Username>gogbpacker91</Username><Timestamp>1347457346737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:42:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347457351411-25</Id><Topic><Title>Bill wil be shocked</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347410913988</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 20:48:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will Magoo retire his dumb.ivan id now?? Looks really stupid saying Bill Ayers has been dead for about 35 years.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL How does your foot taste,Magoo????LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347457351411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347457461850-26</Id><Topic><Title>perhaps you would like to read a little</Title><Username>gogbpacker91</Username><Timestamp>1347457296878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Loser has NO CONTROL over what's going on in the country. He is 100% focused on his re-election campaign. WHY govern now. Time for a new hope and change.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347457461850</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347457551711-27</Id><Topic><Title>Joe's latest gaffe.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347397979689</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-09-11 17:12:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump... Biden...a democrat leader!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347457551711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:45:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347457749629-28</Id><Topic><Title>perhaps you would like to read a little</Title><Username>gogbpacker91</Username><Timestamp>1347457296878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember Obama saying Qaddafi and Mubarak must go.And others warned that we might wind up with even worse than those two.........well??????</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347457749629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:49:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347458023167-29</Id><Topic><Title>hilarious that idiot teabillysbring up bill ayers - who has been a teacher employed by a right wing conservative for 35 years. the gop wetbrains are totally clueless and</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347457811000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:50:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ooooopsie,Magoo.You were the one who posted Bill Ayers died when Obama was 15. Not me!!! You one dumb dude. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458023167</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:53:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347458054011-30</Id><Topic><Title>perhaps you would like to read a little</Title><Username>gogbpacker91</Username><Timestamp>1347457296878</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:41:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Many said the muslim brotherhood would take over, the administration said that wouldn't happen. Ooopsieeeeeeeee</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347458054011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347458185302-31</Id><Title>thanks yahoo. here's what my csco board looks like..........</Title><Msg>Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 48 seconds ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 minute 19 seconds ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 9 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 12 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 12 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 16 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 25 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 27 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 35 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 39 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 41 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 48 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 59 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 0 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 2 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 6 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 21 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 40 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 1 hour 40 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 2 hours 11 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 2 hours 21 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 2 hours 43 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 2 hours 48 minutes ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 3 hours ago Topic hidden because you ignored this user Show Post 10 hours ago</Msg><Username>febru3012</Username><Timestamp>1347458185302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347458483741-32</Id><Title>This pres has to go</Title><Msg>Apologizing to Libya. He really disgust me.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347458483741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:01:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347458864829-33</Id><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Msg>Upon hearing that Magoo had pronounced him dead on the world wide internet, a visibly shaken Bill Ayers is now contemplating legal action.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459102613-34</Id><Topic><Title>This pres has to go</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347458483741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:01:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Monkey Boy just sent out Hillary to do damage control. What a #$%$</Msg><Username>generic_erick</Username><Timestamp>1347459102613</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459252511-35</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carey, Dont let up on the #$%$ Hope he's embarrassed enough to go away. Not likely though.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347459252511</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459373533-36</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>carey don't be a complete idiot, it wasn't meant to be a factual statement, lol</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347459373533</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459419200-37</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but I'm glad it's wasted a few hours of your time</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347459419200</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459685276-38</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thats so weak,its pathetic,Magoo. It was a statement of fact by you.You stepped on your weenie with that dumb remark, All other posters who read it know that.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347459685276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:21:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347459945106-39</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I read it and laughed. Magoo got confused between Frank Marshall Davis and Ayers . Funny that the guy who likes to make fun of the rest of us did that. Squirm,Magoo, squirm.lol</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347459945106</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:25:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347460251384-40</Id><Topic><Title>Board loon messed up!!!</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347458864829</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:07:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TOOOOOO FUNNY. Magoo made a giant mistake and now trying to wiggle out of it!!!!! HILARIOUS!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347460251384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:30:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347460431163-41</Id><Title>ATTENTION KOLOBITES, WILLARD WILL BE SHOVELING THE CRAP TODAY, AND I GOD...</Title><Msg>expect you to eat it !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347460431163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347461321757-42</Id><Title>History lesson for a dolt</Title><Msg>Magoo, Frank Marshall Davis died in1987. Bill Ayers is doing just fine. I will remind you of that when you tee hee someone here for a typo or a misspelling . Your childishness is disgusting.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347461321757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:48:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347462219412-43</Id><Title>Who is pro life teascum??</Title><Msg>For example, Obama’s Affordable Care Act does not pay for abortions. In Massachusetts, Romney’s health care law does. Obama favors, and included in the Affordable Care Act, $250 million of support for vulnerable pregnant women and alternatives to abortion. This support will make abortions much less likely, since most abortions are economic. Romney, on the other hand, has endorsed Wisconsin Republican Paul Ryan’s budget, which will cut hundreds of millions of dollars out of the federal plans that support poor women. The undoubted effect: The number of abortions in the United States will increase. On these facts, Obama is much more pro-life than Romney. But let’s not stop there. Obama does not financially profit from the abortion industry. Romney does. Bain Capital, in the time Romney was listed as its legal head and even when he was attending Bain board meetings, was an owner of Stericycle, a major disposer of the dead bodies of aborted children in the United States. (See: Romney Invested in Medical-Waste Firm That Disposed of Aborted Fetuses, Government Documents Show.) Bain owned a share of Stericycle until 2004, selling its interest for a profit in the tens of millions of dollars. We can parse what Romney’s 1999 “retroactive retirement” from Bain means, but he still gets an annual payout from the firm. To the extent those dollars are part of Bain’s Stericycle profits, a strong argument exists that Romney is an abortion profiteer. How pro-life is that?</Msg><Username>asswipesforbush</Username><Timestamp>1347462219412</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347462490828-44</Id><Title>Romney earned money grinding up dead babies</Title><Msg>not very pro life now is it</Msg><Username>asswipesforbush</Username><Timestamp>1347462490828</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:08:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347463706946-45</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fantastic Info. Thanks for sharing.</Msg><Username>nedraqux783</Username><Timestamp>1347463706946</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:28:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347464161799-46</Id><Topic><Title>HISTORY LESSON: BUSH ALLOWED 9/11 THRU NEGLIGENCE AND INCOMPETENCE, NOT BARRY. BUSH CRASHED THE MARKETS AND BAILED OUT THE BANKS. BARRY DID NOT DO THESE THINGS.</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347462272211</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:04:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo, Have you ever heard of Frank Marshall Davis???lol</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347464161799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347464343837-47</Id><Title>WILLARD SAYS TO EVERY WORKING AMERICAN "GIVE ME $20,000 FOR THE PENTAGON"</Title><Msg>"Yes, I know the pentagon does not want the $2T, but my friends that make the weapons do"</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347464343837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347464440623-48</Id><Title>willard thinks being a bully is good foreign policy</Title><Msg>A high school classmate of presidential candidate Mitt Romney told ABC News today that he considers a particular prank the two pulled at Michigan’s Cranbrook School to be “assault and battery” and that he witnessed Romney hold the scissors to cut the hair of a student who was being physically pinned to the ground by several others. “It’s a haunting memory. I think it was for everybody that spoke up about it … because when you see somebody who is simply different taken down that way and is terrified and you see that look in their eye you never forget it. And that was what we all walked away with,” said Phillip Maxwell, who is now an attorney and still considers Romney an old friend. “I saw it with my own eyes,” said Maxwell, of the anecdote first reported by the Washington Post. Maxwell said Romney held the scissors helping to cut the hair of a student, John Lauber, who was presumed to be gay and who had long hair. “It was a hack job … clumps of hair taken off.” Maxwell said he held the boy’s arm and leg, describing he and his friends as a “pack of dogs.” Asked if Lauber was targeted because he was gay, as reported by the Post, Maxwell said, “We didn’t know that word in those days … but there were other words that were used. We weren’t ignorant, we just didn’t use the current names for things.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347464440623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347464623767-49</Id><Topic><Title>History lesson for a dolt</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347461321757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:48:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo, You're the one who posted Ayers was dead .Quit acting like a little kid and admit you got him mixed up with Davis. Instead you try to turn it on someone else .We be laughing at you.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347464623767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:43:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347464629690-50</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD SAYS TO EVERY WORKING AMERICAN "GIVE ME $20,000 FOR THE PENTAGON"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347464343837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>willard thinks paying billions to keep our troops overseas generates jobs domestically but thinks spending money fixing our schools, roads and bridges is a waste of money that costs us jobs, LOL you just can't underestimate the stupidity of the baggers</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347464629690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:43:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347464825650-51</Id><Topic><Title>willard thinks being a bully is good foreign policy</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347464440623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:40:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This guy had the courage to speak up. Not easy. And too bad Romney did not tell the truth.</Msg><Username>a6ni2me</Username><Timestamp>1347464825650</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:47:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347464937239-52</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD SAYS TO EVERY WORKING AMERICAN "GIVE ME $20,000 FOR THE PENTAGON"</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347464343837</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:39:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid is saying Bill Ayers is dead when he's on tv every month or two. Right,Magoo???LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347464937239</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:48:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347465383571-53</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Killed in Libya, and Obama APOLOGIZES??!?!!!!??!!</Title><Username>johnlarry961</Username><Timestamp>1347462924856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I pretty much don't care about Moslem sensitivities...it's the real world, and one of our good guys got killed, just for being an American. THAT IS REALITY....time to take out Libyans, just for being Libyans</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347465383571</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:56:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347465420820-54</Id><Title>Our navy isn't good enough????????</Title><Msg>At the dem convention in a tribute to our military, the dems used a video of Russian warships instead of the U.S.navy. as a backdrop. What is wrong with these people!!!!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347465420820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347465571254-55</Id><Title>DEATH IN LIBYA...THE HARVEST OF OBIMBO'S BOWING TO ISLAM....</Title><Msg>Obimbo sowed the wind, and his ambassador, the man representing Obimbo in Libya, harvested the whirlwind.... Time to kick #$%$..carefully. Not stupidly. Precision strikes, drones in the night, masked men in silent helicopters taking out the bad guys....which bad guys? Any bad guy the CIA has in its Libyan sights...time to pull that trigger. No boasting, no press, no publicity, just DEATH FROM ABOVE....and out.</Msg><Username>narniaway</Username><Timestamp>1347465571254</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347465807809-56</Id><Title>ARITHMETIC SAYS...</Title><Msg>Paul Ryan should have kept driving the wienermobile. Bwwwwwahahahahahah.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347465807809</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:03:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347466178610-57</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Killed in Libya, and Obama APOLOGIZES??!?!!!!??!!</Title><Username>johnlarry961</Username><Timestamp>1347462924856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This is Obamas fault. He is weak and the evil doers do as they please.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347466178610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:09:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347466302012-58</Id><Topic><Title>Americans Killed in Libya, and Obama APOLOGIZES??!?!!!!??!!</Title><Username>johnlarry961</Username><Timestamp>1347462924856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:15:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will issue a statement later today saying it was Bush's fault.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347466302012</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347466542269-59</Id><Topic><Title>"If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," -George Will &amp; Ann Coulter If the Republican Party cannot win in this environment, it has to get out of politics and find another business," declared George Will on ABC's "This Week With George Stephanopoulos" Sunday.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347455705746</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ssssssssssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466542269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:15:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347466558767-60</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICA DOESN'T LIKE HATE: The Greater Phoenix Tea Party Patriots group has pulled the plug on Pat Boone and Sheriff Joe Arpaio, cancelling their Sept. 22 "Birther" bash at the city's Celebrity Theatre "due to inadequate ticket sales</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347450594376</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 07:49:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>aaaaaaaaaaaa</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466558767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:15:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347466572970-61</Id><Topic><Title>increasingly anxious conservatives are calling on Romney to spell out more of his plans - even if it risks alienating some undecided voters.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347455624629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 09:13:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sssssssssssss</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466572970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:16:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347466649163-62</Id><Title>trump gave Gaddafi a safe haven no one would allow Gaddafi a place to stay EXCEPT TRUMP</Title><Msg>trump gave Gaddafi a safe haven in my neighborhood UNTIL we got him OUT no one would allow Gaddafi a place to stay EXCEPT TRUMP trump rented Gaddafi space on his property to pitch his tent 9/2009 After being rejected by New York City's Central Park and by the town of Englewood, N.J., the Libyans posed as Dutch diplomats to rent a Manhattan town house that had a large roof that could have accommodated a tent. When that deal fell through, the Libyans apparently used intermediaries to rent Trump's 113-acre estate called the Seven Springs in the posh Westchester County suburb of Bedford As workers began pitching the tent, local officials were pitching a fit. By Tuesday evening, as media helicopters filmed the progress of the tent's construction, the Bedford town lawyer issued a stop work order However Bedford residents are not all too happy and the Bedford town attorney Joel Sachs said that the town ordered the construction of the tent to stop Residents and US Representative John Hall are trying to block Gadhafi from staying at the estate. Trump’s people are not commenting either although a no parking order and security company were hired to keep people away from the Trump estate. Reporters are being blocked from filming or on Oregon Road near the estate. ANYTHING FOR MONEY TRUMP</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466649163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:17:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347467015673-63</Id><Title>The lead is disappearing</Title><Msg>My,oh,my. That five point lead the loons were crowing about has dropped to one point in two days. This Libya/Egypt fiasco will drop Obama even more.lol</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467015673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347467255720-64</Id><Topic><Title>trump gave Gaddafi a safe haven no one would allow Gaddafi a place to stay EXCEPT TRUMP</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466649163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did I miss something?? Is Trump still running??? Did he get elected president?? Why is Magoo bringing up Trump???? LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467255720</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347467283475-65</Id><Topic><Title>The lead is disappearing</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467015673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>over 8% unemployment, the economy sucks, and what, OBAMA is STILL AHEAD? GOD, how BAD A CANDIDATE MUST MITT ROMNEY BE? HAR HAR HAR!! as per RASMUSSEN: OBAMA 48% MITT the #$%$ 45%</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347467283475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:28:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347467432338-66</Id><Topic><Title>trump gave Gaddafi a safe haven no one would allow Gaddafi a place to stay EXCEPT TRUMP</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347466649163</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:17:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HINT: we don't post only about presidential candidates on this board.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347467432338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:30:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347467480369-67</Id><Title>ROMNEY'S NEGATIVE CAMPAIGNING is getting old- BLAMING OBAMA for everything; perhaps that's why the conservatives are getting tired of MITT's act and want him to state some concrete facts about his plan for recovery? That and RASMUSSEN has OBAMA AHEAD AGAIN!</Title><Msg>ROMNEY'S NEGATIVE CAMPAIGNING is getting old- BLAMING OBAMA for everything; perhaps that's why the conservatives are getting tired of MITT's act and want him to state some concrete facts about his plan for recovery? That and RASMUSSEN has OBAMA AHEAD AGAIN!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347467480369</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:31:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347467546820-68</Id><Topic><Title>The lead is disappearing</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467015673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lied again,Magoo.Rasmussen has Obama 46 and Romney 45 today. BTW, thanks for reminding us how bad things are under Obama.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467546820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:32:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347467973990-69</Id><Topic><Title>The lead is disappearing</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467015673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOPE!! This morning it was OBAMA 48% ROMNEY 45%</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347467973990</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347468010502-70</Id><Title>Bulletin from Chicago</Title><Msg>Chicagoans were amazed to see Bill Ayers walking down the street today. Said he looked pretty good considering Magoo said Ayers died 35 years ago .LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347468010502</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:40:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347468019656-71</Id><Title>"The United States condemns in the strongest terms this outrageous and shocking attack," Obama said with Secretary of State Hillary Clinton at his side in hastily arranged public remarks in the Rose Garden of the White House. "Today, we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake: Justice will be done."</Title><Msg>"The United States condemns in the strongest terms this outrageous and shocking attack," Obama said with Secretary of State Hillary Clinton at his side in hastily arranged public remarks in the Rose Garden of the White House. "Today, we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake: Justice will be done."</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468019656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:40:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347468100973-72</Id><Title>Virgil Goode- PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE in VIRGINIA - RUNNING AS A REPUBLICAN? NEW COMPETITION FOR MITT?? WELL IT'S ABOUT TIME the GOP puts a qualified candidate up there!</Title><Msg>Virgil Goode- PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE in VIRGINIA - RUNNING AS A REPUBLICAN? NEW COMPETITION FOR MITT?? WELL IT'S ABOUT TIME the GOP puts a qualified candidate up there! on the conservative constitution ticket in 25 -30 states trump: The Republicans must get Virgil Goode out of the race in Virginia. He will take votes away from @MittRomney. QUELLE DOMMAGE</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468100973</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:41:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347468147038-73</Id><Title>We kill more in USA Cities than get killed at our embassies.</Title><Msg>Not much anyone can do if they cant protect American cities.</Msg><Username>smkpit</Username><Timestamp>1347468147038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:42:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347468523189-74</Id><Topic><Title>The lead is disappearing</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347467015673</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:23:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Today is Sept.12th,cretin.....Obama 46 and Romney 45 .Check out RealClearPolitics.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347468523189</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347468529380-75</Id><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Msg>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347468770267-76</Id><Topic><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Then why are you spending so much time bashing Romney under your different ids??LOL Just sit back and enjoy your victory.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347468770267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:52:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347468834469-77</Id><Topic><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just use magoo, how many more lies will you be posting today? thanks in advance.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468834469</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:53:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347469069993-78</Id><Topic><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You didn't answer the question .Instead you lied about your ids...again.Bye.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347469069993</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:57:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347469274449-79</Id><Topic><Title>"The United States condemns in the strongest terms this outrageous and shocking attack," Obama said with Secretary of State Hillary Clinton at his side in hastily arranged public remarks in the Rose Garden of the White House. "Today, we mourn four more Americans who represent the very best of the United States of America. We will not waver in our commitment to see that justice is done for this terrible act. And make no mistake: Justice will be done."</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468019656</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:40:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why US support the al-Qaid to overthrow the Gaddafi. Gaddafi already warn the West the insurgent is al-Qaid. No one willing to listen.</Msg><Username>hzhou6310</Username><Timestamp>1347469274449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:01:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347469453743-80</Id><Topic><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I answered the question, I only use MAGOO, no other userids........... Why insist on lying?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347469453743</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:04:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347469611110-81</Id><Title>Last poll. Real #'s from newsmax</Title><Msg>If the election were held today, who would you vote for? Barack Obama - Joe Biden 458,463(29%) Mitt Romney - Paul Ryan 1,041,199(67%) Other 44,776(2%)</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347469611110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:06:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347469621405-82</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just subscribed. I am hoping for the best.</Msg><Username>lethahjg63372</Username><Timestamp>1347469621405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347469854426-83</Id><Title>What is this guys problem?</Title><Msg>Palin is better at foreign policy Foreign Policy Hands Voice Disbelief At Romney Cairo Statement “Bungle… utter disaster…not ready for prime time… not presidential… Lehman moment.” And that's just the Republicans. Posted Sep 12, 2012 11:10am EDT Mitt Romney's sharply-worded attack on President Obama over a pair of deadly riots in Muslim countries last night has backfired badly among foreign policy hands of both parties, who cast it as hasty and off-key, released before the facts were clear at what has become a moment of tragedy. Romney keyed his statement to the American Embassy in Cairo's condemnation of an anti-Muslim video that served as the trigger for the latest in a series of regional riots over obscure perceived slights to the faith. But his statement — initially embargoed to avoid release on September 11, then released yesterday evening anyway — came just before news that the American Ambassador to Libya had been killed and broke with a tradition of unity around national tragedies, and of avoiding hasty statements on foreign policy. It was the second time Romney has been burned by an early statement on a complex crisis: Romney denounced the Obama Administration's handling of a Chinese dissident's escape just as the Administration negotiated behind the scenes for his departure from the country. "They were just trying to score a cheap news cycle hit based on the embassy statement and now it’s just completely blown up," said a very senior Republican foreign policy hand, who called the statement an "utter disaster" and a "Lehman moment" — a parallel to the moment when John McCain, amid the 2008 financial crisis, failed to come across as a steady leader. He and other members of both parties cited the Romney campaign's recent dismissals of foreign policy's relevance. One adviser dismissed the subject to BuzzFeed as a "shiny object," while another told Politico that the subject was the "president's turf," drawing a rebuke from Weekly Standard editor Bill Kristol. "I guess we see now that it is because they’re incompetent at talking effectively about foreign policy," said the Republican. "This is just unbelievable — when they decide to play on it they completely bungle it." "It’s deeply unfortunate when the circumstance of the statement becomes the story," said Rick Perry's former foreign policy adviser, Victoria Coates, who is now an adjunct fellow at the Foundation for the Defense of Democracies, and who suggested that Romney should simply have "gone earlier rather than save it for midnight" to avoid appearing to play politics on September 11. "It’s unfortunate that it’s playing out this way, and hopefully they can get back on message, because their point is sound," she said. Other conservatives were less sympathetic. "It's bad," said a former aide to Senator John McCain's 2008 presidential campaign. "Just on a factual level that the statement was not a response but preceding, or one could make the case precipitating. And just calling it a 'disgrace' doesn't really cut it. Not ready for prime time." A third Republican, a former Bush State Department official, told BuzzFeed, "It wasn't presidential of Romney to go political immediately — a tragedy of this magnitude should be something the nation collectively grieves before politics enters the conversation." The Republicans declined to speak for attribution, for fear of being publicly disloyal to their party's nominee. Veteran Democratic foreign policy hands, operating under no such restriction, called Romney's quick move all but disqualifying. "He did jump the gun. It revealed yet again that his foreign policy team is not ready for prime time," said David Rothkopf, a former Clinton State Department official. "It is ugly and amateurish. It also seems strangely out of character with Romney who elsewhere in the campaign seems inclined to be restrained to a fault." Heather Hurlburt, who heads the National Security Network, a Democratic group, said the statement "shows not just poor judgment and a willingness to use tragedy for political gains, regardless of the security consequences — but also poor management. He has policy people on his team who know better. Clearly they weren't consulted."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347469854426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347470214974-84</Id><Topic><Title>What is this guys problem?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347469854426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:10:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>is there any doubt he would mess up foreign policy and put us in another useless war?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347470214974</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:16:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347470729080-85</Id><Topic><Title>Last poll. Real #'s from newsmax</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347469611110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the funny thing is the baggers actually will believe this, Now that's funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347470729080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347471991001-86</Id><Title>Johnson on the ballot in 48 states, woopsie, Obama leads by 8 points!!!</Title><Msg>Obama only won by 7% last time, Washington (CNN) – Gary Johnson's poll numbers may not give him much-of-a shot at winning the presidency, but in the latest CNN/ORC Poll, he is registering enough of a following to possibly tip the balance in an increasingly close election. Three percent of likely voters responded that they would vote for Johnson, the Libertarian Party's candidate for president, in November. That number is slightly higher among registered voters, with 4% identifying with the former governor of New Mexico. – Follow the Ticker on Twitter: @PoliticalTicker – Check out the CNN Electoral Map and Calculator and game out your own strategy for November. The poll also finds that Johnson's inclusion, along with the Green Party's candidate Jill Stein, hurts Republican candidate Mitt Romney more than it does President Barack Obama. Obama leads Romney 52% to 46% when Romney and Obama are the only candidates in question, but Romney's support goes down three percentage points with the inclusion of the third party candidates. Obama's support only drops one point. "The inclusion of the two minor-party candidates turns a six-point margin for President Obama into an eight-point lead," said Keating Holland, CNN's Polling Director. Since third party candidates are typically not on the ballot in all 50 states, those numbers can be slight deceiving when relating them to the support the candidates will receive on Election Day.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347471991001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:46:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472252295-87</Id><Topic><Title>Johnson on the ballot in 48 states, woopsie, Obama leads by 8 points!!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347471991001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:46:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget Virgil Goode running in Virginia, Virgil Goode will deliver the GOODS (Virginia) to OBAMA as he takes valuable votes away from MITT ROMNEY in KEY SWING STATE VIRGINIA!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347472252295</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:50:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347472295391-88</Id><Title>RASMUSSEN NOW HAS ROMNEY ON TOP!! WOW, POLLS ARE REALLY LOOKING GOOD FOR ROMNEY</Title><Msg>Strange how bad Obimbo is. Libyan ambassador killed, murdered. I thought the President gave those jobs to his friends? Don't most Presidential supporters get a cushy 'Ambassador' type job around the world? On the other hand, Libya?, hardly an easy spot as we can now see. SEND IN THE KILLERS! No need to send in 100,000 troops...just the operatives in black masks in the middle of the night, the silent drone.......OUR ENEMIES WILL NO LONGER BE AMONG THE LIVING... But can Obimbo pull it off? That goober can't even tie his own shoes, he has Velcro shoes</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347472295391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472426900-89</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN NOW HAS ROMNEY ON TOP!! WOW, POLLS ARE REALLY LOOKING GOOD FOR ROMNEY</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347472295391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:51:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>HINT: when OBAMA has 45% and ROMNEY has 45% it means OBAMA is on top!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347472426900</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:53:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472450046-90</Id><Topic><Title>Even Laura Ingraham admits that MITT ROMNEY is useless If this is the best you repubs can dredge up as a candidate, it's pretty clear that the party is finished.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347468529380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 12:48:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Conservative talk show host Laura Ingraham tore into Republican presidential candidate Mitt Romney on her Monday radio show, arguing that the 2012 presidential race was what she called a "gimme election." Speaking to the GOP, Ingraham said, "If you can't beat Barack Obama with this record, then shut down the party. Shut it down. Start new, with new people." Ingraham focused her dissatisfaction towards the political consultants Romney hired to run his campaign.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo27</Username><Timestamp>1347472450046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472525224-91</Id><Topic><Title>Last poll. Real #'s from newsmax</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347469611110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:06:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Keep beating that 'forlorn' drum, Dumb Ivan. We love you, man, but wow, you are so out of it. We're ok with that. I know it hurts to be you, but never fear, dude, we are on your side. We promise to make sure you've got a place to live, three hots and a cot.......after Romney takes over...no kidding man. Us Tea Party folks have big hearts. We care about our unfortunate lesser, drooling, incompetent, bumbling, confused little brothers.....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347472525224</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472613093-92</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow free of charge. I love it. Thanks</Msg><Username>simonneaks70845</Username><Timestamp>1347472613093</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:56:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347472628006-93</Id><Topic><Title>deadpainting with his endless personal attacks</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo9</Username><Timestamp>1338918322000</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-06-05 13:45:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama ain't my ideal candidate by a long shot, as I've said before many times on this hyere board, and his pro-corporatist, pro-Wall Street inclinations have become pretty clear during his first term (NOTE - first of TWO). But he HAS done a credible job under insanely bad financial/economic circumstances, AND with Congressional RepuginCONs pushing nose-over full-force on the yoke all the while Obama has been struggling to keep the plane in the air. Shameful (shameless) CONs. BTW, hlarious how you CONs try to get the "in over his head" meme to stick to Obama... If ever there was a textbook example of a President who was in over his head, George W. (the "W" stands for "Warren G.") Bush would BE that example.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347472628006</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:57:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347473291285-94</Id><Topic><Title>RASMUSSEN NOW HAS ROMNEY ON TOP!! WOW, POLLS ARE REALLY LOOKING GOOD FOR ROMNEY</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347472295391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 13:51:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess you didn't read the poll, eh? Romney, when you add 'leaners' to the poll, has a 49% total and Obimbo comes in at 45% WOW..fun to watch Democrats self immolate</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347473291285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:08:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347473428062-95</Id><Title>SECURITY COMES FROM STRENGTH..NOT APOLOGY, NOT TIMIDNESS, NOT HESITANCY...</Title><Msg>Obimbo's behaviour is a recipe for disaster, and now we are seeing that come true. Sorry for the death of American ambassador, but really, Obimbo knows nothing! We need Romney in charge!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347473428062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347474947067-96</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm looking for great articles. Nice to be here.</Msg><Username>mingkkn834</Username><Timestamp>1347474947067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347476764675-97</Id><Topic><Title>SECURITY COMES FROM STRENGTH..NOT APOLOGY, NOT TIMIDNESS, NOT HESITANCY...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347473428062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, junior, why did you stand down, eh?</Msg><Username>narniaway</Username><Timestamp>1347476764675</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347476787257-98</Id><Topic><Title>SECURITY COMES FROM STRENGTH..NOT APOLOGY, NOT TIMIDNESS, NOT HESITANCY...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347473428062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior stood down because he is a timid Democrat.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347476787257</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347476858841-99</Id><Title>OK, LETS LOOK AT THIS ANOTHER WAY. SUPPOSE A CHINESE EMBASSY IN LIBYA WAS BURNED......</Title><Msg>How would the Chinese handle this? Just thinking out loud</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347476858841</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347477166258-100</Id><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Msg>and this is what the W.P. says, LOL Mitt Romney seems repeatedly unsteady on foreign policy — the gaffes this summer in England and now his popping off about a very fluid and tragic situation in Libya and Egypt. As violence was brewing in Cairo and Benghazi, our embassy in Egypt issued a statement condemning the actions of religious bigotry against Islam in an effort to calm the situation. Mitt Romney seized on this statement as “disgraceful,” an appeasement by the Obama administration of a mob attack that killed our ambassador to Libya and other Americans. Problem is, Romney had his timing wrong, or one can only hope that is the reason for his stupidity. Romney must not have known that the administration’s first statement was made to try to prevent the violence from escalating. And he must not have known that the administration condemned the attacks forcefully when it learned the situation on the ground. If that is the case, then we can only say that Romney hasn’t learned that timing is everything in a fluid international crisis. Romney’s foreign policy approach seems to be shoot your mouth off first, before trying to put your foot in it.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347477611877-101</Id><Topic><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Seems you are living in a very different universe. Everything I have heard is how the Obama administration BUNGLED the response to the terror attacks in Egypt and Libya. They are now backtracking from earlier statements. Spread some more lies for your Loser in chief.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347477611877</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:20:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347478375382-102</Id><Title>Who's Advising Mitt Romney on Foreign Policy?Dan Senor is one of Romney's closest advisers on foreign policySenor is the former spokesman for the American government in Iraq (the Coalition Provisional Authority at the beginning of the Iraq war under George W. Bush) and is a particularly close adviser to Romney on the Middle East</Title><Msg>Who's Advising Mitt Romney on Foreign Policy? With Mitt Romney's comments on Libya drawing attention today-specifically, his criticism of Obama-it's worth examining whom Romney listens to on such matters. Dan Senor is one of Romney's closest advisers on foreign policy. Since Paul Ryan has been selected as the GOP's vice presidential candidate, Senor has been traveling with Ryan-but today, he left the trail because of the "foreign policy developments" and is in Boston and NYC. Senor is the former spokesman for the American government in Iraq (the Coalition Provisional Authority at the beginning of the Iraq war under George W. Bush) and is a particularly close adviser to Romney on the Middle East. (He has traveled with Romney to Israel three times, as well as written a book on Israel that Romney often cites). With Ryan, he consults on domestic and foreign policy issues. Last month, the New York Times described Senor as an "advocate of neoconservative thinking that has sought to push presidents to the right for years on Middle East policy." Senor led a foreign policy briefing for Ryan on the plane yesterday from Seattle along with Jamie Fly, executive director, Foreign Policy Initiative and Reuel Marc Gerecht from the Foundation for Defense of Democracies. Romney keeps a large group of foreign-policy advisers, eight of whom participated in the early neoconservative group Project for a New American Century think tank, founded in 1997 and headed by William Kristol, the Nation's Ari Berman reported in May. In the same month, The New York Times' Magazine's David Sanger reported on discontent within that big team, with some complaining that Romney only listens to Bolton. Romney has long sought to distinguish himself from the president by drawing a contrast between weakness and strength, and his posture is reflected in the team he's chosen, peppered with luminaries from the Bush administration. The "special advisers"-who do not comprise the entire foreign policy team-are listed on Romney's campaign website: Cofer Black Christopher Burnham Michael Chertoff Eliot Cohen Norm Coleman John Danilovich Paula J. Dobriansky Eric Edelman Michael Hayden Kerry Healey Kim Holmes Robert Joseph Robert Kagan John Lehman Andrew Natsios Meghan O'Sullivan Walid Phares Pierre Prosper Mitchell Reiss Daniel Senor Jim Talent Vin Weber Richard Williamson Dov Zakheim Michael Hayden served as CIA director under president Bush, who nominated him in 2006. Michael Chertoff served as Bush's second Homeland Security secretary. Jim Talent and Norm Coleman are former Republican senators. At least one of them presaged Romney's attack line on Libya. Richard Williamson, who served as Bush's special envoy to Sudan and ambassador to the U.N. Security Council, leveled an attack at Obama last night before it was known that Americans had been killed. "The events in Egypt and Libya show the failure of the Egyptian and Libyan governments to uphold their obligations to keep our diplomatic missions safe and secure and the regard in which the United States is held under President Obama in these two countries," he told Foreign Policy's Josh Rogin. "It's all part of a broader scheme of the president's failure to be an effective leader for U.S. interests in the Middle East." Michael Falcone contributed to this post.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347478375382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347478522539-103</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are the best.</Msg><Username>fridamow0713</Username><Timestamp>1347478522539</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:35:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347478535279-104</Id><Topic><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dude it is a cut and paste from the very conservative Washington Post, LOL the entire media is ripping Romney apart on his response, check out the WSJ They mock him with the headline "Romney of Arabia" LOL you know the WSJ the print version of Faux news. LOL so you are telling us that Rush is the only news source you use, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347478535279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:35:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347478748863-105</Id><Title>why would anyone ever vote for someone</Title><Msg>who does not believe in contract and keeping your word. obama thinks real estate contracts dont matter he thinks an agreement must only be kept if you can afford it. if not it is null and void. liberals dont see a problem with this? enjoy his historicly highest HC tax on the middle class. you dumb dumbs still support this dead beat. how can you believe in someone who thinks you can avoid a contract at any time because your situation is inconvienced by it. why would we even have law or money if that is reality.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1347478748863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:39:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347478838309-106</Id><Topic><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Juniormagooivan, Is Bill Ayers really dead?? Lot of people think you are full of poo. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347478838309</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:40:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347478869351-107</Id><Topic><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Last I knew Noonan and the WSJ were conservative voices, LOL Noonan: Romney not helping himself Comments (159) By MACKENZIE WEINGER and DYLAN BYERS | 9/12/12 11:31 AM EDT The Wall Street Journal’s Peggy Noonan is criticizing Mitt Romney’s response to the death of a U.S. diplomat in Libya, telling Fox News today she doesn’t feel that the Republican presidential nominee “has been doing himself any favors” in the past few hours. “I was thinking as he spoke, I think I belong to the old school of thinking that in times of great drama and heightened crisis, and in times when something violent has happened to your people, I always think discretion is the better way to go,” Noonan said. “When you step forward in the midst of a political environment and start giving statements on something dramatic and violent that has happened, you're always leaving yourself open to accusations that you are trying to exploit things politically.” In a statement last night, Romney slammed the Obama administration for sympathizing "with those who waged the attacks" rather than condemning the attacks outright. Romney doubled-down on that attack today during a press conference, telling reporters the statement was “akin to apology" and that it was “disgraceful to apologize for American values.” But Romney's effort to politicize the violence in Libya was met with blowback not just from the Obama administration but from the media. "[Romney's] doubling down on criticism... is likely to be seen as one of the most craven and ill-advised tactical moves in this entire campaign," Time magazine's Mark Halperin wrote on his blog. (PHOTOS: Anti-U.S. attacks in Cairo, Libya) Noonan's criticism delivers a harder blow, however, coming as it does from high within the ranks of the conservative establishment. Indeed, it is just the latest in a string of criticisms Romney has faced from the right's most influential media outlets in recent days, including The Wall Street Journal editorial page and the Weekly Standard. “I don't feel that Mr. Romney has been doing himself any favors, say in the past few hours, perhaps since last night,” Noonan told Fox News. “Sometimes when really bad things happen, when hot things happen, cool words or no words is the way to go.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347478869351</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:41:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347479372439-108</Id><Topic><Title>Who's Advising Mitt Romney on Foreign Policy?Dan Senor is one of Romney's closest advisers on foreign policySenor is the former spokesman for the American government in Iraq (the Coalition Provisional Authority at the beginning of the Iraq war under George W. Bush) and is a particularly close adviser to Romney on the Middle East</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347478375382</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:32:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Mitt gets elected we will be in at least one more war within 6 months, probably two more, expect a draft, Glad I'm rich I'll spend the winters in New Zealand and the summers in Italy</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347479372439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:49:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347479630475-109</Id><Title>Check the picture</Title><Msg>Foxnews website has a picture of the U.S ambassador in Libya being dragged around by the mob. Truly disgusting!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347479767475-110</Id><Title>ROMNEY CAUSES a MAJOR GAFFE with the content of his lastest attack on the Obama administration. SO GLAD MITT is not running a negative campaign though!</Title><Msg>ROMNEY CAUSES a MAJOR GAFFE with the content of his lastest attack on the Obama administration. SO GLAD MITT is not running a negative campaign though! Here’s Romney’s language: “It's disgraceful that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize with those who waged the attacks.” The statement contains three major errors (or can we say lies?). Not only does it attribute an embassy statement to the Obama administration and falsify its timing, but it also ignores the administration’s actual “first response” to the Libyan violence (a sharp condemnation by Hillary Clinton). As if that weren’t bad enough for a single sentence, Romney also libels the president by accusing him of sympathizing with terrorists. Perhaps stuff like this will mobilize Romney’s base, but its Palin-esque, trigger-happy invective will drive away swing voters he supposedly covets. And keep in mind that Romney rushed to release this statement before the facts were even in — before we learned that the American ambassador and three others were killed in Libya. It’s hard to imagine how Romney’s statement could be more incendiary or tasteless in the tinder-box context of the moment. Even the right-wing blogger Erick Erickson tweeted that Romney should avoid this kind of bluster: “I think the Romney camp has to be very delicate in how it approaches this issue. Hard for partisans to see, but POTUS is POTUS.” If even a hothead like Erickson suggests that Romney is being reckless, you can see he now has blundered into yet another self-inflicted political mess.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347479767475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:56:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347479866635-111</Id><Topic><Title>Check the picture</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What does that have to do with how that man is being treated.What a kool-ade chugging imbecile you are.Too bad it wasn't you instead of him.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479866635</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:57:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347479886510-112</Id><Title>from CONSERVATIVE Bill Kristol "I guess we see now that it is because they’re incompetent at talking effectively about foreign policy," said the Republican. "This is just unbelievable — when they decide to play on it they completely bungle it."</Title><Msg>from CONSERVATIVE Bill Kristol "I guess we see now that it is because they’re incompetent at talking effectively about foreign policy," said the Republican. "This is just unbelievable — when they decide to play on it they completely bungle it."</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347479886510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:58:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480162364-113</Id><Topic><Title>LOLOL! ROMENY DOES A PALIN ON LIBYA!!! LOLOLOLOL!!!! MITT IS DUMBER THAN PALIN!!! YOU TEABILLY LOSERS SURE KNOW HOW TO PICK THEM LOLOL</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347478907277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:41:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thank you very much Ignore this</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1347480162364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:02:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480218287-114</Id><Topic><Title>LOLOL! ROMENY DOES A PALIN ON LIBYA!!! LOLOLOLOL!!!! MITT IS DUMBER THAN PALIN!!! YOU TEABILLY LOSERS SURE KNOW HOW TO PICK THEM LOLOL</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347478907277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:41:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Here’s Romney’s language: “It's disgraceful that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize with those who waged the attacks.” The statement contains three major errors (or can we say lies?). Not only does it attribute an embassy statement to the Obama administration and falsify its timing, but it also ignores the administration’s actual “first response” to the Libyan violence (a sharp condemnation by Hillary Clinton). As if that weren’t bad enough for a single sentence, Romney also libels the president by accusing him of sympathizing with terrorists. Perhaps stuff like this will mobilize Romney’s base, but its Palin-esque, trigger-happy invective will drive away swing voters he supposedly covets. And keep in mind that Romney rushed to release this statement before the facts were even in — before we learned that the American ambassador and three others were killed in Libya. It’s hard to imagine how Romney’s statement could be more incendiary or tasteless in the tinder-box context of the moment. Even the right-wing blogger Erick Erickson tweeted that Romney should avoid this kind of bluster: “I think the Romney camp has to be very delicate in how it approaches this issue. Hard for partisans to see, but POTUS is POTUS.” If even a hothead like Erickson suggests that Romney is being reckless, you can see he now has blundered into yet another self-inflicted political mess. from CONSERVATIVE Bill Kristol "I guess we see now that it is because they’re incompetent at talking effectively about foreign policy," said the Republican. "This is just unbelievable — when they decide to play on it they completely bungle it."</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347480218287</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480245293-115</Id><Topic><Title>LOLOL! ROMENY DOES A PALIN ON LIBYA!!! LOLOLOLOL!!!! MITT IS DUMBER THAN PALIN!!! YOU TEABILLY LOSERS SURE KNOW HOW TO PICK THEM LOLOL</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347478907277</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:41:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>PALIN URGES MITT to call OBAMA a COMMUNIST! HERMAN CAIN URGES MITT to state that if you are not successful, it is YOUR fault!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347480245293</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:04:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480279699-116</Id><Topic><Title>Check the picture</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These people are animals. Where is the outrage for the far left DEMANDING an APOLOGY. And to think Obama was backing these people. Truly disgusting.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347480279699</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:04:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480494213-117</Id><Topic><Title>Romney taken to the woodshed by Conservative Commentators.</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347477166258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:12:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Apparently you are not listening to ALL the news. You just get all your far left views from those HACKS at MSNBC. The Obama administration had to pull back from its take and comments yesterday. Apparently you MISSED THAT. Typical of you head in the sand attitude.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347480494213</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:08:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347480671320-118</Id><Title>PALIN URGES MITT to call OBAMA a COMMUNIST! HERMAN CAIN URGES MITT to state that if you are not successful, it is YOUR fault!</Title><Msg>PALIN URGES MITT to call OBAMA a COMMUNIST! HERMAN CAIN URGES MITT to state that if you are not successful, it is YOUR fault!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347480671320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:11:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347480717932-119</Id><Topic><Title>Check the picture</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The loons on this board are too busy slamming Romney to worry about the people these animals killed.That picture is probably only an inkling of what those people went through. It was Obama who helped" free" Libya and Egypt. Now look whats going on.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347480717932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347481026983-120</Id><Topic><Title>Check the picture</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You find humor in how the ambassador was being treated in that picture, you sick fk??</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347481026983</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:17:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347481188124-121</Id><Title>Obama has lost control......</Title><Msg>Doesn't look like he has a handle on foreign policy. This is what happens when you elect a community organizer who spends half his 4 year term campaigning. This bozo has to go.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347481188124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:19:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347481307330-122</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nice one. I will subscribe now.</Msg><Username>claudeadp458</Username><Timestamp>1347481307330</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347481574212-123</Id><Topic><Title>Our navy isn't good enough????????</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347465420820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior, DNC issued an apology this afternoon. Another oooooopsie for you.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347481574212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347481685299-124</Id><Topic><Title>Check the picture</Title><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347479630475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior has the i.q. of a turnip .</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347481685299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347481913331-125</Id><Title>After 9-11 America rallied around the President!!</Title><Msg>after the terrorist anniversary attack yesterday Mitt and his Neocon advisors tried to turn an American tragedy into a political attack, Conservative commentators are saying this might have been the day he definitively lost the election</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347481913331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347481960044-126</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has lost control......</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347481188124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He never had control. He's been incompetent from day one.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347481960044</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:32:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482090450-127</Id><Topic><Title>from CONSERVATIVE Bill Kristol "I guess we see now that it is because they’re incompetent at talking effectively about foreign policy," said the Republican. "This is just unbelievable — when they decide to play on it they completely bungle it."</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo17</Username><Timestamp>1347479886510</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:58:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean this Bill Kristol? He must be part of the lame stream media just attacking Mitt, LOL William Kristol (born December 23, 1952) is an American neoconservative[1] political analyst and commentator. He is the founder and editor of the political magazine The Weekly Standard and a regular commentator on the Fox News Channel. Kristol is associated with a number of prominent conservative think tanks. He was chairman of the New Citizenship Project from 1997 to 2005. In 1997, he co-founded the Project for the New American Century (PNAC) with Robert Kagan. He is a member of the board of trustees for the free-market Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, a member of the Policy Advisory Board for the Ethics and Public Policy Center, and a director of the Foreign Policy Initiative. He is also one of the three board members of Keep America Safe, a think tank co-founded by Liz Cheney and Debra Burlingame, and serves on the board of the Emergency Committee for Israel and the Susan B. Anthony List.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482090450</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:34:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482132099-128</Id><Topic><Title>After 9-11 America rallied around the President!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347481913331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is Bill Ayers still dead,fool???? What a stupid post that was by you last night....even worse than usual.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347482132099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:35:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482262265-129</Id><Topic><Title>romney stone cold busted for lying</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347479627778</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 15:53:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>even the conservatives are running from Mitt, clear we can't have him in charge of foreign policy</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482262265</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482262534-130</Id><Topic><Title>After 9-11 America rallied around the President!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347481913331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obimbo is a very weak leader. He skips more than half of all security briefs. He did not call a meeting of his so called 'jobs council' for six months. He will leave office in November as the worst President in history....worse than Jimmy.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347482262534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:37:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482268719-131</Id><Topic><Title>After 9-11 America rallied around the President!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347481913331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And he was talking about my education!!!HILARIOUS!!!!!! And the dummy didn't know Ayers was still alive.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347482268719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:37:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482361905-132</Id><Topic><Title>SECURITY COMES FROM STRENGTH..NOT APOLOGY, NOT TIMIDNESS, NOT HESITANCY...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347473428062</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 14:10:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Besides leading backwards, what has your man, Obimbo done, exactly?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347482361905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:39:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482437858-133</Id><Topic><Title>LNMAO! FRUTICUP GREG SURFACES LONG ENOUGN TO HUMILIATE HIMSELF LOLOLOL!!!</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347482264899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:37:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I bet Greg knew Ayers wasn't dead....unlike you.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL You be ignorant,dude. LOLOLOLOLOLOL...BTW,what does LNMAO stand for????</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347482437858</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:40:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347482465959-134</Id><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Msg>(CBS News) In response to Mitt Romney's criticism of the Obama administration for its handling of recent violence in Egypt and Libya, President Obama told CBS News on Wednesday that Romney "seems to have a tendency to shoot first and aim later." "There's a broader lesson to be learned here," Mr. Obama told "60 Minutes" correspondent Steve Kroft. "And I think -- you know, Governor Romney seems to have a tendency to shoot first and aim later. And as president, one of the things I've learned is you can't do that. That, you know, it's important for you to make sure that the statements that you make are backed up by the facts. And that you've thought through the ramifications before you make 'em." Asked if Romney's attacks were irresponsible, the president replied, "I'll let the American people judge that." Romney released a statement last night - on Sept. 11 - asserting "that the Obama administration's first response was not to condemn attacks on our diplomatic missions, but to sympathize with those who waged the attacks." The criticism was in response to a statement put out by the U.S. embassy in Egypt, not the Obama administration. In addition, the statement was released before violence began in an apparent effort to head off the attacks.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482589884-135</Id><Topic><Title>After 9-11 America rallied around the President!!</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347481913331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:31:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>O'Loser said and I quote, " Governor Romney seems to have a tendency to shoot first and aim later. And as president, one of the things I've learned is you can't do that. REALLY Mr. President, like your " the cops acted stupidily " comment? How about your " shout out " before the fort hood shooting press conference. Obumbles should have been out last night condemning the attacks and the killings of Americans. As usual he waits to see which way the wind is blowing and then he acts. He is NOT a leader.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347482589884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:43:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347482680347-136</Id><Title>FREE SPEECH.....OK for everyone, but not if you say anything bad about a Moslem</Title><Msg>you can insult, blaspheme..#$%$ christ', 'life of bryan'.....you can abuse, belittle mock, insult and generally crap all over the christian faith, but NOOOOOOO, not the Moslems..you must RESPECT their beliefs...cannot make mocking films about Mohammed..oh noooooooooo!!!! IT SHOULD BE AGAINST THE LAW TO SAY ANYTHING BAD ABOUT MOSLEMS...OOOOOOOO PUNISH THOSE FILMAKERS....say the liberal creeeeps!!!!! Porno is great, abuse of Christians and Jews is just fine, say the liberal creeeeps!!!! but don't upset a fricking Moslem.....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347482680347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482697507-137</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So who helped oust the regimes in Libya and Egypt??? Obama or Romney??Obama was warned there could be worse than Mubarak and Qaddafi....well???????</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347482697507</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:44:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347482740034-138</Id><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Msg>OPINION Noonan: 'Romney Looked Weak Today' WSJ 'Declarations' Columnist Peggy Noonan says Mitt Romney "didn't do himself any favors" with his response to the U.S. Embassy attacks in Libya, and describes why she believes the Republican presidential candidate is ceding foreign policy to the Democrats in this election season. UP NEXT Opinion: Moving On From 9/11?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482798089-139</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, you mean the way you, OBIMBO, impugned the policeman who questioned the angry black Harvard professor?? YOU MEAN THE WAY YOU SHOOT OFF YOUR MOUTH OBIMBO, ALL THE TIME like the Treyvon Martin looked just like your son? Shoot first, President Obimbo, then aim later, have a beer at the White House? Gonna have a beer at the White House, Obimbo, with those folks who killed, murdered, your ambassador??? Just wondering</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347482798089</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:46:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347482849403-140</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter ousted the Shah of Iran. Khomeini took over and look what we have today.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347482849403</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347482965371-141</Id><Title>ROMNEY ALWAYS LOOKS STRONGER THAN OBIMBO....Romney does not bow</Title><Msg>Obimbo is weak....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347482965371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:49:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483009461-142</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big news today should be Bill Ayers still walking around after dumbivanMago declared him dead.LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347483009461</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:50:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483110736-143</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jimmy Carter ousted the Shah of Iran. Khomeini took over and look what we have today. Wow and I thought the people overthrew the dictator the U.S. put into power, turns out Carter was on the side of the revolutionaries, (LOL you can never misunderestimate a bagger LOL)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347483110736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347483426222-144</Id><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Msg>I'm here, come try me.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347483459094-145</Id><Title>DNC, CAN'T TELL RUSSIAN NAVY FROM US NAVY...OH WELL, they don't care either</Title><Msg>Which is why they have to go...ALL DEMOCRATS have to be tossed out of DC if this nation is to survive....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347483459094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483493470-146</Id><Topic><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Millions of us are on your side...BILLIONS of us, in fact.</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347483493470</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:58:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483641320-147</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You stepped in it again,Magoo.The shah wanted help and Carter left him swinging in the breeze and then the radicals took over...just like Libya and Egypt. You should do some reading before posting, and you wont look so stupid.....Bill Ayers for instance.. that was funny,really stupid but funny.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347483641320</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:00:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347483782299-148</Id><Title>Just one question?</Title><Msg>How is that global warming deal working out for you pecker-woods?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347483782299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483827017-149</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>this adds to his dismal record on creating jobs, his dismal record on the debt,and the dismal record on race relations, oh boy do we need change.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1347483827017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:03:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483871535-150</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would think Magoo has the Alzheimer problem. Carey knew Ayers was still alive,right .It was dumbivan who messed up. Aint that right,Magoo???</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347483871535</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:04:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347483997621-151</Id><Topic><Title>ready, shoot, aim</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482465959</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:41:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just adds to his dismal record on everything</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1347483997621</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:06:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484027177-152</Id><Topic><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that I mean it but have a right to say it.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347484027177</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484027210-153</Id><Topic><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not that I mean it but have a right to say it.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347484027210</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484106440-154</Id><Topic><Title>Just one question?</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347483782299</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:03:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>about as good as arab spring</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1347484106440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:08:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484129853-155</Id><Topic><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So does Juniors daddy.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347484129853</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:08:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484283377-156</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try to focus, Crankfurter. The thread topic is idiot opportunist empty suit (and future deity) Myth RobbedMe's ill-advised and self-destructive attempts at criticizing Obama foreign policy.</Msg><Username>jason_baby2003</Username><Timestamp>1347484283377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347484341860-157</Id><Title>Obama leading from behind, AGAIN.</Title><Msg>Waits until he reads the papers and then comes out with his response. What a weak community organizer. Can't wait until SHELLACKING 2.0 in November.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347484341860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:12:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484512963-158</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jason, What happened in Libya is Obama's foreign policy?? Thanks for admitting it. Will Obama apologize to the families of the dead Americans or just to the Libyans?</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347484512963</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484616855-159</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I never missed a single article from you. Thank you and please keep it coming.</Msg><Username>claudeadp458</Username><Timestamp>1347484616855</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347484637826-160</Id><Topic><Title>Obama leading from behind, AGAIN.</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347484341860</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:12:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bring back Khaddafi!!!! LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347484637826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:17:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347484990172-161</Id><Title>IF YOU KICK A DEM IN THE CROTCH...REALLY, REALLY, REALLY HARD, DOES</Title><Msg>it hurt your foot? MAYBE, but it's ok......</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347484990172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:23:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347485339090-162</Id><Topic><Title>Romney Looked Weak Today, WSJ</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1347482740034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:45:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What foreign policy you apologist? Afghanistan is a mess, France hates Obama, he has shunned Israel, Egypt is a boiling pot, Iran could be the beginnings of WWIII, Syria is murdering tens of thousands of its own citizens. Oh I get it, I remember his foreign policy, " We Americans apologize for everything we have done ". Congrats on being the IDIOT of the day.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347485339090</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347485402268-163</Id><Title>Must read this email sent to me after my post</Title><Msg>May be peace with you I would like to share some very important information with you. If you were to believe in it and accept it, it would make your life better, it would make you happy &amp; it would benefit you. Information that if you were to believe in it and accept it, it would make the life of people around you better, it would make them happy and would bring benefit to them &amp; this will have a ripple effect on the society around you and them hence, making it better for everyone to live and enjoy their life. I would like to speak with you about the 'Purpose of this life'. Look around yourself. Look at the pen, at the paper, at the chair, at the table, at the bed and everything else around it. Look at everything and think about them. You will find each &amp; everything has a purpose. The pen is there to write, the paper is there to be written upon, the chair is there to sit upon and the table is there to eat upon, the bed is there to sleep upon &amp; everything else has a purpose. I guarantee you that we will not find anything that does not have a purpose &amp; these are the items that we as human beings have produced &amp; developed because we need them and would like them to serve a purpose to make our life easy &amp; better. Now let us look at ourselves. Look at our eyes, ears, hands, feet, tongue, nose and everything else in the body. The eyes are there to see, ears are there to hear, hands are there to pick &amp; hold items, feet are there for us to walk &amp; the nose is there to smell. Look &amp; think about each &amp; everything in the body and we will see its purpose. Let us look at the perfect body and think about it. Like we created &amp; produced items for a purpose, our body, our presence in this world has a purpose and there is a Creator who has created us for a reason &amp; the purpose of our life is to use our body to worship the Creator. Creator of the heavens &amp; earth, Master &amp; Sustainer of everyone Say: He is Allah, the One Allah is the Self-Sufficient Master He begets not nor was He begotten</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347485402268</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347485472705-164</Id><Title>Continued</Title><Msg>And there is none comparable unto Him The Creator sees everything, hears everything &amp; knows everything. He wants us to live our life in this world in the best possible way to benefit ourselves, people around us &amp; the whole community. I invite you to accept in the Creator -- Allah (GOD) as your lord and worship him. Accept &amp; worship the Lord of Adam, Noah, Abraham, Moses, Jesus &amp; Muhammad (may peace be upon them). Turn to Allah (God) alone in your prayers &amp; supplication &amp; ask him for everything you need. Let us submit to the Creator. Amazingly enough, all of us are already in a state of submission. Look at the new born baby. The baby comes out of the mother's womb without its consent. Who gave this baby its basic humanly instincts? The baby breathes not that it chooses to but it must breathe in order to live. No one forces the baby to breath. The baby submits itself to the air. We drink water as it is a need of the body and we need it to live. No one forces us to drink water. We eat to live as the body needs it. No one forces us to eat. We submit ourselves to the needs. Now let us change the word 'NEED' to 'ISLAM'. If we were to believe in the Creator as he wants us to believe, it will mean that ; We submit ourselves to the Creator &amp; belive in Islam. The word Islam comes from the word S-A-L-A-M-A, which means peace. We submit ourselves to the will of the Creator to bring about peace in this world &amp; once we die we will have happy after life. I invite you to accept in the Creator -- Allah (GOD) as your lord and worship him. Accept &amp; worship the Lord of Adam, Noah, Abraham, Moses, Jesus &amp; Muhammad (may peace be upon them). Turn to Allah (God) alone in your prayers &amp; supplication &amp; ask him for everything you need. Let us submit to the Creator. I am humbly calling you to shift yourself from the dreadful consequences of polytheism to the beauty of monotheism. Enter Paradise after this life and save yourself from the hellfire by worshipping God alone &amp; believing in the final messenger of Allah. If you believe in the Creator of the heavens &amp; the earth, that He is the Master &amp; the Sustainer, that He is the only one worthy of worship &amp; not any of His Creation, including any of the prophets, from Adam to Moses to Jesus to Muhammad. If you believe, then say it now with your tongue. 'I bear witness that there is no one worthy of worship except Allah and i bear witness that Prophet Muhammad is the final messenger of Allah' Then say the translation in Arabic ' Ash hadu Alla Illaha Illa Allah wa Ash Hadu Anna Muhammadan Rasool ul Allah. This is the testimony that enters a person into the fold of Islam. You will immediately feel relief. After that, take your time to slowly learn the beauty of this religion.</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347485472705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347486397296-165</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I have entered my email address. Waiting for the update.</Msg><Username>jeanettamiy085571</Username><Timestamp>1347486397296</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347486730066-166</Id><Title>Quote from the Bible</Title><Msg>etched on the memorial thats stands in the shadow of WTC-"Then I heard the voice of the Lord saying, Whom shall I send? And who will go for us? And I said, "Here am I, Send me"</Msg><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347486730066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347488157060-167</Id><Topic><Title>Our navy isn't good enough????????</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347465420820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 11:57:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DNC says it was "Vendor error"...pathetic</Msg><Username>nidan7500</Username><Timestamp>1347488157060</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347489004155-168</Id><Title>ROMNEY LOOKS REALLY STRONG..PEGGY NOONAN, LOOKS RATHER 'PEGGY-ISH'</Title><Msg>Yup, Peggy Noonan represents no constituency, which is the reason for the rise of the Tea Party. Liberal media bias is so blatant it no longer registers, and 'Republican' observers like Peggy Noonan, Joe Scarborough and a host of others, represent absolutely no one....so the Tea Party emerges, grass roots, strong and powerful...full of vigor and bullish on America</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347489004155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:30:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347489019751-169</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More more and more articles please.</Msg><Username>mellisaesg442539</Username><Timestamp>1347489019751</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:30:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347489053483-170</Id><Topic><Title>IF YOU KICK A DEM IN THE CROTCH...REALLY, REALLY, REALLY HARD, DOES</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1347484990172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 17:23:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Isn't this an activity that should be going on round the clock, seven days a week? Kicking Democrats, I mean.</Msg><Username>schnitlerbeim</Username><Timestamp>1347489053483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 18:30:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347492776763-171</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm subscribed. Cool</Msg><Username>violakkl8063</Username><Timestamp>1347492776763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 19:32:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347493717083-172</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems, Inc. : Important Info Inside</Title><Username>domingacqf572</Username><Timestamp>1347459405696</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 10:16:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good job. Informational article.</Msg><Username>kareygpy1762</Username><Timestamp>1347493717083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 19:48:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347494426520-173</Id><Topic><Title>**************CLOWN MITT ROMNEY********************</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347493583003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 19:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You've been a lifelong clown, loser.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347494426520</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:00:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347494976278-174</Id><Title>the recently humanized rich c-riminal Romney with Swiss Bank Accounts and businesses in Bermuda and the Cayman Islands, is ready to send our kids to fight for the homeland. He was in France learning french during the Vietnam war so he never got a chance to show us how tough he really is...but he is ready now.</Title><Msg>what a buffoon!</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1347494976278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:09:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347495478532-175</Id><Title>Sitting ducks?????</Title><Msg>Wonder if someone will ask the Obama admin. why our embassies,particularly in Arab countries, weren't on high alert on the Sept.11th anniversary.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347495478532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:17:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347495996788-176</Id><Title>DimWit Mitt Gives Support to Al Qaeda</Title><Msg>As soon as America is attacked, Mitty decides to also attack America's Commander in Chief. What a coward! Disgraceful that Mitt is even considered a candidate for the office. The idiot should resign the position to someone else.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347495996788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347496107341-177</Id><Topic><Title>**************CLOWN MITT ROMNEY********************</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347493583003</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 19:46:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do almost all on this board have the same opinion of you??? Aren't you embarrassed?</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347496107341</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:28:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347496202737-178</Id><Topic><Title>Mike Huckabee Accidentally Tells The Truth About Fox</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo26</Username><Timestamp>1339011925000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-06-06 15:45:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My old Republican worldview was flawed because it was based upon a small and particularly rosy sliver of reality. To preserve that worldview, I had to believe that people had morally earned their “just” desserts, and I had to ignore those whining liberals who tried to point out that the world didn’t actually work that way. I think this shows why Republicans put so much effort into “creat[ing] our own reality,” into fostering distrust of liberals, experts, scientists, and academics, and why they won’t let a campaign “be dictated by fact-checkers” (as a Romney pollster put it). It explains why study after study shows that avid consumers of Republican-oriented media are more poorly informed than people who use other news sources or don’t bother to follow the news at all.</Msg><Username>notarethug</Username><Timestamp>1347496202737</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347496226219-179</Id><Topic><Title>DimWit Mitt Gives Support to Al Qaeda</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347495996788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you related to Junior? He posts a lot of really stupid stuff too.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347496226219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:30:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347496450791-180</Id><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Msg>Mitty and the Ronald Wilson Reagan 666Group are the AntiChrist. Phoney Evangels who attack True Christians.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347496611985-181</Id><Topic><Title>DimWit Mitt Gives Support to Al Qaeda</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347495996788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:26:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey #$%$ you're Al Qaeda lover. Down with Quaddafi and his Al Qaeda supporters!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496611985</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:36:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347496689327-182</Id><Title>JHEWS AGAIN DRAGGING US TO DO THEIR DIRTY WORK...</Title><Msg>Drop a nuke on that patch of dirt and all our problems in the ME will be over. The Wall Street Journal identified the filmmaker as Sam Bacile, an Israeli-American real estate developer. The Journal reported that, in its telephone interview with Bacile, he characterized his film as "a political effort to call attention to the hypocrisies of Islam." "Islam is a cancer," he told the newspaper. "The movie is a political movie. It's not a religious movie." CNN has not been able to contact Bacile and cannot verify that he made the movie. A CNN search of public records on Sam Bacile came up empty.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347496689327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:38:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347496912934-183</Id><Title>Desperate Repubs trying to replay their AntiAmerican Iran Support in 1979</Title><Msg>These Repubs should be JAILED for Treason!!!! Cowards. America is home of the free and brave. We don't cave to Al Qaeda apologist like DimWit Mitt. Resign Axxhole!!! Go back to Utah you AntiChrist!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496912934</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:41:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347497199544-184</Id><Topic><Title>JHEWS AGAIN DRAGGING US TO DO THEIR DIRTY WORK...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347496689327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you really think it had anything to do with that movie? It was 9-11,fool. The nuts were sending us a message.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347497199544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347497249404-185</Id><Title>Go back to Utah you DimWit!!! Mitt Should Quit!!!</Title><Msg>Phoney Americans love Mitt. Al Qaeda must have been laughing when the idiot decides to attack the President of our country. Send Mitt to France for another missionary duty. The idiot lacks leadership and wisdom. Mitt &amp; Akin, two peas in a pod.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347497249404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:47:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347497461322-186</Id><Topic><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You phony bastid.You'd never heard of that ambassador before today .He may have been a great American but you sure didn't know it. BTW,three other Americans died with him. What about them???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347497461322</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:51:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347497510326-187</Id><Topic><Title>JHEWS AGAIN DRAGGING US TO DO THEIR DIRTY WORK...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347496689327</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:38:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boysurfer is an apologist for murderers.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347497510326</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:51:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347498184115-188</Id><Topic><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wonk, what Al Qaeda sect are you from Axxhole? You and DimWitt Mitt should be kicked out of the country. How DARE the Axxhole attack the decison of Americans who are in harms way? The people in the Libya showed more courage than Mitt did during Veitnam. Where was Mitt's honor for America during Veitnam? What a COWARD!!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347498184115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:03:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347498205624-189</Id><Topic><Title>Obama has lost control......</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347481188124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:19:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is NO LEADER, he shows his community organizer colors. He waits a FULL day to give a response to the terrorist killing of 4 Americans. He has NEVER led, he always waits to see which way the wind is blowing.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347498205624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:03:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347498362219-190</Id><Topic><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What a POS you are. Go crawl back into your hole and shed some skin.</Msg><Username>bamapride57</Username><Timestamp>1347498362219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:06:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347498409543-191</Id><Topic><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Another fuggggkgin redneck on this board. You know having sex with your sister is against the law, right?</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1347498409543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347498418895-192</Id><Topic><Title>A Great American was Murdered in Lybia And Mitt The DimWit Sides with Al Qaeda.</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347496450791</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:34:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So what branch of service did your #$%$clown Obama serve in?</Msg><Username>bamapride57</Username><Timestamp>1347498418895</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:06:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347498425512-193</Id><Title>DimWitt Mitt has emboldened the Terrorist. Phoney American Coward?</Title><Msg>Where were you Mitt during Veitnam? Hiding out in France I bet. The American's who died were their to spread our American principles. Where were you Mitt? You blowhard!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347498425512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:07:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347499419570-194</Id><Topic><Title>DimWitt Mitt has emboldened the Terrorist. Phoney American Coward?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347498425512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I spent a year in Vietnam...Oct,1966-Oct.1967. When were you there,pal ? Lets compare notes.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1347499419570</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:23:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347499781810-195</Id><Title>UNITED STATES OF ISRAEL, ONE WAR AT A TIME...</Title><Msg>Remember when the Palestinians and the Jhews were at peace and then Sharon visited the famous tomb to light up a fire so that peace talks would collapse. Why don't we just rip the flag of the marines uniforms as substitute it with the star of David. What a fkng disgrace.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347499781810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:29:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347500291193-196</Id><Title>These ISLAMIC DEVILS will NEVER EVER police themselves</Title><Msg>CANCEL ALL ARAB FOREIGN STUDENTS VISA'S ASAP !!! Let them go home and cry to daddy and mommy BUCK$</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1347500291193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:38:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347500384318-197</Id><Topic><Title>UNITED STATES OF ISRAEL, ONE WAR AT A TIME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347499781810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>OUTLAW ISLAM IN AMERICA NOW !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1347500384318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:39:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347500481191-198</Id><Topic><Title>Sitting ducks?????</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1347495478532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 20:17:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's right! more dim_lib incompetence !</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1347500481191</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:41:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347500484672-199</Id><Topic><Title>DimWitt Mitt has emboldened the Terrorist. Phoney American Coward?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347498425512</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:07:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crank, if you are trying to provide cover for an American Coward, it ain't working. Punk Mitt is a... PUNK! Thanks for your service. True men stand up when called. Cowards hide. Hey Mitt, why didn't you defend America's principles in Veitnam when other like Crank were? You COWARD!!!! Get off the Ticket, you embarass true Americans.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347500484672</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:41:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347500494741-200</Id><Title>ARMAGEDDON COMING...</Title><Msg>You can thank the Israelis.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347500494741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:41:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347500563590-201</Id><Topic><Title>ARMAGEDDON COMING...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347500494741</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:41:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks to the ISLAMIC DEVILS, FOOL !!!</Msg><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1347500563590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:42:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347500626861-202</Id><Title>Mitt is the AntiChrist Puppet of Al Qaeda Terrorist</Title><Msg>Get off the ticket. You're an embarassment!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347500626861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:43:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347500708337-203</Id><Topic><Title>UNITED STATES OF ISRAEL, ONE WAR AT A TIME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347499781810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too bad for you, we have the 1st Amendment IDIOT.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347500708337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347501047648-204</Id><Title>Veitnam Dodger Questions the Patriotism of true Men in the line of Fire?</Title><Msg>Quit the ticket Mitt, you DimWit. better yet lets all just "Quit the DimWit" Where were you when men were dying in Veitnam, you Coward!!!</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501047648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347501048278-205</Id><Topic><Title>UNITED STATES OF ISRAEL, ONE WAR AT A TIME...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347499781810</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:29:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf is a commie .</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347501048278</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347501066485-206</Id><Title>One more question</Title><Msg>How come junior and dumb are so stupid? Maybe just looking for attention and typing what ever?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1347501066485</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:51:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347501216229-207</Id><Topic><Title>Veitnam Dodger Questions the Patriotism of true Men in the line of Fire?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501047648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Learn how to spell Vietnam if you want to rant about it. Also,do you know where Bill Clinton was during Vietnam?</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1347501216229</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347501305154-208</Id><Topic><Title>Veitnam Dodger Questions the Patriotism of true Men in the line of Fire?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501047648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>#$%$ you ignorant little twaht.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501305154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:55:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347501557387-209</Id><Title>Clinton's Neglect DIRECTLY Caused 9/11 Attack - Now Obama is cowering to terrorism too</Title><Msg>What the heill is wrong wqith Democrat libtards? Why does Bubba get a free pass for telling Bush that attack was going to occur but did not take deal with the threat himself and did not tell Bush when, where and how the attack would happen? Clinton is a massive American traitor.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501557387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347501619811-210</Id><Topic><Title>Veitnam Dodger Questions the Patriotism of true Men in the line of Fire?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501047648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I guess the Religious Community Organizer for his AntiChrist Church was too busy to go to Vietnam? Hey Mitt when are you going to accept Christ as the Messiah? When will you denounce Mr. Smith and his books? Phoney Christians support Mitt the DimWit Coward as he gives support to Al Qaeda Terrorists. Mitt ain't christian and will never accept Jesus Christ as Savior. Hey Mitt, did Jesus forget to tell the disciples something that Mr. Smith only could? You Phoney Christian and American.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501619811</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347501806033-211</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton's Neglect DIRECTLY Caused 9/11 Attack - Now Obama is cowering to terrorism too</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501557387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe the same way Bush Sr. wasn't blamed for the first World Trade Center Bombing. You apologist for the coward.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501806033</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347501990154-212</Id><Title>WILLARD THE TRAITOR, BUSH THE TRAITOR, CHENEY THE TRAITOR...</Title><Msg>Do we see a pattern here.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347501990154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:06:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347502501286-213</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton's Neglect DIRECTLY Caused 9/11 Attack - Now Obama is cowering to terrorism too</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501557387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Listen dikbreth.....why are you libtards always such poozies? Aren't you proud? I thought so. Take a hike, meathead.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347502501286</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:15:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347502642694-214</Id><Topic><Title>Veitnam Dodger Questions the Patriotism of true Men in the line of Fire?</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347501047648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:50:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut the phf*k up you blabbering #$%$ You are making a fool of yourself.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347502642694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347502721808-215</Id><Topic><Title>WILLARD THE TRAITOR, BUSH THE TRAITOR, CHENEY THE TRAITOR...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1347501990154</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:06:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They just hate America and its values. Force that #$%$ to move in with his money in the Caymen Island.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347502721808</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:18:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347502772774-216</Id><Title>supershorty....what a</Title><Msg>...whiney little bedwetting libtard. The blabbering more-on NEVER shuts up.... The little priek is not even ashamed at himself.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347502772774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347502927892-217</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton's Neglect DIRECTLY Caused 9/11 Attack - Now Obama is cowering to terrorism too</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501557387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey dittohead, go support the AntiAmerican Traitor, Phoney Christian and Al Qaeda mouthpiece.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347502927892</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:22:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347503447223-218</Id><Topic><Title>supershorty....what a</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347502772774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL, you're a joke. The truth hurts doesn't it? Like your 12 year of nowhere stock. Are you tired of supporting losers yet?</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347503447223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:30:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347503475921-219</Id><Title>Clinton and Obama</Title><Msg>Clinton allows North Korea to make nukes and now Obama allows Iran to produce weapons of mass destruction. Anyone who votes for Obama is nutz! CAGE</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1347503475921</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:31:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347503879377-220</Id><Topic><Title>Prophet Muhammad likes little boys</Title><Username>moneylap03</Username><Timestamp>1347483426222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 16:57:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Magoo likes little goats in Suffolkganistan</Msg><Username>cages_are_the_enemy</Username><Timestamp>1347503879377</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347504036394-221</Id><Topic><Title>supershorty....what a</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347502772774</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:19:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't own any CSCO, you mush-brained dunce. I have made a mint on Big Oil though. Too bad, dimwit.....get over it you miserble libtard POS.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347504036394</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347504171805-222</Id><Topic><Title>Clinton's Neglect DIRECTLY Caused 9/11 Attack - Now Obama is cowering to terrorism too</Title><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347501557387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:59:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Shut the phf*k up you blathering libtard idiot. Now get back to the gay bath house where you belong, ya freakin' dipwad.</Msg><Username>sentry85nm</Username><Timestamp>1347504171805</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347504686042-223</Id><Topic><Title>CLEARLY, MITT ROMNEY DISGRACED HIMSELF &amp; HIS COUNTRY TODAY..</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1347500216844</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:36:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you betcha. what a coward and al qaeda mouthpiece.</Msg><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347504686042</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 22:51:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1347505396648-224</Id><Topic><Title>Mitt is the AntiChrist Puppet of Al Qaeda Terrorist</Title><Username>superdupershortysporty</Username><Timestamp>1347500626861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 21:43:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are just an HIV infected liberal dumb F</Msg><Username>bamapride57</Username><Timestamp>1347505396648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 23:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347507374115-225</Id><Title>THE WEAK SISSY OBAMA SYMPATHIZED WITH THE LIBYA MOOSLIM ATTACKERS</Title><Msg>just like the gutless traitor Hussein is!!! The obama faygut patted on the back those who murdered our people!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1347507374115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 23:36:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1347507924851-226</Id><Title>OUR Libya Ambassador Butchered and Four Others And OLOSER does NOTHING!</Title><Msg>he sits on his #$%$ saying little and doing NOTHING!!!</Msg><Username>juniorclassmate</Username><Timestamp>1347507924851</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-09-12 23:45:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>