<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345349626716-1</Id><Topic><Title>according to Obama, Romney is a felon and murderer, so my question how much lower can a President go</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345327236394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The WHOLE THING is a red herring to distract from Obama's pathetic record. DON'T YOU PEOPLE GET IT YET??? GEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEZZZZZZZZZZZZZ</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1345349626716</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 00:13:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345355600034-2</Id><Title>WHITE CHRISTIAN VOTING FOR THE ANTICHRIST</Title><Msg>The biggest irony of them all ! You gotta give it to the repukes, they are one fk up circus show !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345355600034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:53:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345361680969-3</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE CHRISTIAN VOTING FOR THE ANTICHRIST</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345355600034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so how many dihks though are you sucking as you wrote this "ingenius" post? Two, three? Using your usual deepthroat method on jasonbaby and "dumbivan", oh wait, you ARE those guys, stupid peckerpuffer</Msg><Username>deepscrotum</Username><Timestamp>1345361680969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 03:34:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345386489165-4</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey + Ryan=NO medicare or social security for anyone !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376400026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:40:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Somebody should ask Romney/Ryan why not make current seniors use vouchers to buy their health care now, if it's such a good idea. Why is it not a good idea now to current seniors now to use vouchers and buy private insurnace?</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1345386489165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:28:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345388125466-5</Id><Topic><Title>2008 was all about RACE, And better believe it so will this one, only this time</Title><Username>assad.syria</Username><Timestamp>1345365432080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 04:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The libs turned it into race. Americans have found you cant criticize this president without being called racist. I happen to think his policies are terrible and he is incompetent,nothing to do with race. Americans may decide if you cant criticize a black president,the solution would be not to elect one again.That's sad . Is that what liberals want???</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345388125466</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 10:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345389102502-6</Id><Topic><Title>2008 was all about RACE, And better believe it so will this one, only this time</Title><Username>assad.syria</Username><Timestamp>1345365432080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 04:37:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>and the next one.</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1345389102502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:11:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345389687035-7</Id><Topic><Title>according to Obama, Romney is a felon and murderer, so my question how much lower can a President go</Title><Username>gergray1968</Username><Timestamp>1345327236394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 18:00:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boy you need an education. You are wrong on what the add says, what the bible says and on religious history. Why do you think Jesus was Crucified, Because he was so mainstream and not an outrageous agitator attacking the establishment? People were excommunicated from the jewish religion, when they were cast out they were considered dead, no one was to even speak to them or acknowledge their existence. Their only way to live was to go live on the town dump. Lets not forget the money changers either. What evidence do you have to judge Obamas sexuality or his adherence to christian concepts. Do you remember the admonition against bearing false witness? Do you recall to whom judgement is reserved?</Msg><Username>libertydies30</Username><Timestamp>1345389687035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:21:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345390547402-8</Id><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Msg>Romney would be serving 5 - 10 years at a Fed run country club with Bernie Madoff.</Msg><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393008981-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey+Ryan are just PUPPETS for FILTHY RICH,,wake up,,please think</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376127086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(GOP is out to tear down our MIDDLE CLASS,,,,) What are you crying about? Will not affect you -- as you are certainly the lower class, really low!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1345393008981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:16:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393352864-10</Id><Topic><Title>NO religious wack job for President, who cheats on his TAXES,, unfit</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376556058</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:42:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I thought Democrats were supposed to be tolerant of others? Guess I misunderstood the Media on that one!</Msg><Username>hohoo69</Username><Timestamp>1345393352864</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345393484555-11</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey+Ryan are just PUPPETS for FILTHY RICH,,wake up,,please think</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376127086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Make that finish tearing down the middle class - finish the job begun by gw douche - good job brownie - mission accomplished - the Pinocchio twins are just fine upstanding greedy republicans</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1345393484555</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:24:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345395050675-12</Id><Title>CSCO Poor performance</Title><Msg>Cisco has been in the doldrums for far too long. It has billions of dollars overseas, but is not rewarding its stockholders with decent dividents. As a result its stock price is languishing and its long term shareholder are becoming increasingly disinchanted. Does the well-paid management care? I don't think so. Al.</Msg><Username>algailpopowits</Username><Timestamp>1345395050675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:50:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345398596484-13</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Poor performance</Title><Username>algailpopowits</Username><Timestamp>1345395050675</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 12:50:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well, Cisco stock dividend has nearly double every quarters since Cisco decided to pay a dividend. Tell me a stock that is doing that</Msg><Username>blue_cube</Username><Timestamp>1345398596484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 13:49:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345399738300-14</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He still may go - if he is elected - the Democrats should start an investigation with an eye toward impeachment - or at least toward making him a one term president - from day one - no negotiations with fascists.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1345399738300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:08:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345402070285-15</Id><Title>Its Beyonce not Moochelle who gets Obama pulse up</Title><Msg>Can't get excited by the wife? I guess Obama only eats animals not getting excited by them. Moochelle is going to send him to the dog house for admitting it.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345402070285</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:47:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345402300096-16</Id><Topic><Title>WHITE CHRISTIAN VOTING FOR THE ANTICHRIST</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345355600034</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 01:53:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lame...keep trying. Maybe you'll get one zinger before the year ends. But right now you are boring me to tears.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1345402300096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345402501382-17</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pelosi and lots of Dem donors have Swiss accounts, in fact the head of UBS is a bundler for Obama, that is why this is just more mud slinging without any meaning. The fact is that international commerce is not illegal, Look at all the Stimulus money and Solar energy money money from our taxes that was given to hire foreigners. The fact is that we can send our money to bank where we want, and Swiss don't have the secrecy they once had or you wouldn't know about it. Romney gave his taxes or we probably wouldn't know about it. Lets see Obama's School transcripts so we can see who paid for his education. Lets see the foreign contributors list from Obama's 2008 campaign that he didn't divulge. I bet there were lots of Saudis, maybe even some communist money given, and this all is illegal.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345402501382</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 14:55:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345404349532-18</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey + Ryan=NO medicare or social security for anyone !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376400026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:40:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious that the polls show a great part of the white middle class slobbering to have their taxes raised and medicare and social security taken away - fat stupid white people -</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1345404349532</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 15:25:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345407177159-19</Id><Title>gotta love the GOP,</Title><Msg>“First of all, from what I understand from doctors, (pregnancy from rape) is really rare,” Akin told KTVI-TV in a clip posted to YouTube by the Democratic super PAC American Bridge. “If it’s a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down.” Akin added: “But let’s assume that maybe that didn’t work or something. I think there should be some punishment, but the punishment ought to be on the rapist and not attacking the child.” According to a 1996 study, approximately 32,000 pregnancies result from rape annually in the United States, and about 5 percent of rape victims are impregnated.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345407177159</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345407544560-20</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Tonopah Solar company in Harry Reid's Nevada is getting a $737 million loan from Obama's DOE. The project will produce a 110 megawatt power system and employ 45 permanent workers. That's costing us just $16 million per job. One of the investment partners in this endeavor is Pacific Corporate Group (PCG). The PCG executive director is Ron Pelosi, who is the brother to Nancy 's husband. Just move along folks. Nuthin' goin' on here.</Msg><Username>free2491</Username><Timestamp>1345407544560</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:19:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345409061862-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey+Ryan are just PUPPETS for FILTHY RICH,,wake up,,please think</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376127086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The day the Democrats took over was NOT January 20, 2009, it was actually January 3, 2007, the day the Democrats took over the House of Representatives and the Senate, at the very start of the 110th Congress. The Democrat Party controlled a majority in both chambers for the first time since the end of the 103rd Congress in 1995. For those who are listening to liberals propagating the fallacy that everything is "Bush's Fault", think about this: On January 3, 2007, the day the Democrats took control of Congress: The DOW Jones closed at 12,621.77 The GDP for the previous quarter was 3.5% The Unemployment rate was 4.6% George Bush's Economic policies had SET A RECORD of 52 STRAIGHT MONTHS of JOB CREATION! Remember that day...? January 3rd, 2007 was the day Barney Frank took over the House Financial Services Committee and Chris Dodd took over the Senate Banking Committee. The economic meltdown that happened 15 months later was in what part of the economy? BANKING AND FINANCIAL SERVICES! THANK YOU DEMOCRATS (especially Barney), for taking us from 13,000 DOW, 3.5 GDP and 4.6% Unemployment to this CRISIS by (among MANY other things) dumping 5-6 TRILLION Dollars of toxic loans on the economy from YOUR Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac FIASCOES! (BTW: Bush asked Congress 17 TIMES to stop Fannie &amp; Freddie - starting in 2001 because it was financially risky for the US economy). Barney blocked it and called it a "Chicken Little Philosophy" (but...the sky did fall!) And who took the THIRD highest pay-off from Fannie Mae AND Freddie Mac? -- OBAMA!!! And who fought against reform of Fannie and Freddie? OBAMA and the Democrat Congress, especially BARNEY!!!! So when someone tries to blame Bush... REMEMBER JANUARY 3rd, 2007.... THE DAY THE DEMOCRATS TOOK OVER!" Bush may have been in the car, but the Democrats were in charge of the gas pedal and steering wheel while they were driving the economy into the ditch. Budgets are not passed in the White House. They are passed by Congress, and the party that controlled Congress since January 2007 is the Democrat Party. Furthermore, the Democrats controlled the budget process for 2008 &amp; 2009 as well as 2010 &amp; 2011. Obama has now gone 1,000 days without a budget, and is still blaming it on the Republicans! In that first year, Congress had to contend with George Bush, which caused them to compromise on spending when Bush, somewhat belatedly, got tough on spending increases. For FY 2009 though, Nancy Pelosi &amp; Harry Reid bypassed Lame Duck President George Bush entirely, passing continuing resolutions to keep government running until Barack Obama could take office. At that time, they passed a massive omnibus spending bill to complete the 2009 budget. And where was Barack Obama during this time? He was a member of that very Congress that passed all of those massive spending bills, and he signed the omnibus bill as President to complete 2009. Let's remember what the deficits looked like during that period: If the Democrats inherited any deficit, it was the 2007 deficit, the last of the Republican budgets. That deficit was the lowest in five years, and the fourth straight decline in deficit spending. After that, Democrats in Congress took control of spending, and that includes Barack Obama, who voted for the budgets. If Obama inherited anything, he inherited it from himself and a Democratic Congress. In a nutshell, what Obama is saying is: "I inherited a deficit that I voted for, and then I expanded that deficit four-fold since January 20th 2009."</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1345409061862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:44:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345409891470-22</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey+Ryan are just PUPPETS for FILTHY RICH,,wake up,,please think</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376127086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Capt. trying to confuse the kool-ade chuggers with facts.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345409891470</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 16:58:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345411862268-23</Id><Title>Big money are coming to invest in CSCO!!!!</Title><Msg>CSCO to see $ 24 soon !!!!</Msg><Username>one_dogydog</Username><Timestamp>1345411862268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345412106245-24</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL Snopes says mostly another GOP lie, do you idiots bother to research anything or do you just believe every stupid thing some other idiot sends you?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345412106245</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:35:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345413051251-25</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now Obama fundraiser Corzine is a real crook, I know he had Cayman accounts, Swiss ones, but the difference is Corzine doesn't know what happenned to his investors Billions of dollars. Maybe they are in his bank accounts. For sure Romney earned the money in his accounts, has been an honest , successful CEO who is entitled to Bank elsewhere Just like many Europeans and Saudi Sheiks bank here. As long as its their money , not like Corzine missing Client account money I see a big difference. Obama still is getting money raised via Corzine. But then Obama dealt with Rezko and Blago.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345413051251</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345413323112-26</Id><Topic><Title>Big money are coming to invest in CSCO!!!!</Title><Username>one_dogydog</Username><Timestamp>1345411862268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You got to be kidding , money guys make 8% passthru, can make about that in REITS, corporate bonds, and if you know how to write puts you can make 2 percent every few weeks with low risk. Best we can hope for is that the SHORTS go elseware because people will hold CISCO and fewer share will be available for shorts, and short interest in Cisco will go down.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345413323112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:55:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345413582468-27</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey+Ryan are just PUPPETS for FILTHY RICH,,wake up,,please think</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1345376127086</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 07:35:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soros bought into Brazils oil field, he convinced Obama who won't allow drilling here or even the keystone pipeline, to invest $20 billion in Brazil Also, GE pays no taxes to the Feds and sends its jobs overseas shuting down local plants, and yet Immelt is his Jobs creation taskforce Czar. Obama is the Real Puppet. And Warren Buffet still owes on his taxes.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1345413582468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:59:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345413593323-28</Id><Topic><Title>Good Thing Bush IRS Gave Amnesty to SWISS Bank Tax Dodgers Like ROMNEY</Title><Username>gop_clown_circus</Username><Timestamp>1345390547402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 11:35:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nope,dumdum, you post idiotic stuff every day. No one believes any of it.For instance have you been skiing in New Zealand lately?? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1345413593323</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345420221405-29</Id><Topic><Title>Big money are coming to invest in CSCO!!!!</Title><Username>one_dogydog</Username><Timestamp>1345411862268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dividend will keep holding CSCO longer - that will squeeze the short - also, the Feds may surprise the markets with a simulas package to make Obama look better before the election. Always seem to happen. Plus the end of year run we get most years. DELL and HPQ along with some other tech companies will likely surprise to the up side this week with the bar set so low. CSCO could jump a buck this week.</Msg><Username>maveric_trader1</Username><Timestamp>1345420221405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 19:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345421948475-30</Id><Title>Ryan says don't worry if you get raped</Title><Msg>you can't get pregnant if your raped, he is empowering women!!!LOL “First of all, from what I understand from doctors, (pregnancy from rape) is really rare,” Akin told KTVI-TV in a clip posted to YouTube by the Democratic super PAC American Bridge. “If it’s a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down.” Akin added: “But let’s assume that maybe that didn’t work or something. I think there should be some punishment, but the punishment ought to be on the rapist and not attacking the child.” According to a 1996 study, approximately 32,000 pregnancies result from rape annually in the United States, and about 5 percent of rape victims are impregnated.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345421948475</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:19:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345422003707-31</Id><Title>As opposed to all those illegitimate rapes, LOL</Title><Msg>“If it’s a legitimate rape, the female body has ways to try to shut that whole thing down.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345422003707</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:20:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345422338413-32</Id><Title>Has mitt released his tax returns</Title><Msg>the ones proving tax fraud and voter fraud yet? let's face it, if it didn't prove tax and voter fraud he would have released them like every other Presidential Candidate, He hasn't released enough information to be approved as a political appointee yet thinks he is above the law</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345422338413</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345422560841-33</Id><Title>throw Momma under the train</Title><Msg>so Mitt can pay no taxes instead of 14% And what are these facts? 1. Traditional Medicare works better, and more cheaply, than most private-insurance plans. With tens of millions of enrollees, Medicare can exploit its bargaining power to pay health-care providers less than private insurers do: that is the great advantage of a single-payer system. Typically, doctors and hospitals receive twenty or thirty per cent less from Medicare for a given procedure than they do from private insurers. They don’t like it, but they need the business. 2. Medicare’s big challenge is demographics, not cost inflation. We’ve all seen the projections: if nothing is done to constrain it, spending on retiree health care will virtually swallow the federal budget. But what’s driving that spending is the growing number of enrollees—another million and a half Baby Boomers every year—rather than rising spending per person. “[W]hen it comes to what health-care costs per person, Medicare’s growth rate is remarkably low,” Feder pointed out—about three per cent a year over the next decade, according to the latest projections, which is considerably less than the cost inflation in the private-insurance sector. 3. In the health-care industry, competition hasn’t produced the savings that economists expected, and it has led to other problems, such as gaps in coverage. Remember the rise of H.M.O.s, another idea promoted by Enthoven that was supposed to revolutionize health care and drive down costs? Part of the problem is the advance of costly treatments. But a bigger problem is that private insurers, rather than haggling with doctors and hospitals, try to make money by limiting the procedures they cover and by aggressively managing their risk pools—that is, taking on fewer sick people. This problem can be addressed through vigorous oversight, but that’s not an easy thing to implement, especially when half of Congress is controlled by a party that breaks out in hives at the very idea of government regulation.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345422560841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1345425841053-34</Id><Title>MAGOO'S GAY "FRIEND"</Title><Msg>aka Surfnski, aka Jasonbaby, aka dumbivan etc. All the same weiner boy, a worthless sack of shyt GAY LIB!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1345425841053</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:24:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426364669-35</Id><Topic><Title>throw Momma under the train</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1345422560841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 20:29:20 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They want to throw seniors to the private - unregulated - insurance system - there is no competition - all the companies do is legally collude on prices to gauge the consumer. That is why there was such a desperate lobby against the Presidents insurance plan - every lie in the book - the insurers would be put off the gravy train - especially the executives.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1345426364669</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345426657996-36</Id><Topic><Title>Big money are coming to invest in CSCO!!!!</Title><Username>one_dogydog</Username><Timestamp>1345411862268</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 17:31:02 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>stocks never goes straight up. employees will be dumping their shares. It may hit 24, but won't go there right away.</Msg><Username>nonelogic</Username><Timestamp>1345426657996</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 21:37:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345429512541-37</Id><Topic><Title>23 Million Americans Unemployed</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1345336830482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LibTURD don't want to talk about the economy. ALL they have and want to discuss is entitlements, or as we smart people call it, BUYING VOTES. Vote for us and we ill give you this, vote for us and we will give you that. JUST VOTE for us and we will figure out something free to you, SCREW the debt. DemonCRAP mentality. You heard it here first.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1345429512541</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 22:25:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1345432582202-38</Id><Topic><Title>23 Million Americans Unemployed</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1345336830482</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2012-08-18 20:40:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>No one will talk about the fact that free market capitalism is a complete and utter failure - complete collapse twice within a century - even Greenspan has recognized that the self-regulating markets is a complete myth. Romney has no history of any competency to create jobs either as governor or at stain capital (except in China). The republicans don't care about creating jobs - ONLY TAX CUTS FOR THEMSELVES AND THEIR BIGGEST CONTRIBUTORS.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1345432582202</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2012-08-19 23:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>