<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2012-08-01"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343805804273-1</Id><Topic><Title>Why CSCO Will Not Go Anywhre ... read this</Title><Username>for_the_idiots</Username><Timestamp>1343774354386</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 18:39:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have identified why I have been against stock buybacks. Chambers issues stock bonuses at least $40 billion in stock, then takes our money buying them back, and the float barely ever gets smaller. Cisco has paid out about 80 billion in stock buybacks, and the whole total Cap for the stock is 100 billion, how is that when there is more than 5 billion shares still out there? I have always been not just for dividends, but for getting the stock to rise. Gaming the stock for 12 years now not to increase in price Chambers game. A puny dividend is not fair to the stocks shareholders. The help at CSCO is very well paid, an employee stock purchase plan is the only way I think they should get shares. Then everyone at Cisco makes money by a rising share price and a paid dividend. If Chambers made bad deals, then his own salary should be cut. Its no accident that Chambers bad CC guidance helps the SHORTS 4 times a year, every year. But we don't see the SEC doing anything about this.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1343805804273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 03:23:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343820508428-2</Id><Title>5% dividend</Title><Msg>what is the chance Chambers will listen to Mark Sue and increase the dividend to 5%? My guess is slim to none...at least for now. Chambers has two more years before he retires. In my opinion, he is collecting cheap shares right now and will increase the share price right before he is about to retire. With a market cap of 85 billion, about 30 billion in cash and 12 billion in deferred revenue, Cisco is super cheap right now. I read an article, where it said Cisco is the cheapest stock in the DOW. I believe that and I think anyone buying now and holding for two years will see a very good return.</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343820508428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:28:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343820854371-3</Id><Topic><Title>5% dividend</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343820508428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mark Sue doesn't have a really good track record on Cisco. He pumped it when it went down and when we had the last run to $21 he was negative. Anyone in Sue's position who would advocate a 5% dividend for a tech stock should retire. Going to 2 1/2% would be tops in my opinion. If President Romneys passes a tax holiday for the 2 trillion in overseas profits maybe Cisco could give a $1 - $2 special dividend.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343820854371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:34:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343821361107-4</Id><Topic><Title>5% dividend</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343820508428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hmm, I think Romney would pass a tax holiday, and I'm still voting for Obama! Funny, that is kind of similar to the way the white trash is voting republican...he,he,he on any rate, the way you and I trade Cisco is probably the best way to make money here. Waiting on Chambers or the politicians to make a decision is a waste of time...</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343821361107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:42:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343821961063-5</Id><Title>Romney is ready for a war with Iran</Title><Msg>In preparation for that, his 5 boyz have joined the military and are ready for deployment. His Mormon church contribution has been re-directed towards funding the war. His Swiss bank accounts have been closed, the Bermuda businesses moved to US, and the Olympic horse donated to the US cavalry. His most recent comment was in French but has been translated as: "let's roll as a united nation".</Msg><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343821961063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:52:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343822299276-6</Id><Topic><Title>5% dividend</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343820508428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Trading Cisco is the ONLY way to make money on it. Serious question, are you voting for Obama because you are a Democrat or are you voting for him because you think he has done a great job? I have always had a problem with people who vote party line, both parties seem to have gone either far right or far left in the last decade. Republicans went there in Bush's 2nd term but I think the Tea Party has helped to right their ship. Democrats are as far left as I have ever seen them. Just calling it as i see it.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343822299276</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:58:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824121455-7</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The conservative collective is in full panic mode because they know their deeply flawed candidate ruined his chance to prove to the world that he’s up to the task of handling international diplomacy. The world compared his trip full of gaffes and idiocy with then candidate Obama’s trip that proved to the world that he is someone the world can respect. The British clearly think Romney is a joke, and they are clearly devoted to Obama. Romney proved that he’ll jump at the chance to go to war with Iran and support the oppression and occupation of the Palestinian people, simply because a few potentates in Israel, and one multi-billionaire in America, snaps their fingers. Romney proved that he surrounds himself with small minded, bitter jerks who hurl gutter vulgarities, and that he is terrified of the press. Conservatives and Republicans are supporting an obviously incompetent nincompoop. They know this, of course. But they cannot do anything but support him, and clean up after his every gaffe, because if they don’t then Obama – the man they hate and fear above all others – might win. And in a few weeks they’ll all line up in Tampa to debase themselves by genuflecting in front of, and screaming out high hosannas to, someone they know is as much a real conservative as I am. They will sway and chant in rapturous adoration of their newest beloved prophet of profit, even though they know he’s an idiot liar. They do this because they hate Obama, and are terrified of him. If he were only white. And for this, conservatives and Republicans demand that we Americans respect them.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1343824121455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:28:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824364901-8</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you nailed it again gfo</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343824364901</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824410129-9</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Full panic mode???? Now that is laughable, and this from the far left who will only talk about outfits and making up issues. Full panic mode is when you REFUSE to talk about the economy and jobs which is what is important to the American people. You people on the FAR LEFT can repeat the same trivial things over and over, but the American people are far smarter than you give them credit for. IE, SHELLACKING 2010.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343824410129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:33:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824561388-10</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,why dont you SHOW US YOUR TAXES,hiding something????</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822125947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's clear he cheated on his taxes, that is the only thing that makes sense, otherwise he would have released them by now</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343824561388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:36:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343824631785-11</Id><Title>The Hypocritical Left</Title><Msg>Pokes fun at Ann Romney for wearing a $900 silk blouse, the Lame Stream Media says the Romneys are out of touch with the American people. Michelle Obama wears a $7,000 jacket, not a single word from the so call journalists. PROOF these HACKS are a bunch of HYPOCRITES.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343824631785</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:37:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824818637-12</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no I can't agree with that, nothing short of a rock can make W look intelligent</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343824818637</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:40:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343824942905-13</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,why dont you SHOW US YOUR TAXES,hiding something????</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822125947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on your approach, you are also saying Obama is a LIAR and is also hiding something since he is paying lawyers millions to seal up his past. He must be hiding something since he refuses to unseal anything. Thanks for FINALLY acknowledging that Obumbles is hiding something. It's about time.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343824942905</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:42:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343825138590-14</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets look at intelligence....... A guy who graduated from Harvard talking about a Corpse-Man, in Austrian, in the 57th state. The rock is starting to look good here. LMAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343825138590</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:45:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343825165868-15</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is ready for a war with Iran</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343821961063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:52:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he will go to war with Iran but his boys won't be involved, he will fight with the existing tea bagger army, they are the only ones dumb enough to fight another useless war</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343825165868</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343825955349-16</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY LOOKS FANTASTIC IN ISRAEL, IN POLAND AND IN LONDON!! SHINES LIKE A STAR..</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1343788094259</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 22:28:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In bird brains rabbit hole this is great press for Romney, LOL The touchdown of Romney’s campaign plane on American soil on Tuesday afternoon brings to a merciful end one of the most star-crossed foreign ventures since June, 1777, when General Burgoyne and his army of redcoats marched out of Quebec and headed for the Hudson Valley. Like Burgoyne’s ill-fated journey, which ended in surrender to the American colonists at the Battle of Saratoga, Romney’s trip was ill-conceived, poorly executed, scarred by miscommunication, and, ultimately, it had the effect of encouraging the enemy. Fittingly, it ended in farce, with Team Romney being obliged to apologize for a press spokesman shouting “kiss my #$%$ to reporters, following a wreath-laying ceremony at one of Poland’s most revered sites, the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier in Warsaw. Yet as Romney headed for the airport, one of his top strategists, Stuart Stevens, insisted (presumably with a straight face) that the six-day jaunt had been “a great success.” It’s amazing what people will say when they are on the sort of hefty financial retainer that political consultants receive. A three-country trip that was intended to burnish the Mittster’s Presidential credentials has reduced him to a laughing stock—the butt of tabloid headline writers and late-night comics alike.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343825955349</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:59:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343827108819-17</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey,why dont you SHOW US YOUR TAXES,hiding something????</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822125947</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:55:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey skin flute player can you name one thing Obama hasn't released that Mitt has? I can name a bunch that Obama has released that Mitt refuses to release. But Mitt is white so that seems fair to you right?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343827108819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 09:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343827739311-18</Id><Topic><Title>MORE HORRIBLE NEWS FOR DUMBOCRATS</Title><Username>dkcjpa1</Username><Timestamp>1343759129147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:25:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oooops...what state did you say you live in.....??</Msg><Username>dkcjpa1</Username><Timestamp>1343827739311</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 09:28:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343828393241-19</Id><Topic><Title>MORE HORRIBLE NEWS FOR DUMBOCRATS</Title><Username>dkcjpa1</Username><Timestamp>1343759129147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 14:25:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gfo99 lives in a state of confusion.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343828393241</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 09:39:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343829960814-20</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well the Chimp has an MBA from Harvard, The Captain has a Harvard degree, what's your point?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1343829960814</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:06:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343830609010-21</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How many elections did you smart libs beat that dumb George Bush in??? LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL .,He kicked your fannies his whole career. LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL LOSERS!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343830609010</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:16:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343831687655-22</Id><Title>CHICK-FIL-A: NO QUEARS ALLOWED!</Title><Msg>HAHAHAH! YEAH BABY!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343831687655</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:34:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343831751054-23</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Manufactured gaffes by the far left lame stream media looking for headlines. You people are just a bunch of HYPOCRITES, for example, Media lamblasted Ann Romney for wearing a $900 silk blouse, YET says nothing about Michelle's $7,000 jacket she wore. This is WHY no one pays attention to you and your ILK and your hyped up NON STORIES. Americans want to talk about the economy and jobs, IMPORTANT things, you Bozo's want to talk about anything else. SHELLACKING 2.0 in November, you lose.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343831751054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:35:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343831958068-24</Id><Title>DEMS DON'T EAT AT CHICK-FIL-A....ANY GUESS WHY!!!??</Title><Msg>their loafers and too light and their wrists are too limp to lift their cups! HAHAHAHAHA! YEAH BABY!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343831958068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:39:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343831995129-25</Id><Topic><Title>5% dividend</Title><Username>virtualgh0st</Username><Timestamp>1343820508428</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:28:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If Obama elected, he is a lame duck and doesn't have to work for the next 4 years, he just collects his paycheck and starts writing his memoirs. If a new guy gets in (Romney) he has to work for 4 years to get to be a lame duck and write his memoirs. It's all a game, neither have a plan nor strategy for the country. BTW CSCO a great value play.</Msg><Username>albacornus</Username><Timestamp>1343831995129</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343832171379-26</Id><Title>Romney to USA "KISS MY %##"</Title><Msg>This is his view on taxes, transparency, religion, business, and ill-begotten wealth. London, Israel and Poland show what kind of man he is--low on common sense and diplomatic skllls.</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1343832171379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:42:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343832467920-27</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to USA "KISS MY %##"</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1343832171379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:42:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Try the truth,pal. That was one of Romney's aides telling off an obnoxious reporter. You loons seem a little desperate.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343832467920</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:47:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343832721861-28</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to USA "KISS MY %##"</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1343832171379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:42:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More TYYPICAL far left LIES. Reporting was screaming at Romney at a religious site. Aide told reporter to be respectful of a foreign countries religious site, reported MOUTHED OFF, aide said kiss my #$%@%#^. Those are the facts, don't expect anything even close to the facts out of these extremists.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343832721861</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:52:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343832729624-29</Id><Topic><Title>DEMS DON'T EAT AT CHICK-FIL-A....ANY GUESS WHY!!!??</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343831958068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They prefer "tube steak"....if you know what I mean....LOL Magoo will munch on a tube steak all night.....Junior too!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343832729624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343833418165-30</Id><Topic><Title>DEMS DON'T EAT AT CHICK-FIL-A....ANY GUESS WHY!!!??</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343831958068</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:39:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL i agree. Those rump rangers love their weener sandwiches: the ghey and AIDS ridden little peckers!</Msg><Username>rationalthoughtll</Username><Timestamp>1343833418165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 11:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343834247753-31</Id><Topic><Title>Romney to USA "KISS MY %##"</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1343832171379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 10:42:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Romney "views" towards the release of information are "Kiss My %##". This sometimes comes from him, and sometimes from his staff. What is he hiding? Could it cause large penalties or fines? Could it land him in jail? Could the GOP turn to another in Tampa?</Msg><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1343834247753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 11:17:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343836205995-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ronmey makes GW Bush look intelligent</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822712960</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 08:05:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The whole time Romney was gone,he didn't say " You didn't build that" once." LOLOLOLOLOL That was Obama's greatest gaffe and it will cost him votes.LOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343836205995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 11:50:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343836907503-33</Id><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Msg>Leaders of the black religious community came out yesterday and said they WILL NOT for Obama because of his stance on gay marriage. How come the Lame Stream MEdia is not reporting this like they did the chic - fill - a fiasco. Obumbles done got himself in a pickle. Oppsieeeeee</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343837123231-34</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he'll "evolve" into being against gay marriage again.LOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343837123231</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343838160501-35</Id><Topic><Title>If I have taxes taken out of my paycheck how can REPUBS say I'm not paying</Title><Username>smedley_the_ape</Username><Timestamp>1343322569963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 13:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no wonder the government gives bad service, look at the lack of incentive, the GOP wants to make gov't workers the working poor!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1343838160501</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343838220056-36</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean like Romney evolved about Gay Marriage and abortion and gun controls? LOL you morons nominated a RINO and now you have to live with him, just to funny I agree with Soros it really doesn't matter which liberal candidate gets elected</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343838220056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343838353298-37</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And you're an expert on leaders of black religious communities, right?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1343838353298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343838501988-38</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles losing votes left and right, blabber on all you want about Romney, Obumbles own people not going to vote for him. That is HUGE, puffer.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343838501988</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:28:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343840421711-39</Id><Topic><Title>If I have taxes taken out of my paycheck how can REPUBS say I'm not paying</Title><Username>smedley_the_ape</Username><Timestamp>1343322569963</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-07-26 13:09:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>republicans are not saying that. liberals are...you seem confused and misguided. republicand want to lower EVERYONES taxes as they did under W.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1343840421711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:00:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343841021826-40</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders WON'T vote for Obama</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343836907503</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 12:01:47 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I really don 't know what that statement means. I do comprehend the english language and when I see a half dozen black preachers standing around a microphone on TV saying " We will not vote for Obama ", it's easy to get the jist. Obumbles going to get cut off at the knees.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343841021826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:10:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343842701466-41</Id><Title>Are pukes stupid enough</Title><Msg>to vote to increase their taxes so Mitt can pay less? WASHINGTON, Aug 1 (Reuters) - Republican U.S. presidential challenger Mitt Romney's proposal to slash income taxes by 20 percent across the board would boost income for the wealthiest taxpayers while reducing it for the middle class, according to a nonpartisan analysis released on Wednesday. The report by the centrist Tax Policy Center found that Romney's tax cuts would boost after-tax income by an average of 4.1 percent for those earning more than $1 million a year, while reducing by an average of 1.2 percent the after-tax income of individuals earning less than $200,000. Tax policy and how to tame the U.S. government's budget deficit, topping $1 trillion in recent years, is a major point of contrast in the presidential race, in which Romney will face President Barack Obama on Nov. 6. The Tax Policy Center, a joint venture between the Brookings Institution and the Urban Institute, is led by Donald Marron, a former economic official in the administration of Republican President George W. Bush. Another of the study's authors, William Gale, was an economic adviser to Republican President George H.W. Bush.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343842701466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:38:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343843133926-42</Id><Title>Surprise! Romney Tax Plan Favors the Rich</Title><Msg>According to Bloomberg news!! LOL Mitt will have to pretend to flip on this until after the election</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343843133926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:45:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343843403261-43</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz wins Palin wins 7 out of 7</Title><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1343784093221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:21:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing this proves is that TexASS is as stupid as ever. Believe me, we expected no less.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343843403261</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:50:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343843761164-44</Id><Title>PAYROLL TAXES AND INCOME TAXES...</Title><Msg>Automatic deductions from your paycheck, FICA, Social Security and Medicare cost you about 17 to 18 percent of your paycheck. Your employer 'matches' the 6.25% that is deducted from your paycheck, and Medicare is about 3%... So, before you pay any income tax, the government has raped your pay check about 17 to18%. Since the Federal income tax rates are so skewed, about 47% of working and non-working Americans PAY NO FEDERAL INCOME TAX....they do pay those payroll deduction taxes.. POINT IS...'RICH' people carry most of the burden of the Federal tax load, and they ARE NOT STUPID. THEY WILL NOT CARRY THAT LOAD FOREVER OR IF IT GETS EVEN MORE BURDENSOME, AT HIGHER RATES...AIN'T GONNA HAPPEn, they just stop working, down tool, take off, take a vacation, close up shop, plant 600 acres instead of 1200 acres, close the office early, put all employees on unpaid leave until they restart the business in three months....it's just the way it goes. AMERICANS ARE NOT STUPID...Democrats are stupid, but they are hardly American, they are the pitiful, sniveling offspring of the mongrel breed known as 'Entitled'...or 'StupidAsDirt'...or..."Where'sTheFood?'.....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1343843761164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:56:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343844366644-45</Id><Topic><Title>PAYROLL TAXES AND INCOME TAXES...</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1343843761164</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:56:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>right bird brain except you see the rich don't pay 17 to 18% to automatic deductions, they are capped at the first 100k, Mitt payed ZERO last year, so middle income payers are paying 33 +18%=51% while Mitt was paying 13% on his 35 million in income, best part is his tax plan means you pay more and he pays less!!! and he is your guy, LOL just to funny</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343844366644</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343844438085-46</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise! Romney Tax Plan Favors the Rich</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343843133926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you mean the rich 1% that pay about 95% of the us tax burden already? who is flipping the truth?</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1343844438085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:07:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343844522008-47</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz wins Palin wins 7 out of 7</Title><Username>miter_banisdirti</Username><Timestamp>1343784093221</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2012-07-31 21:21:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember this if the GOP had a runoff like Texas has when nobody gets 50% of the vote, then Romney loses to either Santorum or Gingrich. Wow wouldn't that have been great, all Polls show they would have lost to Obama in the largest landslide in human history, sorry sucker your stuck with a Mass. Liberal as your candidate, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343844522008</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:08:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343844635799-48</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise! Romney Tax Plan Favors the Rich</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343843133926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL making up silly statistics really doesn't advance your position, THE FACT IS THE MIDDLE CLASS PAYS 8 MILLION PERCENT OF ALL TAXES!! LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343844635799</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343845115126-49</Id><Topic><Title>Surprise! Romney Tax Plan Favors the Rich</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343843133926</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:45:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dead has no clue as to what payroll deduction means.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo28</Username><Timestamp>1343845115126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:18:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343845420121-50</Id><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Msg>Mitt Romney's tax plan could force 95 percent of the country to pay more, while cutting taxes for the "1%" by tens of thousands of dollars, according to a new analysis from the Tax Policy Center and the Brookings Institution. The Romney plan begins by cutting marginal rates by 20 percent and eliminating the estate tax and Alternative Minimum Tax, which would decrease federal tax revenue by $360 billion by 2015. This report considered what would happen if Romney eliminated tax expenditures to make his plan revenue-neutral, so that it wouldn't blow an enormous hole in our budget. Here's what they found: The revenue-neutral Romney plan would raise taxes on a typical family by more than $600. A household making between half-a-million and $1 million would get a tax cut equal to almost twice the disposable income of the poorest 20 percent. Think about this plan as two steps. The first step, Romney's intended tax cuts, dig a hole. Step two is filling that hole by cutting tax spending, like the mortgage interest deductions and child tax credit. Even with a careful pruning of tax spending, the inevitable result is to massively swing the burden of taxes toward the "bottom 95%" because the top benefits so much from Romney's step one.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343845529534-51</Id><Topic><Title>Are pukes stupid enough</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343842701466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 13:38:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, pukes are stupid enough. Actually they are REALLY stupid</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845529534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:25:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343845552726-52</Id><Title>Are libTURDS stupid enough</Title><Msg>To vote for a community organizer who has given the country the longest stretch of UE above 8% since the great depression? He is a complete failure.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343845552726</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:25:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343845577789-53</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This isn't a surprise to anyone paying attention, of course this is what Mitt would like to do, the surprise is he would be so stupid as to put that forward as his policy in front of the election, can't wait to see all the commercials and hear more about this in the debates, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343845577789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:26:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343846035188-54</Id><Title>Obama to RAISE taxes on EVERYONE</Title><Msg>His new plan would be to take away the tax cuts from the rich which EVERYONE got from Bush and then everyone will get taxed who doesn't get FORCED healthcare. He promised NOT to raise taxes yet there are a DOZEN hidden taxes in Obamacare.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846035188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343846155360-55</Id><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working?</Title><Msg>NOPE, hasn't met with his jobs council for at least 6 months. He has been playing golf, traveling, and campaigning for the last year. That's your HOPE and CHANGE.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846155360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343846587925-56</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One of the authors of the study was a former Treasury department aide under Obama. Obama's plan is for more of the same which has given us 41 straight months of UE above 8%. Time for someone else to give it a try. Romney believes as do many Americans that lower tax rates and less government will lead to a better economy and growth.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846587925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:43:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343846743522-57</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes lets hear Obama's plan and how he explains his 3 1/2 years of failure. We all would welcome that debate. PLease explain to the American people how you presided over the LONGEST string of UE above 8% since the great depression. You libTURDS are too funny. PLease, lets finally start talking about the economy, WE WELCOME IT.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846743522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:45:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343847133518-58</Id><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working</Title><Msg>I've seen it and read it, you can to skin flute player, just google The American Jobs Act President Obama’s Plan to Create Jobs Now LOL of course surprise, surprise baggers like you can completely ignore reality when Rush tells you Obama doesn't have a plan, Obama's plan is a much better one then Romney's plan which is cut his own taxes (anyone notice that Romney's plan, by eliminating the estate tax, cuts his taxes by almost 200 million dollars??)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343847133518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:52:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343847159623-59</Id><Topic><Title>Make Ronmey stay is USA,,,makes America look stupid</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822028202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:53:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He does make America look stupid but only your liberal half of America.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1343847159623</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:52:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343847605896-60</Id><Title>Did Mitt get the Fed Gov to bail out the Olympics</Title><Msg>Actually it already had been bailed out by the time Mitt showed up, Indeed, of the half-dozen Olympic officials interviewed for this article, none said that the games would have been a failure if not for Romney's intervention. David Wallechinsky, a commentator for NBC's Olympic coverage and the author of several Olympic reference books, said that Romney played an important role in budget and PR matters. But beyond that, "his involvement is greatly exaggerated." "A lot of people could have stepped in and made it work," he told The Huffington Post. "Not to say he did anything wrong. He did what he had to do. What he did was fine. The way he portrays it, however, is absurd ... The Olympic movement had survived two world wars, a terrorist attack, and boycotts. It could have survived a bribery scandal."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343847605896</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:00:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343847619956-61</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343847133518</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:52:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Have you seen one from the Mutt?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1343847619956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:00:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343847727071-62</Id><Topic><Title>Make Ronmey stay is USA,,,makes America look stupid</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343822028202</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 07:53:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont remember Bush ever saying" You didn't build that". LOLOLOLOLOLOLOL That ranks as one of the dumbest gaffes EVER!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343847727071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:02:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343847771054-63</Id><Title>Liberal support you first amendment rights</Title><Msg>as long as you support their demented agenda. Look who the Nazi's are now. Close your business down and shut you up. We are not going to tolerate intolerence of free expression.</Msg><Username>eagle1776321</Username><Timestamp>1343847771054</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:02:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343848159564-64</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846155360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Where is it? If there is one, why hasn't it passed. If it passed WHERE are all the jobs? Obama also had a budget, but guess what, NOBODY voted for it, not a single member of his party voted for it. LibTURDS are in their own little world.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343848159564</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343848314011-65</Id><Title>Only 30% of GOPERS</Title><Msg>Admit they are racists (be sure to read all the way to the last line baggers, have your mother/sister help you sound it out if you need help) Charles and Te'Andrea Wilson were looking forward to saying "I do" in the First Baptist Church of Crystal Springs, Miss. on July 21. But the day before their Big Day, their pastor told them their wedding had been cancelled. Fox 6 in Alabama reports that the couple had booked the church and distributed invitations only to find out that the church's congregation had decided that the Wilsons, an African American couple, could not tie the knot in their church. "The church congregation had decided no black could be married at that church, and that if he went on to marry her, then they would vote [the pastor] out the church," Charles Wilson told Fox. The Wilsons regularly attend the predominantly white church, though they are not members. Watch the video above to learn more. Even though the U.S. elected its first African American president in 2008, and the Civil Rights movement was successful more than 40 years ago, the Deep South is still struggling with racism. In March, almost 30 percent of likely GOP voters polled said that they thought interracial marriage should be illegal.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343848314011</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:11:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343848669757-66</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846155360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WAIT a minute, I guess there might be a plan. Obama's jobs council is working on it....Oppsie, he hasn't met with them for over 6 months. I guess jobs really aren't that important. Working on the campaign for the last year has been front and center. Hope and Change.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343848669757</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343849081384-67</Id><Title>skin flute player</Title><Msg>Obama's job council met and gave him their recommendations, Obama proposed his jobs act the GOP Senate Filibustered it, why wouldn't they let it go up for a vote? Could it be so they could say Obama hasn't passed a jobs plan? LOL you baggers are so stupid you believe what ever the college drop out mouth pieces tell you, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849081384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:24:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343849320472-68</Id><Title>30% of GOPERS admit they are racist</Title><Msg>Of course the real number is a lot higher. Even though the U.S. elected its first African American president in 2008, and the Civil Rights movement was successful more than 40 years ago, the Deep South is still struggling with racism. In March, almost 30 percent of likely GOP voters polled said that they thought interracial marriage should be illegal.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849320472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:28:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343849326694-69</Id><Title>Dumb Dumb Ivan</Title><Msg>Obama has not met with his jobs council in 6 months. If you come up with a pizzzz poor plan that no one likes you go back to the drawing board. And stop your WHINING about the Senate, your boy Reid has HELD UP every single bill including budgets sent over from the House. How STUPID are you morons.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343849326694</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:28:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343849363080-70</Id><Title>#$%$</Title><Msg>is the matter with this board, I'm going short Yahoo, they can't even get a simple message board to work</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849363080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:29:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343849530173-71</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849363080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's because it turns off IDIOTS.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343849530173</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:32:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343849709333-72</Id><Title>finaly ?</Title><Msg>Close over $16 ?</Msg><Username>alfankosh22</Username><Timestamp>1343849709333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:35:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343850271466-73</Id><Title>I like Obama's job plan</Title><Msg>independent sources say it would add 4 to 5 million jobs in 18 months, that is apparently why the GOP choose to filibuster it, they wan't the economy to get worse so they will get elected</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343850271466</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:44:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343850288250-74</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, it created the greatest financial collapse in history. But never mind the facts, you keep drinking the Koolaid, OK ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343850288250</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:44:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343850408788-75</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple, you can't fix in 3 years the disasters of 8 years. Doesn't take much brains to figure that one out, but and IDIOT like yourself doesn't have even that much. Keep throwing me softballs, I'll keep hitting them out of the park.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343850408788</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:46:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343850553271-76</Id><Title>Obama's job plan is a JOKE</Title><Msg>Congress rejects it. Who would trust a guy with a plan when the last 3 1/2 years has given you 8%+ UE. Obama and Pelosi thinks jobs are created from UE benefits. NO LIE, that is what they said. You can't make this stuff up folks.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343850553271</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343850837298-77</Id><Topic><Title>finaly ?</Title><Username>alfankosh22</Username><Timestamp>1343849709333</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:35:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess not today !!</Msg><Username>alfankosh22</Username><Timestamp>1343850837298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:53:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343851372215-78</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And stupid BOYsurfer does it again, after 3 1/2 years he is STILL blaming Bush. The epitome of a true WHINER. You are owned, BOY.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343851372215</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:02:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343852070885-79</Id><Title>MITT CONTINUES TO LEAD OLIAR IN POLLS</Title><Msg>WOW if only election day were tomorrow!</Msg><Username>rationalthoughtll</Username><Timestamp>1343852070885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343852673718-80</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles in his own words said if he can't fix this in 3 years he doesn't deserve another term. Those are your boys own words, we will grant him his wish. More egg on your face dopey.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343852673718</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:24:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343852753020-81</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's plan is no budgets ever, where is his budget, OH I forgot, no budgets, just higher debt than all the previous 41 presidents combined Obama wants to give us the 2 biggest tax hikes, mostly on the middle class, healthcare tax and expiration (tax hike) early next year increasing everyone's rates. Romney brought taxes down as Gov. Obama wants to tax your cap gains more. Say I earned that money and already paid taxes on it. Class warfare is losers complaining about people who are doing better because mostly they work for themselves 60 hours per week instead of 40 hours per week. I want to see the 50% of Americans who pay only SS pay at least 5% fed taxes, they should pay their fair share.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1343852753020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:25:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343853867258-82</Id><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Msg>The Romney group is trying to sell the equivalent of the Brooklyn Bridge in Ohio. They are trying to get people in Ohio to believe that the auto bail-out cost jobs. The idea that an automotive bankruptcy would have been good for jobs, or the state of Ohio is false, and would have led to the "Second Great Depression". Romney is falling further behind in Ohio, for good reason: taxes, business, religion, foreign policy.</Msg><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343853889072-83</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to RAISE taxes on EVERYONE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846035188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just wait until everyone is forced to buy healthcare insurance. If you refuse, the IRS will come after you in the form of a tax. If you buy it but didn't want it, it's the same as a tax since you wouldn't have spent the money. TOP that off with the dozens or so other taxes in the bill. Obumbles gonna get your money one way or the other, EVERYONES money. Those of you koolaid chuggers who think otherwise are naive.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343853889072</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854028887-84</Id><Topic><Title>MITT CONTINUES TO LEAD OLIAR IN POLLS</Title><Username>rationalthoughtll</Username><Timestamp>1343852070885</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:14:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>After Romney is the official candidate,he' ll be able to start spending all the campaign money. DickMorris is a slimeball but he knows his politics. He says the polls will then start turning decidedly for Romney and he will win fairly easily. Hope he's right.</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343854028887</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:47:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854078584-85</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There were THOUSANDS of jobs lost when Obama created government motors, not to mention the rule of law he broke by favoring the Unions over bondholders.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343854078584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:47:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343854210789-86</Id><Title>THE BUSH LEGACY, A MILITARY DESTROYED...</Title><Msg>Looks like the morons at the pentagon thought that sending soldiers to fight for 10 years is not a problem. ******************************* Before dawn, shaking and stuttering, Russell walked through the still desert outside Baghdad to the quarters of Captain Peter Keough, the 54th Engineer Battalion’s chaplain. Keough listened, and hastily made the sergeant’s fourth appointment in four days at an Army mental-health clinic. “I believe he is deteriorating,” Keough e-mailed an Army psychiatrist. “He doesn’t trust anyone.” Russell, the chaplain wrote, “believes he is better off dead.” It was 10:07 a.m. on May 11, 2009. The battalion, military police and combat stress specialists had three hours and 34 minutes to avert tragedy. Instead, after lost opportunities and miscalculations, the blue-eyed sergeant from Texas used a stolen gun to kill three enlisted men and two officers in the deadliest case of soldier-on-soldier violence in the war zone. His victims’ bodies are buried across the U.S., from Arlington National Cemetery to the Texas panhandle. Russell slipped through the safety net constructed to catch troubled soldiers. More and more are falling. The armed services’ mental-health epidemic has deepened since the Camp Liberty killings. In June, Defense Secretary Leon Panetta ordered a Pentagon review of every diagnosis from 2001 on</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343854210789</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:50:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854445015-87</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When I feel like hearing from a toothless, curled lip, two bit Vegas hooker I'll let you know, OK ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343854445015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:54:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854534119-88</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849363080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, you are still posting.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343854534119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:55:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854535483-89</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are right, but only THOUSANDS of jobs were lost, not TENS of THOUSANDS. The auto industry survived, and many of the jobs returned, Hoover/Bush/Romney type policies would have been an absolute disaster leading to, "The Second Great Depression"</Msg><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343854535483</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:55:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854585923-90</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are still 27 billion in the hole for the GM bailout .And yet GM just signed a deal with the English soccer team Manchester United to pay them 600 million to sponsor them. Why didn't GM spend that money in this country?????</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343854585923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:56:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854795243-91</Id><Topic><Title>#$%$</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1343849363080</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 15:29:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yo BOYsurfer, why don't you explain to the class how Candidate Romney while talking tuff on Iran was doing so to purposely raise the price of oil. Oil DOWN 2% since your little tirade from a couple days ago. Seems stupid is as stupid does when it comes to you. Another fit of stupidity out of your piehole. It seems like everyday I have to school you in one way or another. Keep em coming BOY, you simply make my day enjoyable. LMAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343854795243</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:59:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343854931273-92</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to RAISE taxes on EVERYONE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846035188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Liar !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343854931273</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 17:02:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343855257826-93</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to RAISE taxes on EVERYONE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846035188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Refute it BOY.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343855257826</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 17:07:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343858766242-94</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It did cost jobs - in China - but that was balanced out by all the jobs romney created in China.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1343858766242</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:06:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343859371245-95</Id><Topic><Title>Romney is at it again with new "creative lies" in Ohio</Title><Username>sidesaddlex</Username><Timestamp>1343853867258</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 16:44:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Come come now my good man - the rich would trickle down their largess upon the middle class - we can all buy a dancing horse for a tax deduction - GOOD JOB BROWNIE - MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1343859371245</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:16:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343859445724-96</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Perfectly justified - the rich in this country do not have enough.</Msg><Username>hulksweider2000</Username><Timestamp>1343859445724</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:17:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343861108863-97</Id><Title>Obama HAS RAISED TAXES ON U.S. CITIZENS WITH</Title><Msg>THE LARGEST TAX INCREASE IN U.S., if not WORLD HISTORY: all through Obamacare! He's one socialistic-facist POS!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343861108863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:45:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343861384999-98</Id><Topic><Title>Obama HAS RAISED TAXES ON U.S. CITIZENS WITH</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1343861108863</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:45:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasting your words, these Liberal Pecker-woods are way to stupid to understand.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1343861384999</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:49:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343861544459-99</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Carter sure left things bad for Reagan, double digit inflation, 20% credit, unemployment and as Carter said Malaise. Hey Surfbum, your writing and vocabulary is of a grade school drop out. Don't call me names, you never did half as much in your life as I have. Nobody here has respect for you, even libs here are interested in my opinions.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1343861544459</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:52:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343861654118-100</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reagan got the economy growing over 5% in less than one year. Obama is an inexperienced dogmatic inflexible dunce.</Msg><Username>rhonda_edelstein</Username><Timestamp>1343861654118</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 18:54:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343862166234-101</Id><Title>No confidence - Chambers must go or CSCO makes Cramer's Wall of Shame ?</Title><Msg>We are getting reports that Cramer is considering putting CISCO on his "wall of shame" Is it time for Chambers to get a "no confidence" and yet a younger CEO aboard with FRESH new ideas for this sinking whale? What do you all think?</Msg><Username>elvisprty</Username><Timestamp>1343862166234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:02:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343862387165-102</Id><Topic><Title>Obama to RAISE taxes on EVERYONE</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846035188</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:33:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Simple one liners from the simpletons. Why can't you puffers refute my claim.. Oopsie....YOU CAN'T.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343862387165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343862394439-103</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you bore me.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343862394439</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:06:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343862638475-104</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNEY TO RAISE TAXES</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343845420121</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:23:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Interested in your 'opinion' ? You are a running joke you idiot. You are like Bush, you think we are laughing with you while we are laughing at you. Stop thinking you are going to get any smarter by spreading your legs. It ain't gonna happen you mop-carrying toilet-scrubbing burger-flipping trollop</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343862638475</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:10:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343862766598-105</Id><Topic><Title>No confidence - Chambers must go or CSCO makes Cramer's Wall of Shame ?</Title><Username>elvisprty</Username><Timestamp>1343862166234</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:02:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" We are getting reports " ............. Do you have a mouse in your pocket or what? #1, it is time for Chambers to go, he has NO regard for the owners, I mean shareholders of the company, and B) NOBODY cares about Cramer. He is a clown who pumped Cisco at the top and dumped on it at the bottom. The clown is no better than a Weatherman, he's barely right half the time.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343862766598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:12:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343863752406-106</Id><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Msg>Thanks to Obamacare there will be no co-payment on breast and gynecological exams. Thank you Mr Obama for caring about the citizens of this country. Thank you for preventing decease and saving tax payer money. Thank you for giving a sjit while under the assault of the repuke inbreeds.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343863964646-107</Id><Title>CHICK FILLET used to be good.</Title><Msg>They used to have a good chicken sandwich, you know like a nice piece. About 8 months ago they starting to serve in their sandwich a 'fillet' the size of a fkn potato chip. Greedy repuke ripping off customers.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863964646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:32:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343864332378-108</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fukcnugget BOYsurfer, why don't you go cry and whine to someone who really gives a chit. Everyone cares about all AMericans, it's just that DemonCRAPS prey on the poor and unfortunate for political gain. So why don't you stick your hypocritical view up your aszasszzzzzzzzsaszzzzzx. Have you screwed the IRS anymore like you did following a windfall several years ago when your company was bought by Cisco. Your story. You're a HYPOCRITE and a loudmouthed puffer. Magoo says so.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864332378</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343864470840-109</Id><Title>BOysurfer back on the crackpipe</Title><Msg>Whining like a drugged out dropout. Obumbles must have brought him some dust. Who knew.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864470840</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:41:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343864639426-110</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Flutie I didn't screw anybody. I used the tax laws designed by your repuke heroes. You can't have it both ways BOY. Now about those government contracts you live off, your words, how is that milking coming along ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343864639426</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:43:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343864668219-111</Id><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Msg>Can anyone verify that he isn't still doing lines in the back room. What kind of #$%$ votes for a coke snorting community organizer. I wonder how many koolaid chuggers really know that the guy they voted for was a cocaine user. We can talk about his communist ties later.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343864832750-112</Id><Title>IF ROMNEY WAS AN ABSENTEE TERRIBLE GOVERNOR...</Title><Msg>How come he is going to be a good president. He couldn't even handle a small state. The only thing good that he did for MA was implementing the Romneycare = Obamacare.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343864832750</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:47:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865075084-113</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>it's YOU who can't have it both way you fughgiin HYPOCRITE. You whine and complain about the rich and corporations and Romney, yet you engaged in the SAME activity hiding behind the loop holes. Explain government contracts? I have had some contracts with a few local school corporations but other than that NEVER had a government contract. Sorry DUMBASZZZZZZ, looks like you are talking out of your backside again. Seems you can't get anything right, HYPOCRITE. Why don't you WHINE a little more about Romney using a LEGAL tax haven, HYPOCRITE. Once AGAIN, another daily SCHOOLING.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343865075084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:51:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865083553-114</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Problem with Surf's millionaire story is he consistently spells the name of his company wrong. In the future when you #$%$ us,Surf, spell it correctly. It's Cerent ,not Cerant. What a phony you are!!!!! When you want to tel la big lie,do a little research first!! Maybe it wont be quite so easy to catch you lying!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1343865083553</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:51:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865142733-115</Id><Topic><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Everybody has done drugs at some point in their life. It is only when it becomes and addiction that there is the problem, you know like what happened with G.W. Why do you think his daddy invaded Panama. He saw junior spread eagle on the floor bleeding from his nose like a stuck pig. Then he heard he was doing lines of asian's #$%$ butt cracks with uncle Neil. Finally sr, decided to shut down the line.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343865142733</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:52:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865292172-116</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He told the story naming Cisco as the company at one point. It's obvious, BOYsurfer is just another LYING trailer trash redneck. I'm laughing at your welfare ridden trailer trash life, surffffyyyyy...... LMAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343865292172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:54:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865409446-117</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am not claiming to create jobs for americans while I am outsourcing them. I did pay my taxes unlike Willard who is hidding his.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343865409446</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865438526-118</Id><Topic><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sorry boy puffer, I have never done drugs. I suppose to losers like you everyone wouldn't be that many people. How many friends do you have 1 maybe 2? LMMFAO</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343865438526</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:57:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865479298-119</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You used the same laws to reduce your tax liability as Romney did????????LOLOLOLOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh50</Username><Timestamp>1343865479298</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:57:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865629659-120</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BOYpuffer is a HYPOCRITE. Trying to change subject to job outsourcing. Clear signal he admits defeat and wants to move on. ha ha ha</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343865629659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:00:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343865730705-121</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Boypuffer is nothign more than your typical loudmouthed libTURD. oh, and a hypocrite.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343865730705</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:02:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343866233890-122</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Uh ? Cisco bought the company. I wish I had been the 20th employee at Cisco, it would have been a lot more than what I made at Cerent. B</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343866233890</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:10:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343866559193-123</Id><Title>Black religious leaders tell Obama we won't vote for you</Title><Msg>Apparently Obama evolving is not setting well with a portion of the black community. Those folks will either stay home or vote for Romney. HUGE mistake on Obumbles part. His own people won't vote for him. Talk about putting yourself in a corner, what a junior sized move. Opsieeeeeeee</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343866559193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343866618627-124</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco bought Cerent. I have never said I was one of the first 20 employees at Cisco. That would have been a lot more than what I got.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343866618627</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:16:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343866827380-125</Id><Topic><Title>MOTHERS, WIVES, AND DAUGHTERS ARE PROTECTED TODAY</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863752406</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:29:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We are talking about you being a HYPOCRITE for abusing tax laws for your benefit. You complain about Romney being rich and using the tax system, YOU did the same thing. Maybe you didn't, you can't get your story straight or spell your company correctly. Maybe you should just get back to your janitorial position. LOSER</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343866827380</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:20:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343869235925-126</Id><Title>JUST GOT BACK FROM CHICK-FIL-A....1,000s of people standing in line</Title><Msg>laughing, talking, telling stories...like a community of good hearted folks! Buying from Chick-Fil-A to celebrate the fact that in America, we have FREEDOM OF SPEECH...and when Dan Cathy, the CEO of Chick-Fil-A said out loud that he supports the Biblical tradition of marriage as a covenant between a man and a woman....the CREEPS BEGIN TO ATTACK HIM, THE BIG GAY MACHINE REVVED UP AND THE criminal in Chicago, City of Murder, said...mincingly, 'Chick-Fil-A doesn't celebrate our Chicago virtues, like drive by killings of toddlers and corrupt politicians and HOMICIDE by the bucket full, take your Chick-Fil-A somewhere else, we've got too much killing to allow a drive by restaurant, we only interested in Drive By Shootings"... Watch the reports...I'll bet Chick-Fil-A beat the world wide record for one day sales at any fast food joint in the history of the WORLD!!!!</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1343869235925</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 21:00:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343872823025-127</Id><Topic><Title>Black religious leaders tell Obama we won't vote for you</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343866559193</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:15:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama losing his own base. I wonder what he will evolve into next? This could be a landslide.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343872823025</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:00:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343873281763-128</Id><Topic><Title>GREG, A BRIT A J/E/W AND APOLISH GUY WALK INTO A BAR</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1343872804107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Poor Junior, how is that Cisco short doing From $15. Must be getting pretty painful.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343873281763</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:08:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343873394099-129</Id><Topic><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do all the Obamabots know this guy did Cocaine? I wonder if they also know his mentor was communist Frank Marshall. Let the REAL vetting begin.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343873394099</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343874287929-130</Id><Topic><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama admitted using briefly. He was not an addict. GWB had a problem and his wife admitted to his excessive alcohol abuse. Flute, you must idolize Hannity who spews the fertilizer you seem to repeat.</Msg><Username>eyeprosper</Username><Timestamp>1343874287929</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:24:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343874499203-131</Id><Topic><Title>Obama did Cocaine</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343864668219</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:44:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GWB using is a LIE spread by the far left, he was a heavy drinker but quit. Obama is a proverbial LIAR, he also said he never heard Reverend Wright say anything abusive in 20 years. You people are cute, but naive.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343874499203</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:28:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343874836574-132</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNMEY,,,what are you hiding,,,SHOW USA YOUR TAXES !!!!!!!</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343866663835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He cannot show Americans his tax returns as it will expose how little he paid. It's OK to be filthy rich but he does not pay his fair share. A working blue collar man pays more percentage in taxes than the corrupt 1%ers do. Even Reagan was for everyone paying his fair share and he was aiming that speech to the wealthy.</Msg><Username>eyeprosper</Username><Timestamp>1343874836574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:33:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343875221680-133</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846155360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He has a plan that the teanuts and GOP refuse to work with. They would rather sink the country as to work with a rational black Dem president. Question is, Where is the repubs jobs plan?</Msg><Username>eyeprosper</Username><Timestamp>1343875221680</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343876636266-134</Id><Title>obama is simply a marxist and a muuslim terrorist</Title><Msg>that's all that shoe shine crack head is</Msg><Username>aj_guar</Username><Timestamp>1343876636266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:03:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343876747932-135</Id><Topic><Title>ROMNMEY,,,what are you hiding,,,SHOW USA YOUR TAXES !!!!!!!</Title><Username>dfallis32</Username><Timestamp>1343866663835</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 20:17:43 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obumbles has been hiding his entire past for 4 years, you people are laughable. Who pays lawyers millions to seal their records. Somebody with something to hide.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343876747932</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:05:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343876990714-136</Id><Topic><Title>CHICK FILLET used to be good.</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1343863964646</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 19:32:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, poor little homosexual upset over outpouring of support to chik-fil-a</Msg><Username>bamapride57</Username><Timestamp>1343876990714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:09:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1343877054939-137</Id><Title>Two Weeks Until Report...</Title><Msg>It should be interesting. Cisco is cheap.</Msg><Username>gordonfan4life2</Username><Timestamp>1343877054939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:10:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343877264110-138</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone seen a plan from Obama to get people working?</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343846155360</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 14:35:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You jackwagons had COMPLETE and unfettered control of all 3 branches of government for 2 years and instead of focusing on the economy you passed a garbage healthcare bill that the majority of Americans told you they didn't want. There is no refusal to do anything, you people FAILED, PERIOD.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343877264110</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:14:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1343877359024-139</Id><Topic><Title>GREG, A BRIT A J/E/W AND APOLISH GUY WALK INTO A BAR</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1343872804107</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 22:00:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIAR, you told everyone to sell with abandon last week at $15. Too funny, you should let your mommy take care of your allowance.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1343877359024</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2012-08-01 23:15:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>