<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-19"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382182045271-1</Id><Topic><Title>It Appears that it was Divine Intervention that Destroyed the Obamacare Debut</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1382152602553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 23:16:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Moronic statement, it was the govet demanding lots of extras and changes to the software after it was completed. Most of the individual states (done by the same Canadian company) are up and running without problems. Biggest problem with the ACA, it is not single payer! Maybe Hillary can fix this in 2016.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1382182045271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 07:27:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382184400431-2</Id><Title>Even Bigger than Benny-Gazzi!</Title><Msg>DOJ Brings Fresh Manslaughter Charges Against Blackwater Mercenaries for Iraqi Massacre Four private military contractors reindicted for their role in 2007 Nisour Square massacre that left fourteen Iraq civilians dead - Jon Queally, staff writer The Justice Department on Thursday announced new manslaughter charges against four Blackwater mercenaries involved in the 2007 Nisour Square massacre in Iraq that left dozens of innocent civilians dead or severely wounded. Ali Kinani, only nine years old at the time, was among the victims in the 2007 killings in Nisoor Square. The deadly incident in many ways began the unraveling of Blackwater, founded by a wealthy, ex-Navy Seal named Eric Prince. Subsequent to Nisour Square, Blackwater changed its name twice—first to Xe and then to its current name, Academi—and Prince ultimately severed ties with his company following a stream of bad press. Justice for the victims of the killings, however, remained illusive as earlier charges against the for-profit militants were dropped and coverage of the story dimmed as the U.S. media turned its attention away from the damage wrought by the bloody and extended damage caused by the U.S. occupation of Iraq.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1382184400431</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:06:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382184421486-3</Id><Topic><Title>It Appears that it was Divine Intervention that Destroyed the Obamacare Debut</Title><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1382152602553</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 23:16:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>god destroyed the gop fantastic</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382184421486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:07:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382184565757-4</Id><Title>It Appears that it was Divine Intervention that Destroyed the Gop and preserved Obamacre</Title><Msg>GOD IS ON OUR SIDE</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382184565757</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382184635223-5</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare disaster is only deepening</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382151143979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 22:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean worse than this? TED CRUZ AND THE SHADY JAMAICAN HOLDING COMPANY - Pretty confident we saw "Ted Cruz and the Shady Jamaican Holding Company" open for Rusted Root back in 97. Time: "Texas Republican Senator Ted Cruz potentially violated ethics rules by failing to publicly disclose his financial relationship with a Caribbean-based holding company during the 2012 campaign, a review of financial disclosure and company documents by TIME shows. The relationship originated with a $6,000 investment Cruz made more than a decade ago in a Jamaican private equity firm founded by his college roommate. When Cruz later reported the financial relationship in 2013, he failed to comply with Senate rules requiring full identification of the holding company and its location, triggering an inquiry by Senate Select Committee on Ethics staff and a second amended disclosure...In an amended financial disclosure form filed Oct. 1, Cruz said he still holds a promissory note from a Kingston-based company called Caribbean Equity Partners Investment Holdings LTD, worth between $100,000 and $250,000. No company with that name is registered in Jamaica. There is however a dormant Jamaica-based private equity firm called Caribbean Equity Partners Limited of which Cruz was a founding director and preferential shareholder, according to documents filed with the Jamaican government and reviewed by TIME. The firm held $100 million in assets under management in the mid-2000s, according to local news reports, with a focus on service and tourism investments in Jamaica and the Caribbean." [Time]</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1382184635223</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:10:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382184991079-6</Id><Title>------------------------IT"S BUSH'S FAULT!--------------------------------------</Title><Msg>this is gails first truthful post!!!!</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382184991079</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382185016523-7</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump ROTF!!!</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382185016523</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:16:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382185711993-8</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Construction of the website was authorized three years ago. Has absolutely nothing to do with the political problems of the last month. Your feeble excuses wont fly. Three years to prepare and the website is a dissaster.</Msg><Username>myrtletheturtle28</Username><Timestamp>1382185711993</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:28:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186031745-9</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes the website cost 600 mil the gop wasted $24 billion trying to stop it saavy? obamacare rolls on turtle and with the gop trying to sabotage every day for 5 years......</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382186031745</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:33:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186213468-10</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Five years ago Obama wasn't president You seem prone to exaggeration.</Msg><Username>myrtletheturtle28</Username><Timestamp>1382186213468</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:36:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186344100-11</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes he was dimWit ROTFFLMAO!!!!</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382186344100</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:39:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186495568-12</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In October, 2008 Bush was president .Did you have a problem with math in school??</Msg><Username>myrtletheturtle28</Username><Timestamp>1382186495568</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382186940862-13</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior has disappeared. Maybe he went to the store to buy a calculator.</Msg><Username>myrtletheturtle28</Username><Timestamp>1382186940862</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 08:49:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382190195297-14</Id><Topic><Title>so, did you guys defund obamacare?</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1382144926568</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 21:08:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The moron continues to prove how stupid he is.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1382190195297</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 09:43:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382193260909-15</Id><Title>Not much said about Ayn Rand on this board anymore</Title><Msg>Robert Stein: Connecting.the.Dots "The only thing new in the world is the history you don't know." –Harry S Truman The 2008 Weblog Awards Site Meter Site Meter About Me ROBERT STEIN editor, publisher, media critic and journalism teacher, is a former Chairman of the American Society of Magazine Editors, and author of “Media Power: Who Is Shaping Your Picture of the World?” Before the war in Iraq, he wrote in The New York Times: “I see a generation gap in the debate over going to war in Iraq. Those of us who fought in World War II know there was no instant or easy glory in being part of 'The Greatest Generation,' just as we knew in the 1990s that stock-market booms don’t last forever. We don’t have all the answers, but we want to spare our children and grandchildren from being slaughtered by politicians with a video-game mentality." This is not meant to extol geezer wisdom but suggest that, even in our age of 24/7 hot flashes, something can be said for perspective. The Web is a wide space for spreading news, but it can also be a deep well of collective memory to help us understand today’s world. In olden days, tribes kept village elders around to remind them with which foot to begin the ritual dance. Start the music. View my complete profile Follow by Email Followers Facebook Share Blog Archive ▼ 2013 (173) ▼ October (23) Can Paul Ryan Lie His Way Out Again? Blinks and Winks An Apology (and Challenge) to My Grandchildren Last Station Before Default Unseating Ted Cruz Downside of a Bipolar Decade Gagging on the Obamacare Glitch Is the Pope Rooting for Hillary? Ted Cruz Wins the Shameless Olympics Banana Republic Burlesque Can Politicians Be Scared Straight? Claire Danes Drives Me Crazy The Shutdown's Stockholm Syndrome Elections That Changed America Doomsday Liar's Poker in DC A Medal for Michele Bachmann Why Did Miriam Carey Die? Oxymoron? Wiser GOP Heads Arise Lawless in DC Women Having It All Obamacare Blowback Begins World War II Vets Crash the Shutdown Notes from a "Breaking Bad" Laggard ► September (30) ► August (23) ► July (24) ► June (22) ► May (10) ► April (4) ► March (10) ► February (11) ► January (16) ► 2012 (296) ► 2011 (349) ► 2010 (260) ► 2009 (509) ► 2008 (858) ► 2007 (1112) ► 2006 (41) Two Half Hitches NY Times Caucus Political Wire Divorce Doctor Mock, Paper, Scissors Vagabond Scholar The Reaction Perrspectives Satirical Political Report Democratic Underground New Moderate CenterMovement.org The Atlantic Wire The Week Sustainability, Equity, Development Daily Dish Bad Attitudes Greg Prince's Blog Now Listen Here Arts and Palaver Have Coffee Will Write Freedom Writing Fuzzy Logic The Swash Zone Alex Goodall Talk Left Feeling Up in Down Times Bootstrapping Blue Girl in a Blue State Media Bloodhound Simply Left Behind Jon Swift Real Clear Politics Kiko's House Lance Mannion Borowitz Report The Newshoggers Liberal Values newcritics Sustainable Middle Class memeorandum 2Blowhards Cursor Crooks and Liars Moderate Voice Democratic Daily Thursday, October 17, 2013 Can Paul Ryan Lie His Way Out Again? Last year’s VP loser, like all habitual liars, must have a short memory span and expect others to as well. Otherwise how could Paul Ryan vote to send the nation crashing into default and expect to be taken seriously as a Presidential candidate in 2016? Even sooner, as chairman of the House Budget Committee, can he go to work with a straight face on the Congressional conference to resolve differences on the upcoming budget? Ryan’s mendacity is hard to forget, even for a politician. After years of proclaiming her as his idol, he dropped Ayn Rand in a heartbeat when questioned about her as “an outspoken atheist.” His GOP convention speech set truth meters clanging over lies, distortions and omissions, mounting into double figures. Ryan’s indifference to truth seems more reflexive than expedient. Asked about marathons, he casually noted, “I had a two-fifty something.” When Runner’s World checked, the number was 4.0. Now he is the Tea Party policy wonk, whose figures are expected to be sound even if his arguments are loopy. Can someone who voted to decimate the economy be a deal-maker? Only in the same alternate reality that led Mitt Romney to pair up with Ryan, whose entire working life has been not only as one of Rand’s “moochers and looters” but in the 47 percent of Americans “dependent upon government” cited in Romney’s suicidal gaffe. Since college two decades ago, Ryan has been on government payrolls every day of his career, first as a legislative aide and then as a member of the House, never in the GOP hallowed private sector except for an off-campus stint at a fast-food joint. Now Ryan says, “I look forward to convening the first conference on a budget resolution since 2009. And though a budget resolution by itself can’t resolve our spending problem, I’m committed to making a bipartisan budget conference a success.” Is that a lie? Are his lips moving?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1382193260909</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:34:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382193699908-16</Id><Title>bye-bye</Title><Msg>Is'nt it time for Chambers to say so long and fly away on his private jet?</Msg><Username>senorstreet</Username><Timestamp>1382193699908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 10:41:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382196277080-17</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare disaster is only deepening</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382151143979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 22:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is HIllary Clinton a #$%$ and tax cheat for hiding money in a Caymen island account? Neil where do you libiots get the idea that it's morally fine for any liberal to keep their money in off shore accounts as long as they're not running for President? I don't get that logic.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382196277080</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:24:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382196455607-18</Id><Topic><Title>Obamacare disaster is only deepening</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382151143979</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-18 22:52:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>, The Daily Caller posts news that none other than Democrat Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi who has #$%$ and moaned about Romney’s wealth has between $1 million and $5 million in partnership income from ”Matthews International Capital Management LLC,” a group that emphasizes that it has a “A Singular Focus on Investing in Asia.” Can the Marxistcrats be any more dumb than this? Not only is Pelosi invested in Matthews International Capital Management LLC, but she’s also an investor in “Moduslink Global,” one of the “outsourcing pioneers” that Mitt Romney has been criticized over by Pelosi, Wasserman-Schultz, Axelrod, Obama, Jarret, other Democrats and the pink slime media. Karma really is a #$%$ isn’t it?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382196455607</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382197246281-19</Id><Title>When America revolts against OBAMAcare ...</Title><Msg>Who do you think they'll hold responsible, the Republicans, or OBAMA? Or is that too difficult a question for some of you?</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382197246281</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382197837694-20</Id><Title>those pesky skewed polls, who knew the WSJ just polled Obama supporters, LOL</Title><Msg>According to an NBC News/Wall Street Journal poll taken last week, views of the Republican Party sank to record lows and 70 percent of respondents thought Republicans in Congress were putting their own political agenda ahead of what was good for the country. The poll also found that negative feelings about the Tea Party had risen, with 47 percent saying they had negative feelings about the group, including 34 percent who described their feelings as “very negative.” Just 21 percent of Americans now say they feel positive about the group. But when Cruz was asked Friday about the poll, he dismissed it as having a problematic methodology. He said: “If you seek out liberal Obama supporters and ask them their views, they’re going to tell you they’re liberal Obama supporters. That’s not reflective of where this country is.” In fact, it is Cruz’s methodology that is flawed. His grandiloquence may well be the undoing of the Grand Old Party. You can't make up how stupid this guy is.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382197837694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382198406949-21</Id><Title>Can you believe the dopes at Yahoo Finance ...</Title><Msg>Put Al Gore on the home page? What, there's nothing else going on in the financial world at all that they have to feature a global warming fraud on medication who made millions from Al Jazeera?</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382198406949</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:00:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382199318394-22</Id><Title>Mercury retrograde coming up on Monday</Title><Msg>get your votes in now.</Msg><Username>junior_has_fleas</Username><Timestamp>1382199318394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:15:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382199469935-23</Id><Title>fat tea billies rejoice at destruction</Title><Msg>TWO US scout leaders say they have received death threats after a video of them toppling an age-old rock formation in the western state of Utah went viral online. Nearly two million people have watched the video of Glenn Taylor pushing a massive 170 million-year-old red rock over in Goblin Valley State Park, filmed by his fellow scout leader Dave Hall. The pair, who celebrated by doing high fives after the rock fell, insist they pushed it because it was loose and they feared it could topple onto a visitor to the park. But facing possible felony charges, they admit they probably should have found a park ranger before taking action themselves, whether filmed or not. "I think we made the right decision, but probably the wrong method," Hall said, according to the Salt Lake Tribune. "We take full responsibility for whatever mistake we made, and we're open to whatever that means from the state, from the Boy Scouts' office, etc," he added. -</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382199469935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382201850278-24</Id><Title>tea billies give me hemorrhoids</Title><Msg>Whenever I think of those tea billies, my #$%$ starts to itch and burn. I just can't stand it. Makes me want to drop everything and ride my bicycle to Rome</Msg><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382201850278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:57:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382204126808-25</Id><Title>Ted Cruz to lead Confederacy in Armed Rebellion</Title><Msg>War will soon breakout,,,imho</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204126808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382204191373-26</Id><Title>Obamacare made GW Bush an Alcoholic</Title><Msg>it sure did,,,made him a jack daniels junkie</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204191373</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382204296320-27</Id><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Msg>Poor sick people,,,,</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382204819689-28</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz to lead Confederacy in Armed Rebellion</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204126808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Take another toke of your bong and have a great weekend, choomer ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382204819689</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382206240509-29</Id><Title>LOL</Title><Msg>But the outcome is clear: Safe Republican districts gave us the Tea Party. This is why the Tea Party is so much stronger in the House than in the Senate: Senate districts are states, which can’t be gerrymandered. Freed from chasing the median national voter, Tea Party representatives could move far to the right without fear of being voted out of office. The motivated voters who showed up for primaries pushed out more moderate Republicans still playing the old game. The disastrous consequence for Republicans is a self-perpetuating party-within-a-party that doesn’t care if it makes the wider party unelectable nationally. Tea Party supporters think they are fighting for the Republican soul, and they are: If they win, they will drive the party so far from the median voter that a Republican president will become unimaginable. In theory, this problem should be self-correcting, as Republican voters realize that protest politicians won’t serve their real interests, and replace them with moderates more willing to compromise. If this doesn’t occur, the Republican national leadership will have to push for further redistricting at the state level to help elect more moderate party members. If neither of these things happens, the Republican Party will wither and die. It can’t sustain itself as a permanent minority party that can’t elect a president. A new, more moderate alternative to the Democrats will arise. It’s happened before. The market may need time, but it will shake out.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382206240509</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:10:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382208212872-30</Id><Title>How do you argue with stupid?</Title><Msg>Two-thirds of regular Republicans believe the federal budget deficit has grown this year and 93 percent of Tea Party Republicans agree. Both are wrong; the budget deficit is projected to fall this year from $1.1 trillion to $642 billion.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382208212872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:43:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>7</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382208438932-31</Id><Topic><Title>How do you argue with stupid?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382208212872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"How do you argue with stupid?" It's really not that difficult arguing with you dumb.dumb. You're actually quite predictable ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382208438932</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:47:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382208518320-32</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz to lead Confederacy in Armed Rebellion</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204126808</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:35:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>i'll keep your post in mind. Ur post has teeth!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1382208518320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:48:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382210691485-33</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Halloween</Title><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1382210587426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 15:23:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>B. Gates born on Halloween.</Msg><Username>junior_has_fleas</Username><Timestamp>1382210691485</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 15:24:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382214957405-34</Id><Topic><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well how come you hate Bush? Poor dumb people. Color has nothing to do with it.</Msg><Username>noalliesobama</Username><Timestamp>1382214957405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 16:35:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382215083760-35</Id><Topic><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It has everything to do with it when you're a racist like buddhazenpeace ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382215083760</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 16:38:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382216812502-36</Id><Topic><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well see, there you go again friend. Obama IS white, his mom is white and he was raised by white people. thanks.</Msg><Username>mrjasongayby</Username><Timestamp>1382216812502</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:06:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382217163185-37</Id><Topic><Title>How do you argue with stupid?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382208212872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama spent 42% more than revenues. What would you call that? Facts are how you argue with stupid. Dumas.</Msg><Username>noalliesobama</Username><Timestamp>1382217163185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:12:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382217535490-38</Id><Title>LIKE OBAMA, BILL CLINTON IS APPARENTLY BI-SEXUAL</Title><Msg>what's wrong with these sick, sick, SICK dems anyways?</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1382217535490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:18:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382217632875-39</Id><Topic><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Would have you voted for him if he were white, bud-d-hazy-one? One time in your life, be honest with your answer, pecker-wood!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1382217632875</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:20:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382219712863-40</Id><Topic><Title>If the Presidents not white...Hate Him</Title><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1382204296320</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 13:38:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If the commie Buddhazen was ever honest even one time in his loser liberal anti-American nnuslim loving life he wouldn't be a Democrat, so save your breath.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382219712863</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:55:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221130692-41</Id><Topic><Title>How do you argue with stupid?</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382208212872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 14:43:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny you make up numbers and call them facts. In what year did Obama spend 42% more then revenues? LOL Facts are how you argue with stupid, tea billie made up statistics aren't facts</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382221130692</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:18:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221380451-42</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies give me hemorrhoids</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382201850278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:57:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>go ahead dumbivan, get out of here, you won't be missed turd!</Msg><Username>mrjasongayby</Username><Timestamp>1382221380451</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:23:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221858088-43</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies give me hemorrhoids</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382201850278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:57:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol I can just see your huge, #$%$ draped over a little bike seat as you struggle to peddle just to the end of your block dumbo you 400 lb. freak!</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1382221858088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:30:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382221969170-44</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE OBAMA, BILL CLINTON IS APPARENTLY BI-SEXUAL</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1382217535490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no doubt--he probably does it with the family dog too</Msg><Username>jaysallstarss</Username><Timestamp>1382221969170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:32:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382222260936-45</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies give me hemorrhoids</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382201850278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 12:57:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think that's a fake, a parody of dumb.dumb, LOL. ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382222260936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:37:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382223193286-46</Id><Title>Obama Alllowing Mexican Govt to Hand out USA ID Cards to Ilegal Alien Mexicans in North Carolina</Title><Msg>Obama Alllowing Mexican Govt to Hand out USA ID Cards to Ilegal Alien Mexicans in North Carolina. WT?????</Msg><Username>jimmy_carter_a_miserable_failure</Username><Timestamp>1382223193286</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:53:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382223336928-47</Id><Title>ILLEGAL ALIENS ILLEGALLY BLOCK SAN FRANCISCO DEPORTATION BUS</Title><Msg>I'd like to see a demoncrat illegal alien lover goto Mexico and sit in front of a Mexican deportation bus and see what happens.</Msg><Username>jimmy_carter_a_miserable_failure</Username><Timestamp>1382223336928</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 18:55:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382225249516-48</Id><Title>HAHAHAHAHA DEMOCRAT PEETER TWEETER ANTHONY WEINERS NY MAYORAL CAMPAIGN PETERS OUT!!</Title><Msg>HAHAHAHAHA DEMOCRAT PEETER TWEETER ANTHONY WEINERS NY MAYORAL CAMPAIGN PETERS OUT!! However I was somewhat suprized that the degenerate lowlife sex pervert NYC population didn't elect one of their own kind of sexo pervert.</Msg><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1382225249516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:27:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382225512677-49</Id><Topic><Title>HAHAHAHAHA DEMOCRAT PEETER TWEETER ANTHONY WEINERS NY MAYORAL CAMPAIGN PETERS OUT!!</Title><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1382225249516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Had the peter tweeter won the NYC Mayor election the degenerate NYC voters would have to pay Anthony Weiner more than $100,000 per year to tweet his peter to school girls and young boys during all his working hours.</Msg><Username>teju_lizard_skin_panties</Username><Timestamp>1382225512677</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:31:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382226192187-50</Id><Topic><Title>LIKE OBAMA, BILL CLINTON IS APPARENTLY BI-SEXUAL</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1382217535490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 17:18:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And then the piece of nnuslim siht EATS the dog. . The ASPCA wants to impeach the blud thirsty baby killing e fill dog eating sadistic SOS too. . S= Sack</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382226192187</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:43:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382226500112-51</Id><Topic><Title>HAHAHAHAHA DEMOCRAT PEETER TWEETER ANTHONY WEINERS NY MAYORAL CAMPAIGN PETERS OUT!!</Title><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1382225249516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They, the degenerate low life Dems, would have no problem with that. . After all, look how they love and support their blud thirsty nnurderous nnusllim bone smoking nnessiah.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382226500112</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:48:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382226944091-52</Id><Title>Al Gore eyes Twitter for a possible buy?</Title><Msg>Well, he did invent the internet after all. Might as well own a piece of it too, LOL</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382226944091</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:55:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382227643584-53</Id><Topic><Title>HAHAHAHAHA DEMOCRAT PEETER TWEETER ANTHONY WEINERS NY MAYORAL CAMPAIGN PETERS OUT!!</Title><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1382225249516</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 19:27:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess that means he's free to expose himself all over the internet now without further repercussions. That should make our resident peter tweeter junior happy ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1382227643584</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 20:07:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382229693624-54</Id><Topic><Title>those pesky skewed polls, who knew the WSJ just polled Obama supporters, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382197837694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember how Dumb makes fun of weekend posters? And here he is today. What a moron.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1382229693624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 20:41:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382233141096-55</Id><Topic><Title>those pesky skewed polls, who knew the WSJ just polled Obama supporters, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1382197837694</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 11:50:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah, but notice he is not posting now (as he would point out) because it's his usual scheduled time at the bathhouse with junior, magoo and Al smith to rump ride each other.</Msg><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1382233141096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 21:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1382235381927-56</Id><Title>The crazy Kenyan's Gov shut down cost the country billions!</Title><Msg>Almost as much as one of his vacations.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382235381927</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 22:16:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1382236071096-57</Id><Topic><Title>Now the nnuslim monkey is selling hand grenades to the Mexican Drug Cartel</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382235241237</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 22:14:01 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More blood on the e fill commie Kenyan's e fill hands. . So you know his followers will worship him even more now.</Msg><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1382236071096</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-10-19 22:27:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>