<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-10-16"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381896770626-1</Id><Title>US Congress should Amend the Constitution so it can hang GW BUSH and his mafia for crimes against humanity</Title><Msg>Republican Anglosaxons are against health care reform because they cannot tolerate health care that caters to all, including NON-ANGLOSAXONS. In their mind, good quality medical care should be given only to White Anglosaxons, and that Non-Anglosaxons should get substandard medical care. The concept of universal health care sends shudders down REPUBLICAN ANGLOSAXON spines.</Msg><Username>reps_r_skunks</Username><Timestamp>1381896770626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:12:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381896857731-2</Id><Topic><Title>US Congress should Amend the Constitution so it can hang GW BUSH and his mafia for crimes against humanity</Title><Username>reps_r_skunks</Username><Timestamp>1381896770626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>would yours also, if you had to pay for anything!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381896857731</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381896978629-3</Id><Title>Only way to stop the Republicans' madness is The House = Democrats' in 2014</Title><Msg>Obama can bring prosperity to Americans when unhindered by Republicans in Congress. The Anglo Saxon Republican tactics are designed to benefit rich Republican Anglo Saxons at the cost of exploiting working class democrats and misguided poor republicans. Republican Anglo Saxon cartel's strategy includes brain-washing bible-belt republicans (i.e. misguided red necks and religiously-exploited misguided republican anti-abortionists) into towing the Cartel's line of opposing Democrats' efforts to bring universal health care for all and manufacturing industry back into the USA. Republicans do not want health care for all because they want to concentrate the wealth and benefits of health care only in select few. The value of a currency comes chiefly from tangible manufactured goods, not from services that derive their value from manufactured goods. Republican Anglosaxons are destroying America by promoting outsourcing of manufacturing industries to China, and they are doing so knowingly and wilfully and deliberately--they don't care for anybody other than their own Republican Anglo Saxon kind.. DEMOCRATS understand what the Anglo Saxon Republicans were surreptitiously doing to America. Only DEMOCRATS know how to fix this problem by promoting manufacturing in America and sharing the wealth generated from US manufacturing of goods by providing Universal Health Care for all Americans Only way to stop the Republicans' madness is The House = Democrats' in 2014.</Msg><Username>reps_r_skunks</Username><Timestamp>1381896978629</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:16:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381897704643-4</Id><Topic><Title>US Congress should Amend the Constitution so it can hang GW BUSH and his mafia for crimes against humanity</Title><Username>reps_r_skunks</Username><Timestamp>1381896770626</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:12:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrats want to pay for Universal Health Care (remember -- fines if one doesn't sign up for health insurance), but the Anglo Saxon Republicans don't want to pay for this Health Care because their old-boys-club mentality makes it hard for them to include non-Anglo Saxons within the health care plan, and because for them this change is a bitter pill hard to swallow.</Msg><Username>reps_r_skunks</Username><Timestamp>1381897704643</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381898271130-5</Id><Topic><Title>cant believe obama shut down the government.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381870601147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:56:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>IDIOT.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381898271130</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:37:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381898435075-6</Id><Topic><Title>cant believe obama shut down the government.</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381870601147</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:56:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Geeee the most boring man in america posts another inanity. Yaaaaawwwwwwwwwnnnnn !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381898435075</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:40:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381898551818-7</Id><Topic><Title>The country's in chaos</Title><Username>ivanhoe_ofloxly</Username><Timestamp>1381880119284</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 19:35:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am trying to decide if you are as stupid as Walter or a tad more ? Hmmm tic toc tic toc...</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381898551818</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:42:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381898885667-8</Id><Topic><Title>A DEFAULT WOULD BE GREAT FOR OUR ECONOMY!!! IT WOULD BE A SIGNAL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381869981739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The board idiot has another mental ffahrt</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381898885667</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:48:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381899099652-9</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies say a default wouldn't be that bad</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381869814173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He actually said that every republican has a single branched family tree chimp. At which point Joe idiot flipped over his chair while Betty Quick laughed her ahzz off.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381899099652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:51:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381899377998-10</Id><Title>Obama Says John Boehner 'Can't Control His Caucus'</Title><Msg>I say Obama cannot control a country ---- the buck stops with you pecker-wood! Spin it anyway you like, but your the boss!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899377998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:56:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381899631169-11</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Says John Boehner 'Can't Control His Caucus'</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899377998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:56:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think a president that would let 4 Americans die to get elected, would think twice about letting the country default on their debt, a guy that sold drugs through college?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899631169</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 01:00:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381902022874-12</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Says John Boehner 'Can't Control His Caucus'</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899377998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:56:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Now don't go on the Bengazi rant Gail, you know that is not good for your health girl.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381902022874</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 01:40:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381902879595-13</Id><Title>41% of global wealth in the hands of a mere 0.7% of the world's population</Title><Msg>And the talking heads wonder why there is no growth in the economy.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381902879595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 01:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381906146036-14</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Says John Boehner 'Can't Control His Caucus'</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899377998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:56:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>surf, Obama nor you have sense enough to pour #$%$ out of a boot if the instructions were written on the heel --- why? Pecker-wood</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381906146036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 02:49:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381906288862-15</Id><Topic><Title>41% of global wealth in the hands of a mere 0.7% of the world's population</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381902879595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 01:54:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There is a reason, those 0.7% are not as stupid as you and your messiah</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381906288862</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 02:51:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381907114288-16</Id><Topic><Title>Anyone else get the email from MD   </Title><Username>kingtrader234a</Username><Timestamp>1381794369056</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-10-14 19:46:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>XCTF</Msg><Username>jimmyjohns429</Username><Timestamp>1381907114288</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 03:05:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381917216584-17</Id><Title>1 bitcoin</Title><Msg>=$160 this morning. LoL!</Msg><Username>bvioml123</Username><Timestamp>1381917216584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 05:53:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381921880777-18</Id><Topic><Title>tea billies say a default wouldn't be that bad</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381869814173</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:43:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Using another of your catchphrases? "false dilemma" -Nothing false about what's going on here with the threat of default. Maybe you are referring to the FALSE information on FOX NEWS that it'll be fine if we don't raise the debt ceiling, we can still pay everyone we owe.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381921880777</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:11:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381921930919-19</Id><Topic><Title>A DEFAULT WOULD BE GREAT FOR OUR ECONOMY!!! IT WOULD BE A SIGNAL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381869981739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I see you are feeble-minded and do not understand basic economics.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381921930919</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:12:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381922002595-20</Id><Title>Time for the PRES. to declare MARTIAL LAW and increase the DEBT CEILING through EXECUTIVE ORDER!</Title><Msg>WALL STREET and BIG INVESTOR $$ will back him up!</Msg><Username>deadpainting_is_a_coward</Username><Timestamp>1381922002595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:13:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381922507508-21</Id><Topic><Title>I asked some Vets which they would prefer, continuing getting their checks or have access to the Memorials. They said screw the Tea Party we want our checks.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381864155883</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 15:09:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>what makes u think they weren't white? didn't see any vets of color down in DC!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381922507508</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381922575546-22</Id><Title>Boehner can't even get a REPUB bill passed in the HOUSE- Boehner is utterly USELESS!</Title><Msg>What a wastes of congressional space!</Msg><Username>deadpainting_is_a_coward</Username><Timestamp>1381922575546</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:22:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381922760995-23</Id><Title>So the USA cannot function without issuing endless government debt</Title><Msg>So the USA cannot function without issuing endless government debt, this according to Wall Street and all those who have made trillions over the decades in the black hole of trading and manipulating government debt.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1381922760995</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:26:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381923589532-24</Id><Topic><Title>LATEST POLLS SHOW THAT OBLAMER AND DEMS BLAMED BY VOTERS</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1381879197957</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 19:19:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thoughtful Amerikans did place the blame where it belongs, Uncle Juan McCain was sporting the results of a poll on CNN yesterday , he said they will settle, why? because of this 74% negative rating on the Repukes.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381923589532</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:39:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381923728581-25</Id><Topic><Title>A DEFAULT WOULD BE GREAT FOR OUR ECONOMY!!! IT WOULD BE A SIGNAL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381869981739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rep. Steve King (IA): Debt ceiling limit, default talk is "false demagoguery"</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381923728581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:42:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381923995736-26</Id><Title>Breaking, new proposal by GOP</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—Adding his voice to the eleventh-hour debate about the government shutdown, Senator Rand Paul (R-Kentucky) today proposed reopening just enough of the government to hold new hearings on Benghazi. “Across this great nation of ours, people are suffering,” he told Fox News’s Megyn Kelly. “Suffering, Megyn, because they still don’t know what really happened in Benghazi.” Noting that the government shutdown had furloughed investigators who could be looking into Benghazi, he said, “If there’s something in our government more worthy of funding than that, I can’t think of it.” Senator Paul said he knew that he would draw the ire of fellow Republicans by suggesting that the government be partially reopened, but added, “Sometimes, you have to put politics aside when there is something more important at stake, and I think any reasonable person would agree that there is nothing more important than getting to the bottom of Benghazi.” “For the two weeks of this shutdown, the American people have had no new information about Benghazi,” he said. “It’s time to stop the madness.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381923995736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:46:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381924150165-27</Id><Title>It's no coincidence strengthening tea party is driving wedge between corporate America and Republican Party.</Title><Msg>Many tea-party supporters are small businessmen who see taxes and regulations as direct threats to their livelihood. Unlike establishment Republicans who see potential gains from government programs such as infrastructure funding, these tea partiers regard most government spending as a deadweight loss. Because many of them run low-wage businesses on narrow margins, they believe that they have no choice but to fight measures, such as ObamaCare, that reduce their flexibility and raise their costs—measures to which large corporations with deeper pockets can adjust. It's no coincidence that the strengthening influence of the tea party is driving a wedge between corporate America and the Republican Party. It's hard to see how the U.S. can govern itself unless corporate America pushes the Republican establishment to fight back against the tea party—or switches sides.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381924150165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381924394886-28</Id><Topic><Title>Breaking, new proposal by GOP</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381923995736</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:46:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>remember Hillary &amp; Obama think those dead AMERICANS don't matter!!</Msg><Username>gelinasalan</Username><Timestamp>1381924394886</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:53:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381925209908-29</Id><Title>President Romney said he doesn't believe this poll</Title><Msg>Nearly three-quarters of Americans disapprove of Republicans' handling of the budget crisis, according to an ABC/Washington Post poll released Monday. Disapproval of the GOP, which has risen steadily since just before the government shutdown began, is now at 74 percent, up 11 points from late September. A majority of Americans are also discontented with Democrats' role in the budget negotiations. But disapproval ratings for Democrats in Congress and for President Barack Obama, both of which started at a lower level than disapproval of Republicans in Congress, have remained largely unchanged in the past two weeks. Sixty-one percent of Americans now dislike congressional Democrats' handling of the crisis, while 53 percent dislike Obama's. Those are rises of only 5 points and 3 points, respectively, from before the shutdown began. Republicans themselves are increasingly negative about their lawmakers. In the latest survey, Americans who identified as Republican were about evenly split on congressional Republicans' performance, with 47 percent giving them a thumbs-down. Sixty-three percent of "very conservative" Republicans, however approve. Other surveys have found similarly bleak results for the GOP. A Gallup poll last week showed the party's rating at a record low, while an NBC/Wall Street Journal poll, also released last week, found that Americans assigned Republicans far more blame for the shutdown. The latter survey also found evidence of an "ideological boomerang” against the GOP, with support rising for a Democratic-controlled Congress, Obama's health care law and an expanded role for government. The current political atmosphere is reminiscent of that surrounding the government shutdowns in 1995-1996, said pollster Gary Langer, from which he drew a note of caution. "That result might give some pause to prognosticators who suggest that criticism of the GOP today will spell losses for the party in the 2014 midterm elections, just more than a year off," Langer told ABC. "No such impact seems readily apparent in the 1996 election: Ten months after those shutdowns, Clinton won re-election, but the Republicans held the House and Senate alike. Now, as then, what may matter most is not just today’s blame, but the eventual resolution of the crisis, and the extent of damage done en route." The ABC/Washington Post poll surveyed 1,010 adults between Oct. 9 and Oct. 13, using live telephone interviews.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381925209908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 08:06:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381925615015-30</Id><Title>nice! these picks are killing it</Title><Msg>These people know their stocks. I can’t believe how spot on all of their picks have been. Great tool and asset to have at your disposal. Text the word PROFIT to 5,5,5,8,8,8 now.</Msg><Username>rjustin119</Username><Timestamp>1381925615015</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 08:13:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381927040364-31</Id><Title>Galena (GALE)</Title><Msg>Galena currently has five drugs in its cancer pipeline, two each in Phase 1 and 2, and one in Phase 3. Galena also controls the rights to Abstral, a breakthrough cancer pain tablet that the company acquired from Orexo Pharmaceuticals in March. However, it is Galena's cancer pipeline that I want to focus on today. NeuVax, currently in Phase 3 trials for breast cancer, works by stimulating the patient's immune system to seek out and destroy residual cancer cells. According to the National Cancer Institute, over 230,000 women in the U.S. are diagnosed with breast cancer annually. Of these women, about 75% test positive for Human Epidermal growth factor Receptor 2 (HER2), but only 25% of all breast cancer patients are eligible for Herceptin®. NeuVax is targeting the 50% of breast cancer patients not eligible for Herceptin who have HER2. This is a very large market potential for Galena. However, there is much more to this story and the reason for my interest in Galena as an investment candidate.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381927040364</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 08:37:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381928325536-32</Id><Topic><Title>It's no coincidence strengthening tea party is driving wedge between corporate America and Republican Party.</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo4</Username><Timestamp>1381924150165</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 07:49:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no most tea-party supporters are males over the age of 65 that don't work and collect social security checks</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381928325536</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 08:58:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381928434115-33</Id><Topic><Title>Obama Says John Boehner 'Can't Control His Caucus'</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381899377998</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 00:56:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—Adding his voice to the eleventh-hour debate about the government shutdown, Senator Rand Paul (R-Kentucky) today proposed reopening just enough of the government to hold new hearings on Benghazi. “Across this great nation of ours, people are suffering,” he told Fox News’s Megyn Kelly. “Suffering, Megyn, because they still don’t know what really happened in Benghazi.” Noting that the government shutdown had furloughed investigators who could be looking into Benghazi, he said, “If there’s something in our government more worthy of funding than that, I can’t think of it.” Senator Paul said he knew that he would draw the ire of fellow Republicans by suggesting that the government be partially reopened, but added, “Sometimes, you have to put politics aside when there is something more important at stake, and I think any reasonable person would agree that there is nothing more important than getting to the bottom of Benghazi.” “For the two weeks of this shutdown, the American people have had no new information about Benghazi,” he said. “It’s time to stop the madness.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381928434115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381928575161-34</Id><Title>hot stock trade alerts</Title><Msg>All you have to do is follow their picks. They send them right to your phone. Text the word PROFIT to 5,5,5,8,8,8</Msg><Username>craftl746</Username><Timestamp>1381928575161</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:02:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381929312411-35</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP saves the day!!</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381929312411</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:15:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381929355344-36</Id><Topic><Title>A DEFAULT WOULD BE GREAT FOR OUR ECONOMY!!! IT WOULD BE A SIGNAL</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381869981739</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 16:46:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Meanwhile educated adults Default Doubters Repudiated by Republican Economists By Rich Miller - Oct 11, 2013 12:24 PM ET Republican lawmakers have played down the significance of hitting the debt limit, saying the U.S. can avoid default by putting aside funds to pay bond holders. Economists affiliated with the party aren’t so sanguine. Glenn Hubbard, Douglas Holtz-Eakin and Donald Marron, all of whom served in President George W. Bush’s administration, voiced concern that such a strategy could end up hurting the economy even if default were averted. Former chairman of President George W. Bush’s Council of Economic Advisers Glenn Hubbard, who is now dean of Columbia University’s Graduate School of Business in New York, said, “I regret that both sides have taken positions that make it very difficult now to get to where we need to be.” Photographer: David Paul Morris/Bloomberg “I would still worry about it,” said Hubbard, who was chairman of Bush’s Council of Economic Advisers from 2001 to 2003. “It signals that we have an inability as a nation to get our budget process in order.” That could “do damage to U.S. growth potential and credibility,” he added.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381929355344</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:15:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381930646142-37</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The market is up because the democrats are winning this fight. There will be more borrowing ,more spending ,and with Yellen taking over the fed, more money printing. Just what Wall St. likes. Not good for the country, but good for the fat cats. The rich will continue to get richer</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381930646142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:37:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381931990794-38</Id><Title>Check out NGHT right now! It is about to go on a massive run</Title><Msg>NGHT has proven gold reserves and trades at just .08 cents. This one is going to be huge. Check it out Get the full NGHT profile at: creativework.asia/753597</Msg><Username>colonbrandon956</Username><Timestamp>1381931990794</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 09:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381932757098-39</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Same old story. The bill passes at 1 minute until midnight. But the same thing will happen in three months now. USA is now worse than Greece. Time for a debt downgrade.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1381932757098</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:12:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381932913437-40</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so you don't think the GOP learned its lesson and will hold the country hostage again?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381932913437</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:15:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381933112301-41</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your not looking at the same Bond Market as I am. ???</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381933112301</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:18:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381933260639-42</Id><Topic><Title>WOW, look at those John Boehner Futures!!</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381895805764</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 23:56:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>GOP and Dems hold out on a deal until midnight deadline so they all can get more pork spending, as a bribe to agree to the deal.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1381933260639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381933431713-43</Id><Title>Dems have done NOTHING but sit on their hands and ...</Title><Msg>say, "NO". GOP has been doing ALL the work these past few weeks. FINALLY, in the 11th hour the Dims agree to negotiate. Bunch of manipulating LOSERs...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381933431713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:23:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381934019032-44</Id><Title>CSCO keep increasing Free Cash Flow in the last three year</Title><Msg>The execution is marvelous and accumulating cash and buy back shares while market was weak. per share earning will increase moving forward. Now is the time to join the Internet everything. .Junitper just got upgrade for the same reason.</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381934019032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:33:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381934273807-45</Id><Title>NGHT is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>NGHT is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading upStart your DD on NGHT ASAP Get the full NGHT profile at: creativework.asia/753597</Msg><Username>jacobavery557</Username><Timestamp>1381934273807</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381934279269-46</Id><Title>NGHT is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>NGHT is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading upStart your DD on NGHT ASAP Get the full NGHT profile at: creativework.asia/753597</Msg><Username>jacobavery557</Username><Timestamp>1381934279269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:37:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381934287036-47</Id><Title>NGHT is the next big gainer</Title><Msg>NGHT is looking good here. They show some huge assets in their financials so the book value is atleast .50 cents per share. I am loading upStart your DD on NGHT ASAP Get the full NGHT profile at: creativework.asia/753597</Msg><Username>jacobavery557</Username><Timestamp>1381934287036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:38:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381934436453-48</Id><Topic><Title>Dems have done NOTHING but sit on their hands and ...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381933431713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean my post is reading like one of yours?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381934436453</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:40:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381934712227-49</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO keep increasing Free Cash Flow in the last three year</Title><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381934019032</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:33:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Based on the FCF, it is a $34 dollar stock. From the tech recruitment ads, a lot of hiring for network it folks. It means lots of big IT project is starting for the recovery cycle. The hiring ads is a leading indicator for CSCO.</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381934712227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381934744415-50</Id><Topic><Title>Dems have done NOTHING but sit on their hands and ...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381933431713</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:23:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can't picture myself getting toospecific with the nutcases on this board. Every time I do, they either run away, play shoot the messenger, or sling profane ad hominem. Maybe you should act like an adult for a while?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381934744415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 10:45:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381935736170-51</Id><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Msg>To apologize to the entire country and beg for forgiveness on their knees. They created George W, they created Ted Cruz, hell they created LBJ what is it about Texas that they continue to create political candidates that are so out of touch they hurt the country.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381935956232-52</Id><Title>stock market up 200 points</Title><Msg>on the defeat of the tea billie crazies, Obama wins again, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935956232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381935970923-53</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I can't picture myself getting too specific with the nutcases on this board." Any Questions?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381935970923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:06:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381936146026-54</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb has to be the most asinine poster anywhere on the Yahoo boards. What a total moron!!</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381936146026</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:09:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381936227289-55</Id><Topic><Title>stock market up 200 points</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935956232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bond market is doing squat. The common wisdom is that bond traders are more informed than Stock Market speculators. Evidently, they are still concerned about default.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381936227289</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381936531924-56</Id><Topic><Title>stock market up 200 points</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935956232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thumbs up: Ego and party. Thumbs down: American people. Yeah, that 0bama's a real statesman...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381936531924</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:15:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381936553714-57</Id><Topic><Title>stock market up 200 points</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935956232</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:05:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Odd that Dumb is so happy that the one per centers are making even more money. Can't buy much stock working part time at McDonalds. Thats mostly the jobs Obama has created.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381936553714</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381936708114-58</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am all for freedom of the press, and freedom of speech, but the purpose of both is to create an informed electorate. His posts border on incitement when they aren't just plain stupid. They are not "informative" in any way, except to point out that Libs are liars, when one has the common sense to fact check and think logically. His inflammatory posts should be deleted, and the authorities should be contacted, IMO.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381936708114</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:18:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937099115-59</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Doubt anyone here takes him seriously.. Take away the multiple ids on this board and maybe 6-8 people post here. Dumb wont have much effect on world events posting to that group.lol</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381937099115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:24:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937224056-60</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If only he could do something positive for all of them, like getting them to take their meds, or finding a mentor for the ret*arded kids who agree with him.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381937224056</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:27:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937408697-61</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The real Junior should start posting soon. He always does when Dumb is getting slammed.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381937408697</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:30:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937513148-62</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Take away the multiple ids on this board and maybe 6-8 people post here." There might be one or two racist tea billie gun nuts. The rest of the conservatives seem, well, "conservative."</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381937513148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:31:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937639112-63</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'd like to own the franchise on his pharmaceuticals. That company must be raking it in, and the shyt evidently doesn't work.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381937639112</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:33:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381937853392-64</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The intelligent posters left. Doremi and Joeb were smart whether you agreed with them or not. And idiot Magoo brags about running them off. When I tire of picking on Junior, I 'll be gone too.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381937853392</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:37:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381938078248-65</Id><Topic><Title>It's time for TEXAS</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381935736170</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:02:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I know I got better things to do than keep correcting their propaganda. You're right, there aren't that many people here, and it's not like politics will change because of a handful of voters. He "ran them off?" Maybe they took a peek at reality and didn't want to waste so much time trying to cure the permanently insane?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381938078248</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:41:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381938220132-66</Id><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Msg>The democrats handily defeated the republicans in the budget battle. And now they will gloat. Real losers will turn out to be the American people.</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381938651029-67</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Really? I thought the whole thing was political theater. Comedy or tragedy. The comedy continues for what, another month? How long before the desperation to save "Pin the tail on the donkey" healthcare will turn into an effort to throw it from the train? They got what they wanted? This healthcare will turn into their albatross.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381938651029</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:50:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381938962544-68</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with that. Obamacare will fail on its own.But until it does it will greatly damage America.</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938962544</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:56:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939044384-69</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think it will fail. I think they will slice and dice it to make it the "Slaw of the Land"</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381939044384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:57:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939286977-70</Id><Title>Thank god the DEMOCRATS prevailed- the HOUSE wanted to SHUT DOWN THE GOVERNMENT</Title><Msg>to meet their demands!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381939286977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:01:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939312275-71</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reid and Obama have made it obvious there will be no changes as long as they are in power.</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381939312275</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:01:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939338247-72</Id><Title>buy MTSL</Title><Msg>buyout coming</Msg><Username>drtej202</Username><Timestamp>1381939338247</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:02:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939382094-73</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>THANK GOD!!!</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381939382094</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:03:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939389753-74</Id><Title>yes chalk one up for the democrats and america</Title><Msg>please explain why hte gop wanted to shut down the government because a law was passed giving americans affordable health insurance wow did the gop lose big</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939389753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:03:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939418067-75</Id><Topic><Title>Thank god the DEMOCRATS prevailed- the HOUSE wanted to SHUT DOWN THE GOVERNMENT</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381939286977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:01:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>can you imagine the destruction those geezer losers would have on america?</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939418067</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:03:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939437244-76</Id><Title>News articles will soon be coming out</Title><Msg>about how much money the DNC is raising on the stupidity of the tea party, big business is fleeing the GOP now that the tea party has infected the party</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381939437244</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:03:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939501266-77</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Major provisions have been delayed by both. So they pick and choose what they mean by "no changes?"</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381939501266</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:05:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939528415-78</Id><Title>Funny how the tea billies are all upset</Title><Msg>now that it looks like the Country won't default on the debt and cause a world wide great depression</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381939528415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:05:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939582142-79</Id><Topic><Title>Thank god the DEMOCRATS prevailed- the HOUSE wanted to SHUT DOWN THE GOVERNMENT</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381939286977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:01:26 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Once the DEMS regain the HOUSE in 2014, the ADULTS in the room will be running the show!</Msg><Username>cooler_heads_are_dems</Username><Timestamp>1381939582142</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:06:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939680767-80</Id><Title>so there will be no shut down and the gop was defeated</Title><Msg>spin time no doubt in anyones mind that the gop planned this circus for months</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939680767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:08:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939695786-81</Id><Topic><Title>Funny how the tea billies are all upset</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381939528415</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:05:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how democrats don't know the difference between a Red Line being drawn, and a political bargaining chip being tossed on the table.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381939695786</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:08:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939814205-82</Id><Topic><Title>so there will be no shut down and the gop was defeated</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939680767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sure was fun. We go another round in three months, or what?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381939814205</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:10:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939815337-83</Id><Topic><Title>so there will be no shut down and the gop was defeated</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939680767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Cruz will be hung out to dry by the GOP establishment</Msg><Username>teaparty_are_crazies</Username><Timestamp>1381939815337</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:10:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939855172-84</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The republicans have been unable to change anything. Obama has changed what is beneficial to him and his party such as waivers and the employer mandate. Since I'm not a lawyer, I dont know if that was legal but so far he has done pretty much what he wants.</Msg><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381939855172</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:10:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381939883689-85</Id><Title>Matt Drudge: Get ready for the return of ‘Speaker Nancy Pelosi’</Title><Msg>Drudge Report proprietor tweeted to his 200,000 foll owers on Wednesday that Rep. Nancy Pelosi will regain the gavel she once held as Speaker of the House. “Speaker Pelosi Part 2: Opening Jan 5. 2015,” posted Drudge on his Twitter feed. Drudge rai sed eyebrows in Sept ember when he appe ared to break with the Rep ublican party. He asked on Twitter, “Why would anyone vote Republican? Please give reason. Ra ised taxes; marching us off to war again; approved more NSA snooping. WHO ARE THEY?</Msg><Username>cooler_heads_are_dems</Username><Timestamp>1381939883689</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:11:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939936317-86</Id><Topic><Title>so there will be no shut down and the gop was defeated</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939680767</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:08:00 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>but the tea billie cancer still infects the GOP, they will hold the country hostage again until we manage to throw them out of every level of government</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381939936317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:12:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381939979820-87</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, this time it only cost him a couple of weeks. I wonder what they will cook up the next time? It must be frustrating to run a country on sequester and at risk of another shutdown every 3 months. What did he actually gain?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381939979820</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:12:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940057317-88</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NO US DEFAULT................... for starters</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381940057317</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940059335-89</Id><Title>Hey guys, remember those pesky motor-voter laws?</Title><Msg>OBAMACARE TO PICK UP WHERE THE NEW BLACK PANTHER PARTY LEFT OFF - Soon doctors will be standing outside of polling places, casting menacing glances at your grandmother. National Journal: "The National Voter Registration Act of 1993, also known as the 'Motor Voter' law, requires government agencies to offer individuals the opportunity to vote--and that includes the newly opened Obamacare exchanges. That gives some Republicans one more reason to oppose the law. If low-income applicants lean Democratic, the argument goes, the exchanges could boost the party's voter rolls. 'The practice raises longstanding suspicions on the right that the ACA exchanges are designed for political as well as regulatory purposes,' said Tim Miller, a senior fellow at the American Enterprise Institute...According to the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services, voter registration must be offered on the ACA exchange application because of the Medicaid eligibility determination. To be in compliance, CMS says they are including language on the paper and online applications that says, 'If you want to register to vote, you can complete a voter registration form at usa.gov.' States that have opted to create their own exchanges are able to develop their own applications and choose how they enforce the National Voter Registration Act requirement." [National Journal]</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381940059335</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940090000-90</Id><Title>IF I WAS A CUSSIN' MAN, I'D LAY A HOT HEAVY DARK LAYER OF OBSCENITIES ALL ACROSS</Title><Msg>the entire Democratic spectrum and hopefully move then into the dark and away from any location they could continue to do such damage to Lady America, the loveliest lady every to live in the history of this dark globe. For the sake of petty power and grubby money, Democrats have endebted, entitled, abused and put into bondage countless generations of young lives, born in what was once the greatest nation ever to have existed. A nation that once gave and liberated it's own people from the bondage of 'afirmative action', 'privilege','birth right' and put every tender soul into a public education system that offered one thing, opportunity. And allowed that same young soul to grow rich or poor, as they labored or not. God bless America....who will damn the Democrats???</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381940090000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940099363-91</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>obama and americans win over the gop taliban what is so bad about affordable healthcare for americans? geesh</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940099363</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940114045-92</Id><Topic><Title>Chalk one up for the democrats</Title><Username>redangel6666</Username><Timestamp>1381938220132</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 11:43:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It wasn't defaulted before. I was asking about gains, not covering potential losses.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381940114045</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940124648-93</Id><Topic><Title>IF I WAS A CUSSIN' MAN, I'D LAY A HOT HEAVY DARK LAYER OF OBSCENITIES ALL ACROSS</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381940090000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just admit defeat and move on</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940124648</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:15:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940175961-94</Id><Title>Tea Party loses their mantra- AFTER ALL they were ELECTED to shut down the US GOV'T</Title><Msg>and DEFUND OBAMACARE... now what good are they?</Msg><Username>teaparty_are_crazies</Username><Timestamp>1381940175961</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:16:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940192876-95</Id><Topic><Title>yes chalk one up for the democrats and america</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381939389753</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:03:09 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>god bless america</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940192876</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940199902-96</Id><Title>hey, Magoo</Title><Msg>How many paydays did you gain? Are you still thinking about BK?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381940199902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:16:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940242208-97</Id><Topic><Title>hey, Magoo</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381940199902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dunno about magoo but my FWM is up 20% in three days ROTF!!!</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940242208</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:17:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940257555-98</Id><Topic><Title>hey, Magoo</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381940199902</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:16:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>as it turns out, my agency was funded until tomorrow...... so hopefully, no missing $$ from my paycheck.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381940257555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:17:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940354796-99</Id><Title>gop really embarrassed themselves</Title><Msg>shut down the government because they can't pass a vote? wow so destructive to the gop brand</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940354796</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940379668-100</Id><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Msg>We won't tolerate the tea party anymore, only traitors that hate America will continue to tolerate the American Taliban.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940479625-101</Id><Title>Strong buy from 9 analyst and Buy from 11 analyst.</Title><Msg>It seems like someone is accumulating the stock for Nasdaq year end rally.</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381940479625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:21:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940521819-102</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea party = losers Americans won't tolerate them</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940521819</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:22:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381940539884-103</Id><Title>so whats the gop spin?</Title><Msg>hilarious</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940539884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940645639-104</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rod Dreher: "I hope the House flips to the Democrats in 2014, so we can be rid of these nuts. Let Ted Cruz sit in the Senate stewing in his precious bodily fluids, and let Washington get back to the business of governing."</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940645639</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940787931-105</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Maher had a few words for wingnut Michele Bachmann and her counterpart on the Supreme Court, Antonin Scalia during his New Rules segment on Real Time this Friday evening, and I particularly enjoyed this bit on Bachmann: And finally, New Rule, I know we can't establish a religious test for office, but if you believe we're living in the end times, like Michele Bachmann does, we get to take away the car keys. Yes, let Jesus take the wheel. If you think the world is about to end, that's your right, but you don't get to vote on next year's budget, because it doesn't concern you! Don't we wish. She's finally going to scurry out of office now that she's under investigation and might not have been reelected anyway, but not before she's got a chance to inflict more damage on the American public. He wrapped things up by going after Scalia and his remarks about the devil being "a real person running around, getting people not to believe in god." As Maher noted, a lot of "reasonable people" see Bachmann as a "total lune, but Scalia as a serious intellectual, when actually, they're the exact same idiot." Maher cited some of Scalia's idiocy about the devil making pigs run off of cliffs before letting him have it. MAHER: Pigs running off cliffs? Hey, leave the debt ceiling deniers out of this. And what is Justice Scalia's theory as to why we don't see the devil anymore? Is it the logical answer that fictions like the devil are in the Bible because it was written before the age of science, when humans didn't know where the sun went at night, and is obviously a reflection of mankind's thinking in his intellectual infancy? Of course not! That makes sense. What Scalia said about the devil is, “He used to be all over the New Testament... What happened to him?... He got wilier.” Motherf**ker! Of course! Wilier. He may be evil, but he's always looking to improve himself. Antonin Scalia once said that people like him, who adhere to a traditional belief, were “regarded as simple minded.” We are, he said, fools for Christ. You know, whether you're fools for Christ, or coo coo for Cocoa Puffs, I really don't care why someone acts like a fool, just that they do and when they do, we keep them away from decision making. It would be one thing if Mr. Scalia sold pizza for a living, but this is a man we go to to interpret our laws. It's like smelling a gas leak and calling an exorcist. Antonin Scalia put George Bush in the White House and he believes the devil went down to Georgia. He gets to decide when life begins and he thinks evil is a person, you know, like a corporation. Here's the problem with believing the devil exists. It means you see the world divided into teams of good and evil and suspect the wily one, may be on the side of them, and when you start seeing compromising with your opponent as a compromise with evil, well, there's your tea party.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381940787931</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:26:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940818345-106</Id><Topic><Title>so whats the gop spin?</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381940539884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:22:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Cruz won't filibuster he must be a RINO, tea party should primary him</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940818345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:26:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381940839049-107</Id><Topic><Title>Everyone loves CSCO</Title><Username>bigtraderjoe</Username><Timestamp>1381521267387</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 15:54:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I like a diversified global hedge fund.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381940839049</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:27:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381941072148-108</Id><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Msg>fantastic</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381941228126-109</Id><Title>US needs a budget without debt increasing to infinity</Title><Msg>Starting to lose hope in the process.</Msg><Username>think5pm</Username><Timestamp>1381941228126</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:33:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941346910-110</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep. Wake up in trailer, watch FOX and Friends, take a dump, drink beer, listen to Rush Limpdik, watch Hanutty/O'Really, drink beer, read Guns and Ammo, masturbate, go to sleep.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381941346910</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:35:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941350594-111</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL that would be so funny if it wasn't so true,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381941350594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:35:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941428781-112</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>some of the regulars here are noticeably absent.</Msg><Username>deadpainting_is_hiding_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941428781</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:37:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941541556-113</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Reminds me of a book by Herb Cohen. The strategy of both parties was lose/ lose. What did you gain? Three more months of running a country on sequester? It seems like playing Basketball from a wheelchair against an NBA team.</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941541556</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:39:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381941764058-114</Id><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Msg>Did Obama shoot himself in the foot to save ACA?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381941880104-115</Id><Title>As part of the deal, Rafael Cruz to be deported to Canada. Canada says BS!</Title><Msg>John Boehner and his House Republicans woke to a round of epically horrible press about their role in the ongoing shutdown and debt ceiling crisis. Boehner's failure to corral his members reached a peak on Tuesday when he could not persuade them to go along with a plan to end the shutdown and avert default. The resulting reaction from the media would be enough to make any Republican weep, let alone the already tear-prone speaker. Politico called Boehner's efforts a "disaster." The Washington Post described it as a "humiliating failure," and said Boehner and his leadership colleagues had " lost all control of their majority." An editorial from the arch-conservative Wall Street Journal board fumed about the GOP strategy, saying that the House caucus "might as well hand the Speaker's gavel to Senate Democratic leader Harry Reid" and urging Republicans to give up their fight. Things were not much better on the morning shows. "After a shutdown that lasted 16 days, a shutdown led by House Republicans...by the end of today, those Republicans may leave with little to nothing to show for it," NBC's Peter Alexander said. "House Republicans are the clear losers," was how ABC's Jon Karl put it. "They pushed to the brink and have nothing to show for it." Even conservative media kingpin Matt Drudge got in on the action:</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381941880104</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:44:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941912240-116</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>January 15th is when the SEQUESTER gets negotiated !</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381941912240</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:45:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381941984560-117</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>sequester has nothing to do with affordable healthcare act sorry art</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941984560</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:46:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942019385-118</Id><Topic><Title>Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser. Patton</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381940379668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:19:39 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>hey art - it was just theater - a theater in which the gop got demolished thanks</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942019385</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:46:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942054908-119</Id><Title>i guess the sequester is the only gop win in 5 years</Title><Msg>and the sequester hurts america they need to try harder ROTF!!!</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942054908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:47:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942242583-120</Id><Title>Houston chronicle regrets supporting Ted CRUZ!</Title><Msg>The Houston Chronicle now regrets support for Ted Cruz</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942242583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942291598-121</Id><Topic><Title>Houston chronicle regrets supporting Ted CRUZ!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942242583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>the whole blurb in on the HAL board.......</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942291598</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:51:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942377595-122</Id><Topic><Title>Houston chronicle regrets supporting Ted CRUZ!</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942242583</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:50:42 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ta lk about regr ets. Sen. Ted Cruz's hom etown newsp aper in Texa s is now voicing its disapp ointment about endor sing the Repub lican for U.S. Senate. The Hous ton Chro nicle pays tribute to Cruz's predecessor, Kay B ailey Hutchison, in an edit orial that takes him to task for contributing to the "chaotic, hyper-partisan atmos phere" in Washi ngton. The he adline: "Why we miss Kay Bailey Hutchison." Hu tchi son decided not to run for re-election last year, after 20 years in the Se nate, and was know n for her staunch advocacy for all things Texas. The Repu blican also, as the edit orial notes, was kn own for "reaching acro ss the ais le when n ecessary." "Wh en we endorsed Ted Cr uz in last No vem ber's gene ral election, we did so with m any rese rvations and at least one specific recom mendation — that he follow Hutchison's ex ample in his con duct as a sen ator," the Houston Chr onicle editorial says. "Obviously, he has not done so. Cr uz has be en pa rt of the pro blem in specific situ ations where Hut chison wo uld ha ve be en part of the sol ution.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942377595</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:52:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942415347-123</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unless they pass a budget. The budget was due on Oct 1, and they failed to pass it. You mean the government shutdown was because they agreed on a budget to last until January 15?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381942415347</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:53:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942464307-124</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>senate passed a budget long ago geezer</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942464307</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:54:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942479318-125</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NOPE! Agreed on a CONTINUING RESOLUTION until Jan 15th Hopefully a real APPROPRIATIONS BILL with retracted sequester cuts will be hammered out by Jan 15th and put for a vote</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942479318</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:54:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942493956-126</Id><Title>Do your DD on NGHT, Looks ready to bust out</Title><Msg>NGHT looks prime for a move higher. I have been researching it for a while. Get the full NGHT profile at: bit(dot) ly /GY1q8Y (replace "(dot)" with ".")</Msg><Username>leviflowers523</Username><Timestamp>1381942493956</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:54:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942541368-127</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And if you had the opportunity to fill one hand with wishes that came true?</Msg><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381942541368</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:55:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942547856-128</Id><Title>adding to my SYNA position today</Title><Msg>more good news coming</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381942547856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:55:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942761504-129</Id><Title>Rep. Nancy Pelosi of California, has signaled she will support the plan and her rank and file is expected to vote for it in overwhelming numbers.</Title><Msg>While the emerging deal could well meet resistance from conservatives in the Republican-controlled House, the Democratic Leader, Rep. Nancy Pelosi of California, has signaled she will support the plan and her rank and file is expected to vote for it in overwhelming numbers. That raised the possibility that more Democrats than Republicans would back it, potentially causing additional problems for House Speaker John Boehner as he struggles to manage his tea party-heavy majority. The developments came one day before the deadline Lew had set for Congress to raise the current $16.7 trillion debt limit. Without action by lawmakers, he said, Treasury could not be certain it had the ability to pay bills as they come due. In addition to raising the debt limit, the proposal would give lawmakers a vote to disapprove the increase. Obama would have the right to veto their opposition, ensuring he would prevail.</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942761504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:59:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381942793652-130</Id><Topic><Title>Are we still on Sequester, or not?</Title><Username>globalchili</Username><Timestamp>1381941764058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:42:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>non sequitur noted</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381942793652</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:59:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381942815120-131</Id><Title>White House aides talk about “breaking the will” of the tea party</Title><Msg>, and they glory in each new poll that shows the GOP’s public approval is plummeting toward single digits</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942815120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:00:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381943034691-132</Id><Title>Oh man, He's still attacking our Secretary</Title><Msg>It's been almost a week now, and Fox's Bill O'Reilly is still attacking Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel and pretending that this GOP-induced shutdown and problems with military death benefits being paid is his fault. Bill-O also took the opportunity to attack the rest of the media for not spending enough time to suit him and jumping on board with their latest faux outrage of the day -- and for rightfully placing the blame for the shutdown in Republicans' laps where it belongs. Here's how they covered the segment over at Fox's blog: O'Reilly Calls Out Mainstream Media for Ignoring Death Benefits Controversy: Bill O’Reilly criticized the mainstream media’s lack of coverage on the military death benefits controversy. The Department of Defense said it would not pay for the death benefits of fallen soldiers and blamed the government shutdown. A private charity, Fisher House Foundation, stepped in to help after the president and Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel botched the situation. “All President Obama had to do was take his little pen, sign an executive order that paid the families a $100,000 dollar benefit.” As the American people expressed their growing outrage, the House and Senate passed a separate spending bill to fund the benefits and the president signed it Thursday night – 10 days after the government shut down. “None of that had to happen,” O’Reilly reasoned. “The military benefits chaos shows just how poor our leadership is in Washington, and the folks know it.” Over a two-night period, O’Reilly observed that CNN devoted less than 15 minutes to the coverage during their primetime shows. Broadcast news programs either downplayed the story or barely covered it. It was when NBC and newspapers like The New York Times invested in telling the truth, O’Reilly said, that the government caved. “Here’s the bad news,” the Factor host continued, “MSNBC continued its business as usual of blaming Republicans for just about everything.” Yeah, those poor picked on Republicans. How dare anyone point out that they planned on and continue to use a government shutdown and the debt ceiling for hostage taking. The nerve.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381943034691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:03:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381943102581-133</Id><Topic><Title>White House aides talk about “breaking the will” of the tea party</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942815120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will the White House deport Rafael Cruz to Canada?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381943102581</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:05:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381943245194-134</Id><Topic><Title>White House aides talk about “breaking the will” of the tea party</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381942815120</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have tried, Canada won't take him.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381943245194</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:07:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381943303155-135</Id><Title>Rubio, Cruz, Jindal.... damaged GOP goodn now....... does the GOP get smart and go moderate?</Title><Msg>Chris Christie, Jeb Bush ?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381943303155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:08:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381943427083-136</Id><Title>Now that the tea party has managed to repeal the ACA</Title><Msg>they need to focus on the impeachment over Benghazi LOL America won't tolerate a loser!!</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381943427083</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:10:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381943600151-137</Id><Title>Drunk Florida man sets self on fire while lighting Halloween cross-burning ‘prank’</Title><Msg>gop wetbrain alert</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381943600151</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:13:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381943637269-138</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio, Cruz, Jindal.... damaged GOP goodn now....... does the GOP get smart and go moderate?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381943303155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I don't think America would elect another Bush even if the GOP nominated him, as far as Chris Christie he has zero chance of being nominated by the GOP, he has a better chance changing parties and running as a Democrat. Conservatives hate Christie more then they hate Obama.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381943637269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:13:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381944050749-139</Id><Title>cnbc is wrong again</Title><Msg>Market will be fine. A sell off-NO! Profit taking-maybe. It might be wiser to hold on and see if the holiday sales go out the gate early to make up for 2 weeks lost sales. It's an easy fix.</Msg><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1381944050749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381944370977-140</Id><Title>Green eggs and ham looking a little green. Can you say Tea Party FAILURE?</Title><Msg>Green eggs and ham looking a little green. Can you say Tea Party FAILURE?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381944370977</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:26:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944403302-141</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio, Cruz, Jindal.... damaged GOP goodn now....... does the GOP get smart and go moderate?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381943303155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>so seriously, who would they consider?</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381944403302</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:26:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944485405-142</Id><Topic><Title>Oh man, He's still attacking our Secretary</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381943034691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why dont you just shut up. nobody is hear to listen to that #$%$, right or left.</Msg><Username>francis_sidney2000</Username><Timestamp>1381944485405</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:28:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944560504-143</Id><Topic><Title>Rubio, Cruz, Jindal.... damaged GOP goodn now....... does the GOP get smart and go moderate?</Title><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381943303155</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:08:23 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are they making it so easy for Hillary?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381944560504</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:29:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944562839-144</Id><Topic><Title>Oh man, He's still attacking our Secretary</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1381943034691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:03:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's getting like Hannity with his own personal vendetta driven agenda</Msg><Username>allnewquincymagoo5</Username><Timestamp>1381944562839</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:29:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944613522-145</Id><Topic><Title>cnbc is wrong again</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1381944050749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>cnbc and cartoon channel are the same .</Msg><Username>plainjoe7</Username><Timestamp>1381944613522</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381944758854-146</Id><Topic><Title>cnbc is wrong again</Title><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1381944050749</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:20:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>maybe we should call it the looney tune channel instead.</Msg><Username>ddeboy</Username><Timestamp>1381944758854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:32:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381944903404-147</Id><Title>REMEMBER WHO KICKS THE CAN DOWN THE ROAD AND WHO WANTS TO SOLVE PROBLEMS!!!!</Title><Msg>Democrats kick the can down the road, spend 1.4 trillion more than they take in every year AND ULITMATELY, IN 18 MONTHS..TAKE US OVER A CLIFF, DOWN INTO DEATH Tea Party solves problems...DEMOCRATS WANT MORE PROBLEMS AND MORE DEBT SO THEY CAN BUY VOTES AND KEEP THE ENTITLED ENSLAVED ON THE GHETTO PLANTATIONS THEY HAVE SO CAREFULLY CRAFTED... oh oh oh oh oh...misery to America...courtesy of Democrats...who cannot see this? Who is so blind, that they refuse to see? Who?</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381944903404</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:35:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381945008676-148</Id><Title>Ted Cruz caves on shutdown, but calls it a personal win</Title><Msg>sort of like art ROTF!</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381945008676</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:36:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945021227-149</Id><Topic><Title>IF I WAS A CUSSIN' MAN, I'D LAY A HOT HEAVY DARK LAYER OF OBSCENITIES ALL ACROSS</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381940090000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Tea Party won! Demonstrated the Democratic desire to kick the can down the road and refuse to solve problems or balance a debt that will destroy America... EVEN A FOOL CAN SEE THAT!!!!! Obammy's clever maneuver to shift blame, falls squarely on this shoulders. President Kick the Can...Obambo....</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381945021227</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:37:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945073431-150</Id><Topic><Title>IF I WAS A CUSSIN' MAN, I'D LAY A HOT HEAVY DARK LAYER OF OBSCENITIES ALL ACROSS</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381940090000</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:14:50 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ted Cruz caves on shutdown, but calls it a personal win</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381945073431</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:37:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381945127952-151</Id><Title>Ronald Reagan and the tea party both realized you can't keep spending more then you take in</Title><Msg>tea billie solution is to starve the elderly, deny healthcare to little children, eliminate all regulations that prevent Americans from being poisoned to death, cut taxes for the ultra rich and default on the debt we have already borrowed. Reagan on the other hand raised taxes on the wealthy, five times.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381945127952</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:38:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381945128549-152</Id><Title>PRESIDENT 'KICK THE CAN' OBIMBO...IS SMILING...</Title><Msg>like a dog that just ate its own poo, and like a mongrel that consumes it's on vomit, the President "Kick the Can', just kicked the can again...much closer to the cliff...how far does the road go? When does the can go OVER THE CLIFF....very close now..... REMEMBER AMERICA.. President 'Kick the Can' has delivered all his promises... HOW DO YOU LIKE YOUR OBAMA-CARE? LOVIN' IT???????</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1381945128549</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:38:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945132854-153</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior/Magoo was bragging about how he got rid of the board conservatives a week or two ago. Now you ask where they are??? You got what you wanted. A one sided conversation gets pretty boring , doesn't it? lol</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381945132854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:38:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945432534-154</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Suck my sack,Magoo. LOL!! back at you.</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381945432534</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:43:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945542824-155</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is queenie!! she cant resist the toe tapping!! ROTF!!!!</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381945542824</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:45:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381945597970-156</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gay stuff always gets Junior posting.LOL</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381945597970</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:46:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381946191917-157</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Smart play. I dont short but I bought quality stocks the past several weeks during the budget panic.It was always obvious there would not be a default .I recommended others here do the same but I got laughed at. Started selling some today and doing quite well. Seems I am having the last laugh.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381946191917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:56:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947108725-158</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Louie 'Gomer' Gohmert: Obama Allowing Default Is Impeachable</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381947108725</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:11:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947156387-159</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>SO FAKE JUNIOR AKA QUEENIE IS KINGSY ROTF!!!</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381947156387</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:12:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381947183063-160</Id><Title>GRO China Agriculture Stock Owns 1/2 of $1 Billion Revenue Company</Title><Msg>Agria (GRO) is an undiscovered China agriculture stock beginning to breakout big. China stocks have been exploding in recent days with some rallying 50% to 300% within just 2-3 days. GRO's China seeds business just reported 98% revenue growth, yet is currently receiving NO value at GRO's current share price of $1.60. (GRO has only 55.38 million shares outstanding.) GRO owns a controlling stake in PGG Wrightson (PGW.NZ) a New Zealand Exchange company with NZ$1.13 billion in revenue (USD$946 million). GRO's 80.81% owned Agria Asia subsidiary owns 379.1 million PGW.NZ shares. With PGW.NZ trading for NZ$0.39 these shares are worth NZ$147.85 million (USD$123.85 million), valuing GRO's 80.81% stake at USD$100.09 million or $1.81 per share. GRO's wholly owned China seeds business grew fiscal 2013 revenues by 98% to $17 million. A modest valuation of 3X sales would value it at $51 million and add $0.92 per share to GRO's fair value - making GRO worth $2.73 per share. GRO paid $58 million for prepaid leases on 13,500 acres of farmland in China with 9-27 years remaining on these leases. They are receiving no value on GRO's balance sheet now that GRO has divested its sheep breeding business, but GRO still retains these prepaid leases and could potentially sell these rights to another company. Even if GRO only gets back 1/2 of what they paid or $29 million, it would add $0.52 per share to GRO's fair value - making GRO worth $3.25 per share. GRO controls PGW.NZ's Board of Directors and PGW.NZ's annual shareholders meeting is on Tuesday, October 22nd. If you Google "Seeds deal could grow enormous" the New Zealand Herald reported that GRO wants to merge PGW.NZ's seeds business into GRO to form a NYSE traded international seeds giant that competes with Monsanto (MON). PGW.NZ's seeds business has 15X greater revenues than GRO's seeds business, but GRO's seeds business is growing 12X faster! Disclaimer: We own 550,000 GRO shares that we intend to sell and can sell at any time.</Msg><Username>affye854</Username><Timestamp>1381947183063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:13:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947184419-161</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>you being junior is your wife named Bob?</Msg><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381947184419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:13:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381947417806-162</Id><Title>tea billies in alternative universe</Title><Msg>He said that in Washington, D.C., the agency typically has 300 employees on duty to manage and patrol the District's famed monuments and sites. All but a dozen were furloughed, he said. Explaining the decisions to close off memorials, including open-air sites like the World War II Memorial, he said the agency took "prudent and practical steps." He said the agency has worked "diligently" to ensure "honor flights" of WWII veterans were not turned away from the memorials despite the restrictions -- allowing them access on the basis of their First Amendment rights. "With very few employees available, we are endeavoring to fulfill our mission the best we can," Jarvis said. He denied politics were involved, and said all monuments have to be staffed to protect them from vandalism and other harm. Democrats, meanwhile, took turns lambasting the GOP majority for holding the hearing in the first place, claiming their party was responsible for the partial government shutdown which triggered the parks cuts. "You can't create something and then pretend you're outraged by the result," Rep. Peter DeFazio, D-Ore., said. Rep. Raul Grijalva, D-Ariz., said Republicans are living in an "alternative universe" and "can't cope with reality."</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381947417806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:16:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947470817-163</Id><Topic><Title>lots of quiet gop nuts today</Title><Username>junior_wins_again</Username><Timestamp>1381941072148</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:31:12 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You usually ask that question under your Magoo id. Man, are you stupid!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381947470817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:17:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947585936-164</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>?????????????? What is wrong with you,Junior????</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381947585936</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:19:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381947715907-165</Id><Title>What's new? What a POS on Up-Big market!</Title><Msg>Is this ShitsCo？</Msg><Username>coolheadwarmblood</Username><Timestamp>1381947715907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:21:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381947787332-166</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How does it feel to be totally fooled????? LOL I fell out of my chair laughing at you!!!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381947787332</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:23:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381947896458-167</Id><Title>Cisco Board</Title><Msg>I see the Cisco board continues be a political haven. Haven't been to this board in years... Keep up the good work... By the way, Cisco stock continues to languish. Move on!</Msg><Username>thubsheeshmoodoo</Username><Timestamp>1381947896458</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:24:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381948168020-168</Id><Title>tea party is like the bully</Title><Msg>who finally gets beaten up by all the kids in the school yard and now has to realize far from being the big man on campus he is a hated little twerp</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381948168020</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:29:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381948391690-169</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>do you go to church after you do the things you post about here queenie?</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948391690</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:33:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381948412221-170</Id><Topic><Title>Thanks Republican Surrender Monkeys</Title><Username>kingsmandean1631</Username><Timestamp>1381945735419</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 13:48:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>she cannot - she is a toe tapper</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948412221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:33:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381948571817-171</Id><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Msg>There is no such thing as a debt ceiling. Since 1977 the " ceiling " has been raised 55 times to prevent defaulting. We will go through this again early in 2014. Use it as an opportunity to make a lot of money as I am now doing on this current fiasco.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381948651345-172</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there is no such thing as a ethical republican either</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948651345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:37:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381948895555-173</Id><Title>Rush Limbaugh: GOP 'so irrelevant'</Title><Msg>whoa!</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948895555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:41:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381949290542-174</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh: GOP 'so irrelevant'</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948895555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fox News psychiatrist: Obama backs food stamps because grandmother ‘didn’t trust men of color’</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381949290542</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:48:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381949752440-175</Id><Topic><Title>Rush Limbaugh: GOP 'so irrelevant'</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381948895555</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:41:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The funniest part about what he said was he claims they are irrelevant because they didn't collapse the economy. LOL He doesn't say they are irrelevant because they refuse to negotiate. LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381949752440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:55:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381949820943-176</Id><Title>Who keeps bidding up my SYNA?</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$ so easy to make money when the adults are in charge</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381949820943</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:57:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950137766-177</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your comment had absolutely nothing to do with the topic. What is your problem ??? Do you have difficulty with cognitive reasoning or concentration??? Do you remember UNXL ? That was a missed opportunity for you,wasn't it ? Hope you enjoyed making fun of me as I made a lot of money on it. You have a nice day, Junior</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381950137766</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:02:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950316804-178</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior enjoys being stupid.</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381950316804</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:05:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950407744-179</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think it does.</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381950407744</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:06:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950427686-180</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>fake junior loves the johnson juice</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381950427686</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:07:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381950561374-181</Id><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Msg>"Creditworthiness is like virginity, It can be preserved but not restored very easily." Warren Buffet. Corollary "Once you lose your reputation it is hard to get it back". So long repukes And we get to do it all over again come January. The do nothing congress. Where is my freakn space rock, it should have hit the capitol by now.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950664594-182</Id><Topic><Title>Another opportunity coming</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1381948571817</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 14:36:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stop the toe tapping,creep.</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381950664594</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:11:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381950764282-183</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Was that Warren Buffet or Bill Clauson who said that, Magoo??</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381950764282</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:12:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381951393554-184</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO ! joe_b73 you forgot to switch or ID man. Wait, walter just used mongrel and dog eating their own vomit, trademarks of mine. I think I am walter too. So find MY walterbirdman posts and insult me there too. Dance puppet dance !!! LOL! LOL! You dunce LOL!</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381951393554</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:23:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381951582691-185</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Love to see you make a fool of yourself. Keep posting!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381951582691</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:26:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381951631222-186</Id><Title>WHO IS HAVING A BOWL OF SHHJJJJJJJT FOR DINNER TONIGHT ?</Title><Msg>Bonehead, McConnell, Eric 'closet' Cantor and their treasonous teabillies THAT'S WHO !!! POW !!! Right in the fkng kisser</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381951631222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:27:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381951779117-187</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>joe_b73 don't hate me because I already made the round trip when you are only half way there. Just learn from it my puppet, who knows, one day you might get there...NOOOOT ! BWwwwwahahahahaha.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381951779117</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:29:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381951787806-188</Id><Topic><Title>Magoo is sick</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_0l</Username><Timestamp>1381517591654</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-10-11 14:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What is your fascination with poop, SurfMagoo???</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381951787806</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:29:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381951975780-189</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure I'm not Art or Deadpainting or one of your many other guesses?? What a moron.lol</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381951975780</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:32:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381952266958-190</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Magoo ran off to another board for a few minutes. He'll be back. What a dolt!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381952266958</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:37:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381952916830-191</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Nah, Art is smarter than you. And you are more boring than dead, you are just as boring as juniorclass(whatever)0l so you could be him. But regardless, I sure know you are joe_b. Give up my little ankle bitter, you are out of your league here.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381952916830</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:48:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381953001776-192</Id><Title>SYNA up 4.7% today</Title><Msg>$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ easy to make money when the adults are in charge</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381953001776</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:50:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381953186440-193</Id><Topic><Title>WHO IS HAVING A BOWL OF SHHJJJJJJJT FOR DINNER TONIGHT ?</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381951631222</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:27:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh and I forgot the obvious, the repuke/teabillies on this board. Oh lordy !!! ROTF !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381953186440</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:53:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381953374907-194</Id><Title>TO THE GOP: SHOW ME YOU ARE SERIOUS ON CUTTING THE DoD (GOLDEN COW) BUDGET</Title><Msg>and you can cut the same from ANY program you choose. Until then, ride the Obama meat pole teahicks.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381953374907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:56:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381953488263-195</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior likes to call people anklebiters too.Strange how you libs all use the same slurs. lol Man, are you stupid!!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381953488263</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:58:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381953988574-196</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>dead made up this id 11 days ago, LOL what a looooooser, he has dozens of id's just to post drivel. get a job dead, take a walk, do something besides post 24/7 on this board LOOOOOOOSER</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381953988574</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:06:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954156038-197</Id><Topic><Title>TO THE GOP: SHOW ME YOU ARE SERIOUS ON CUTTING THE DoD (GOLDEN COW) BUDGET</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381953374907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>if you cut the DOD where will the uneducated southern tea billies find jobs?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381954156038</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954194395-198</Id><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Msg>fake junior is angry and a tappin' rotf!!! no? ROTF!!!</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954204899-199</Id><Title>Quote of the day</Title><Msg>"The fact that we are here today to debate raising America's debt limit is a sign of leadership failure. America has a debt problem and a failure of leadership. Americans deserve better. I, therefore, intend to oppose the effort to increase America's debt." -BO</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954204899</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:10:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954335388-200</Id><Title>Another day dumb.ivan spends posting all day on the board</Title><Msg>poor little angry shut in. sad.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954335388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:12:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954348122-201</Id><Topic><Title>QUOTE OF THE DAY...</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381950561374</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:09:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I did borrow that one from Jr, perfect term for you. Arfff, arfff Joey boy ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381954348122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:12:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954390269-202</Id><Title>KEEP IT CLOSED</Title><Msg>give gov money back to tax payers.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954390269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:13:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954505519-203</Id><Title>Why did the liberals close down the government</Title><Msg>sad day for our creditors.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954505519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:15:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954511324-204</Id><Topic><Title>KEEP IT CLOSED</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954390269</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:13:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>too bad</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954511324</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954556338-205</Id><Topic><Title>TO THE GOP: SHOW ME YOU ARE SERIOUS ON CUTTING THE DoD (GOLDEN COW) BUDGET</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381953374907</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 15:56:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>McDonalds, Walmart, waste disposal, cow manure shoveling, Public restroom cleaning, doorman. C'mon Ivan, lots of jobs for teabillies out there ! LOL !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381954556338</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:15:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954582393-206</Id><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Msg>sad.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954737917-207</Id><Topic><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh jesus Joe, you have ANOTHER id. C'mon man, have some pride. Ooops, I forgot, GOP pride was flushed down the toilet today. BWWWWWWWWWWHAHAHAHAHAHAAH.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381954737917</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:18:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381954742084-208</Id><Title>Went for a wonderful bike ride</Title><Msg>on my boat in rome to get filet "minion. Why is the world so unfair when will I pay my fair share...bush did it.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954742084</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381954784262-209</Id><Topic><Title>Another day dumb.ivan spends posting all day on the board</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954335388</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:12:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"two" bad.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954784262</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:19:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955079409-210</Id><Topic><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You really looking like a fool now!!!!!! Lol</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381955079409</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:24:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955229843-211</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the liberals close down the government</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954505519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:15:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I would suspect it's some sort of Kenyan, secret-Muslim, Benghazi-Furious related conspiracy. Or the GOP #$@^ed up. Either/or LOL</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381955229843</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:27:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955232212-212</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Gee, you are like a mental patient. You are sad about it, you are happy about it. Maybe you can get together with wally. He suffers from the same dementia. He claims to be a "Houston fan TO THE CORE, but FICKLE". He hates government run healthcare, but loves medicare. He hates socialism, but loves social security. I mean he is a basket case...just like you.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381955232212</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:27:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955351264-213</Id><Topic><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>C'mon now Joe, you know you are my little board pet. Now come here, I'll rub your head a little before your next beating. LMAO!</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381955351264</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:29:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955361221-214</Id><Topic><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lets see. Dumb thinks I'm Dead and Surf thinks I'm Joe. But now Surf thinks I'm also Junior_the 32. I have every one fooled!!! LOVE IT !!!!!!!! Libs are so stupid!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381955361221</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:29:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381955721975-215</Id><Title>Buddies screwing each other</Title><Msg>Junior_the 32 made Surf look like an idiot. I'm still laughing!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381955721975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:35:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381955973531-216</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>tea billies prove over and over they aren't simply stupid they are delusional also</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381955973531</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:39:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381956046658-217</Id><Topic><Title>Buddies screwing each other</Title><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381955721975</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:35:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe b said he was leaving.But if he's still around bet he's laughing too.Hope Dead will tell Dumb he is not me. Have I got the board libs confused or what??????? lol</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381956046658</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:40:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381956156610-218</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Stupid is thinking everyone you disagree with is Dead!!!!! You are really dense!!!!</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381956156610</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381956367143-219</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I just keep putting your stupid new id's on ignore dead and then laugh watching how many times you respond to my posts, LOL LOOOOOOOSER</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956367143</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:46:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381956532980-220</Id><Title>I'm on FACEBOOK, Baggers.</Title><Msg>In two weeks I became friends with over 200 BAGGERS who do not know me and who I will never meet. That is how LONELY and STUPID you baggers are. Desperate fo be liked by people who would pass you by on the street and avert their eyes. In other news, there is one bagger who is going to be in for the shock of his life soon. I'm coming to your town, BAGGER. I'm gonna enjoy it. Punk.</Msg><Username>joseph.lederer</Username><Timestamp>1381956532980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:48:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381956729034-221</Id><Topic><Title>Why did the left close the government?</Title><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1381954582393</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:16:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You said my id was11 days old but you're still responding to me. Seems you dont have me on ignore after all.You are known as the board liar and you keep proving it.</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381956729034</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:52:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381956825519-222</Id><Title>At least those in the GOP can look forward to this:</Title><Msg>10.The battle for the White House will be anybody's game in 2024. 9. FOX News still plans to enforce their "No Fat Chicks" hiring policy. 8. Ted Cruz is still technically a Senator, and Michele Bachmann is still on the Intelligence Committee. 7. The Pawn Stars will only give you $550 and not a penny more. 6. No minorities have infiltrated the ranks. Have they ?!? 5. Two Words: Citizens United 4. FL Governor Rick Scott hasn't had to plea the 5th in 13 years! 3. GUNS! 2. There's nowhere to go but up! 1. "Tickle" is still on the air.</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381956825519</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:53:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381956937908-223</Id><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Msg>and why do the moron tea billies believe them when it's easy to prove it's a lie Jack Kingston teabillie moron R Georgia just on CNBC saying we are borrowing 42 cents for every dollar we spend. Let's review in 2012 the Federal Government spent 3.8 trillion and ran a deficit of 1.3 trillion meaning it was borrowing 34 cents in 2012. In Fiscal year 2013 we are on track to spend 3.8 trillion (wow talk about growing the socialist government 0% LOL) and we are on track for a deficit of 800 billion, that would be 21 cents Jack, not 42 cents. Note the deficit dropped by 40% the fastest in history. Let us also note that Federal spending represents 20.5% of GDP exactly the last 30 year average. Most forecasts for 2014 are for spending to be at or below 3.8 trillion and a deficit of 400 million. yes jack that would be 10 cents of borrowing for every dollar spent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381957157802-224</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LIes?? How about the closing of Gitmo. How about keeping your own doctor .How about having Al-Qaeda on the run?? Want more?????</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381957157802</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:59:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381957158957-225</Id><Title>Made bank with millionaire daytrader</Title><Msg>Millionaire daytrader (google em) just came out with a detailed report on ROGR today - I recommend any fellow shareholders here sign up immediately and wait for the next update, last time they alerted a stock as a buy it went up 1350%, and last two times they put out sell ratings the stocks dove over 75% - don't be the last to know and get screwed, I learned my lesson on their AAPL sell alert, and GOOG buy alert sub $400</Msg><Username>hunecomb2</Username><Timestamp>1381957158957</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:59:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>18</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381957360085-226</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oops! Dumb cant answer me because he has me on ignore.Guess Junior will have to do it. lol</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381957360085</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:02:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381958206711-227</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why does Obama lie about EVERYthing except what's on his personal agenda?</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381958206711</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:16:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381958465399-228</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dummy, I come to this site once a day and once a day I have to prove what a idiot you are. Just google how much do we borrow for everydollar we spend: The federal government borrowed 46 cents of every dollar it has spent so far in fiscal 2013, which began Oct. 1, according to the latest data the Congressional Budget Office released Friday. The government notched a $172 billion deficit in November, and is already nearly $300 billion in the hole through the first two months of fiscal year 2013, underscoring just how deep the government’s budget problems are as lawmakers try to negotiate a year-end deal to avoid a budgetary “fiscal cliff.” Higher spending on mandatory items such as Social Security, Medicare and interest on the debt led the way in boosting spending compared with the previous year, which also highlights the trouble spots Congress and President Obama are struggling to grapple with. All sides agreed to discretionary spending cuts and automatic spending cuts last year, but have been unable to agree on ways to control entitlement costs, which are the long-term drivers of deficits and debt. Fiscal year 2013 began on Oct. 1 and so far the government has spent $638 billion and taken in just $346 billion in revenue. That tax revenue is up by $30 billion compared with last year, or about 10 percent.</Msg><Username>noalliesobama</Username><Timestamp>1381958465399</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:21:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381959042940-229</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because low info types like gallo and wet listen to every word</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381959042940</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:30:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381959060186-230</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>of clurse he does not maybe consider yourinbred feelings</Msg><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381959060186</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:31:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381959398158-231</Id><Title>Make no mistake, GOP wins...</Title><Msg>with the Sequester. LibTards can choke on it ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381959398158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:36:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381959507561-232</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I can use your argument to twist the numbers also. In April the Federal Gov took in a lot more then it spent, therefore it didn't borrow any money it spent. Sorry tea billie, if you use full year numbers it's clear how mislead you tea billies are.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381959507561</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:38:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381959595279-233</Id><Title>REPUKE'S DINNER TONIGHT...</Title><Msg>Harry's Turhds in a love juice sauce, Obama's meat sausage with a brotha spit demiglace, and girlie vomit a la Nancy, and for dessert a sliced #$%$ over a torn Cruz rectum. Yummmmie, enjoy my little pukes.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381959595279</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:39:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381959677077-234</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow for someone who created his id last month you sure harbor a lot of hatred, of course we all know there are only one or two tea billies spending all day posting under multiple id's. So funny watching Dead squirm.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381959677077</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381959706719-235</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LOL...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381959706719</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:41:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381960062552-236</Id><Topic><Title>I'm on FACEBOOK, Baggers.</Title><Username>joseph.lederer</Username><Timestamp>1381956532980</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:48:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow. You're scary! But at least you're not political, just psycho. Carry on....</Msg><Username>deadairez</Username><Timestamp>1381960062552</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:47:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381960188001-237</Id><Title>WHAT TIME IS THE PUKES PUBLIC HUMILIATION ...I MEAN VOTE.</Title><Msg>Will Bonehead cry. Will there be repuke mass suicides ? Will Michelle Bachmann hysterically yell, "my husband is a poof and it is all Obama's fault !!!" Will Eric Cantor show up hand in hand with Marcus Bachmann ? And will Paulie Ryan take a look at the circus he once wanted to lead and think, I better get moving and buy my hot dog truck back. Stay tuned, it is going to be a hell of an evening.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381960188001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:49:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381960954223-238</Id><Topic><Title>WHAT TIME IS THE PUKES PUBLIC HUMILIATION ...I MEAN VOTE.</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381960188001</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:49:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>why would bonehead cry, don't you watch FAUX news the GOP got everything they wanted, LOL they did repeal the ACA right? Obama did cave right? I heard it on FAUX, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381960954223</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381962216668-239</Id><Title>Have to give Obama credit</Title><Msg>He did a great job of deflecting criminal charges against him and Hillary! Benghazi, IRS, using money not belonging to him and a lot of other charges</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381962216668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:23:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381962710884-240</Id><Topic><Title>Make no mistake, GOP wins...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381959398158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>LMAO ! LOL ! LOL! Oh my, the white flags already waving. I would have thought you would wait for the public humiliation...I mean vote. As for the sequester, everyone is for it Forrest, You are the ones that had a cow when you found out that it also included cuts to your penile extension, the DoD. Pffffff.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381962710884</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:31:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381963565371-241</Id><Topic><Title>Have to give Obama credit</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381962216668</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:23:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>when did you press charges?</Msg><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381963565371</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:46:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381963587584-242</Id><Topic><Title>Make no mistake, GOP wins...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381959398158</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 17:36:38 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>leave it to the low functioning hicks like gallo;;;;;;;;;</Msg><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381963587584</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:46:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381963830356-243</Id><Title>At 11th Hour, Republicans Blink in Standoff...</Title><Msg>At 11th Hour, Republicans Blink in Standoff...</Msg><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381963830356</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381963868476-244</Id><Title>Why do Liberals treat Conservatives like Skunks</Title><Msg>Smelly Skunks...................................</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1381963868476</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381963897872-245</Id><Title>Michelle Botchedmann: "GOP gave bonehead standing ovation...</Title><Msg>He delayed delayed delayed and in the end we are going to get our hinds spanked by Harry and Nancy. That is what we always wanted !" ROTF.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1381963897872</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:51:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381963955133-246</Id><Title>Republicans won a Hotdog without Mustard</Title><Msg>No Saurkraut........................</Msg><Username>buddhazenpeace</Username><Timestamp>1381963955133</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:52:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381963991391-247</Id><Title>Ted Cruz stands down on Obamacare</Title><Msg>gop wins? ROTF!!</Msg><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381963991391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381964499017-248</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz stands down on Obamacare</Title><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381963991391</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 18:53:11 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The GOP rolled over on everything. Obama gets his way totally!</Msg><Username>dumpbernanke</Username><Timestamp>1381964499017</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:01:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381964541036-249</Id><Topic><Title>wow surf has fake junior tied up in knots</Title><Username>junior_the32</Username><Timestamp>1381954194395</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:09:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bump</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381964541036</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:02:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381964554793-250</Id><Title>Congrats Democrats win</Title><Msg>17 TRILLION in debt, no remedy to our underlying problems and Democrats have won THEIR little war to continue to kick the can down the road. NO ONE wants to address the elephants in the room. Everything now is about the win for the party and not the good of the country. Congrats Dems, you win.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1381964554793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:02:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381964808124-251</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats Democrats win</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1381964554793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:02:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>first you must face reality: it was bush who busted the debt, not barry. And yes, the dems won big.</Msg><Username>m_juniorslcassmate</Username><Timestamp>1381964808124</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:06:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381964846784-252</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These are CBO numbers. Of course you think your numbers are more correct than theirs. That's because you are in denial as all your libs are. CBO numbers don't lie. Unfortunately you and Obama's do.</Msg><Username>noalliesobama</Username><Timestamp>1381964846784</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:07:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381964897030-253</Id><Topic><Title>Congrats Democrats win</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1381964554793</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:02:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>National debt when Obama took office 10 trillion......NOW 17 TRILLION. Welcome to reality CHUMP, take another far left libTARD pill.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1381964897030</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:08:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381965013486-254</Id><Title>Celebrate this, dems</Title><Msg>Only 36,000 people signed up for Obamacare the first week. 99.6% of visitors left the site without enrolling. Looks like Cruz and his bunch should have just let Obamacare die on its own. LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381965013486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:10:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381965155856-255</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate this, dems</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381965013486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Btw, before Junior calls me a liar, the article is on CNBC website. Certainly not a right wing outfit.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381965155856</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:12:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381965234455-256</Id><Title>let's review another tea billie lie</Title><Msg>Rep Heulskamp teabillie R from Kansas was on CNN talking about how the GOP was right to try and close the government in order to defund the ACA. He kept talking about Nichole one of his constituents who was upset because SHE COULDN'T afford the $446 dollars it was going to cost her to sign up for healthcare. LOL Let's review, it is entirely possible she can't afford $446 dollars for the healthcare insurance offered to her. Of course Kansas hasn't made a decision to accept the 100% funding of the expansion of medicare for poor people with incomes less then140% of the poverty level, so it's possible she can't afford something that would be free if the GOP would give her free healthcare. (It's free already for her if she makes less then 100%) It's possible that she makes more then that 140% and doesn't feel she can afford $446 dollars a month, but of course Heulskamp failed to mention she doesn't have to sign up for healthcare (it wouldn't be $446 anyway it would be subsidized unless she makes a lot of money. But let's ignore all this reality because we are in the tea billie rabbit hole. She could pay the fine. The fine of course is $95 a year or 1% of your family income (which ever is more). Does she mean she can't afford the $95 (remember it's 0 if she makes less then the poverty level) or does she mean the 1% family income fine if she chooses not to get healthcare and instead rely on us all to pay for her going to the emergency room for free? If she means the fine would be 1% of her income and that amounts to $446 a month or $5,350 a year it means her family is earning $535,200 a year. LOL tea billies have decided to just out right lie to the public, just because they hate a black man.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381965234455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:13:54 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381965379448-257</Id><Topic><Title>let's review another tea billie lie</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381965234455</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:13:54 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The reality for Nichole is she probably hates Heulskamp and MAYBE doesn't support Obamacare because she supports a single payer system LIKE EVERY OTHER DEVELOPED NATION IN THE WORLD HAS. She doesn't want Obamacare repealed she wants what everyone else in the developed world has.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381965379448</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:16:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381965707568-258</Id><Topic><Title>Why do the tea billies leaders outright lie to the public</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381956937908</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 16:55:37 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>silly tea billie, my numbers are CBO numbers, I just used a whole year, you cherry picked a period of time where tax receipts are low and expenditures are high. Last April the IRS took in more then the Federal Government spent, therefore under your logic there is no deficit at all. Your argument is like having my daughter come to me and tell me she just deposited her pay check this afternoon and hasn't spent a penny since. Therefore she is saving 100% of her income.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381965707568</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381965920063-259</Id><Title>Independents support fiscal responsibility</Title><Msg>It's the only reason we supported the GOP in the past, now we know the GOP idea of fiscal responsibility means defaulting on the debt. Woopsie.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381965920063</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:25:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381966404449-260</Id><Title>looks like the GOP is standing firm</Title><Msg>In an interview with National Journal, Louisiana Republican Charles Boustany expressed his great frustration with the “20-30″ members of Congress who make up the Tea Party wing, accusing them of caring more about appearances and ideological purity than actually governing. “There are members with a different agenda,” Boustany said to National Journal. “And I’m not sure they’re Republicans and I’m not sure they’re conservative.” Boustany went on to describe these Tea Party Republicans as “members who are in complete denial about their responsibility to govern and to try to use conservative principles to get the best possible legislative package we can get.” The Louisiana congressman’s criticisms didn’t end there, however. He also questioned the institutional loyalty of the Tea Party bloc. “Their allegiance is not to the members in the conference,” Boustany said. “Their allegiance is not to the leadership team and to conservative values. Their allegiance is to these outside Washington DC interest groups that raise money and go after conservative Republicans.” Yet although Boustany’s comments make him second only to Devin Nunes when it comes to Republican-on-Republican verbal assaults, the usually mild-mannered congressman insists he’s far from alone: “There is a very large silent majority that’s getting frustrated with what’s happening because of what these outside groups have done by setting false expectations, deliberately misleading the public on some of these issues and commanding allegiance of certain members who falsely place their allegiance to these groups rather than to their constitutional responsibility to govern.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966404449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:33:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381966709854-261</Id><Topic><Title>Strong buy from 9 analyst and Buy from 11 analyst.</Title><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381940479625</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 12:21:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crammer just point out the obvious of buying this stock. If a company can grow its free cash flow like Cisco, the CFO should be commended. Well, right stock at the right recovery time.,</Msg><Username>topinvestgun1</Username><Timestamp>1381966709854</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:38:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381966891659-262</Id><Title>woopsie, stupid doesn't pay after all</Title><Msg>. The GOP is losing ground, even in its gerrymandered districts. The shutdown and debt-ceiling fights have sent the national opinion of Republicans to record lows, but as I reported earlier this week, that’s all the more so in the gerrymandered districts that were once thought to be “safe” seats for conservative Republicans. The swings are so great in these districts that Princeton professor Sam Wang, whose predictions nailed the 2012 election results, says the chance of Democrats taking over the House has risen from 13 percent before the shutdown to as high as 50 percent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966891659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:41:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381966945252-263</Id><Title>Why Is Rush Calling the Republicans the BIGGEST Disaster out there?</Title><Msg>What's up with that?</Msg><Username>repubs_vs_teabaggers</Username><Timestamp>1381966945252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:42:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381967307285-264</Id><Title>24 BILLION ,WASTED AND THEY SAY THEY ARE CONSERVATIVES !</Title><Msg>Bend over #$%$, cruz and cantor you lil #$%$ ! Here comes the big black bone, run al the bums outta office , gop is trash and for the wealthy , get it trailer park joe and silly sally .</Msg><Username>settegast_scholar</Username><Timestamp>1381967307285</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:48:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381967746046-265</Id><Topic><Title>woopsie, stupid doesn't pay after all</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966891659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes Obama and Liberal Tree Hugging Pecker-woods have done such a marvelous job, with a Chicken in every pot, a new car in every drive way, all kids being educated, and all middle class and low income peoples now have and are wearing diamonds big as horse turds -- HAIL TO THE KING and MASTER OF HIS SERVANTS!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381967746046</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:55:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381968334331-266</Id><Title>vote 83 to 16</Title><Msg>woopsie, after almost destroying the entire country the GOP votes overwhelmingly for the bill. LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381968334331</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:05:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381968439233-267</Id><Topic><Title>looks like the GOP is standing firm</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966404449</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:33:24 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to get a lot of crickets to your posts, Dumb. Reason?? Maybe because most consider you a lying koolade slurping weasel ???</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381968439233</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381968527055-268</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Rush Calling the Republicans the BIGGEST Disaster out there?</Title><Username>repubs_vs_teabaggers</Username><Timestamp>1381966945252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:42:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>because they're weak john mc shames, that's why dummy. ted cruz knows we're going broke.</Msg><Username>dadiooftheradio</Username><Timestamp>1381968527055</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:08:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381968596683-269</Id><Topic><Title>Celebrate this, dems</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381965013486</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:10:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>None of the board loons want to comment on this. Must really be embarrassing.</Msg><Username>juniorsuckslittleboys</Username><Timestamp>1381968596683</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:09:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381968953815-270</Id><Topic><Title>woopsie, stupid doesn't pay after all</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966891659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>under Bush I was shorting stocks like a mad man trying to preserve my wealth, 800,000 jobs a month were being lost, the auto, banking and housing industries were destroyed, he started two useless wars for no reason costing the country 6 trillion dollars, Bush started torturing people making him the first convicted presidential war criminal in history, endangering our troops and throwing away the moral standing of the country yeah Obama has done a wonderful job, thanks for noticing</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381968953815</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:15:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381969514230-271</Id><Topic><Title>They'll kick the can again</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381888815744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 22:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>So congress did exactly what I and many others predicted. In three months we'll be doing this all over again. Both parties should be ashamed of themselves.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381969514230</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:25:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381970560472-272</Id><Topic><Title>woopsie, stupid doesn't pay after all</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381966891659</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:41:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What are you trying to justify, dumb.dumb? If you're right, why post here non-stop breathlessly every hour of every day? If you're just posting nonsensical blather, much like Obama and Jay Carney speak it, then you are to be pitied. Get some professional help, sparky...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381970560472</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:42:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381970801115-273</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1377034072789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 17:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Cruz is an American citizen .So am I. Cruz has as much chance of being president as I do.LOL" Remember when you posted that one Ivan, LOL I think you have a better chance now. LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381970801115</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 20:46:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381974564540-274</Id><Topic><Title>Ted Cruz</Title><Username>the_verk_knows</Username><Timestamp>1377034072789</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-08-20 17:27:52 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL British people are witches, talking in riddles. All British people.</Msg><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1381974564540</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:49:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381974696702-275</Id><Title>The Queen of England</Title><Msg>is the Queen Bee of the Witches of England. All Brits are witches, see their massive piles of POEMS!</Msg><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1381974696702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:51:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381974829323-276</Id><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Msg>she is the best thing for the DNC Newark Mayor Cory Booker, a rising national Democratic star, was elected to the U.S. Senate Wednesday and will become New Jersey's first ever African American senator. Booker defeated Republican Steve Lonegan, a former mayor of Bogota. With 58 percent of the vote counted, the Associated Press called the contest for Booker, who was carrying 56 percent of the vote. When Booker is sworn in, the Democratic Caucus will once again hold a 55-45 advantage over the GOP Conference. Booker will fill the seat once held by Frank Lautenberg, a long-serving Democratic senator who died in June. Gov. Chris Christie appointed fellow Republican Jeff Chiesa to be Lautenberg's interim replacement. Booker, 44, will become the chamber's second African American member along with Sen. Tim Scott (R-S.C.).</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381975234717-277</Id><Topic><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Crissakes,man.Get a life. All you do is post junk on this board</Msg><Username>wakkytobakky</Username><Timestamp>1381975234717</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:00:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381975523066-278</Id><Topic><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>lol how do you know you just made up this id a few minutes ago dead, LOL dead thinks it's ok to post under multiple id's 24/7 but posting occasionally under the same id is posting all the time, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381975523066</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:05:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381975747071-279</Id><Title>Obama says, "we need to win back the trust of the American people...</Title><Msg>that we've lost over the past few weeks..." The only question is, how is an egomaniac pathological liar going to win back the trust of the American people?</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381975747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381976148923-280</Id><Title>I have nothing to do but post all day on a Yahoo message board</Title><Msg>I have no life so I recently altered my ID to reflect my true calling</Msg><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976148923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:15:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976508543-281</Id><Topic><Title>I have nothing to do but post all day on a Yahoo message board</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976148923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>funny how desperate dead is for my attention he makes up yet another id for me to put on ignore, LOL LOOOOSER</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976508543</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:21:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976538357-282</Id><Topic><Title>I have nothing to do but post all day on a Yahoo message board</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976148923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>bumb.ivan member for the last 5 minutes, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976538357</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:22:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976560624-283</Id><Topic><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb has 43 posts so far today and calls that "occasionally" .Wonder why he's made fun of all the time?????? He's a lying piece of dog poo.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381976560624</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:22:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381976626875-284</Id><Title>OK kids let's look at how bad the GOP really shot itself, we are witnessing a 100 year event, the death of a political party, LOL</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON — For the Republicans who despise President Obama’s health care law, the last few weeks should have been a singular moment to turn its problem-plagued rollout into an argument against it. Instead, in a futile campaign to strip the law of federal money, the party focused harsh scrutiny on its own divisions, hurt its national standing and undermined its ability to win concessions from Democrats. Then they surrendered almost unconditionally. “If you look back in time and evaluate the last couple of weeks, it should be titled ‘The Time of Great Lost Opportunity,’ ” said Senator Lindsey Graham of South Carolina, among the many Republicans who argued that support for the health care law would collapse once the public saw how disastrous it really was. “It has been the best two weeks for the Democratic Party in recent times because they were out of the spotlight and didn’t have to showcase their ideas,” Mr. Graham added. Now, near the end of a governing crisis that crippled Washington and dismayed a nation already deeply cynical about its political leaders, Republicans are struggling to answer even the most basic questions about the cause and effect of what has transpired over the last few weeks. They disagree over how, or even whether, they might grow from the experience. Many could not comprehend how they failed to prevent such avoidable, self-inflicted wounds. Others could not explain why it took so much damage, to their party and the millions of people inconvenienced and worse by the shutdown, to end up right where so many of them expected. “Someone would have to explain that to me,” said Senator John McCain, Republican of Arizona. “I knew how it was going to end,” he added. “I’m trying to forget it,” said Senator Lisa Murkowski, Republican of Alaska, still in disbelief that many of her fellow Republicans could not grasp that this was a losing battle. “Here we are. Here we are. We predicted it. Nobody wanted it to be this way.” All the while, they had</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976626875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:23:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976719345-285</Id><Topic><Title>Obama says, "we need to win back the trust of the American people...</Title><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381975747071</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What he really means is that the DNC needs to do a better job of brainwashing and deceiving the ignorant masses.</Msg><Username>fat_womans_cellulite</Username><Timestamp>1381976719345</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:25:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976879457-286</Id><Topic><Title>The Queen of England</Title><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1381974696702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just like all birds can sing, all Brits can write good poems. That is about it.</Msg><Username>junior_has_fleas</Username><Timestamp>1381976879457</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381976903764-287</Id><Topic><Title>I have nothing to do but post all day on a Yahoo message board</Title><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976148923</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:15:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny how desperate you are for attention from anybody. 43 posts and counting in one day. Must be pretty lonely in that trailer, eh Dumb.LOL</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381976903764</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:28:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381977469122-288</Id><Topic><Title>They'll kick the can again</Title><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1381888815744</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-10-15 22:00:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Will it happen forever, Mr.Knowitall?</Msg><Username>dirty_rotten_handles</Username><Timestamp>1381977469122</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:37:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381977677343-289</Id><Topic><Title>OK kids let's look at how bad the GOP really shot itself, we are witnessing a 100 year event, the death of a political party, LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381976626875</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:23:46 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wow, 43 posts in one day, most of which no one responded to. I really need to get a life.</Msg><Username>bumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381977677343</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:41:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381977968612-290</Id><Title>Are all these guys still</Title><Msg>dead? How soon and easy Obama and Hillary are able to forget them! Christopher Stevens, Sean Smith, Glen Doherty and Tyrone S. Woods or Border Patrol Agent Brian Terry, you know, the guy killed with guns that Holder and Obama sold to the drug cartel to use as a gun control example?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381977968612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381978528745-291</Id><Topic><Title>The Queen of England</Title><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1381974696702</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:51:36 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yeah, but England houses most of the good witches of the world. 90% of British witches are good witches.</Msg><Username>junior_has_fleas</Username><Timestamp>1381978528745</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:55:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381978593267-292</Id><Topic><Title>Are all these guys still</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381977968612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>wow I guess Obama and Hillary can forget the one attack on a consulate as easy as bush can forget the 37 attacks he had on embassies and the 9-11 pre warned attack on american soil. But then Obama didn't have the CIA saying it was going to happen like Bush did, Tea Billies ignore the truth.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381978593267</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:56:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381978790087-293</Id><Topic><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>As an outside observer, I'm beginning to think dead and the Hoe are the only true pukes on this entire board.</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381978790087</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:59:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381978860379-294</Id><Topic><Title>Are all these guys still</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381977968612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I'm sorry capt, I really got carried away there. Sometimes I over do it on the insults. Please just ignore me.</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381978860379</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381978946119-295</Id><Topic><Title>Why Is Rush Calling the Republicans the BIGGEST Disaster out there?</Title><Username>repubs_vs_teabaggers</Username><Timestamp>1381966945252</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 19:42:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>John McShames? That's really pushing it, pun-wise.</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381978946119</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:02:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381979019058-296</Id><Topic><Title>let's hope Sarah continues to campaign for republicans</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1381974829323</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 21:53:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's gotta be some kind of special post the Democrats can give Sarah to keep her in the spotlight. Whatever FOX is paying her, the DNC should double it!</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381979019058</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:03:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381979998939-297</Id><Topic><Title>Are all these guys still</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381977968612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>he he he he ...</Msg><Username>proconsul_gallio</Username><Timestamp>1381979998939</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:19:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1381980455187-298</Id><Title>What can a witch turn a clown into?</Title><Msg>Any amount of numerous things?</Msg><Username>papparspray_aea_n_friends</Username><Timestamp>1381980455187</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:27:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1381980684509-299</Id><Topic><Title>Are all these guys still</Title><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1381977968612</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 22:46:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Funny, pukes clutch their conspiracy theories about Benghazi, but when you ask them WHY the State Department would "let" Americans die, they have no answer. Just more Un-American, desperate, ignorant tripe. Thank God America will get a reprieve from this kind of nonsense in 2014 thanks to the failed GOP Congress.</Msg><Username>asdfv99</Username><Timestamp>1381980684509</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-10-16 23:31:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>