<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-29"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364554295541-1</Id><Title>Scalia, bitter, to leave court</Title><Msg>March 28, 2013 Bitter Scalia Leaves U.S. Posted by Andy Borowitz WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—Justice Antonin Scalia dropped a bombshell on the Supreme Court today, announcing his decision to resign from the Court “effective immediately” and leave the United States forever. Calling this week “by far the worst week of my life,” Justice Scalia lashed out at his fellow-Justices and the nation, saying, “I don’t want to live in a sick, sick country that thinks the way this country apparently thinks.” Justice Scalia said that he had considered fleeing to Canada, “but they not only have gay marriage but also national health care, which is almost as evil.” He said the fact that nations around the world recognizing same-sex marriage are “falling like deviant dominoes” would not deter him from leaving the United States: “There are plenty of other countries that still feel the way I do. I’ll move to Iran if I have to.” Throwing off his robe in a dramatic gesture, Justice Scalia reserved his harshest parting shot for his fellow-Justices, screaming, “Damn you! Damn each and every one of you to hell! You call yourself judges? That’s a good one. You’re nothing but animals!” Breathing heavily after his tirade, he turned to Justice Clarence Thomas and said, “Except you, Clarence. Are you coming with me?” Justice Thomas said nothing in reply.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364554295541</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 06:51:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364555762753-2</Id><Title>Wingnutters, ya better protest this</Title><Msg>Despite 'Enormous Risk' White House Reaffirms Commitment to Arctic Drilling As US renews pledge to drill in Arctic waters, Greenland places moratorium on new leases - Lauren McCauley, staff writer A White House official reaffirmed Wednesday the Obama administration's commitment to the Arctic offshore drilling program despite the "dangerous risk" of catastrophic consequences for the pristine marine ecosystem. Celebrating news of the moratorium, Greenpeace now calls for "total ban of drilling" in Arctic waters. (Photo: Jiri Rezac/ Greenpeace) Speaking via video conference before a Alaskan Senate hearing in Anchorage regarding the recent grounding of Shell's Kulluk drilling rig, Bureau of Ocean Energy Management Director Tommy Beaudreau said, “The administration is committed to supporting safe and responsible exploration of potential energy resources in frontier areas such as the Arctic.” Beaudreau's statement came as the US Coast Guard made a plea to the Justice Department to consider "taking action" against Shell for marine pollution violations—referring to the International Convention for the Prevention of Pollution From Ships—committed in the operations of the Kulluk drillship, said head of the Alaskan Coast Guard Rear Admiral Thomas Ostebo. Environmental groups, who have long campaigned against the Arctic offshore drilling program citing an assuredly "catastrophic impact on one of the most pristine, unique and beautiful landscapes on earth," are calling on the Administration to completely shut down operations there. Other governments are gradually beginning to acknowledge these risks. On Thursday, the Guardian reports that the Greenlandic government has placed a moratorium on issuing new licenses to oil companies hoping to drill in their waters. According to oil industry experts, the new licensing round which would have opened up waters off the north east of Greenland would now no longer take place. "This is yet another blow to the oil industry's crumbling</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364555762753</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:16:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364555879407-3</Id><Title>Dividend</Title><Msg>Do you think that the dividend increase was enough to satisfy shareholders? While 3.3% is generous, I would have thought they would increase more substantially.</Msg><Username>hairytoadus01</Username><Timestamp>1364555879407</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:17:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364559419606-4</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>helpful info!</Msg><Username>jaydenwilliams934</Username><Timestamp>1364559419606</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 08:16:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364563593261-5</Id><Title>Cisco RAISES dividend by 21%</Title><Msg>Cisco announced today that it is raising its dividend from .14 to .17 a share payable April 24th to shareholders of record on April 8th.</Msg><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1364563593261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 09:26:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364567413057-6</Id><Title>Happy good Friday to ya</Title><Msg>March 27, 2013 "Bill Clinton now says he wishes he had supported gay marriage back when he was president. Clinton said at the time he was too busy campaigning for open marriage." –Conan O'Brien "Rush Limbaugh said that lesbians don't have to worry about their appearance, so they are free to get fat. Moments later, Rush Limbaugh officially come out as a lesbian." –Conan O'Brien "A new poll shows that 64 percent of New Jersey residents don't care about New Jersey Governor Chris Christie's weight. That's mostly because Chris Christie IS 64 percent of New Jersey." –Conan O'Brien "Congresswoman Michele Bachmann is under investigation for alleged misuse of campaign funds. She's blaming the accusations on her arch nemesis: the facts." –Jay Leno "Last year at Easter, Governor Chris Christie was rushed to the hospital. It was an emergency. It turned out he had an impacted peep." –David Letterman "Last year there was some trouble at the White House's Easter egg hunt. One kid looking for eggs turned up Obama's birth certificate." –David Letterman "Today is the second day on which the Supreme Court heard arguments for and against same-sex marriage, commonly referred to as gay marriage, which is commonly referred to as the magic of Siegfried and Roy." –David Letterman "The current marriage act defines marriage as a union between one man and one impossible woman." –David Letterman "I hope they legalize gay marriage because I need to be alive when 'Gay Divorce Court' hits the air. That's how I'll be spending my days." –David Letterman "Yesterday former CIA director David Petraeus apologized for having an affair with his biographer. He said he hopes this begins a new chapter in his life. It got awkward when he said, 'Any of you ladies want to write it?'" –Jimmy Fallon "A new survey found that the average American stays at his job for about four-and-a-half years. That is unless they're a late-night host on NBC." –Jimmy Fallon</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1364567413057</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 10:30:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364568579855-7</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco RAISES dividend by 21%</Title><Username>fluteman_greg</Username><Timestamp>1364563593261</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 09:26:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looking Good......"Recently, the company announced its dedication to shareholders, and plans to show it via returning cash back to investors. It plans to use 50% of its free cash flow for dividend payments and stock repurchases. This is a great sign for investors. Both of these activities will increase the value of a stock and draw in more investors. . . "</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1364568579855</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 10:49:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364569565691-8</Id><Topic><Title>Secret CSCO Info Revealed</Title><Username>willson_ethan</Username><Timestamp>1363607782953</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-03-18 07:56:22 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>very detailed update</Msg><Username>martin.ayden</Username><Timestamp>1364569565691</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:06:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364569672515-9</Id><Topic><Title>allnewmagoo6 • Stop spreading your gay lies on CSCO Board.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364441715384</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 23:35:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxie Dude you need to get a LIFE</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1364569672515</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:07:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364570052206-10</Id><Topic><Title>Advice for everyone is the doorstep to the temple of wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364555699396</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 07:14:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maxie, Dude you need to get a LIFE and get your incessant BS off this board!!</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1364570052206</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 11:14:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364572998711-11</Id><Title>Never underestimate the predictability of utter stupidity...</Title><Msg>All the local gun stores are out of stock and no one knows when they will resupply. Thanks Obozo!!!</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364572998711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:03:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364573791660-12</Id><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Msg>Maybe we can also soon start polinating female and female flowers together and breeding male dogs with male dogs, etc. Oh wait, animals and non-human organic matter are too smart for that. It's the gay humans that are all mixed up...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364574038290-13</Id><Topic><Title>Never underestimate the predictability of utter stupidity...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364572998711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NRA membership increased by 100k since Sandy Hook. Gun dealers are making a fortune. Now Harry Reid drops the assault gun ban from the gun control bill.The kool-ade chuggers got played and they dont even realize it. SUCKERS!!</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364574038290</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:20:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364574479696-14</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's not about equal rights at all. It's about equal access to leaching off the government. If there is any benefit to marriage, it's not a right. It's the privilege of having access to marriage freebies that the government offers. What about the rights of single people? Can't I just buddy up with a pal and get the same beniefits without marriage?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364574479696</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:27:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364576042131-15</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Soon as we sink to allowing men to marry men and women to women, what's next?? I'm extremely fond of my neighbors cocker spaniel. Perhaps wedding bells are in our future.LOL We are on a slippery slope. Morality is vanishing.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1364576042131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:54:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364576107131-16</Id><Topic><Title>Never underestimate the predictability of utter stupidity...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364572998711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:03:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well wonka, the republicans have been played on the abortion issue for years. Millions wasted on both issues which will never be resolved to the satisfaction of both sides. Abortion doctors are making a fortune. 50 million new members to the dead fetus club.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364576107131</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:55:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364576606532-17</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why do you have to marry the spaniel if it's a rights issue? Aren't single dog lovers entitled to the same rights as the idiot who wants to marry the spaniel?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364576606532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:03:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364576847919-18</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In other words, I don't want to marry the dog. I just want the government to pay for his healthcare and allow him to visit me when I am sick in the hospital.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364576847919</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:07:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364577049283-19</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morality is shrouded somewhere in the morass of the Left, or it simply doesn't exist...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364577049283</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:10:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364577073608-20</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ??? It's a choice or desire. Will a male be able to marry his brother if same sex marriage is legalized?? Where do you draw the line??</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364577073608</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:11:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364577573708-21</Id><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Msg>Of course it's your right to want. I want a billion dollars and nobody is ever going to infringe on my right to want it. Of course, with wants and wishes in one hand, and ____ in the other, which one fills up first? " Will a male be able to marry his brother if same sex marriage is legalized?" That's a paradox, the same "rights" should apply. I was just thinking of marrying a young female just to pass on my SS benefits to her at young age. It's not a right, but it should work without any problem. It's all about getting the freebies that the idiots want to give away.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364578348532-22</Id><Topic><Title>Same secks marriage...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364573791660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 12:16:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Morality is subjective. You won't find it in the pages of a book. Most people would say that theft is immoral, yet they approve of the government which steals money from the taxpayer, and the police who steal drugs from addicts. Most people would call "kidnapping" immoral, but countless criminals are kidnapped and placed into confined quarters as punishment for their crimes. It is too situational for the feeble minded to grasp. "Do unto others as you would have others do unto you" is actually immoral. "Do unto others as others would have you do unto them, unless of course, they are idiots who don't know what is best for them."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364578348532</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:32:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364578967917-23</Id><Topic><Title>TEABILLY LAND OF FREE DUMB</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364578875522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>There's always an idiot in every political movement. You, for example.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364578967917</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:42:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364579711944-24</Id><Topic><Title>TEABILLY LAND OF FREE DUMB</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364578875522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Politics aside,Junior is just a complete idiot, period. See anyone else get as much derision as Junior does???</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1364579711944</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:55:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364580395711-25</Id><Title>WHEN is x- dividend date ?</Title><Msg>Cant seem to find it</Msg><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1364580395711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:06:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364581223443-26</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>We're all being suckered by this term "same sex" before the word marriage. The fact is, this is an aberration created by the LGBT radicals. There is ONLY marriage, period. Man+Woman, end of story...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364581223443</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:20:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364582305450-27</Id><Topic><Title>WHEN is x- dividend date ?</Title><Username>joespada282</Username><Timestamp>1364580395711</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:06:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"The company will distribute $0.17 per share of its common stock on April 24 to shareholders of record as of April 8." Somebody should be able to calculate the ex date pretty soon.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364582305450</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:38:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364582311103-28</Id><Title>White House tours</Title><Msg>Since no agents were laid off, only moved to different locations, Obama and Carney should explain how cancelling the tours saves money.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364582311103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364582442222-29</Id><Topic><Title>TEABILLY LAND OF FREE DUMB</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364578875522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I rarely see anyone who deserves it as much as he. I really don't think he gets enough, so he returns for more.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364582442222</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:40:42 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364582641410-30</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Next, Junior or Dumb will want to marry their Gerbils? Couple sick pecker-woods those two are?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1364582641410</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:44:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364582740510-31</Id><Topic><Title>TEABILLY LAND OF FREE DUMB</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1364578875522</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:41:15 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I try to refrain from the silliness on this board. Junior is an obvious attention seeker. Best to just not answer anything he posts.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364582740510</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:45:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364583016557-32</Id><Topic><Title>White House tours</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1364582311103</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:38:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Do you think they could explain how to sell candy in a kindergarten?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364583016557</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:50:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364583571158-33</Id><Title>New Poll says Dems are shallow.</Title><Msg>"Lanae Erickson Hatalsky, the director of social policy and politics for Third Way, said her group has conducted polling in some of these states where gun violence isn’t a major issue. When they asked if they thought policies would be effective in reducing crime, most respondents said it wouldn’t. When asked if legislation was addressing a problem in their community or somewhere far away, most respondents went with the latter. The support for gun-control policies then is “really high but shallow,” Hatalsky said."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364583571158</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:59:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364583759305-34</Id><Topic><Title>Now Angry Obama is complaining almost 100% of the time now Good thing we can change channels on the TV.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583193487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:53:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't forget about the volume and power controls. I hear one syllable out of Bammy's face and it's clickity-click, "bu-bye"...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364583759305</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:02:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364583975085-35</Id><Title>tea billies lie, everyone knows it</Title><Msg>PolitiFact is a Pulitzer prize winning project that rates the claims of office-seekers and office-holders. Its Texas branch is headed up by the Austin American-Statesman’s Gardner Selby, one of the most respected political reporters in the state capital. To assess Cruz’s accuracy rate, PolitiFact investigated 14 of the senator’s statements and found that he wasn’t telling the truth 50 percent of the time. Seven of Cruz’s claims have earned either the grade of “pants on fire!” or “false.” The other half of the time Cruz is on the more truthful side, but has earned a perfect “true” score just once. Here’s a summary of the findings:</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364583975085</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:06:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364583987500-36</Id><Topic><Title>Why Hillary Clinton will never be President. ________ EVER!_______________!!!!</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364435213669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I hate to break it to you, but Americans are pretty stupid. Way too early to predict an awakening of that kind. There still aren't enough jobs to keep people from voting for the freebies.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364583987500</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:06:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364584159773-37</Id><Title>tea billies say Hillary will never be president</Title><Msg>same tea billies that said anyone could beat Obama in 2012, LOL what losers</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364584159773</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:09:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364584218876-38</Id><Topic><Title>Now Angry Obama is complaining almost 100% of the time now Good thing we can change channels on the TV.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583193487</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 14:53:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He's not just a liar, but a whining liar - it doesn't get much worse than that..</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364584218876</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:10:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364584396763-39</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Democrats Rasmussen poll says that Obama has a favorable rating of 46 % now..at new Low.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583779550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well in the real world Friday, March 29, 2013 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Friday shows that 53% of Likely U.S. Voters approve of President Obama's job performance. Forty-five percent (45%) disapprove. and in the real world Rasmussen was a GOP consultant before he started his right wing and often wrong polling company remember when he said Mitt would win in a landslide, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364584396763</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:13:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364584615680-40</Id><Title>and in the real world the GOP biased Rasmussen polls are some of the worst</Title><Msg>A Fordham University study by Dr. Costas Panagopoulos compared pre-election polling with the results from election day. The study ranked Rasmussen Reports 24th out of 28 polls in accuracy, one slot above Gallup.[52] An analyis by Nate Silver on FiveThirtyEight, ranked Rasmussen 20th out of 23 pollsters for accuracy in the 2012 elections with an average error of 4.2 points.[53] After the election, James Rainey of the Los Angeles Times wrote that "Some conservative media outlets used the Rasmussen polling to prop up a narrative in the final days of the campaign that Romney had momentum and a good chance of winning the White House."[54]</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364584615680</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:16:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364585468408-41</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Did you see God writing the Bible? How can you prove he had anything to do with it? I won't argue with "God knows best," but how do you know that the Devil didn't corrupt the Bible?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364585468408</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364586267293-42</Id><Topic><Title>Why Hillary Clinton will never be President. ________ EVER!_______________!!!!</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364435213669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't worry too much. Most Americans are too stupid to notice that there is a census every 10 years, and Obama's shellacking in 2010 has locked the Republican dominance of the House for 10 years. They call it "gerrymandering." I call it "just desserts."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364586267293</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:44:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364586924597-43</Id><Topic><Title>Why Hillary Clinton will never be President. ________ EVER!_______________!!!!</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364435213669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-03-27 21:46:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>One might also note, that when Obama bypassed all of the "Locked up" places to campaign only in swing states, He probably assured the republicans would gain instead of lose support until 2014. "the reports of my demise are somewhat premature" Too bad, the Republican party could use a bit of fearful reflection and revision of their platform. Unlikely considering the actual realities. We shall see how it plays out, but barring dramatic results to match the overdramatic blame game, I think republicans will fare well.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364586924597</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:55:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364587304634-44</Id><Title>Bush library to open soon</Title><Msg>Most prized exhibit: A book titled My pet Goat. LOL.</Msg><Username>ursofulofkrap</Username><Timestamp>1364587304634</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:01:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364587859583-45</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"how do you know that the Devil didn't corrupt the Bible?" Because he is sitting in the White house, cannot even write a budget, let alone the whole bible.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1364587859583</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364588528881-46</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He only had to change a few words to corrupt the meanings. The real answer is: "Why would the devil bother? Men have already done the work for him."</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364588528881</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:22:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364588701404-47</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If you're asking seriously, than answer have to come from knowledge of the Bible and honestly seeking of truth. If you are playing devil's advocate, you are not helping anyone with these questions. Just muddying the water. Every assumption must be based on some fundamental principle, an axiom. For a believer presence of G-d or who is the author of the Bible doesn't need a proof, it is axiomatic. Devil comes from the Bible itself, if you know. If he "corrupted" the Bible, than first thing he should take out is any negative connotations about himself. He failed. As far as marriage goes, here is Webbster: "1. The act of marrying, or the state of being married; legal union of a man and a woman for life, as husband and wife; wedlock; matrimony." We have a definition standing for thousands of years. Want something similar for homosexuals? Fine. Give it another definition. Marriage already has one.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364588701404</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:25:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364588705591-48</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Democrats Rasmussen poll says that Obama has a favorable rating of 46 % now..at new Low.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583779550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Rasmussen was the most accurate pollster in '08 missing Obama's victory margin by .1 . In 2012 I dont recall anyone except DickMorris predicting a Romney landslide.Think everyone else said Obama in a close one .Turned out pretty close in the popular vote but an Obama landslide in the electoral.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1364588705591</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:25:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364589002960-49</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Devil comes from the Bible itself, if you know. If he "corrupted" the Bible, than first thing he should take out is any negative connotations about himself. He failed." He did you one better than that. He pretends to be your God.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364589002960</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:30:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364589543313-50</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Men make careers of finding errors in the Bible. How could a God who is perfect allow such error? It would seem the description of the Devil is one inspires guile and errors to mislead the chosen. It sounds a lot like the game plan of people who try to teach with this archaic book.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364589543313</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364589770775-51</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Democrats Rasmussen poll says that Obama has a favorable rating of 46 % now..at new Low.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583779550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>in the tea billie rabbit hole comming in 24th out of 28 makes you the most accurate pollster, LOL tea billies not so bright A Fordham University study by Dr. Costas Panagopoulos compared pre-election polling with the results from election day. The study ranked Rasmussen Reports 24th out of 28 polls in accuracy, one slot above Gallup.[52] An analyis by Nate Silver on FiveThirtyEight, ranked Rasmussen 20th out of 23 pollsters for accuracy in the 2012 elections with an average error of 4.2 points.[53] After the election, James Rainey of the Los Angeles Times wrote that "Some conservative media outlets used the Rasmussen polling to prop up a narrative in the final days of the campaign that Romney had momentum and a good chance of winning the White House."[54] Less</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364589770775</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:42:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364590027606-52</Id><Title>Rasmussen off by more then 40 points in their polls, LOL</Title><Msg>The 105 polls released in Senate and gubernatorial races by Rasmussen Reports and its subsidiary, Pulse Opinion Research, missed the final margin between the candidates by 5.8 points, a considerably higher figure than that achieved by most other pollsters. Some 13 of its polls missed by 10 or more points, including one in the Hawaii Senate race that missed the final margin between the candidates by 40 points, the largest error ever recorded in a general election in FiveThirtyEight’s database, which includes all polls conducted since 1998. Moreover, Rasmussen’s polls were quite biased, overestimating the standing of the Republican candidate by almost 4 points on average. In just 12 cases, Rasmussen’s polls overestimated the margin for the Democrat by 3 or more points. But it did so for the Republican candidate in 55 cases — that is, in more than half of the polls that it issued. If one focused solely on the final poll issued by Rasmussen Reports or Pulse Opinion Research in each state — rather than including all polls within the three-week interval — it would not have made much difference. Their average error would be 5.7 points rather than 5.8, and their average bias 3.8 points rather than 3.9. Nor did it make much difference whether the polls were branded as Rasmussen Reports surveys, or instead, were commissioned for Fox News by its subsidiary Pulse Opinion Research. (Both sets of surveys used an essentially identical methodology.) Polls branded as Rasmussen Reports missed by an average of 5.9 points and had a 3.9 point bias. The polls it commissioned on behalf of Fox News had a 5.1 point error, and a 3.6 point bias. Rasmussen’s polls have come under heavy criticism throughout this election cycle, including from FiveThirtyEight. We have critiqued the firm for its cavalier attitude toward polling convention. Rasmussen, for instance, generally conducts all of its interviews during a single, 4-hour window; speaks with the first person it reaches on the phone rath</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364590027606</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:47:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364590206334-53</Id><Title>never the less Rasmussen has Obama at 53% tea billies just make up numbers</Title><Msg>Friday, March 29, 2013 The Rasmussen Reports daily Presidential Tracking Poll for Friday shows that 53% of Likely U.S. Voters approve of President Obama's job performance. Forty-five percent (45%) disapprove.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364590206334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364590777660-54</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who is Devil? Where does he come from? I read the Bible, I know who he is. You don't. That makes you his best target .</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364590777660</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:59:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364591347340-55</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Other men dedicated their lives to disprove the Bible. Oddly enough, some became believers. No idea what errors you are talking about.</Msg><Username>pacifican54</Username><Timestamp>1364591347340</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364591711437-56</Id><Title>DIVIDEND INCREASE - DATES for CISCO</Title><Msg>Cisco Systems, Inc. declared a quarterly dividend of $0.17 per share, or $0.68 annualized. The dividend will be payable on April 24, 2013, to stockholders of record on April 8, 2013, with an ex-dividend date of April 4, 2013.</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1364591711437</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:15:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364592624913-57</Id><Title>Jim nails it, LOL</Title><Msg>I’ll just say this: in my opinion Fux News is a last resort for kinda-sorta-almost-journalists whose options have been severely limited by their extreme and intolerant views; a media colostomy bag that has begun to burst at the seams and should be emptied before it becomes a public health issue. I sincerely believe that in time, good people will lose patience with the petty and poisonous behavior of these bullies and Fux News will be remembered as nothing more than a giant culture fart that no amount of Garlique could cure.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364592624913</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:30:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364593596861-58</Id><Topic><Title>never the less Rasmussen has Obama at 53% tea billies just make up numbers</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1364590206334</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 16:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Odd that you would go on and on about Rasmussen inaccuracies and then place such great emphasis on his 53% approval for Obama. Almost like you want it both ways. LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1364593596861</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:46:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364593878317-59</Id><Title>Does Obama know he's president?</Title><Msg>He still sounds like he's running for office every time he flaps his blue lips...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364593878317</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 17:51:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364594511779-60</Id><Topic><Title>Even the Democrats Rasmussen poll says that Obama has a favorable rating of 46 % now..at new Low.</Title><Username>maxwizard688</Username><Timestamp>1364583779550</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 15:02:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont lump me in with dumbivan .I have no use for him or Obama.However in this instance he is right, I used Google and as of yesterday Rasmussen showed Obama at 53%</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1364594511779</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:01:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364595771959-61</Id><Title>UGLY FATSLOB MANCHELLE TURNS A FUN DAY INTO A FAT CAMP</Title><Msg>UGLY FATSLOB MANCHELLE TURNS A FUN DAY INTO A FAT CAMP Why do the most repulsive obsese ugly monstrosities always try to lecture everyone on being slim and beautiful???</Msg><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1364595771959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>24</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364596333461-62</Id><Topic><Title>UGLY FATSLOB MANCHELLE TURNS A FUN DAY INTO A FAT CAMP</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1364595771959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>My Parents are 100 years old. We dont need no ugly fatslob like manchelle obama to tell us about being healthy. We've done fine without her ugly mug lecturing everyone.</Msg><Username>manchelle_obama_is_a_gargoyle</Username><Timestamp>1364596333461</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:32:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>23</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364596750904-63</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"I read the Bible, I know who he is. You don't. " The devil lives in the minds of men who pretend to know things they don't know. He is "the father of lies" and murder from the beginning.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364596750904</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:39:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364596896128-64</Id><Title>DEMOCRATS WANT TO EXEMPT CALIFORNIA UNIVERSITIES FROM POLLUTIONS LAWS</Title><Msg>Democrats want to exempt california universities from pollutions laws along with employers of lots of union workers. usa goverment has become extremely corrupt.</Msg><Username>manchelle_obama_is_a_gargoyle</Username><Timestamp>1364596896128</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:41:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364597064906-65</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>(The devil lives in the minds of men who pretend to know things they don't know. He is "the father of lies" and murder from the beginning.) Then he is a Democrat? That explains a lot!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1364597064906</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:44:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364597709929-66</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"Then he is a Democrat? That explains a lot!" Not all liars are Democrats. He seems to play his games on both sides. When a Church's best members are conceited, selfish, prideful, and can't tell the truth from a well constructed fib, it would seem he is their leader. There is no "magic" in the Bible. It's just a book.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364597709929</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:55:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364600191943-67</Id><Title>Is this just ONE nutcase posting this nonsense with</Title><Msg>multiple IDs,or is it a group of nutcases?Rightwingers ARE crazies no matter.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1364600191943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 19:36:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364600406625-68</Id><Topic><Title>Is this just ONE nutcase posting this nonsense with</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1364600191943</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 19:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good one Junior. Self identification is the first step to healing your sickness. One nutcase is surely posting nonsense with multiple ID's.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364600406625</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 19:40:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364604021610-69</Id><Title>CON ARTIST OBAMA PRINTING MONEY TO LEND TO HIMSELF MAKES BERNIE MADOFF LOOK LIKE</Title><Msg>Con artist obama printing money to lend to himself makes bernie madoff look like an amateur</Msg><Username>bill_oreilly_is_looking_out_4u</Username><Timestamp>1364604021610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:40:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>22</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364604358355-70</Id><Topic><Title>CON ARTIST OBAMA PRINTING MONEY TO LEND TO HIMSELF MAKES BERNIE MADOFF LOOK LIKE</Title><Username>bill_oreilly_is_looking_out_4u</Username><Timestamp>1364604021610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:40:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The corrupt chicanery by Obama and Geithner has caused the US Dollar to lose 40% of it's buying power. It is worst than Cypress Govt stealing money from everyone's bank account in Cypress. Get ready for Obama to try and steal money from everyones bank account, 401k, investment accounts ect.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1364604358355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:45:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364605078156-71</Id><Topic><Title>UGLY FATSLOB MANCHELLE TURNS A FUN DAY INTO A FAT CAMP</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1364595771959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Manchelle is ugly and obese. It is ridiculous that she is trying to force everyone to follow her 'beauty' tips and her tips on how to be slim.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1364605078156</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:57:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364605321267-72</Id><Topic><Title>UGLY FATSLOB MANCHELLE TURNS A FUN DAY INTO A FAT CAMP</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1364595771959</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 18:22:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>An ugly monstrosity like Manchelle should not be lecturing people on how to be beautiful</Msg><Username>cook_ee_monster</Username><Timestamp>1364605321267</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:02:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>13</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364605859708-73</Id><Title>IF OBAMA AND VLADIMIR PUTIN GOT IN FIST FIGHT WHO WOULD WIN??</Title><Msg>If obama and vladimir putin got in fist fight who would win?? a usa sissy or a russian macho man??</Msg><Username>arnold_schwarzenegger_sukks</Username><Timestamp>1364605859708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:10:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>25</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364606490593-74</Id><Topic><Title>IF OBAMA AND VLADIMIR PUTIN GOT IN FIST FIGHT WHO WOULD WIN??</Title><Username>arnold_schwarzenegger_sukks</Username><Timestamp>1364605859708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:10:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a cowardly draftdodger. Putin is a 3rd degree black belt in Sambo and combat trained by the KGB. Obviously Putin would easily win.</Msg><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1364606490593</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:21:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>19</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364607302505-75</Id><Topic><Title>CON ARTIST OBAMA PRINTING MONEY TO LEND TO HIMSELF MAKES BERNIE MADOFF LOOK LIKE</Title><Username>bill_oreilly_is_looking_out_4u</Username><Timestamp>1364604021610</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:40:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think you mean Cyprus. Cypress is a city in So Cali.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364607302505</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 21:35:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364608996060-76</Id><Title>WHICH DEMOCRAT CONGRESSMAN TWEETED HIS PETER TO SCHOOLGIRLS???</Title><Msg>WHICH DEMOCRAT CONGRESSMAN TWEETED HIS PETER TO SCHOOLGIRLS??? Hint: His wife is Hillary Clintongues lackee.</Msg><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1364608996060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364609307609-77</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT SENATOR MENENDEZ SEX PARTIES WITH YOUNG CHILDREN= NO MORALS OR DECENCY</Title><Username>weiner_the_peter_tweeter</Username><Timestamp>1360296154630</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-02-07 23:02:34 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The dirty pervet Anthony Weiner wants to be congressman again so that he can act pius while molesting minors.</Msg><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1364609307609</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:08:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364609364645-78</Id><Title>Which democrat Congressman had #$%$ with a Male Congressional Page in his office???</Title><Msg>Which democrat Congressman had #$%$ with a Male Congressional Page in his office??? Barney Frank.</Msg><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1364609364645</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:09:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364609744088-79</Id><Topic><Title>WHICH DEMOCRAT CONGRESSMAN TWEETED HIS PETER TO SCHOOLGIRLS???</Title><Username>is_weiner_child_molester</Username><Timestamp>1364608996060</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:03:16 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Democrat Congressman Anthony Weiner resigned for tweeting his peter to minors.</Msg><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1364609744088</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:15:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364610461671-80</Id><Title>Which Democrat Congresswoman Let Her Bulldog Kill a Baby Seal and escaped being Charged</Title><Msg>Which Democrat Congresswoman Let Her Bulldog Kill a Baby Seal and escaped being Charged with animal cruelty??? Answer Gabrielle Giffords. The goverment is so corrupt that because she is a democrat she isn't charged with a crime while any other schuck would be charged and put in prison.</Msg><Username>atenwithbrains_isa_giggling_homo</Username><Timestamp>1364610461671</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>16</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364610983228-81</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>" Will a male be able to marry his brother if same sex marriage is legalized?" " I was just thinking of marrying a young female just to pass on my SS benefits to her at young age." A straight male can marry a young female. A straight male cannot marry his female sister. It;'s not really complicated. I don't see the gays asking for rights the straights don't have. The "plural" (only 1 man, multiple women) will be introduced in Utah soon. It won't pass, but if that's the sort of thing that represents a move in your direction, go for it... My marriage is not strained by gays getting married. Yours? Assuming you have one.</Msg><Username>jsf00000714</Username><Timestamp>1364610983228</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:36:23 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1364611376301-82</Id><Title>A Negguh president and his B-2's</Title><Msg>showboating and underestimating the potential for North Korea to turn up the heat on the DMZ and other US military bases by about 150 Million degrees F. This is what you voted for libs. In Japan during WWII those atomic bombs left innocent civilians clamoring in the street, eye balls in hand and skin falling off cooking from the inside. Today that same threat comes to American military bases with young boys and girls that couldn't get any other job because this Obama economy sucks so bad.........but atleast today we have gay marriage and free lunch for mexicans right?</Msg><Username>westpalmbeachrentals</Username><Timestamp>1364611376301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:42:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364611785964-83</Id><Topic><Title>Which Republican Wanted A Male Monica Lewinsky? Tom Foley!...</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1364609166780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously not all Republicans are model politicians, just like most Democrats claim to be the "good guys" watching out for the little fella but are really just BIG GUBMENT radicals who want to shove it down our throats. There still remains just one president to date who used his power and position to get felacio in the Oval Office - and HE was a DemocRAT... speaking of shoving something down someone's throat...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1364611785964</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:49:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364612397886-84</Id><Topic><Title>How is wanting to marry someone of the same sex a " right" ?</Title><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364577573708</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 13:19:33 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>"A straight male can marry a young female. A straight male cannot marry his female sister." Yeah, I'll probably have to find a second cousin to keep the money in the family, all legal and shyt. Thanks for the tip!</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364612397886</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:59:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364612649234-85</Id><Topic><Title>A Negguh president and his B-2's</Title><Username>westpalmbeachrentals</Username><Timestamp>1364611376301</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:42:56 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I believe they call it "wagging the dog?" He has to show military strength because of something else lacking in his administrative abilities.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364612649234</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:04:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364612919963-86</Id><Topic><Title>Who Do Americans Blame Most For The Economy, The President, McConnell Or Boehner?,..</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1364513791202</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-28 19:36:31 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler said it, too. He actually proved that it works. You simply use the deficit to take over other countries. What's not to understand?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364612919963</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:08:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364613928582-87</Id><Topic><Title>President Obama Has Been Re-Elected President In A Land Of 47% Ignorant Racist Filth!,..</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1364602292314</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 20:11:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're probably right. He proved that evolution has an inverse. When stupid people breed like rabbits, evolution reverses direction until you have a nation of idiots.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364613928582</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:25:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1364615913257-88</Id><Topic><Title>Which Republican Wanted A Male Monica Lewinsky? Tom Foley!...</Title><Username>the.word999</Username><Timestamp>1364609166780</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 22:06:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Politicians from both sides are particularly vulnerable to hiding their perceived character defects and becoming hypocritical. Often they need to promote behaviors they are not capable of handling in their own lives. One needs to refine one's morality when accounting for politicians. We all should know they are liars. If we don't know that, we should probably work harder on our own skills.. One should probably diagnose oneself a moron if he can't tell when a politician is lying. "His lips are moving" is clear evidence of the fact. There are several orders of crime. One should likely consider levels of the crimes in proper order. First, would likely be perfidy, which is treason disguised as patriotism or civility, commonly known as "spying" or "terrorism," "false flag," "subversion," or "sabotage." Second would be probably be visible treason. Third, one might consider crimes of moral turpitude. Moral turpitude is more serious than a crime of passion. It represents willful destruction or theft. Crimes of passion should be considered with leniency. The game of who f*u*c*ked who was fun in high school. Yeah, Jimmy took drugs, and so did Buffy.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1364615913257</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-29 23:58:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>