<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-01-12"><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357970885400-1</Id><Topic><Title>Bush had negative GDP growth, created the worst recession since the great depression</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1357931394161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 14:09:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>***** bush doubled UE You are so stupid you real ID must be dropkickuuuuuuuu!!!!!!!!!</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1357970885400</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:08:05 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357971314241-2</Id><Topic><Title>Bush had negative GDP growth, created the worst recession since the great depression</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1357931394161</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 14:09:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>*** That's not much for eight years. Democrats tend to equate lots of pages of legislation as an accomplishment. Sometimes, doing nothing is a great accomplishment. The 2700 page ObamaCare and its several thousands of pages of axillary laws &amp; regulations may well prove to be a disaster for America. Not to mention Obama Admins some 50,000 pages of new administrative regulations. Buddha advised that a good ruler was one who ruled the least. Obama is a heavy handed fascist.</Msg><Username>natasha.fatale011</Username><Timestamp>1357971314241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:15:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357971389831-3</Id><Topic><Title>FORMER DEMOCRAT GOV AND CEO EMBEZZLES BILLIONS - NO CHARGES???</Title><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1357954587504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 20:36:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Heil Obama!</Msg><Username>whrutter</Username><Timestamp>1357971389831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 01:16:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357976803377-4</Id><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Msg>From NBC Miami website. "A naked intruder who was trying to choke a pet Rottweiler was shot by a homeowner in Miami Wednesday morning, police said.......Police said the suspect, who refused to give his identity, will be charged with burglary of an occupied dwelling with assault, animal cruelty, resisting arrest with violence and lewd and lascivious behavior. Read full story at the NBC Miami website From the photo in the news article, intruder looked like travon martin.</Msg><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357977055788-5</Id><Title>OBAMACARE = HIGHER MIDDLE CLASS COSTS FOR DENTAL BRACES FOR KIDS</Title><Msg>From Americans for Tax Reform website: "Braces for the Kids Just Got More Expensive: Obamacare Tax Hike Case Study In 2013, the tax increases in Obamacare will increasingly conspire against kitchen-table family healthcare decisions. As just one example, below are some of the taxes that will impact the purchase of dental braces: Obamacare Medical Device Tax: As of Jan.1, Obamacare imposes a new tax of 2.3 percent on medical device manufacturers, including those who make dental braces. The tax is imposed on gross sales -- even if the company does not earn a profit in a given year. While the tax will be paid to the IRS by the manufacturer, the tax will be passed along as a higher cost of the product, ultimately to be borne by the parent buying the braces for their child. With the cost of braces being as high as $7,625 this new tax could raise the cost of these braces by $175. Read full story at the Americans for Tax Reform website.</Msg><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977055788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:50:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1357977270019-6</Id><Title>GLOBAL COOLING THREATENS CALIFORNIA CITRUS CROPS</Title><Msg>From Reuters: "An Arctic air mass sent temperatures plunging across California, forcing the 17-hour closure of a key interstate highway through the mountains north of Los Angeles and threatening citrus crops in the state's vast central valleys, authorities said on Friday." Read full story at Reuters website.</Msg><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977270019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:54:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997249754-7</Id><Topic><Title>GLOBAL COOLING THREATENS CALIFORNIA CITRUS CROPS</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977270019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:54:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>On its way to 25! Way to go CSCO...</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997249754</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:27:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997308026-8</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMACARE = HIGHER MIDDLE CLASS COSTS FOR DENTAL BRACES FOR KIDS</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977055788</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:50:55 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, the graph certainly shows a break out so I agree with your analysis on CSCO. $25 is coming soon!!</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997308026</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:28:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997381627-9</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>More solid analysis on your part! CSCO's fundamentals are strong so $25 should be coming soon!</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997381627</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:29:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997447154-10</Id><Topic><Title>FORMER DEMOCRAT GOV AND CEO EMBEZZLES BILLIONS - NO CHARGES???</Title><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1357954587504</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 20:36:27 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Certainly good value as you point out in your analysis so I would agree that CSCO is a strong buy</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997447154</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:30:47 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997496540-11</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco looks undervalued</Title><Username>lws2000</Username><Timestamp>1357962695355</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 22:51:35 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Leaner and meaner these days. Here comes $25!</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997496540</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:31:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1357997683299-12</Id><Topic><Title>Just CISCO here</Title><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1357875780906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 22:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Above avg. volume and a nice rise in the stock since Nov. from what, 17? Leaner and meaner, lots of cash, good divi....$25 sometime in the next 6 months.</Msg><Username>kedzie114</Username><Timestamp>1357997683299</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:34:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358002524553-13</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>She must have been a rightwinger. A liberal woman would have helped him finish off the dog,invite him in for breakfast and some quality time with one of her young daughters, then taken him to city hall to sign up to vote democrat in the next election.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1358002524553</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 09:55:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>12</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358003696504-14</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior got shot?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1358003696504</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:14:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>14</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358003785284-15</Id><Title>A heart beat away</Title><Msg>Joe Biden said yesterday " we are shooting for Tuesday" on the presidents gun proposals and" there is no silver bullet to stop the killing". The gaffe master at his finest. A democratic leader.LOL</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1358003785284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:16:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004013769-16</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's this has to do with Cisco?</Msg><Username>astute_investors</Username><Timestamp>1358004013769</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:20:13 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358004924247-17</Id><Topic><Title>Just CISCO here</Title><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1357875780906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 22:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Just ignore them &amp; report them as you go,soon no more OT political diarrehea.</Msg><Username>williamdavis960</Username><Timestamp>1358004924247</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:35:24 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Buy</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358005190843-18</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Wasn't Junior. He'd have been trying to have sex with the dog, not strangle it.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1358005190843</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:39:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358006162690-19</Id><Title>These are the worst of times....</Title><Msg>If Bush used an EO on gun control, Bill-O would say that he did it because he felt he was compelled to. End of story. But then O'Reilly flipped the 'cocky' part of Obama and adeptly transitioned into how the people that want to pass gun control only are doing it because they hate America. or, in BillO's words A driving philosophy behind this is that America is a bad country.... President Obama believes that America is a flawed country and it is his duty to correct those flaws. See, Obama the cocky hates America and it's his duty to correct those flaws that we here at FOX News make you believe there really aren't any. We're perfect, without flaw, God fearing and righteous. Heck, if we do happen to blow up a few countries along the way I'm sure the folks will be virtuous and forgive em. As the days tick by in Obama's second term, Bill-O is going to lose it more and more. I don't see how he makes it through without taking a lot of time off. If not, I imagine that he'll blame Obama for fluoridation and other such things. But for now he'll stick to the basics of dog-whistle politics. General Jack D. Rippe: Do you realize that fluoridation is the most monstrously conceived and dangerous Communist plot we have ever had to face?' I can no longer sit back and allow Communist infiltration, Communist indoctrination, Communist subversion and the international Communist conspiracy to sap and impurify all of our precious bodily fluids." General Jack D. Ripper: Mandrake, do you realize that in addition to fluoridating water, why, there are studies underway to fluoridate salt, flour, fruit juices, soup, sugar, milk... ice cream. Ice cream, Mandrake, children's ice cream. Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: [very nervous] Lord, Jack. General Jack D. Ripper: You know when fluoridation first began? Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: I... no, no. I don't, Jack. General Jack D. Ripper: Nineteen hundred and forty-six. 1946, Mandrake. How does that coincide with your post-war #$%$ conspiracy, huh? It's incredibly obvious, isn't it? A foreign substance is introduced into our precious bodily fluids without the knowledge of the individual. Certainly without any choice. That's the way your hard-core #$%$ works. Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: Uh, Jack, Jack, listen... tell me, tell me, Jack. When did you first... become... well, develop this theory? General Jack D. Ripper: [somewhat embarassed] Well, I, uh... I... I... first became aware of it, Mandrake, during the physical act of love. Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: Hmm. General Jack D. Ripper: Yes, a uh, a profound sense of fatigue... a feeling of emptiness followed. Luckily I... I was able to interpret these feelings correctly. Loss of essence. Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: Hmm. General Jack D. Ripper: I can assure you it has not recurred, Mandrake. Women uh... women sense my power and they seek the life essence. I, uh... I do not avoid women, Mandrake. Group Capt. Lionel Mandrake: No. General Jack D. Ripper: But I... I do deny them my essence.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1358006162690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:56:02 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358007830221-20</Id><Title>WEATHER GOING CRAZY...</Title><Msg>Record heat, deadly cold temperatures, flooding and rare snowfall - a wide range of extreme weather events have taken place around the world in the last few weeks. Play VideoSnowstorm Blankets Holy Land The latest such example is from the Middle East, where flooding rains this week were followed by rare snow on Thursday. Several inches of snow accumulated in Jerusalem and the West Bank on Thursday, according to reports from The Associated Press. The snow, reportedly the most in a decade, had significant impacts on transportation. Prior to the snow, heavy rainfall led to flooding in parts of the Middle East. ************** Meanwhile back in repuke land they are concerned about guns ! Donate to the Redneck College Fund because a mind is a terrible thing to waste...NOT !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358007830221</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:23:50 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358008752121-21</Id><Title>Oh no!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Msg>AP Interview: George P. Bush weighing run in Texas Jan 12, 3:22 AM (ET) By WILL WEISSERT AUSTIN, Texas (AP) - George Prescott Bush is gearing up to run for a little-known but powerful office in a state where his family already is a political dynasty and where his Hispanic roots could help extend a stranglehold on power Republicans have enjoyed for two decades. The 36-year-old Fort Worth attorney says he is close to settling on campaigning for Texas land commissioner next year. He doesn't expect to make up his mind until he knows what Texas Gov. Rick Perry, a fellow Republican, decides to do. "We for sure are running, the question is the office," Bush told The Associated Press during the first interview about his political future since filing paperwork in November to seek elected office in Texas. Bush's father is former Florida Gov. Jeb Bush, his grandfather is former President George H.W. Bush and his uncle is former President and Texas Gov. George W. Bush. Perry has been governor since George W. left for the White House.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358008752121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:39:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009185392-22</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358008752121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:39:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I think W took care of sinking the Bush family for good. No worries.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009185392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:46:25 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358009256249-23</Id><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Msg>Atlanta (CNN) -- Authorities in Georgia are investigating the apparent homicide of a Georgia man who produced popular gun-related YouTube videos. Keith Ratliff was found shot in the head January 3 in his home-office in Carnesville, Georgia, about 80 miles northeast of Atlanta. Ratliff was co-owner of FPS Industries, whose website says it "is proud to be world leaders in product development and testing for hard use firearms shooters." Investigators from many agencies -- including the Georgia Bureau of Investigation and the federal Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives -- are investigating, and the GBI said Friday that they are making progress in identifying the shooter. Several guns were found at the scene, but none of them were used to shoot Ratliff, the GBI said in a news release. Ratliff's YouTube channel had more than 530,000,000 views</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009355629-24</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358008752121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:39:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A member of the corrupt Bush family should never be permitted to run for any office,in any state,higher than animal control.</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358009355629</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:49:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009686618-25</Id><Topic><Title>Oh no!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</Title><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358008752121</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:39:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Land commissioner traditionally has been a steppingstone to higher office, but Bush said little about any plans to eventually become a national political force. Instead, he spoke of how his past experience as an asset manager would help him manage the Permanent Schools Fund, which pays for public education and is managed by the land commissioner. He also said his perspective as an Afghanistan war veteran will help him use the post to become a leader in veterans' affairs. Bush said he would announce his final decision after the Texas Legislature adjourns in May but added that his choice will depend "where the governor's thinking is." Perry, who flamed out as a presidential candidate but remains popular in Texas, says he'll reveal this summer if he will seek another term. Some have speculated that Bush could challenge Perry for governor - and even if he doesn't, what Perry decides will trigger political dominos falling. Land Commissioner Jerry Patterson plans to run for lieutenant governor next year, creating a vacancy in his office. But Attorney General Greg Abbott, a Republican, may himself run for governor in 2014, meaning his post could be open too. Bush suggested he'd be willing to wait his turn politically rather than immediately seeking top positions coveted by others in the state GOP. "We've said that we want to be team players in the party, providing a younger, fresher vision for our values," he said in the interview Friday. Bush speaks Spanish, and his mother Columba is from Mexico. Conservatives view George P. Bush on the ballot as a way to solidify support among Hispanics. A Democrat has not won statewide office in Texas since 1994, but Hispanics tend to vote overwhelmingly Democratic and accounted for two-thirds of Texas' population growth over the last decade. Bush noted: "We'll be majority Hispanic in six years." "I don't necessarily agree with the idea that having a candidate of Hispanic origin, or someone who can speak Spanish, can automatically obtain these votes," Bush said of Hispanics. "Having said that, it's important tactically to have candidates that understand issues of the community." Bush's mother has said that one of the reasons she and Jeb Bush left Texas for Florida in the 1970s was because she felt like she had experienced racism here. But George P. Bush said, "the way I view it, rather than an issue of discomfort, is economic opportunity." "This has been, at least for our generation, the best place to be economically," he said of Texas and its record of strong job creation. He said he didn't think there was more intolerance toward Hispanics in Texas. "Obviously, I think that issue exists wherever you go," he said. "I don't think it's just unique here." Bush said of trying to stand out among his famous political family, "It's always been the thing of my grandmother to say, 'Go out and make a name for yourself' and that's something that I've followed." "But who better to ask for advice on politics than two former presidents and a former governor?" he said. "They're not involved in the day-to-day operations. They're not involved in formulating my ideology. It's more of an informal advice." Bush said his grandfather inspired him to join the military, and he was deployed to Afghanistan as an intelligence officer in the U.S. Naval Reserve. He said that before enlisting, he knew politics was in his blood but felt he was too inexperienced to run for office. It wasn't until the last few months, however, that "I felt it was time for my generation to step forward in state politics," Bush said. Bush now spends his time crisscrossing Texas and the country, raising money and meeting with supporters. He was in Austin on Monday and posed for pictures outside the state Capitol before disappearing into meetings with legislators. Someone he didn't see, however, was Perry. The governor said Bush's seeking elected office is a good thing for Texas and the Republican Party, and that he would like to speak to him about it adding: "He knows my phone number." But then, Bush has his uncle to turn to for Texas gubernatorial perspective. "It's much like starting a business," Bush said, "and having people who have been there and done it and run statewide, it's definitely been helpful."</Msg><Username>alsmith581</Username><Timestamp>1358009686618</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:54:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358009851035-26</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Is that some sort of racist guilt bay association post, or just the ranting of some qweer that hats fat people?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1358009851035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:57:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358009971306-27</Id><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Msg>Survey says only 17% of Americans were aware of the payroll tax going back to 6.2%. The rest were surprised their checks were smaller. Hard to believe how uninformed Americans are.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358010299534-28</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf would rather hear a fat boy fart than a pretty girl sing.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1358010299534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:04:59 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358010771710-29</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And they vote.</Msg><Username>trofholz</Username><Timestamp>1358010771710</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:12:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011335065-30</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anklebiter ! LMAO !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358011335065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:22:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358011431673-31</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh oh, looks like Fartie is over 300 POUNDS !!! LMAO ! Oh noooo ! ROTF !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358011431673</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:23:51 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012493214-32</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like Magoo is switching from Surf to Junior. And dont even bother with the denials.LOLOLOLOLOL</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1358012493214</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:41:33 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012752414-33</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In the first bank closing of 2013, the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation said Friday that it shut down Westside Community Bank in Washington. The crisis is over. All is well. The economy is getting stronger that's why banks are failing.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358012752414</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:45:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012850184-34</Id><Topic><Title>These are the worst of times....</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1358006162690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:56:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>And these are the bet of times... *** You sound like Charles Dickens. They should focus on spending control first not gun control, unless they are expecting a civil war to erupt.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358012850184</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:47:30 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358012924135-35</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You seem to have a chip on your shoulder .I didn't point the finger at anybody. I simply said the public was uninformed. Which is true.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358012924135</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:48:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358013014042-36</Id><Topic><Title>A heart beat away</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1358003785284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:16:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Joe Biden said yesterday " we are shooting for Tuesday" on the presidents gun proposals and" there is no silver bullet to stop the killing". The gaffe master at his finest. *** What a clown. Highest priority should be controlling spending.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358013014042</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:50:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358013060657-37</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cisco is going to $30 -- just wait. In the meantime, macros are all that matter. Whaddaya new?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358013060657</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:51:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358013466225-38</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior is a complete idiot. See why every one here hates him?????</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1358013466225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 12:57:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014256118-39</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The nightly news is all happy propaganda - 1984. The Corvette is the symbol of the successful plumber... an old man's toy.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358014256118</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:10:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014376356-40</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whimpy, another fat angry white dude. Whimp, call Linsdey Graham, he said the pukes were running out of your kind. Give him some hope ! LOL! LOL! LOL!</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358014376356</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:12:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014416429-41</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Pray to Martin Luther King. Black Power. Minority Rule. Obama is God. Ruler for ever. Only white trash commits abortion.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358014416429</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:13:36 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014518644-42</Id><Topic><Title>GLOBAL COOLING THREATENS CALIFORNIA CITRUS CROPS</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977270019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:54:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>CSCO was the largest of the large caps. Too many acquisitions. Bad CEO. P/E should be 10.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358014518644</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:15:18 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358014940004-43</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>White people are working mules to be taxed. Black is the preferred race. Most blacks don't work, get free handouts from the dictator and get special preferred treatment to get into the best universities instead of more qualified whites.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358014940004</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:22:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015028279-44</Id><Topic><Title>AMERICAN EXPRESS LAYING OFF 5400 WORKERS IN 2013</Title><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1357956332431</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-01-11 21:05:32 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Good for the stock. Warren Buffet wins again. Obama has done nuttin for black unemployment.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358015028279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:23:48 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015108654-45</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>intruder looked like travon martin. *** Was junior riding the dog like a little bronco?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358015108654</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:25:08 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358015141856-46</Id><Topic><Title>HOMEOWNER SHOOTS NAKED INTRUDER WHO WAS STRANGLING HOMEOWNERS DOG</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357976803377</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:46:43 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs care more about dogs than humans.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358015141856</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:25:41 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358016055542-47</Id><Topic><Title>The problem with AMERICA and all his babies moma</Title><Username>callmewhimpy</Username><Timestamp>1357998878064</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 08:54:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>TABLE 1 - Section 1(a) - Married Individuals Filing Joint Returns and Surviving Spouses Income over $223,050 - $49,919.50 tax plus 33% of the excess over $223,050 Income over $398,350 - $107,768 tax plus 35% of the excess over $398,350 Income over $450,000 - $125,846 tax plus 39.6% of $450,000 You live better if you drop out and take handouts like the black people and illegal aliens do. Obama Banana Republic of America. QE has created a Keynesian liquidity trap. GDP now near zero -- stagnant like Cuba. CSCO no dividend. Bad CEO.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358016055542</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:40:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358016561549-48</Id><Topic><Title>A financial surprise.</Title><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358009971306</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:59:31 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I posted the truth and the stats to back it up. Pretty evident I did have the facts .I usually dont respond to the silliness you seem to enjoy. So you can give me one more inane response and we will be done. Have a nice day.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1358016561549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 13:49:21 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358017507706-49</Id><Title>Section 8 Housing Handouts Cancelled After Thousands of Welfare Bums Stampeded like Wild Animals</Title><Msg>Section 8 Housing Handouts Cancelled in Taylor Michigan After Thousands of Welfare Bums Stampeded like Wild Animals and bum rushed the Handout Office.</Msg><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358017507706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:05:07 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>11</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358017879127-50</Id><Topic><Title>Section 8 Housing Handouts Cancelled After Thousands of Welfare Bums Stampeded like Wild Animals</Title><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358017507706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:05:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Were any of them Obama supporters?lol</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1358017879127</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:11:19 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358018318318-51</Id><Topic><Title>Section 8 Housing Handouts Cancelled After Thousands of Welfare Bums Stampeded like Wild Animals</Title><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358017507706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:05:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every single one.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358018318318</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:18:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358018437220-52</Id><Title>LEFT WING PROPAGANDA OUTLET TO LAY OFF 700 DEMOCRAT PROPAGANDISTS IN 2013</Title><Msg>LEFT WING PROPAGANDA OUTLET to LAY OFF 700 DEMOCRAT PROPAGANDISTS in 2013 DEMOCRAT PARTY CONTROLLED LAPDOG and Propaganda outlet TIME MAGAZINE is LAYING OFF 700 It is wonderful to see hardcore Obama voters getting the shaft from Obama-nomics.</Msg><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358018437220</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:20:37 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358018457170-53</Id><Topic><Title>GLOBAL COOLING THREATENS CALIFORNIA CITRUS CROPS</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1357977270019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 02:54:30 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Lemmings believe it. Obama says he will not build the Death Star That’s the message from the White House in an official response to a petition urging President Barack Obama to build the moon-sized planet-killing space station from Star Wars. “The Administration shares your desire for job creation and a strong national defense,” writes Paul Shawcross, chief of the science and space branch of the White House’s budget office. But “the Administration does not support blowing up planets.” Plus, Shawcross points out: “Why would we spend countless taxpayer dollars on a Death Star with a fundamental flaw that can be exploited by a one-man starship?” (Cue speculation that China has built an X-Wing fighter). And with the price tag estimated to run at least $852 quadrillion, Shawcross says, “we’re working hard to reduce the deficit, not expand it.” (Hmmm, so the stimulative impact of government infrastructure spending does not balance out its cost? That might come up again as Obama clashes with Republicans this Spring over how best to reduce the national debt.) Shawcross goes on to list various high-tech projects funded with taxpayer dollars, throwing in a few Star Wars reference for good measure (the International Space Station features “onboard garbage mashers.” NASA has a Commercial Crew and Cargo Program Office – C3PO? Really? Someone had a bit of fun with that one). It’s sad news in a way, as if more than 34,000 petition signers cried out in terror and were suddenly silence. But it’s good news for the Senate! After all, building the first Death Star enabled Emperor Palpatine to dissolve the Senate. That means that there’s no need for regional governors to take direct control over their territories and use fear to keep the local systems in line.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358018457170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:20:57 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358018685065-54</Id><Title>8 GUN ROBBERIES IN DC IN 7 HOUR PERIOD</Title><Msg>Democrats worried about honest people buying guns. Democrat felons who dont obey stupid democrat gun laws,on the other hand simply rob gun stores with the illegal guns they stole and now that democrats put the names and addresses of law abiding gun owners on the internet, democrat felons can simply goto this list and rob the homes of law abiding gun owners.</Msg><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358018685065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:24:45 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358018996794-55</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Maybe he just toetapped the next stall and his boyfriend is posting?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1358018996794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:29:56 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358019009300-56</Id><Title>COLD WEATHER IN DENVER, Oh oh...WILL RAVENS UPSET BRONCOS ?</Title><Msg>Or will the Ravens have one of those mediocre games ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358019009300</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358019202224-57</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fartie how is that twinkie diet coming along ? You think you will ever drop under 300 lbs ?</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358019202224</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:33:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358019854519-58</Id><Topic><Title>GUN NUT SHOT DEAD !!! ROTF ! HOW DO YOU LOVE YOUR BULLETS NOW FAT BOY !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1358009256249</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 11:47:36 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I find it strange Junior keeps bringing up toetapping, but then says how much he enjoys oral from Carey. Since Carey says he has a beard,maybe Junior likes being tickled.</Msg><Username>wonka9090</Username><Timestamp>1358019854519</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:44:14 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358020455409-59</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR TAKING UPSKIRT PICS OF YOUNG GIRLS</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you sure it was a democrat? They usually prefer young boys.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1358020455409</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:54:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358020580933-60</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR TAKING UPSKIRT PICS OF YOUNG GIRLS</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>degenerate democrat sex offender teacher union perverts may prefer young boys but they will target anything that moves including animals.</Msg><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020580933</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:56:20 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358021078329-61</Id><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION MEMBER SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS PAID PEDOFILE UNION TEACHER $400000 TO COVERUP THE CRIMES</Title><Msg>DEMOCRAT UNION MEMBER SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS PAID PEDOFILE UNION TEACHER $400000 TO COVERUP THE CRIMES From Fox News: "The former third-grade teacher charged with committing lewd acts on students was paid $40,000 to drop an appeal of his firing, a newspaper reported Friday. The Los Angeles Unified School District settled with Mark Berndt because it couldn't defend his February 2011 firing, district general counsel David Holmquist told the Los Angeles Times. The 61-year-old recently was charged with 23 counts of lewd acts upon children, ages 6 to 10, accused of feeding his semen to some students during "tasting games" in his classroom from 2005 to 2010. A second Miramonte teacher, 49-year-old Martin Springer, was fired this week and has pleaded not guilty to committing three lewd acts on one girl in class in 2009. He was freed on bail early Friday, though the Los Angeles County sheriff's department said he was fitted with a court-ordered electronic ankle monitor." Read full story at Fox News website</Msg><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358021078329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:04:38 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358023204589-62</Id><Topic><Title>CALIFORNIA UNION TEACHER SUFFOCATES BUNNY 2ND GRADERS WATCH</Title><Username>chinchilla_pals</Username><Timestamp>1351825294250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:01:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Couldn't agree more</Msg><Username>general_colin_bowels</Username><Timestamp>1358023204589</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:40:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>9</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024369018-63</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>davideunice914</Username><Timestamp>1358019414688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:36:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What's the catalyst? This POS shouldn't even be in the Dow 30. This is old dead tech like HPQ.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358024369018</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:59:29 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024566693-64</Id><Topic><Title>SIDEWALK COLLAPSES WHEN 400 POUND WOMAN WHO LOOKS LIKE MANCHELLE</Title><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358019080961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:31:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>a democrat union worker must have built that sidewalk. *** 5 democrat union leaches stood and watched him work, called his mother names then criticized his work but offered no help. The vulgar nasty bas*tuds of America are all democrats.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358024566693</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:02:46 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358024655807-65</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION MEMBER SCHOOL ADMINISTRATORS PAID PEDOFILE UNION TEACHER $400000 TO COVERUP THE CRIMES</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358021078329</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 15:04:38 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Read full story at Fox News website *** Another lib who watches Fox. When is Rush Limbaugh on the air?</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358024655807</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:04:15 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358025724935-66</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>davideunice914</Username><Timestamp>1358019414688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:36:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Big guys think otherwise ---" Cisco Systems (NASDAQ: CSCO) was Edinburgh’s top pick with the fund reporting a position of almost 12 million shares at the beginning of 2013. Cisco was also one of billionaire Ken Fisher’s Fisher Asset Management’s favorite stocks according to that fund’s recently released 13F (check out Fisher's latest stock picks). The stock trades at 13 times trailing earnings, despite 18% earnings growth in its most recent quarterly report compared to the same period in the previous fiscal year; revenue growth was lower, but still moderate. We think that Cisco could be a value play." we will see who is right!</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1358025724935</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:22:04 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358026708198-67</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>davideunice914</Username><Timestamp>1358019414688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:36:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes siree, its gonna be fun watching the short squeeze...lol</Msg><Username>jeanettesolomon709</Username><Timestamp>1358026708198</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:38:28 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358027983480-68</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO Is Looking Good!</Title><Username>davideunice914</Username><Timestamp>1358019414688</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:36:54 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Typical sell job to bag holders. When they pump it, it's time to dump it. You should have bought CSCO at $17-18.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358027983480</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 16:59:43 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358028824878-69</Id><Topic><Title>SIDEWALK COLLAPSES WHEN 400 POUND WOMAN WHO LOOKS LIKE MANCHELLE</Title><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358019080961</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:31:20 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Okay…I’ve HAD it….REALLY had IT WITH MICHELLE OBAMA! This anti American socialist blathering FOOL has gone WAY too far. There she sat on Barack’s right side as bagpipers played and an honor guard folded an American Flag. You know how it’s done…With reverence and respect, folded precisely and crisply…honored. It was during that moment that our nations “First Lady” leaned to her husband’s ears and asked the question that should set your TEETH on fire!!! “All of this for a damned flag?” When Barack nodded, she sat back and gave a look of disgust. What a pill.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358028824878</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:13:44 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358029406396-70</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR TAKING UPSKIRT PICS OF YOUNG GIRLS</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He didn't show up for his inauguration. Pull the plug.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358029406396</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 17:23:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032672649-71</Id><Topic><Title>CALIFORNIA UNION TEACHER SUFFOCATES BUNNY 2ND GRADERS WATCH</Title><Username>chinchilla_pals</Username><Timestamp>1351825294250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:01:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's financial repression policies suk balz -- worst president in our lifetimes.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358032672649</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:17:52 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>8</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032774873-72</Id><Topic><Title>"There are only two options to deal with the debt limit: Congress can pay its bills or it can fail to act and put the nation into default,"</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1358031681666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:01:21 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Cut spending -- that is the only answer; there is so much waste and corruption in gubment a 10% across the board cut won't hurt anything; it will make gubment more efficient.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358032774873</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:19:34 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358032870636-73</Id><Topic><Title>These are the worst of times....</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1358006162690</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:56:02 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama insists on wasting money on inefficient, wasteful and corrupt gubment agencies. Obama worst President in our lifetimes -- America has become a Banana Republic under Obama.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358032870636</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:21:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358033470624-74</Id><Topic><Title>A heart beat away</Title><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1358003785284</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 10:16:25 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At least 11 people have been killed and more than 75 injured when two buses crashed into a lorry on their way to the inauguration of Hugo Chavez. Hugo did not show up. Many say he is dead in Cuba.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358033470624</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 18:31:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358035392110-75</Id><Title>A little myrth</Title><Msg>What do you get when you put Piers Morgan and 31 other Limeys in the same room? A full set of teeth. ROTFL</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmates_5</Username><Timestamp>1358035392110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:03:12 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035586870-76</Id><Topic><Title>A little myrth</Title><Username>juniorsclassmates_5</Username><Timestamp>1358035392110</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:03:12 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You went to public school and community college. Obama's plan to make housing affordable -- put all the homeowners underwater.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1358035586870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:06:26 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358035810405-77</Id><Topic><Title>Section 8 Housing Handouts Cancelled After Thousands of Welfare Bums Stampeded like Wild Animals</Title><Username>barack_the_kenyan_zombie</Username><Timestamp>1358017507706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:05:07 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Not only did these welfare bums stampeded and bum rush the Goverment Handout office, when the Handout office shutdown because of the unruly and uncivilized welfare mob, the mob of able bodied moochers rioted, and vandalized the Goverment Office. Most of these Obama voters are violent criminal minded parasites on society.</Msg><Username>general_colin_bowels</Username><Timestamp>1358035810405</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:10:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358036252908-78</Id><Title>OHIO DEMOCRAT PROPOSES ARMING UNIONIZED SCHOOL JANITORS WITH MACHINE GUNS TO PROTECT CHILDREN</Title><Msg>OHIO DEMOCRAT PROPOSES ARMING UNIONIZED SCHOOL JANITORS WITH MACHINE GUNS TO PROTECT CHILDREN The problem is that there is an epidemic of unionize school janitor molesting school kids. Don't democrat parents want their kids protected from pedofile union janitors???</Msg><Username>general_colin_bowels</Username><Timestamp>1358036252908</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:17:32 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037322181-79</Id><Topic><Title>CALIFORNIA UNION TEACHER SUFFOCATES BUNNY 2ND GRADERS WATCH</Title><Username>chinchilla_pals</Username><Timestamp>1351825294250</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2012-11-01 23:01:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>all the above posts are pathetic</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358037322181</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:35:22 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037430041-80</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR TAKING UPSKIRT PICS OF YOUNG GIRLS</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>isn't this a cisco stock board?</Msg><Username>m.swanger</Username><Timestamp>1358037430041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:37:10 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358037895133-81</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED FOR TAKING UPSKIRT PICS OF YOUNG GIRLS</Title><Username>theory_of_evolution_rocks</Username><Timestamp>1358020226872</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 14:50:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes it is a Cisco stock board but Poncho took it over. ROTFL</Msg><Username>juniorsclassmates_5</Username><Timestamp>1358037895133</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 19:44:55 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1358041680029-82</Id><Topic><Title>Just CISCO here</Title><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1357875780906</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-01-10 22:43:00 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>how do you keep this cisco at the top of this political spew??</Msg><Username>brat81us</Username><Timestamp>1358041680029</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 20:48:00 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1358051409011-83</Id><Title>BYE, BYE Packers..49ERS CRUSH THEM</Title><Msg>Niners!</Msg><Username>futureperson</Username><Timestamp>1358051409011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-01-12 23:30:09 EST</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>