<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-03-17"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363506613007-1</Id><Title>LAPD BUYS WOMEN NEW TRUCK AFTER LAPD OPEN FIRE ON WOMENS TRUCK WITHOUT WARNING</Title><Msg>LAPD BUYS WOMEN A NEW TRUCK AFTER LAPD OPEN FIRE ON WOMENS TRUCK WITHOUT WARNING WHILE LAPD TRYING TO KILL CHRIS DORNER (only problem is the LAPD shot the wrong truck with hundreds of rounds of ammo). The women were actually shot. LAPD wants women to pay sales tax on the truck. This new truck does not compensate the women for their medical bills. Heck Rodney King got millions in his lawsuit for just a beating. LAPD does not have the right to pepper any vehicle with machine gun fire just because they want to murder another cop. LAPD job is to arrest people not send a swat team hit squad after people.</Msg><Username>zombies_want_to_eat_brains</Username><Timestamp>1363506613007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:50:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363507266066-2</Id><Topic><Title>LAPD BUYS WOMEN NEW TRUCK AFTER LAPD OPEN FIRE ON WOMENS TRUCK WITHOUT WARNING</Title><Username>zombies_want_to_eat_brains</Username><Timestamp>1363506613007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>These women should pay the sales tax on the truck. If you won a truck on a game show you would have to pay the sales tax on the truck. If a white person was shot by LAPD swat team with hundreds of rounds of ammo emptied into the white persons truck and the LAPD bought the white person a new truck the white person would have to pay the sales tax on the new truck. Because these women were mexicans they dont have to pay the sales tax on the truck.and win the truck for free. The LAPD was out to get a cop killer and feared for their lives so they opened fire on the first blue truck that they saw. That is how they are trained.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1363507266066</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:01:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363507376991-3</Id><Topic><Title>LAPD BUYS WOMEN NEW TRUCK AFTER LAPD OPEN FIRE ON WOMENS TRUCK WITHOUT WARNING</Title><Username>zombies_want_to_eat_brains</Username><Timestamp>1363506613007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Too many people are sue happy and file frivolous lawsuits for economic gain.</Msg><Username>republicans_rnot_people_persons</Username><Timestamp>1363507376991</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363508790825-4</Id><Title>ANOTHER DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED THIS TIME FOR DRUGGING PRESCHOOLERS WITH SLEEPING PILLS</Title><Msg>From ABC news: "A teacher at a Morgan Hill, Calif., preschool has been arrested after the school accused her of slipping sleeping pills in sippy cups of children under the age of 2. “We do not know the quantity, but we believe she was breaking the pill into smaller pieces and putting it into the children’s sippy cups,” Morgan Hill Sgt. of Investigations Troy Hoefling told ABC News. The school told ABC News it had “terminated” Debbie Gratz, 59, last Friday “for failure to follow Kiddie Academy standards and processes.” “Ms. Gratz was witnessed adding a substance to the water cups for her classroom of 10 children,” Morgan Hill Kiddie Academy added in a prepared statement. “The cups were confiscated before they came in contact with any children prior to the academy opening for business that day.”</Msg><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1363508790825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:26:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363509388051-5</Id><Title>SCHOOL PAYS $10.8 MILLION TO CHILDREN MOLESTED BY 3rd GRADE UNION TEACHER Mark Berndt</Title><Msg>From Edmonton Journal: "The Los Angeles school district will pay millions of dollars to settle claims and lawsuits filed by students and families from an elementary school where a third-grade teacher was accused of spoon-feeding children semen in what he called "tasting games," lawyers in the cases said Tuesday. District officials did not reveal the total amount of the settlement, but attorney Raymond Boucher, who represents several Miramonte Elementary School students, said each claimant will receive $470,000. District General Counsel David Holmquist said the settlement covers 58 of the 191 claims and lawsuits filed by students and parents against the district after the January 2012 arrest of former third-grade teacher Mark Berndt on 23 charges of lewd behaviour spanning five years at Miramonte." Read full story at the Edmonton Journal news website.</Msg><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1363509388051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:36:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363522317426-6</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I agree with this report</Msg><Username>harrisedgar953</Username><Timestamp>1363522317426</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:11:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363524073456-7</Id><Title>This weeks winner</Title><Msg>1. Erik Rush This week’s “winner” is right-wing conspiracy theorist Erik Rush, who went on Alan Colmes’ radio show last Friday to defend his paranoid ravings. According to Rush, Obama is a “Marxist dictator” who is planning to impose martial law and cancel the 2016 election so he can stay in office. When Colmes pressed Rush on how likely this scenario is, Rush replied “Oh geez… I dunno, I’d say 50 percent.” If it’s any consolation to Colmes, this was only the second-craziest interview that he’s taken part in this month.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363524073456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:41:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363527179007-8</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy workin' hard to become an historic president...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363483147969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 21:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bill Clinton the Cigar Sex expert with Monica. *** That's wasn't cigar juice on her dress. She worshipped Slick Willie just like Junior worships Obama, the first gay president and biggest fraud ever perpetrated upon the American people. He's not black. He's Indonesian. He's not Kenyan. He's Keynesian.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363527179007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:32:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363527359038-9</Id><Topic><Title>This will make your day</Title><Username>emsggim</Username><Timestamp>1363490103964</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 23:15:03 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Looks like great short. Earnings have topped out and airline businesses haven't been profitable for 30 years. All airlines go bankrupt.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363527359038</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:35:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363527543699-10</Id><Topic><Title>This weeks winner</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363524073456</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 08:41:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a “Marxist dictator” who is planning to impose martial law and cancel the 2016 election so he can stay in office. *** It happened in Venezuela, it could happen here. We're a Banana Republic. We went from world's largest creditor nation to world largest debtor nation. Obama just needs to replace two Supremes with libs and he is ruler for life. Hitler changed his name. Hitler hid his birth certificate.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363527543699</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:39:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528006438-11</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Anybody id ever going to vote for Obama again! Junior thought I made a mistake with that statement. He could change the Constitution to remove term limits so he could be re-elected. All he has to do is replace two Supremes with libs. Americans are stupid. Hugo Chavez did it. Hitler did it. Hitler changed his name. Hitler hid his birth certificate. Hitler promised the German people that the government would "make use of these powers only insofar as they are essential for carrying out vitally necessary measures...The number of cases in which an internal necessity exists for having recourse to such a law is in itself a limited one." So the German congress voted on the bill, with the end result being the legal destruction of the German Democratic Republic. The bill gave Hitler enormous, unprecedented powers to do as he saw fit for the government of the German people. It was the act that offically created a legal dictator who was answerable to no one. The people cheered, and National Socialism became the law of the land from that day forward Today, Barack Obama is changing times and laws in America, giving himself unprecedented power never before seen. His ObamaCare bill. now the law of the land, empowers him to create his own private army, forces citizens to abide by unconstitutional laws, and will use the IRS in much the same way that Hitler used his brown shirts to make people get in line behind his policies. Many Americans will awake too late to the fact that Obama has subverted the United States Constitution, and stolen our precious liberties and freedoms. That's why Obama's followers are encouraged and taught to follow and have faith in Obama the man, and not in our God or in our country. This is exactly the ploy that Hitler used to great and terrible effect in #$%$ Germany. Obama went to Notre Dame and Georgetown -- the two oldest Catholic institutions in America -- to promote anti-Catholic morals; abortion and birth control. He is not Christian.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363528006438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:46:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528089496-12</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is worse than Bush. Obama = Nixon = Hitler. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363528089496</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:48:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528175766-13</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy workin' hard to become an historic president...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363483147969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 21:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is a lying Ir*ish bas*tud fraud. Happy St. Patrick's Day.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363528175766</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:49:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363528398494-14</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy workin' hard to become an historic president...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363483147969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 21:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior would like to have some of Obama's juice on his tonsils.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528398494</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 09:53:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363528827392-15</Id><Title>True to his word</Title><Msg>Remember Obama telling the Russians he'd be more " flexible "after the elections. Today he canceled deployment of missile interceptors in Eastern Europe. Just what the Russians wanted him to do.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363530678549-16</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Remember Obama telling the Russians he'd be more " flexible "after the elections. Today he canceled deployment of missile interceptors in Eastern Europe. Just what the Russians wanted him to do. *** WOW! No debate? Two dictators making their own non-aggression agreement. Sounds like Hitler and Mussolini all over again.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363530678549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363530689825-17</Id><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Msg>and drove prices of food out of reach for hundreds of millions of third world people, causing millions to die? Funny the tin foil hats didn't mind the Gov spending billions on that. Backed by government subsidies and mandates, hundreds of ethanol plants rose among the golden fields of the Corn Belt, bringing jobs and business to small towns, providing farmers with a new market for their crops and generating billions of dollars in revenue for the producers of this corn-based fuel blend. Those days of promise and prosperity are vanishing. Nearly 10 percent of the nation’s ethanol plants have stopped production over the past year, in part because the drought that has ravaged much of the nation’s crops has pushed commodity prices so high that ethanol has become too expensive to produce.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363530856395-18</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Great point!!! How stupid of Obama to deploy those defenses against North Korea, LOL the tin foil hats are out in force. LOL Russian officials here have so far declined to comment on the announcement, which was made in Washington on Friday by Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel as part of a plan to deploy additional ballistic missile interceptors to counter North Korea. The cancellation of some European-based defenses will allow resources to be shifted to protect against North Korea.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530856395</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:34:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363531115035-19</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior, I saw your picture -- Obama youth pledging allegiance to Obama and promoting his agenda. Slurping every word. Tastee!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363531115035</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:38:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363531349574-20</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior is a member of Obama Youth (brown shirts) "We cannot continue to rely on our military in order to achieve the national security objectives we've set. We've got to have a civilian national security force that's just as powerful, just as strong, just as well-funded." Barack Obama A remarkable aspect of both the personalities of Hitler and Obama is that they both put heavy emphasis on getting the children and young people on board. If a regime is to be successfull, it is imperative that the leaders have the next generation waiting in the wings to carry on the work as the people at the top either step down, or are "forcibly retired." Obama's gun control gives power to the Obama Youth. Most Obama voters already have guns. Your out numbered.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363531349574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:42:29 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363531411013-21</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ya, and when Obama took over during Bush's Great Depression he has singlehandidly made Amerika the leading producer of energy in the world, not bad for a Kenyan communist, huh!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363531411013</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:43:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363531474392-22</Id><Title>Happy Sunday</Title><Msg>Happy Sunday. “We have a new Pope. The Vatican has chosen the first ever Argentinean Pope. So once again, a bunch of old white guys got a Hispanic to do a job they didn’t want to do.” –Conan O’Brien “Thousands and thousands of people at Vatican Square were looking at the chimney. And the white smoke means we have a white Pope.” –David Letterman “What do we know about Pope Francis? Well, he’s 76 years old. He’s a former archbishop, and he likes long walks on the beach, giant hats, and the music of Coldplay.” –Craig Ferguson “With the selection process going on for the new Pope, there’s a lot of papal trivial. For example, did you know that no Pope has ever in the history of the church been elected without carrying Ohio?” –David Letterman “The cardinals each write down their choice on a small slip of paper and put in a silver chalice and then they mix all the names up and they’re drawn out. It’s the same thing they do for the Vatican’s Secret Santa.” –David Letterman “The nation of Iran is threatening to sue the makers of the movie “Argo.” They say the movie was an unrealistic portrayal of their country. You can’t do that! That would be like Scotland suing over the movie ‘Shrek.’” –Craig Ferguson “After tours of the White House were canceled due to budget cuts, Donald Trump offered to pay for them. All he’s asking is they rename it the Trump White House and Casino.” –Conan O’Brien “They’re calling it Obama’s charm offensive because he took Republicans to dinner, and then he had Paul Ryan over for lunch. And it’s working apparently. This has been the problem all along. Republicans will put out, you just have to buy them a meal and tell them they are pretty first.” –Bill Maher “Two key questions emerged from the dinner: 1) whether anything can get done without the Republican leadership; and 2) why do John McCain and Lindsey Graham always go to the bathroom in pairs. I’m just going to call them McCainsey from now on.” –Bill Maher “President Obama to</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363531474392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:44:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363532343771-23</Id><Title>Krazy Canadian</Title><Msg>Every single week, Republican Senator Ted Cruz takes his crazy up to a new level. Rep. Joaquin Castro put it well: “Republicans in Texas have gone off the rails. More folks are waking up and realizing these folks have gone too far.” Every time you look at the news, Cruz is embarrassing Texas in new ways. When he’s not hanging out with his friends Sarah Palin and Donald Trump at CPAC, Cruz is acting crazy in the Senate. In a recent debate about assault weapons, Cruz got into a fight with Senator Feinstein. Senator Feinstein became mayor of San Francisco after Harvey Milk and Mayor Moscone were shot and killed in City Hall. She saw their bullet-riddled bodies. She broke the news to the public. She has sat on the Senate Judiciary Committee for twenty years. Cruz decided he needed to give her a lecture to explain the Constitution and guns. Republican Joe Scarborough gave a fierce and impassioned response to Cruz’s lecture, calling it, among other things, “complete and utter ignorance.” “I am not a sixth grader,” Senator Dianne Feinstein replied. “I am reasonably well-educated, and I thank you for the lecture.” As one news outlet put it: She looked, really, like she might throw some water in his face Don’t us Texans know that feeling! Cruz is setting new records for crazy. Yesterday Dana Milbank wrote in the Washington Post that Cruz’s actions in the Senate are essentially the same as inmates running an insane asylum. And when Senator John McCain recently referring to Cruz as a “wacko bird,” you know we’ve crossed into some seriously crazy territory! That’s our representation in the Senate. It doesn’t have to always be this way. We have an upcoming Senate race in 2014, and then we can replace Cruz in 2018. But there’s a lot of work we need to do first.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363532343771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:59:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363532563809-24</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>By those that practice it, it is called a "religion of peace". There are those, however, who would disagree with that statement. Some people see the Muslims as an angry, violent people who use the two-fold method of Jihad and Fatah to further their geo-politcals plans, and sadly, the vast majority of people both here in America and abroad, remain blissfully ignorant of the ever-swelling tide of Muslim cultural expansion. In this lesson we will show you, mostly in their own words and pictures, just exactly what the goal of Islam really is. We will not defame, demean or otherwise say anything that is not true about the position they hold. We will show you their words, photos of them in "action", and let you make up your mind about what Islam is really all about. A picture is worth a 1,000 words A quick Google images search of the words Islam will dominate gives you quite the eyeful. It shows very quickly photos from around the world of Muslims carrying signs and banners that proclaim things like "freedom can go to hell", "Islam will dominate the world", and "Shariah law - the true solution", as well as many other cute little tag lines. My first take on that is that it doesn't seem overly friendly. Americans are stupid,</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363532563809</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:02:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363532965637-25</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Koran The Muslim "holy" book, the Koran, is filled with words of wisdom on how Muslims should live their lives, and how they should interact with those around them. The following is just a few quotes taken directly from the Koran. Just let the reassuring, calming words of the Prophet Muhhamed and his "religion of peace" wash over you like gentle rain from above. On Interacting with Jews and Christians "O you who believe! do not take the Jews and the Christians for friends; they are friends of each other; and whoever amongst you takes them for a friend, then surely he is one of them; surely Allah does not guide the unjust people." (Sura 5, verse 51). "And the Jews say: Uzair is the son of Allah; and the Christians say: The Messiah is the son of Allah; these are the words of their mouths; they imitate the saying of those who disbelieved before; may Allah DESTROY them; how they are turned away!" (Sura 9, verse 30). "And the Jews will not be pleased with you, nor the Christians until you follow their religion. Say: Surely Allah's guidance, that is the (true) guidance. And if you follow their desires after the knowledge that has come to you, you shall have no guardian from Allah, nor any helper." (Sura 2, verse 120). On Living In Peace With Non-Muslims "And KILL them (the unbelievers) wherever you find them, and drive them out from whence they drove you out, and persecution is severer than slaughter, and do not fight with them at the Sacred Mosque until they fight with you in it, but if they do fight you, then slay them; such is the recompense of the unbelievers." (Sura 2, verse 191). "Let not the believers take the unbelievers for friends rather than believers; and whoever does this, he shall have nothing of (the guardianship of) Allah, but you should guard yourselves against them, guarding carefully; and Allah makes you cautious of (retribution from) Himself; and to Allah is the eventual coming." (Sura 3, verse 28). Obama learned the Koran as a boy.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363532965637</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:09:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533247278-26</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama is fulfilling prophesy this week. A War Unlike Any Other War In World History But the Bible tells us that in the End Times, there will be another "world war", and it will be led by Russia, Iran, and a group of other nations that surround the nation of Israel, to plunder her resources and steal her wealth. We find this prophecy in the 38th chapter of the book of Ezekiel - "And the word of the LORD came unto me, saying, Son of man, set thy face against Gog (Russia), the land of Magog, the chief prince of Meshech and Tubal, and prophesy against him, And say, Thus saith the Lord GOD; Behold, I [am] against thee, O Gog, the chief prince of Meshech and Tubal: And I will turn thee back, and put hooks into thy jaws, and I will bring thee forth, and all thine army, horses and horsemen, all of them clothed with all sorts [of armour, even] a great company [with] bucklers and shields, all of them handling swords: Persia, Ethiopia, and Libya with them; all of them with shield and helmet: Gomer, and all his bands; the house of Togarmah of the north quarters, and all his bands: [and] many people with thee... More than 2,500 years ago, a captive of the Babylonian Empire named Ezekiel penned a prophecy, dated for some future era called "the latter days," saying an alliance will arise, which Ezekiel calls collectively, "Gog, the land of Magog, the ruler of Rosh, Meschech and Tubal." It, together with an alliance led by Persia, including Turkey, makes up much of the Baltic region and the Mediterranean Middle East. ...And it shall come to pass at the same time when Gog shall come against the land of Israel, saith the Lord GOD, [that] my fury shall come up in my face." Ezekiel 38</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363533247278</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:14:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533429729-27</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The major nations that will attack Israel, and they are: • Magog - this is modern day Russia • Persia - this is modern day Iran • Meshech and Tubal, Togarmah - this region is modern day Turkey • Ethiopia - this is modern Ethiopia • Libya - this is modern day Libya • Gomer - this is modern day Germany While there is slight debate among bible scholars, the above list represents the best consensus of the identity of the nations in Ezekiel 38. Suffice to say that the main players, of which there is no doubt, are Russia, Iran, Turkey, Libya and Ethiopia. Now if we were living in the End Times, there would have to be a growing union between the biggest players in this group. A quick look at some recent headlines tells us this: • Russia, the biggest End Times player, has already helped Iran build a nuclear reactor • Iran has repeated over and over their desire to wipe Israel off the map • Iran now has nuclear weapons capable of reaching Israel These nations will attack Israel, the bible says, "To take a spoil, and to take a prey; to turn thine hand upon the desolate places [that are now] inhabited, and upon the people [that are] gathered out of the nations, which have gotten cattle and goods, that dwell in the midst of the land." Ezekiel 38:12 Bin Ladin Moo*slime terrorists attacked USA on 9/11 for USA support of Israel.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363533429729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:17:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533660666-28</Id><Topic><Title>Cisco Systems Insider Trading Reported</Title><Username>isaiahlyons50</Username><Timestamp>1361369710669</Timestamp><DateTime>Wed, 2013-02-20 09:15:10 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect</Msg><Username>hobert.stockton</Username><Timestamp>1363533660666</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:21:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533707191-29</Id><Topic><Title>MAD MONEY FEATURES Cisco Systems. Strong buy recommended!!</Title><Username>paulhall367</Username><Timestamp>1361793645201</Timestamp><DateTime>Mon, 2013-02-25 07:00:45 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>perfect</Msg><Username>hobert.stockton</Username><Timestamp>1363533707191</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:21:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363533995917-30</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are you really certain that the West, particularly the U.S., will not come to Israel's defense during the War of Gog and Magog? Given the historically strong and strategic relationship between our two countries, that just doesn't seem possible. Unfortunately, Ezekiel's account is clear--no one comes to Israel's defense. By definition, that includes the United States. I agree that is difficult to imagine, especially when one considers how consistent American public opinion has been in favor of the Jewish state over the past four decades. You can't trust Obama. He just gave the Muslim Brotherhood 1/2 a Billion dollars of taxpayers money and shut down the White House to save $12 Million. Sounds like bull*sheet to me. Obama a trained bul#$%$. Everything out of his mouth is bull*sheet. You can't trust Obama.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363533995917</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:26:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363534864459-31</Id><Topic><Title>trong Performance By Auto Sector Another Sign Of Improving Economy CHRISTOPHER S. RUGABER WASHINGTON (AP) — A strong increase in auto ou</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_5</Username><Timestamp>1363364215540</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 12:16:55 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>They have found 15,000,000,000 cubic feet of natural gas in Israel, watch for oil to be discovered next. Using tracking, they can tap the same reservoir of oil that Iraq, Iran, Saudi's have been tapping. The world has massive amounts of oil. It's formed by natural processes. It's not all dinosaurs. Around the world, as soon as Noble goes to a place, many other companies follow in its wake. The prospects here are amazing, and I have no doubt that we'll see an economic boom, and a rush of more companies to Israel from overseas following Noble." The U.S. Geological Survey estimates that 122 trillion cubic feet of undiscovered, recoverable natural gas are in the Levant Basin Province in the eastern Mediterranean region, according to a new report. The area includes the coastal areas near Israel, Lebanon and Syria.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363534864459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:41:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363534964490-32</Id><Topic><Title>NEW POPE: "SAME SEX MARRIAGE IS MACHINATIONS OF FATHER OF LIES"</Title><Username>maxedout333</Username><Timestamp>1363360565854</Timestamp><DateTime>Fri, 2013-03-15 11:16:05 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New Pope says politicians like Obama who promote gay marriage, abortion and birth control are doing the devil's work. They are not Christians. Obama is a Moos*lime. He is a divisive, negative, lying Ir*sh bas*tud fraud. Happy St. Patrick's Day.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363534964490</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:42:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363535253474-33</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Unfortunatly, obama also supports ethanol because he is from illinois, the home of archer daninals midland, ethanol's prime beneficary.</Msg><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1363535253474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:47:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363535362841-34</Id><Topic><Title>Happy Sunday</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363531474392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:44:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>“Republicans in Arkansas passed the strictest abortion law ever…they say in the bill that life begins when your sister gets drunk.” –Bill Maher</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363535362841</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:49:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363535371019-35</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Guess Dumb is admitting Obama can only handle one problem at a time. Good thing he wasn't president when we had to fight Germany and Japan at the same time. Wonder which one he'd have retaliated against?</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363535371019</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:49:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363535687914-36</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>New technology and drilling on private land has increased U.S. oil production,not Obama. Quit drinking the kool-ade and do some research.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363535687914</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 11:54:47 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363536985161-37</Id><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Msg>From the March 6, 2013, edition of “Viewpoint.” John Fugelsang: So for tonight’s F-bomb, we cover a little-covered report that affects all of us. Because it’s from Stuart Bowen. He’s the special inspector general for Iraq reconstruction. And that’s more than just a sexy title — he’s the guy whose job it is to officially notify Congress about how much of our money was spent on the Iraq invasion and occupation and reconstruction. Now, Bowen just reported that maybe, just maybe, the Iraq War wasn’t a great idea from a money perspective. I could quote you highlights from the report: how the reconstruction “grew to a size much larger than was ever anticipated” or how “not enough was accomplished for the size of the funds extended.” Wow. Who knew? And he’s just talking about the $60 billion of U.S. taxpayer money that went to Iraq reconstruction projects. I’d like to repeat that figure, since we’re all so busy arguing about the budget deficit in this country: $60 billion, or $15 million per day. Just to give you some scale, that’s more than Current TV pays me in a whole month. And it’s relevant. Under the austerity politics of D.C., we have Democrats and mostly Republicans now telling us how we have to cut spending to rebuild America after 10 years of nonstop spending to rebuild Iraq after we blew it up. So let’s go back, through the mists of time, to 10 years ago this month. Back when Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld and his capo de tutti capi Paul Wolfowitz were telling us how invading Iraq would pay for itself. And then once we were there they said we couldn’t leave because then Iran would invade Iraq and create the new Islamo-fascist supergroup “Iranq.” Meanwhile, the people who were against the invasion said it would kill a lot of soldiers, would kill even more Iraqis and would only succeed in making a few U.S. businessmen and international oil companies very, very rich. So who was right? Well, according to the report, the American taxpayer spe</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537206534-38</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yes unfortunately big money owns the Gov</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363537206534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:20:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537445848-39</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>When you are done whining about Iraq, lets talk about LBJ's war in Vietnam and the money spent and lives lost. Both wars were giant mistakes but to keep wailing about something you cant change is silly.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363537445848</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:24:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537454876-40</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>nice one</Msg><Username>jose.delmonte</Username><Timestamp>1363537454876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:24:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537704561-41</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Yes, and as added bonus neither kerry or the Kenyan communist will sign off on the Keystone pipeline. Drill Here, Drill Now!</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363537704561</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:28:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363537868679-42</Id><Topic><Title>Remember when Bush pushed through massive subsidies for ethanol</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363530689825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:31:29 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama will approve the pipeline within the next two weeks. Remember my post.</Msg><Username>hairyroid</Username><Timestamp>1363537868679</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:31:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363538338155-43</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumbivan doesn' think before he posts. He just automatically defends Obama. Dumbivan is a retired or unemployed old black man with nothing to do but post here 24/7. He lies about fancy vacations and wealth when its obvious none of it is true. Sad, really.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363538338155</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:38:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363538788610-44</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah when the GOP defunded the SEC and the IRS prosecutions declined, you are right</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363538788610</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:46:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363539176559-45</Id><Title>Rob Portman</Title><Msg>WASHINGTON (The Borowitz Report)—The decision of Sen. Rob Portman (R-Ohio) to support same-sex marriage after learning that his son was gay has inspired hundreds of other Republican lawmakers to stop speaking to their children immediately, G.O.P. leaders confirmed today. “I have gathered my caucus and told them, if your kids are going to tell you something that’s going to cost you the next election, it’s better to nip that situation in the bud,” said House Speaker John Boehner (R-Ohio). “Just stop talking to them altogether, for heaven’s sakes.” Speaker Boehner said he was advising his fellow Republicans who were “hell bent on speaking to their children” to keep things superficial: “You can talk about sports. You can talk about the weather.Â But anything beyond that, your policy should be, ‘Don’t ask, don’t tell.’” But even as Mr. Boehner laid down the new guidelines for not speaking to one’s children, House Majority Leader Eric Cantor (R-Virginia) said that the policy “doesn’t go far enough.” “What if you’re having a conversation with your kids and it turns out they’re in favor of raising the capital-gains tax or banning assault rifles?” he said. “Do what I do—block their calls.” Senate Minority Leader Mitch McConnell (R-Kentucky) agreed with his fellow G.O.P. leaders’ words of caution, adding, “Fortunately, none of my children want to talk to me.”</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363539176559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:52:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363539662461-46</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bush is gone and we need to bust Pelosi: Pelsoi, along with many other democrats. there is plenty of video of them fully supporting the Iraq invasion... and they even state that they've "seen the evidence" about Saddam, WMDs, etc.</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363539662461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:01:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363541662461-47</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah Bush said there were definitely weapons of mass destruction, if you objected and said you wanted to wait for the UN to approve intervention your career was destroyed (see Valerie Plame) you were told you were un-American, you were a traitor and you didn't support the troops. the neocons didn't just lie, they were immoral, criminal and outright stupid, lead by the biggest Presidential Moron in History</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363541662461</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:34:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363542200444-48</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Traitors who didn't support the troops? Are you old enough to remember how democrats and liberals treated the troops during the Vietnam era. LBJ and the dems got us into that and the crazies took it out on the returning servicemen.</Msg><Username>crankf41</Username><Timestamp>1363542200444</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 13:43:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363543411493-49</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>At his first Sunday Angelus prayer, Pope Francis said "A bit of mercy can make the world less cold and fairer. Have a good Sunday." Merkel and Biden will attend the Pope's inauguration mass. Obama wouldn't dare attend.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363543411493</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:03:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363544269623-50</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior, your desperate attempts to try to re-write history by repeating falsehoods is the same technique used by Hitler and Obama. You are a pathetic deluded clown.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363544269623</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 14:17:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363546888210-51</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah Jr. you and the Christian Science Monitor are trying to rewrite history!!! I remember distinctly Bush and Cheney saying the war would cost us Trillions of Dollars, it would last 10 years, it would be humanitarian disaster and there really weren't WMD's now your trying to rewrite history!!! Would the war be cheap and would Iraq pay for it? The projections: Ahead of and shortly after the US invasion of Iraq in 2003, a number of officials, including former Defense Secretary Donald Rumsfeld and his deputy Paul Wolfowitz suggested the war could be done on the cheap and that it would largely pay for itself. In October 2003, Rumsfeld told a press conference about President Bush's request for $21 billion for Iraq and Afghan reconstruction that "the $20 billion the president requested is not intended to cover all of Iraq's needs. The bulk of the funds for Iraq's reconstruction will come from Iraqis -- from oil revenues, recovered assets, international trade, direct foreign investment, as well as some contributions we've already received and hope to receive from the international community." In March 2003, Mr. Wolfowitz told Congress that "we're really dealing with a country that could finance its own reconstruction." In April 2003, the Pentagon said the war would cost about $2 billion a month, and in July of that year Rumsfeld increased that estimate to $4 billion.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363546888210</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:01:28 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363546976550-52</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO CEO Buying Shares!</Title><Username>vincent.middleton</Username><Timestamp>1362511286358</Timestamp><DateTime>Tue, 2013-03-05 14:21:26 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Thanks.</Msg><Username>haugpaul</Username><Timestamp>1363546976550</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:02:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363547059170-53</Id><Title>pretty funny</Title><Msg>how the tea baggers didn't worry about blowing 4 trillion dollars on unnecessary, unjustified wars but are all upset over 60 billion spent supporting the police, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363547059170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:04:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363547380521-54</Id><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Msg>DNC worrying that Obama's cratering poll numbers will cost them seats in 2014. Meanwhile Junior continues to babble that his numbers aren't important since he isn't running in 2016. Wonder who is right?LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363547545981-55</Id><Topic><Title>pretty funny</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363547059170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>9/11 response was justified an necessary. Rumsfeld created two monsters (Saddam and Bin Laden) to fight Iran (the Iran-Iraq War) and then they got out of control. Bush got Saddam. Seals got Bin Laden and the CIA got Gadaffi. Benghazi was the start of the next phase. You are ignorant lemming Obama Youth.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363547545981</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:12:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363547942073-56</Id><Topic><Title>pretty funny</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363547059170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama says the wars cost a little over one trillion. Are you calling him a liar ? No doubt it was a wasted trillion...just tell the truth,chump, not that far left propaganda.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547942073</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:19:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363548212978-57</Id><Topic><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You're the dimwit. He is dropping in every segment of his polls. Do you think the DNC are dimwits? Why are they worried.Wow, are you stupid!!</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363548212978</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:23:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363548374881-58</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bump for the old black guy. lol</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363548374881</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:26:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363549766573-59</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hey, Pecker-wood -- read as soon as you and Junior stop Gerbiling: Why did Bill Clinton, Hillary, John Kerry, and Nancy Pelosi LIE about WMD's in Iraq? "The community of nations may see more and more of the very kind of threat Iraq poses now: a rogue state with weapons of mass destruction, ready to use them or provide them to terrorists. If we fail to respond today, Saddam and all those who would follow in his footsteps will be emboldened tomorrow." -- Bill Clinton in 1998 "In the four years since the inspectors left, intelligence reports show that Saddam Hussein has worked to rebuild his chemical and biological weapons stock, his missile delivery capability, and his nuclear program. He has also given aid, comfort, and sanctuary to terrorists, including Al Qaeda members, though there is apparently no evidence of his involvement in the terrible events of September 11, 2001. It is clear, however, that if left unchecked, Saddam Hussein will continue to increase his capacity to wage biological and chemical warfare, and will keep trying to develop nuclear weapons. Should he succeed in that endeavor, he could alter the political and security landscape of the Middle East, which as we know all too well affects American security." -- Hillary Clinton, October 10, 2002 "I will be voting to give the president of the United States the authority to use force - if necessary - to disarm Saddam Hussein because I believe that a deadly arsenal of weapons of mass destruction in his hands is a real and grave threat to our security." -- John F. Kerry, Oct 2002 "The threat of Saddam Hussein with weapons of mass destruction is real, but as I said, it is not new. It has been with us since the end of that war, and particularly in the last 4 years we know after Operation Desert Fox failed to force him to reaccept them, that he has continued to build those weapons. He has had a free hand for 4 years to reconstitute these weapons, allowing the world, during the interval, to lose the focus we had on weapons of mass destruction and the issue of proliferation." -- John Kerry, October 9, 2002 "As a member of the House Intelligence Committee, I am keenly aware that the proliferation of chemical and biological weapons is an issue of grave importance to all nations. Saddam Hussein has been engaged in the development of weapons of mass destruction technology which is a threat to countries in the region and he has made a mockery of the weapons inspection process." -- Nancy Pelosi, December 16, 1998</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363549766573</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:49:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363549868041-60</Id><Topic><Title>pretty funny</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363547059170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>well doremi I think Obama was making a reference to how much direct costs we have spent I don't think he was including all the interest expense and ongoing vet expenses, thanks for playing and keeping this alive WASHINGTON -- The United States will have spent a total of $3.7 trillion on wars in Iraq, Afghanistan and Pakistan, costing 225,000 lives and creating 7.8 million refugees, by the time the conflicts end, according to a report released on Wednesday by Brown University. The report, written by more than 20 economists, political scientists, lawyers, anthropologists and humanitarian personnel for Brown's Watson Institute for International Studies, gives staggering estimates for the cost of military action in those three countries. Nearly ten years since U.S. troops first entered Afghanistan, the report estimates the final cost of all three conflicts will be between $3.7 trillion and $4.4 trillion -- far higher than the $1 trillion price tag referenced by President Barack Obama earlier this year. The report estimates the U.S. government has already spent between $2.3 trillion to $2.7 trillion and will spend at least a trillion more over the next fifty years. Long-term obligations to war veterans will cause the price tag of the conflicts to climb for decades after troops have returned home. The report puts the cost of health care for veterans at between $600 to $950 billion, not peaking until the 2050s. "Wars, in a sense, are never over when they're over," Catherine Lutz, a Brown University anthropologist, said in the video op-ed. "They go on for decades, and the peak costs for this war will be incurred forty years from now." Costs of War: 225,000 Lives and up to US$4 Trillion from Watson Institute on Vimeo.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363549868041</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:51:08 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363549984724-61</Id><Topic><Title>pretty funny</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363547059170</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:04:19 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Well actually it is 5.4 trillion when you add in the interest expense, thanks W Because the wars have had no true front-lines, there have been a huge number of injuries, primarily to young people serving in the military. There has been a particularly large amount of casualties in Pakistan, the report says. "The costs have been borne unevenly," Lutz said. "The military families, contractor families, the people of Iraq and Afghanistan and Pakistan, have borne a tremendous cost." Even just paying the interest on the United States' war debt will be a large endeavor, according to the report, at a time when the country is set to exceed its current debt limit of $14.29 trillion. The government has already paid about $185 billion in interest on war spending, and could accrue another $1 trillion -- an amount not included in the $3.7 trillion estimate -- in interest by 2020, according to the report. "We have borrowed virtually all of the money that has been used to pay for the Iraq and Afghanistan conflicts, and that has been very expensive, adding at least $1.5 trillion to our national debt," Linda Bilmes, an economist with Harvard University, said in the video op-ed. Now the country is at a decision point, aligned with the current showdown over a deal to raise the debt ceiling by August. "There is immense and urgent requirement to learn from the experience of the past decade and to try to ensure we don't make the same mistakes all over again," Andrew Bacevich, a Boston University military historian and veteran, said in the video.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363549984724</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:53:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363550660378-62</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Who thought the President Bush and Vice President Cheney would out right lie to fight a war Cheney Admits that He Lied about 9/11 Posted on March 8, 2013 by WashingtonsBlog What Else Did He Lie About? The New York Times’ Maureen Dowd writes today: In a documentary soon to appear on Showtime, “The World According to #$%$ Cheney,” [Cheney said] “I got on the telephone with the president, who was in Florida, and told him not to be at one location where we could both be taken out.” Mr. Cheney kept W. flying aimlessly in the air on 9/11 while he and Lynn left on a helicopter for a secure undisclosed location, leaving Washington in a bleak, scared silence, with no one reassuring the nation in those first terrifying hours. “I gave the instructions that we’d authorize our pilots to take it out,” he says, referring to the jet headed to Washington that crashed in a Pennsylvania field. He adds: “After I’d given the order, it was pretty quiet. Everybody had heard it, and it was obviously a significant moment.” *** When they testified together before the 9/11 Commission, W. and Mr. Cheney kept up a pretense that in a previous call, the president had authorized the vice president to give a shoot-down order if needed. But the commission found “no documentary evidence for this call.” In other words, Cheney pretended that Bush had authorized a shoot-down order, but Cheney now admits that he never did. In fact, Cheney acted as if he was the president on 9/11. * Cheney lied about numerous other facts related to 9/11 as well. For example, Cheney: Falsely linked Iraq with 9/11 (indeed, the entire torture program was aimed at establishing such a false linkage; and Cheney is the guy who pushed for torture, pressured the Justice Department lawyers to write memos saying torture was legal, and made the pitch to Congress justifying torture. The former director of the CIA said Cheney oversaw American torture policies) Falsely claimed that spying on Americans, torture, the Patriot Act,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363550660378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:04:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363550858794-63</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Falsely claimed that spying on Americans, torture, the Patriot Act, the Afghanistan war, the Iraq war and the “war on terror” were all necessitated by 9/11 … when all of them started or were planned before 9/11 Falsely stated that an attack such as 9/11 was unforeseeable, when Al Qaeda flying planes into the World Trade Center and Pentagon was something which American military and intelligence services – and our allies – knew could happen Falsely pretended that he was out of the loop during the 9/11 attacks Falsely blamed others for 9/11, when Cheney was in charge of all of America’s counter-terrorism exercises, activities and responses on 9/11. See this Department of State announcement and this CNN article … … And when Cheney was apparently responsible for letting the Pentagon get hit by an airplane (confirmed here and here) And was instrumental in squashing a real investigation into 9/11 * Indeed, Cheney initiated Continuity of Government plans on 9/11 which essentially nullified America’s constitutional form of government.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363550858794</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:07:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363551739370-64</Id><Topic><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Post to the DNC. They are the ones worried, not me. Tell them you said everything is okay.LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363551739370</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:22:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363551770282-65</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Oh, you forgot this one -- the Gebiling has affected your research? ***“I come to this debate, Mr. Speaker, as one at the end of 10 years in office on the Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, where stopping the proliferation of weapons of mass destruction was one of my top priorities. I applaud the President on focusing on this issue and on taking the lead to disarm Saddam Hussein.… Others have talked about this threat that is posed by Saddam Hussein. Yes, he has chemical weapons, he has biological weapons, he is trying to get nuclear weapons.” Congresswoman Nancy Pelosi (Democrat, California) Addressing the US House of Representatives October 10, 2002 Congressional Record, p. H7777</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363551770282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:22:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363551784800-66</Id><Title>Meanwhile in the real world!! LOL</Title><Msg>Republican National Committee Chairman Reince Priebus says the GOP has an image problem. “We've done a really lousy job of branding and marketing who we are,” Priebus said on CBS. Most have an image of the GOP as a room full of “stuffy old guys” but the “reality is we have a very young party,” he added. Priebus went on CBS to talk about the long-anticipated RNC report that will be released Monday and will detail just how the GOP can reverse its fortunes after the November defeats. LOL yeah a real young party!!! But in the real world NEW YORK -- Young voters represented a greater share of the national electorate Tuesday than four years ago, once again voting for President Barack Obama by a huge margin, boosting his reelection. Voters from ages 18 to 29 represented 19 percent of all those who voted on Tuesday, according to the early National Exit Poll conducted by Edison Research. That's an increase of one percentage point from 2008. Obama captured 60 percent youth vote, compared with Mitt Romney's 36 percent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363551784800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:23:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363551986912-67</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile in the real world!! LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363551784800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:23:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Priebus is right on the money.If you keep sticking your head in the sand you'll never solve a problem. Repubs need to change or they wont be winning many elections. Very true.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363551986912</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:26:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552381876-68</Id><Topic><Title>Meanwhile in the real world!! LOL</Title><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363551784800</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:23:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Priebus is a fool, he says the party is a young party, they lost the young vote 60% to 34%, the party can't change until they admit they are not appealing to the majority of Americans. Unfortunately for the GOP as long as they give voice to the tea billies the rest of the voters aren't going to vote for them.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363552381876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:33:01 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552519831-69</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah she was fooled by Bush's lies, who would have thought a President would lie to Congress and the public to go to war,</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363552519831</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:35:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552704415-70</Id><Topic><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah latest CBS Poll 31% of voters approve of GOP 47% approve of DNC</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363552704415</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:38:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552840965-71</Id><Topic><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah Obama is dropping in the Polls Mr. Obama's job approval has taken a hit as a result - 50 percent of respondents approve of how he is handling his job, down from 54 percent in December. Still, he handily bests congressional Republicans, whose job approval stands at a meager 24 percent.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363552840965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:40:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363552876806-72</Id><Topic><Title>Moron's lack of thinking</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363547380521</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 15:09:40 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You get in touch with DNC too. Posting to me wont change anything. As I've said twice it is the DNC who's worried not me.LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363552876806</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:41:16 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363553004089-73</Id><Topic><Title>True to his word</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363528827392</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 10:00:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb ignoring this one. Wonder why??LOL</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363553004089</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:43:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363553660102-74</Id><Topic><Title>CSCO starting to move higher!</Title><Username>lucadobson</Username><Timestamp>1362659226270</Timestamp><DateTime>Thu, 2013-03-07 07:27:06 EST</DateTime></Topic><Msg>just received this report</Msg><Username>williamsbrian924</Username><Timestamp>1363553660102</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 16:54:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363554547126-75</Id><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Msg>George Bush water boarded three terrorists trying to get information to protect the country. Libs have reviled him as the torturer-in-chief. Barack Obama has blown an estimated 4700 people ( including some women and children) to bits with drones without getting one iota of information. Not one peep from the liberals. Maybe Obamabuttlickers Junior and dumbivan can explain the disparity. I'll be waiting. BTW, I'm all for the drone program, but then I'm not a hypocritical lib either.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363555565241-76</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I doubt you are bright enough to understand an armed enemy in the field trying to kill you is different then a captured helpless prisoner. Even Hitler understood torturing captured prisoners was ineffective, immoral and illegal. But W doesn't rise up to the moral level of Hitler.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363555565241</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:26:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557321744-77</Id><Topic><Title>Hey, "invading Iraq would pay for itself"</Title><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1363536985161</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 12:16:25 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>looks like she is the one that lied to Bush, she had 10 years of knowledge, more than Bush had? So who lied to who, pecker-wood?</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363557321744</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:55:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363557451795-78</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>,,have you seen Michelle on the Bill Maher show,with that pony on her fore head ,her eyes peekind from under them and one eye is lasy it is smaller than the other,wih those broad shoulders and horse like teeth,ther is nothing femenine about this gal. barack is punished enough,having this gal in his bed,every night.</Msg><Username>leite8033</Username><Timestamp>1363557451795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:57:31 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363557831609-79</Id><Title>LOL Tea party tired of being called racist</Title><Msg>But not tired of being racist Tea Party leaders in Arkansas are on the defensive after a board member of a Tea Party group in the Ozarks made a racist joke at a rally over the weekend drawing laughs from the audience. The Baxter Bulletin in north-central Arkansas reported that Inge Marler made the comments at the annual rally of the Ozark Tea Party. The remarks, which suggested that African-Americans are on welfare, were condemned by Tea Party leaders in the state. The Bulletin reported that the condemnation came after they contacted the Tea Party for comment. The Bulletin reports that Marler, who told the newspaper she would stop using the joke, said the following as an ice-breaker in her speech: “A black kid asks his mom, ‘Mama, what’s a democracy?’ “‘Well, son, that be when white folks work every day so us po’ folks can get all our benefits.’ “‘But mama, don’t the white folk get mad about that?’ “‘They sho do, son. They sho do. And that’s called racism.’” Audio of the speech can be heard here. The remarks come as national Tea Party leaders have denied accusations that their followers are racist.</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363557831609</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:03:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363558386462-80</Id><Title>RUSH, GLENN and SEAN ARE THREE COLLEGE DROPOUTS BUT THEY ARE THE GOPers EDUCATORS</Title><Msg>You can't make this shjjjt up !</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558386462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:13:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363558514534-81</Id><Title>THE POPE ALREADY CONDUCTING ALTAR BOYS TRYOUTS !</Title><Msg>And they aren't of the singing kind.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558514534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363559991486-82</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler killed over six million people in his prison camps, conducted hideous medical experiments on children, and shot unarmed surrendering soldiers and dumb says Hitler believed torture was immoral,ineffective,and illegal.That has to be one of the dumbest posts ever on this board. Junior gave his expected one line stupid response. Typical of him.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363559991486</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:39:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363560152165-83</Id><Topic><Title>THE POPE ALREADY CONDUCTING ALTAR BOYS TRYOUTS !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558514534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Surf got to thinking about the good old days and got his altar boy suit out of mothballs. Heading off to church with a woody right now.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363560152165</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363560482375-84</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>guess you know by now, Dumb and Junior are not the sharpest knives the drawer? I believe they are the same person, Hillary Clinton posting on this board, why you ask? She is the only one I know was that dumb before, and now after the fall and closed head injury! All this was shown when she lost it before the senate over these 4 guys Obama let die with no help!</Msg><Username>captgail4444444</Username><Timestamp>1363560482375</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:48:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363560725989-85</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior,dumb,alsmith,gfo99,jason,et al are one phony. But that post about Hitler is astoundingly stupid.</Msg><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363560725989</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:52:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363561932088-86</Id><Title>Black swan event flash crash warning!</Title><Msg>90% probability of 10% market flash crash in single day.</Msg><Username>pn1409</Username><Timestamp>1363561932088</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:12:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363562957357-87</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You WRONG AGAIN dum Junior -- you an Obama moron</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363562957357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:29:17 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363563040295-88</Id><Topic><Title>THE POPE ALREADY CONDUCTING ALTAR BOYS TRYOUTS !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558514534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Francis is a very humble man. He declined to wear the red shoes. He will keep his black shoes. Obama should display such humility. I would respect him more.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363563040295</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:30:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363563235842-89</Id><Topic><Title>An attaboy for Obama</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363469717156</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 17:35:17 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>horse teeth and #$%$ eyed descendent of a North Carolina slave *** Obama ain't no descendent of a slave -- he's Indonesian. He's not Kenyan. He was adopted by an American commie sympathizer. His sister who was also born in Jakarta also has a Hawaiian birth certificate. It was the wild west after statehood.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363563235842</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:33:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363563365328-90</Id><Title>Why the rush to buy Friday?</Title><Msg>You sent the stock up parabolically? What were you thinking that you couldn't get a better deal come Monday? Didn't you think for once that something might happen in Europe to give you a better deal on Cisco stock?</Msg><Username>carpet.bomber</Username><Timestamp>1363563365328</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:36:05 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363563439474-91</Id><Topic><Title>THE POPE ALREADY CONDUCTING ALTAR BOYS TRYOUTS !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558514534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>didn't you notice, Obama wears black shoes, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363563439474</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:37:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363563526528-92</Id><Topic><Title>Wet face or death ?</Title><Username>doremifa85</Username><Timestamp>1363554547126</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 17:09:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hitler followed the Geneva convention, W not so much</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363563526528</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:38:46 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363563685975-93</Id><Topic><Title>RUSH, GLENN and SEAN ARE THREE COLLEGE DROPOUTS BUT THEY ARE THE GOPers EDUCATORS</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558386462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:13:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It's no coincidence that the leading voices in the GOP all either failed out of college or never went (I think we can agree Palin taking 5 years to go to 4 non-accredited community colleges to get a degree in communications is just like never going to college.)</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363563685975</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:41:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363564153870-94</Id><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Msg>Junior/dumbivan now defending Adolph Hitler!! This so disgusting even I cant make fun of it!!! Can't get any lower than sticking up for a monster like Hitler. Junior/dumb is a low life piece of excrement!!!!!! Pure effing trash!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363564260378-95</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>no one sticking up for Hitler carey, you tea billies are so easily confused, just pointing out Hitler thought torture was immoral and Bush didn't, what part of that confuses you?</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363564260378</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:51:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363564618095-96</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You are a sack of poop,dumb.Anybody thats knows anything knows what Hitler was.Even you aren't that stupid .You are just a leftwing nut who hates Bush. Everybody here should now refuse to respond to any of your posts and I will campaign for that....including your other ids, slimeball.</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564618095</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:56:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363566603918-97</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dont hide,Junior/dumb.I'll be here tomorrow to remind every one you are a Hitler defender......PROMISE!!!!!!</Msg><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363566603918</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:30:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363566735910-98</Id><Topic><Title>Bammy workin' hard to become an historic president...</Title><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363483147969</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 21:19:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>He had better clear that with Larry Sinclair first...</Msg><Username>carrik.fergus</Username><Timestamp>1363566735910</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:32:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567532437-99</Id><Topic><Title>SCHOOL PAYS $10.8 MILLION TO CHILDREN MOLESTED BY 3rd GRADE UNION TEACHER Mark Berndt</Title><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1363509388051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:36:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ban unions in public schools. Unions protect pedofile sex offender union 'teachers' like the catholic church protects pedofile priests.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363567532437</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:45:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567599894-100</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED THIS TIME FOR DRUGGING PRESCHOOLERS WITH SLEEPING PILLS</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1363508790825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How grotesque.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363567599894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:46:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567687953-101</Id><Topic><Title>SCHOOL PAYS $10.8 MILLION TO CHILDREN MOLESTED BY 3rd GRADE UNION TEACHER Mark Berndt</Title><Username>unions_r_criminal_gangs</Username><Timestamp>1363509388051</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:36:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Taxpayers are being punished for unionized 'teacher' child molestations.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363567687953</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:48:07 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567693208-102</Id><Topic><Title>ANOTHER DEMOCRAT UNION TEACHER ARRESTED THIS TIME FOR DRUGGING PRESCHOOLERS WITH SLEEPING PILLS</Title><Username>democrat_cocoon_of_poverty</Username><Timestamp>1363508790825</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 04:26:30 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama look like been smokin dope</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363567693208</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:48:13 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567713263-103</Id><Topic><Title>RUSH, GLENN and SEAN ARE THREE COLLEGE DROPOUTS BUT THEY ARE THE GOPers EDUCATORS</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558386462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:13:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>''The only way to reduce the number of nuclear weapons is to use them. '' —Rush Limbaugh no they don't say stupid things, LOL</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363567713263</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:48:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363567750525-104</Id><Title>Money day tomorrow</Title><Msg>Looks like Cyprus news has spooked the market and there will be the typical over reaction in the morning. Buy quality stocks and you will be rewarded in a few days.</Msg><Username>banjobob45</Username><Timestamp>1363567750525</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:49:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567777225-105</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Mus;lim Manchurian Messiah *** The Manchurian Candidate for real. Unbelievable but true!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363567777225</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:49:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567894894-106</Id><Topic><Title>WHY IS OBAMA BORROWING $500,000,000,000 FROM CHINA TO GIVE TO THE USA HATING MOSLEM BROTHERHOOD IN EGYPT??</Title><Username>super_samoann</Username><Timestamp>1363457588231</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 14:13:08 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Because he wont be paying back the loan of $500 million dollars to the chinese. The taxpayers will be paying back the loan of $500 million dollars plus interest. Obama doesn't care if he completely bankrupts this country he will keep borrowing until the USA can't pay its debt and then China will have a war with the USA to get back the money Obama borrowed from them.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363567894894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:51:34 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363567900685-107</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Junior/dumb is a low life piece of excrement!!!!!! Pure effing trash!!!!! *** Yeah dumb and dumber. What a pair of #$%$ freak Obama worshippers! They keep getting progressively worse.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363567900685</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:51:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568050965-108</Id><Topic><Title>Bottom of the barrel</Title><Username>careyh5050</Username><Timestamp>1363564153870</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 19:49:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Dumb and Dumber. BWHHWHHAHHHHAHAAAAA!!!! You can't tell a fake nggr from a real nggr! Obama ain't done jack for the black community. It's the same as is ever was, except worse. IMPEACH PELOSI NOW!!!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363568050965</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:54:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568114252-109</Id><Topic><Title>THE POPE ALREADY CONDUCTING ALTAR BOYS TRYOUTS !</Title><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363558514534</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 18:15:14 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama wears black shoes, LOL *** Obama wouldn't dare put on those red shoes. They would burn him!</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363568114252</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:55:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568125262-110</Id><Topic><Title>LAPD BUYS WOMEN NEW TRUCK AFTER LAPD OPEN FIRE ON WOMENS TRUCK WITHOUT WARNING</Title><Username>zombies_want_to_eat_brains</Username><Timestamp>1363506613007</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 03:50:13 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Sounds like the lawyer for these women is in cahoots with the LAPD lawyer. Also sounds lijke you are a racist. What does the race of these women have to do with the LAPD unloading hundreds of rounds of ammo into these womens truck without warning??? The LAPD was criminally negligent and were lucky they didn't murder these women.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363568125262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:55:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568209924-111</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA LAYING OFF GOVT WORKERS IN ORDER TO GIVE EGYPT $500,000,000</Title><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1363447665929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 11:27:45 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>In every decision that Obama makes foreigners (especially foreigners that hate the USA) get American taxpayer dollars and Americans get the shaft.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363568209924</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 20:56:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363568480581-112</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Payroll tax is social security tax. Obama reduced social security funding by 2% the entire time obama's gimmick was in effect. Now Obama has to borrow that 2% from the Chinese and American taxpayers get to pay back the 2% plus interest to the Chinese. Obama is financially destroying the USA with all his stupid gimmicks and games.</Msg><Username>obama_bp_oil_spill_horror</Username><Timestamp>1363568480581</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 21:01:20 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363573788973-113</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Ivan I think you are going to have to argue one side of the debate or the other, you can't argue my side and yours, now can you, either Obama raised taxes on people by letting the GOP vote down continuing his payroll tax cut or you can argue he is undermining social security by allowing his tax cut to expire, choose a side moron</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1363573788973</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:29:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363574793243-114</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama should pass a true wealth tax is he wants to tax the rich. Since they are not creating jobs with their billions, Obama should confiscate 20% of all billionaires net worth to reduce the deficit. They got more money than they need. A 20% haircut will make the leaner and meaner.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1363574793243</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 22:46:33 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Strong Sell</Sentiment></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1363576285764-115</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA PROMISED NO NEW TAXES ON THOSE MAKING $250,000 OR</Title><Username>gregu456</Username><Timestamp>1363474249635</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-03-16 18:50:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>ALL PROMISES ARE NEGOTIABLE</Msg><Username>allouezsup</Username><Timestamp>1363576285764</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:11:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>5</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1363578630262-116</Id><Title>GAME CHANGER, BIGGER THAN 9/11...</Title><Msg>'Cypriot President Nicos Anastasiades bowed to demands by euro-area finance ministers to raise 5.8 billion euros ($7.5 billion) to help fund a bailout by taking a piece of EVERY bank account in Cyprus. ' The word bankers are not going to get your money through taxes or treasury bonds, nope, THEY ARE JUST GOING TO TAKE IT. This is the new world order.</Msg><Username>surfandski</Username><Timestamp>1363578630262</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-03-17 23:50:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>