<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><Date date="2013-06-09"><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370751357357-1</Id><Title>OBAMA'S POSSE OF #$%$ ARE READING YOUR EMAILS, LISTENING</Title><Msg>to your phone calls...we have totally lost our constitutional right to privacy with this dictator in office. That ought to make you mad as hell!!!</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1370751357357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 00:15:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370754984380-2</Id><Title>BUY "ALU" AND DOUBLE YOUR MONEY...........</Title><Msg>C U @ 3.50$$ $OON.........</Msg><Username>bobbo64</Username><Timestamp>1370754984380</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 01:16:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment>Hold</Sentiment></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370773920384-3</Id><Title>Your all hypocrites, if you really cared about your safety and privacy...</Title><Msg>1.) OUT LAW ISLAM 2.) Stop all immigration of MVSLIMS into the USA 3.) DEPORT all here on expired visas 4.) existing mvslims option to live in interment camps OR go back to middle east ! It's OKAY to be MEAN, It's YOUR country, NOT THEIRS ! America WAS a nation of immigrants, NOT terrorists or same who wan't their own 2nd law and consequently talk your freedoms and privacy !!!</Msg><Username>black911operator</Username><Timestamp>1370773920384</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 06:32:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370778953574-4</Id><Topic><Title>O'Bama gives birth control to 12 year old girls</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370736653325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 20:10:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Chimp Decider had this wonderful opportunity too, to bad he didn't take advantage of it.</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1370778953574</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 07:55:53 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370780192271-5</Id><Title>15 years watching you baggers post</Title><Msg>For dang near 15 years I have watched you baggers. I take the good with the bad. It's true I have lost EVERYTHING. Being a bagger is hard work. I prefer not to be a bagger and work and I am getting mine now. Full disability. VA paying me to go to college at my age. My third wife's last words to me were "I can't afford you any longer". Good. I am selfish. You baggers despise us "librels". But we decided never again to make lots of money in the private sector. Never again. It's a happier life living off the taxes of the baggers.</Msg><Username>joseph.lederer</Username><Timestamp>1370780192271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 08:16:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>6</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370784325197-6</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S POSSE OF #$%$ ARE READING YOUR EMAILS, LISTENING</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1370751357357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 00:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You sound really paranoid. Why? Terror plots, child porn? What is it?</Msg><Username>larrymountainmankiwihero</Username><Timestamp>1370784325197</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:25:25 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>10</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370784516423-7</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMANOMICS = PHILADELPHIA JUST ANNOUNCED IT IS LAYING OFF 4000 PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION EMPLOYEES</Title><Username>token_affirmativ_action_blackguy</Username><Timestamp>1370713901279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>That's what the goal is, isn't it. The GOP hates education and love to cut the funds off for schools. They love their sequestration except when it affects them like having to spend a bit more time at the airport when they fly back and forth to DC. So they took care of that but the hell with kids.</Msg><Username>larrymountainmankiwihero</Username><Timestamp>1370784516423</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:28:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>11</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370785683717-8</Id><Topic><Title>15 years watching you baggers post</Title><Username>joseph.lederer</Username><Timestamp>1370780192271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 08:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your constant reference to "baggers" gives you away. Were you even trying to be subtle? Only slime like you would pretend to be a veteran to try and make some twisted, sardonic joke...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370785683717</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:48:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370785844473-9</Id><Topic><Title>funny but true</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1370784268436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Hilarious. You must have spent all night working on that one...</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370785844473</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:50:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370785930921-10</Id><Title>Junior's craving attention again...</Title><Msg>That nutburger really needs a life ..</Msg><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370785930921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:52:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370786988185-11</Id><Topic><Title>O'Bama gives birth control to 12 year old girls</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370736653325</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 20:10:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Your bloodthirsty Chimp Divider is an evil murderous Mxslim Kenyan who is spying on America and Americans. . So you have nothing to worry about. . He's using every opportunity to undermine and destroy the country while all you commie sheep graze and bleat his evil name,... Hussein, Hussein, Hussein! . "Too bad" you're an it e it like your brain dead Kenyan corpse man. . And don't forget to RIH, Donna, you dumb vucking coynte.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370786988185</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:09:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370788737958-12</Id><Title>Beating a dead horse</Title><Msg>Dead horse By Mustang Bobby Republicans have introduced legislation to defund ACORN. No, that is not a headline from 2010. That’s from yesterday. Struggling with the bad publicity and loss of federal funds, ACORN dissolved in early 2010. Just to be sure, however, Rep. John Culberson (R-Texas) included this language in a government funding bill introduced on May 28 of this year: “None of the funds made available in this Act may be distributed to the Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN) or its subsidiaries or successors.” Section 545 of a bill put forward the next day by Rep. John Carter (R-Texas) delves still deeper into faux certainty, extending the funding ban to “any prior appropriations Act.” In fact, ACORN has no subsidiaries, because it has not existed for three years. Neither bill defines “successors,” but the broad language of the original 2009 funding ban left little room for leeway, extending to “Any State chapter of ACORN registered with the Secretary of State’s office in that State,” “any organization that shares directors, employees, or independent contractors with ACORN,” and any organization that “employs” someone “indicted” for violations that ACORN was initially charged with. “Is it too late to defund Saddam Hussein?” mocked Rep. Alan Grayson (D-Fla.). Why are we paying these people?</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1370788737958</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:38:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>4</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370789102802-13</Id><Topic><Title>funny but true</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1370784268436</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:24:28 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Bobby Jindal was right. The party of Stupid keeps digging its own grave</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1370789102802</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:45:02 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370789966438-14</Id><Title>Listen to your kids......</Title><Msg>A new report from the College Republicans says that the GOP has totally trashed their chances with younger voters. Titled the “Grand Old Party for a Brand New Generation,” the report is sharply critical of the GOP on several fronts. The study slams some Republicans’ almost singular focus on downsizing Big Government and cutting taxes; candidates’ use of offensive, polarizing rhetoric; and the party’s belly-flop efforts at messaging and outreach, even as the report presents a way forward and, at times, strikes an optimistic tone. In the report, the young Republican activists acknowledge their party has suffered significant damage in recent years. A sampling of the critique on: Gay marriage: “On the ‘open-minded’ issue … [w]e will face serious difficulty so long as the issue of gay marriage remains on the table.” Hispanics: “Latino voters … tend to think the GOP couldn’t care less about them.” Perception of the party’s economic stance: “We’ve become the party that will pat you on your back when you make it, but won’t offer you a hand to help you get there.” Big reason for the image problem: The “outrageous statements made by errant Republican voices.” Words that up-for-grabs voters associate with the GOP: “The responses were brutal: closed-minded, racist, rigid, old-fashioned.”</Msg><Username>gfo99</Username><Timestamp>1370789966438</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 10:59:26 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370791555020-15</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>A startling 7.9 million Americans are working part-time, because they can't find full-time work in today's jobs market. In total, there are still some 12 million people in the U.S. jobs market looking for work. What's most troubling is that 37.3% of them have been unemployed for more than six months! The longer they stay out of the jobs market, the more difficulties these people will face in finding jobs as their skills become obsolete. Looking closer at May's jobs market report (which I feel was an all-round terrible report), new employment in industries like mining and logging, construction, manufacturing, wholesale trade, transportation and warehousing, and financial activities witnessed next to no change in May. Yes, the growth in the jobs market is in low-paying retail and service positions. We have college graduates working jobs that pay minimum wage -- a nation of burger flippers. There is something definitely wrong with this economic recovery. The government has increased its national debt by $17.0 trillion, and the Federal Reserve's balance sheet has grown to $3.0 trillion… and we still can't get create jobs. This so-called economic recovery smells funny to me. Maybe the recovery doesn't even exist. Take out the sucker's rally in the stock market, and there really isn't much left to the economy. It's all fake. It's all a lie. Everything our of Obama's mouth is a freaking lie.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1370791555020</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:25:55 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370791635106-16</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT CONGRESSMAN JESSE JACKSON JR TO SERVE 4 YEARS IN PRISON PAY BACK $750,000</Title><Username>the_lochnesss_monster</Username><Timestamp>1370715359394</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:15:59 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>barely a slap on the wrist. what a joke.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1370791635106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:27:15 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370792114459-17</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Jr thinks Ben Franklin was an idiot. ROTFLOL.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1370792114459</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:35:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370793108876-18</Id><Title>Oblamo threatens GOP he will shut down gov funding</Title><Msg>If he does not get his way. ROTFLOL. Go ahead child do it I dare you then try to blame GOP. What a child.</Msg><Username>deadpainting</Username><Timestamp>1370793108876</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 11:51:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370794796010-19</Id><Topic><Title>Junior's craving attention again...</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370785930921</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 09:52:10 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>How can consumer spending in the U.S. economy rise under these circumstances? In the first quarter of 2013, hourly compensation of Americans employed in non-farm businesses fell 3.8%. This was the biggest drop since the Bureau of Labor Statistic started to measure this statistic in 1947. (Source: Bureau of Labor Statistics, June 5, 2013.) Consumer spending is not rising as one would expect in a real economic recovery. In fact, real personal consumption expenditures (excluding food and energy) adjusted for price changes rose less than 1% in the first four months of 2013. Things keep progressively getting worse. The rich get richer.</Msg><Username>yohoho_andabottlea</Username><Timestamp>1370794796010</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:19:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370795954134-20</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMANOMICS = PHILADELPHIA JUST ANNOUNCED IT IS LAYING OFF 4000 PUBLIC SCHOOL UNION EMPLOYEES</Title><Username>token_affirmativ_action_blackguy</Username><Timestamp>1370713901279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:51:41 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Fist of all Sequestration is OBAMA'S IDEA and all the democrats voted for sequestration. Secondly, the city of Philadelphia is laying off 4000 assistant principals, teachers, counselors, noontime aides and others. Obviously you DO NOT know the difference between Federal and City Government? The city of Philadelphia is run by Democrats. It is democrats who are laying off all these union slackers.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370795954134</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:39:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796063604-21</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT OPERATIVE WHO WAS ILLEGALLY HACKING INTO GOP GOVERNOR EMAIL ARRESTED FOR CHILD P0RN0</Title><Username>token_affirmativ_action_blackguy</Username><Timestamp>1370712032279</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 13:20:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Obama's DEMOCRAT CULTURE OF CORRUPTION is happening not only at the Federal Level but at the state level as well.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796063604</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:41:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796152362-22</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S CZARS NEED SECRET EMAILS SO THEY CAN VIOLATE LAWS AND SUBVERT US CONSTITUTION</Title><Username>high_falutin_heifers</Username><Timestamp>1370727447402</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 17:37:27 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It is very obvious that all Obama appointees have secret emails so they can violate the US Constitution in secret.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796152362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:42:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796221022-23</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BANS WAR HERO FROM READING BOOKS BY RUSH LIMBAUGH, SEAN HANNITY BANS HERO FROM EATING AT CHICK-FIL-A</Title><Username>semimalformedwolf</Username><Timestamp>1370714571687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama's goal is rule with an IRON FIST and eventually execute ANYONE that does not obey his direct orders.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796221022</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:43:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796337260-24</Id><Topic><Title>USA NEEDS TO IMPEACH OBAMA. WHERE IS KEN STARR?</Title><Username>fukk_france_dot_com</Username><Timestamp>1370675958385</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 03:19:18 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The death of 4 American Bengazi Embassy Personnel due to Obama's criminal negligence is definitely a high crime and misdemeanor.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796337260</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:45:37 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796430081-25</Id><Topic><Title>DEMOCRAT JOURNALISM PROFESSOR DEMANDS MISSILE ATTACK ON THE NRA AND GUNNING DOWN NRA MEMBERS</Title><Username>hillary_clinton_is_a_sea_hag</Username><Timestamp>1370105093106</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-01 12:44:53 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>All these democrat radical extremists that are ubiquitous at Universities need to be fired. All they do is preach hate and missile attacks on those who disagree with their psychotic idealogy.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796430081</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:47:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>7</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370796738578-26</Id><Title>HOW COMFORTING, OBAMA ORDERS THE NSA LEAKER TO INVESTIGATE THEIR OWN LEAK</Title><Msg>HOW COMFORTING, OBAMA ORDERS THE NSA LEAKER TO INVESTIGATE THEIR OWN LEAK and cover it up so that it is no longer in the news.</Msg><Username>citizens_against_toxic_waste</Username><Timestamp>1370796738578</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:52:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370796951200-27</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA BANS WAR HERO FROM READING BOOKS BY RUSH LIMBAUGH, SEAN HANNITY BANS HERO FROM EATING AT CHICK-FIL-A</Title><Username>semimalformedwolf</Username><Timestamp>1370714571687</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 14:02:51 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obama banning a war hero from eating at Chick-Fil-A is extremely un-American and proves that Obama loves Businesses closing their doors, loves UNEMPLOYMENT and likes the economy to be in the toilet.</Msg><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1370796951200</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 12:55:51 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370797248789-28</Id><Title>AP STORY LOOTERS FROM BLUE STATES FLOCKING TO MOORE OKLAHOMO TO ROB TORNADO VICTIMS</Title><Msg>AP STORY LOOTERS FROM BLUE STATES FLOCKING TO MOORE OKLAHOMO TO ROB TORNADO VICTIMS. Does not suprize me one bit that lowlife New York City democrats would find a way to goto Moore Oklahome to rob tornado victims.</Msg><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1370797248789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:00:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370798869107-29</Id><Topic><Title>AP STORY LOOTERS FROM BLUE STATES FLOCKING TO MOORE OKLAHOMO TO ROB TORNADO VICTIMS</Title><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1370797248789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:00:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It just proves that democrats are satans disciples.</Msg><Username>democrats_are_satans_disiciples</Username><Timestamp>1370798869107</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:27:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370799178549-30</Id><Title>DEMOCRAT ANTHONY WEINER TWEETING HIS PRIVATES TO MINORS = WEINER IS SATAN DISCIPLE</Title><Msg>DEMOCRAT ANTHONY WEINER TWEETING HIS PRIVATES TO MINORS = WEINER IS SATAN DISCIPLE. No God fearing mean would engage in such sexual perversions.</Msg><Username>democrats_are_satans_disiciples</Username><Timestamp>1370799178549</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:32:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370800796715-31</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Answer: Liberals are disciples of satan. They lack wisdom and are defined as fools in the bible. They are evil.</Msg><Username>democrats_r_satans_disciples</Username><Timestamp>1370800796715</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:59:56 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370801100047-32</Id><Topic><Title>15 years watching you baggers post</Title><Username>joseph.lederer</Username><Timestamp>1370780192271</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 08:16:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>From your description of yourself, your problem is that you are a fool a disciple of satan and a loser.</Msg><Username>democrats_r_satans_disciples</Username><Timestamp>1370801100047</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:05:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370802158333-33</Id><Title>Ivan the shut in posting all weekend again, LOL</Title><Msg>just back from the Phillips Exeter graduation, headed out to a lacrosse game. Nice to see Ivan keeping busy posting his drivel 24/7, LOL what a loser. Hey Ivan looks like you lose again, LOL WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A conservative Republican overseeing Internal Revenue Service screeners in Cincinnati told congressional investigators that he does not believe the White House was behind IRS scrutiny of conservative groups. Luckily Issa vows to continue the probe until no American of average intelligence or above supports the GOP. LOL (in between stealing cars and starting insurance fires of course).</Msg><Username>dumb.ivan</Username><Timestamp>1370802158333</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:22:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370803728904-34</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Libs aren't stupid. Just the moonbat koolaid chuggers are stupid. I happen to know a few very clever libs who get the chuggers drinking everytime while they lie and cheat their way to power.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370803728904</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:48:48 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370803821282-35</Id><Topic><Title>IRS 'scanda;' a non-event</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1370802727795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:32:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You mean "facts" like the 180 million jobs lost in 57 states because to the sequester?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370803821282</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:50:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370804722615-36</Id><Topic><Title>IRS 'scanda;' a non-event</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1370802727795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:32:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>DRAIN THE SWAMP!</Msg><Username>hardwarenincompoopfrompottsylvan</Username><Timestamp>1370804722615</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:05:22 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>3</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370804989369-37</Id><Title>OBAMA'S EPA ILLEGALLY RELEASED FARMERS PRIVATE INFO TO LEFT WING DEMOCRAT ENVIROMENTAL GROUPS</Title><Msg>Obama's epa illegally released farmers private info to left wing democrat enviromental groups. 24 senators are demanding an answer from epa. epa is stonewalling and lying just like obama's irs.</Msg><Username>the_lochnesss_monster</Username><Timestamp>1370804989369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>6</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370805283074-38</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S EPA ILLEGALLY RELEASED FARMERS PRIVATE INFO TO LEFT WING DEMOCRAT ENVIROMENTAL GROUPS</Title><Username>the_lochnesss_monster</Username><Timestamp>1370804989369</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:09:49 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Obviously Obama's EPA illegally "LEAKED' THE Farmers private information to left wing democrat environmentalist groups in order to paint a target on the farmer that these militant democrat left wing environmentalist groups can physically target and attack the individual farmers who are on Obama's enemy list.</Msg><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1370805283074</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:14:43 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370805621614-39</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>BAM!!! A direct hit! . GREATpost, Dems r satans_dispicable-deciiples. . And their murderous bloodthirsty evil leader is illegally in the white house.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370805621614</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:20:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370806090303-40</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>NIce post Yohoho,… right on the M -A -R -K! . And the really sad part is, liberals are so stoically stupid they need college educations in order to flip burgers. . Thank God none of them are so stupid that they say, Corpse Man. . No human could be THAT stupid. . But a demon could. . One named Hussein.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370806090303</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:28:10 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370806199483-41</Id><Topic><Title>AP STORY LOOTERS FROM BLUE STATES FLOCKING TO MOORE OKLAHOMO TO ROB TORNADO VICTIMS</Title><Username>giggling_democrat_hyeena</Username><Timestamp>1370797248789</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 13:00:48 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>that's what 12 gauges are made for brother! Low-life, shyt-eating, looting Dims! AHHHHHHHAHAHAHAHA!</Msg><Username>clayveuss_johnson</Username><Timestamp>1370806199483</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 15:29:59 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370809352236-42</Id><Title>OBAMA ADMIN TARGETING 29 YEAR OLD NSA WHISTLEBLOWER</Title><Msg>From the blaze website: 29 Year old whistle blower says "I can’t in good conscience allow the U.S. government to destroy privacy, Internet freedom and basic liberties for people around the world with this massive surveillance machine they’re secretly building" Read full story at the blaze website</Msg><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1370809352236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370809650176-43</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN TARGETING 29 YEAR OLD NSA WHISTLEBLOWER</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1370809352236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>This whistle blower has exposed the undocumented imigrant WH occupier of the Executive Branch subverting our USA Constitution.</Msg><Username>who_eats_collard_greens</Username><Timestamp>1370809650176</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:27:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370812871963-44</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN TARGETING 29 YEAR OLD NSA WHISTLEBLOWER</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1370809352236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I am a gorilla and I take great offense at being compared to that low life long armed brain dead knuckle dragging hairy hideous looking anti-American ugly pie faced piece of fascist shjt, moo moo Michelle yeti. . My apologies to any Yetti's that I may have offended, like Verk's mother.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370812871963</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 17:21:11 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370816910230-45</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>But you must be impressed that our President has created 39 straight months of job growth. What do you say about that I-VAN?</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1370816910230</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:28:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370817189929-46</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN TARGETING 29 YEAR OLD NSA WHISTLEBLOWER</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1370809352236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I-VAN your President has led the country to 39 straight months of job growth. You have to be impressed by that.</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1370817189929</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:09 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370817215957-47</Id><Title>DOES THE CONSTITUTION MATTER?</Title><Msg>Of course it does! The original founders clearly understood, as do all thinking folks today, that your biggest threat, IS ALWAYS YOUR OWN MASSIVE, OVERWEENING GOVERNMENT..always! Not terrorists, not jihadists, not illegal aliens from Mexico, El Salvador and other Central American places, not the Chinese, not communism, not facism..(SOCIALISM, YES!...but not communism or facism), NO! NO! The biggest threat always to hard working people is your very own government, state or federal, depending on which one has more power over your everyday life, funds, and freedom. The guys who wrote that paper, the Constitution and the Bill of Rights, had it all RIGHT!!! The Constitution matters, no matter how Democrats today spin it, or liberal media talkers spin...the Constitution and the rule of law is all that stands between us and TYRANNY. Which is why the Supreme Court matters, at least to those who cherish liberty and freedom. Subverting the Constitution, as many of the Supreme Court judges now seem prone to do, see Ginsberg, is a slippery slope that ends with victory for chaos and tyranny. The Tea Party may be the last best hope of America.............</Msg><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1370817215957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:35 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370818214790-48</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Food stamp givaways do create work in those burger flipping jobs. 39 months? Obama has been in office for almost 5 years, so he evidently started the recovery a bit slow. Do you know how many jobs were lost in the first 14 months. Yes. I am impressed that you know how to count the good months. You know you also had the House and Senate in those first 14 months?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370818214790</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:50:14 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370818818936-49</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>It won't change the fact that most of them were created after he lost the house, as did many Americans. The number of jobs he created is "sophistry." The critical facts are how many of the jobs pay real money, and how many of them represent growth, not recovery from previous system problems. You have to remember that Bush also inherited the end of the internet bubble. Maybe you can draw conclusions from the real data, or shall we stick with sophistry and insults?</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370818818936</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:00:18 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370818860011-50</Id><Topic><Title>IRS 'scanda;' a non-event</Title><Username>juniorsclassmate_7</Username><Timestamp>1370802727795</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 14:32:07 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Are those the "fracts?"</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370818860011</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:01:00 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370819164771-51</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The only thing YOUR politburo prone el Presidente created is death and destruction, crime and corruption and 17 trillion dollars of DEBT,… the private sector created jobs in spite of the free market fascist demon thing known in the communist circles where you jerk, as, the Marxist Mxslim. . I am an American, I have no prez, no American does, nor does America, but it does have a Kenyan spy who lives to lie and praise All' ah. . And it likes to cut babies heads off and murder Americans in cold blood just so he could campaign. . But then again, that's why you worship and praise him as your demigod demon.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370819164771</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:06:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370819232885-52</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Face it, your boy got shellacked in 2010, and jobs are growing ever since. He lost the census, too. That is, the reapportionment of congressional districts almost guarantee that the Republicans will hold the House until 2020. The news of their death is premature. The GOP will survive the onslaught of Gays, Single Mothers, and Moochers. The food stamp party might have to give out more free stuff to win.</Msg><Username>artemiagrower</Username><Timestamp>1370819232885</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:07:12 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370819361084-53</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Why are LIbs so Stupid?? ========== . Practice. . And lots OF it.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370819361084</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:09:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370819670729-54</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>I-VAN I wish you would invest some time into expanding your vocabulary It must be frustrating to have no option but to "shoehorn" the same old BS into every discussion.</Msg><Username>jen.co44</Username><Timestamp>1370819670729</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:14:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370820532720-55</Id><Topic><Title>DOES THE CONSTITUTION MATTER?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1370817215957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>If and when the latter part of your post comes to fruition it will usher in the next American Revolution to stop the tyrannical anti-American commie leftists. . The Patriots of the Tea Party will always be the last hope, just as the Founding Fathers had intended. . The 2 party system has many agendas, the left's is abolish the constitution total intrusive communist control and slavery blended with Mxslim Messiah worshipping and the right's is the free market system and individuality laced with small government and limited enforced laws and people's rights,…. but at this point in out Nation's young history, the American Tea Party only has one agenda,… Freedom. . Pure, Don't Tread on Me,… Freedom. . And THAT'S why the anti-American bloodthirsty commie Kenyan despot calls Americans like the Tea Party Patriots,… HIS ENEMIES. . And that's because HE is the ENEMY of America.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370820532720</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:28:52 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370820876484-56</Id><Topic><Title>Why are Libs so Stupid??</Title><Username>libs_r_a_plague</Username><Timestamp>1370734534524</Timestamp><DateTime>Sat, 2013-06-08 19:35:34 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Right now I'm too busy "shoehorning" my massive crank into your mother's as. . I wish you would bring me a can of Crisco to make it easier.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370820876484</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 19:34:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370823177559-57</Id><Topic><Title>DOES THE CONSTITUTION MATTER?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1370817215957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Constitution is an obstacle to democrat party whose goal is a democrat communistic dictatorship. Democrats hate the constitution and are doing everything they can to subvert it with the end goal of replacing it with their dictatorship.</Msg><Username>democrat_occupier_wall_of_doodoo</Username><Timestamp>1370823177559</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:12:57 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370823518590-58</Id><Title>WHO CARES IF ILLEGAL ALIENS ARE TIRED OF WAITING FOR AMNESTY, THEY ARE CRIMINALS</Title><Msg>WHO CARES IF ILLEGAL ALIENS ARE TIRED OF WAITING FOR AMNESTY, THEY ARE CRIMINALS. These foreign criminals (illegal aliens) have dont have the right to make demands. Fk em all.</Msg><Username>democrat_occupier_wall_of_doodoo</Username><Timestamp>1370823518590</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:18:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>10</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370823898462-59</Id><Title>NSA whistle blower, Edward Snowden, expose's the Kenyan's plot to spy on Americans</Title><Msg>"After turning over the documents to The Guardian, Snowden fled to Hong Kong, where he sat for an interview with Greenwald and watched Wolf Blitzer on CNN. Snowden lived in Hawaii with his girlfriend, but told the UK paper that he was willing to give all of that up. He said: I'm willing to sacrifice all of that because I can't in good conscience allow the US government to destroy privacy, internet freedom and basic liberties for people around the world with this massive surveillance machine they're secretly building." ================ . Read the whole article at Huff Post. . . Hussein is more diabolically evil than most care to realize, just because they're getting free stuff.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370823898462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:24:58 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370824061706-60</Id><Topic><Title>NSA whistle blower, Edward Snowden, expose's the Kenyan's plot to spy on Americans</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370823898462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whistle blowers are protected by laws, but Obama believes he is exempt from all laws. Dont be surpised is the whistle blower is killed by an Obama drone.</Msg><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1370824061706</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:27:41 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370824383449-61</Id><Topic><Title>NSA whistle blower, Edward Snowden, expose's the Kenyan's plot to spy on Americans</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370823898462</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:24:58 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Look's like the Marxist Mxslim ran into ANOTHER American Patriot. . Poor,... poor,... evil Mxslim. . When he illegally got into the white house he thought that everyone must be communists,… but was that PieceOS Kenyan ever wrong. . Oop sea for the evil anti-American bloodthirsty Mxslim. . He thinks everyone says corpse man and hates America like he does. . He didn't count on Patriots getting in the way and foiling his evil plot. . Thank GOD the Kenyan's stupid because if he had 2 brain cells he could really be dangerous.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370824383449</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:33:03 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370824956065-62</Id><Topic><Title>DOES THE CONSTITUTION MATTER?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1370817215957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>The Marxist Mxslim said that the "Constitution is a charter of negative liberties." . First of all, #$%$ would a Kenyan know about the AMERICAN constitution? . Negative liberties??? Look's like the brain dead commie Kenyan thinks he is smarter than the Founding Fathers. . Go screw with your own constitution in Kenya you evil bloodthirsty PieceOmuslimS. . That is, IF if has one.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370824956065</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:42:36 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370825406009-63</Id><Title>Go Youtube</Title><Msg>… "53 seconds that should end a presidency." . And then be afraid,… be very afraid. . How can any living thing be that eerily stinking stupid and evil at the same time. . Or better yet, how could the people that put the spy in the white house be that stupid. . Their only saving grace is that the Kenyan used voter fraud to get in, so there is still hope for the dummies that did it. They couldn't have done it with out the Mxslim spy using the IRS to suppress and stop voters.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370825406009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:50:06 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370826290733-64</Id><Topic><Title>Go Youtube</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370825406009</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 20:50:06 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>You have no brain gerbil wrangler.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370826290733</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:04:50 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370826321108-65</Id><Title>OBAMA SPIED ON ENTIRE US POPULATION AND LET BOSTON MARATHON TERORIST EXECUTE THEIR ATTACK</Title><Msg>Obama spied on entire us population and let boston marathon terorist execute their attack. what is good is obama???</Msg><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1370826321108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:05:21 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>4</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370826525362-66</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA'S POSSE OF #$%$ ARE READING YOUR EMAILS, LISTENING</Title><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1370751357357</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 00:15:57 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>yeah but your mom didn't think so last night she was deepthroating my snake</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1370826525362</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:08:45 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370826684342-67</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA ADMIN TARGETING 29 YEAR OLD NSA WHISTLEBLOWER</Title><Username>gorilla_manchelle</Username><Timestamp>1370809352236</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 16:22:32 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>there was a time not so many years ago that the libs all cheered on the whistle blowers, now they want to silence them. Wonder how long it takes for those young rebellious types to start waking up from their Obamalove induced coma.</Msg><Username>lawyergump</Username><Timestamp>1370826684342</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:11:24 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>2</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370826690085-68</Id><Title>LAMEDUCK0BAMA RULED THE REELS IN KICKING DEM'SASSES</Title><Msg>setting a new record for asskicking</Msg><Username>lameduck0bama</Username><Timestamp>1370826690085</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:11:30 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370826704242-69</Id><Title>WELFARE RECIEPIEND AND MOSLEM TERORIST JOHN ZAWAHRI GOES ON SHOOTING RAMPAGE IN SANTA MONICA CALIFA</Title><Msg>WELFARE RECIEPIEND AND MOSLEM TERORIST JOHN ZAWAHRI GOES ON SHOOTING RAMPAGE IN SANTA MONICA CALIFORNIA. Obama is spying on everyone yet he is letting terrorists attack America.</Msg><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1370826704242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:11:44 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>5</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370826879276-70</Id><Topic><Title>OBAMA SPIED ON ENTIRE US POPULATION AND LET BOSTON MARATHON TERORIST EXECUTE THEIR ATTACK</Title><Username>pic_n_save_democrat</Username><Timestamp>1370826321108</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:05:21 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>What good is he? . Maybe he would make a good door stop or speed bump? . . But since he's dumber than a stump, he's not smart enough to be one.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370826879276</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:14:39 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370827120829-71</Id><Topic><Title>WELFARE RECIEPIEND AND MOSLEM TERORIST JOHN ZAWAHRI GOES ON SHOOTING RAMPAGE IN SANTA MONICA CALIFA</Title><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1370826704242</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:11:44 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Don't slander or mess with the Mxslim Marxist's people or he will have you prosecuted, fined and put in jail. . Don't believe it? . Go Google it and see.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370827120829</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:18:40 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>3</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>1</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370827538894-72</Id><Topic><Title>DOES THE CONSTITUTION MATTER?</Title><Username>walterbyrdman11</Username><Timestamp>1370817215957</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 18:33:35 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Every country run by black people are poverty stricken 3rd world doo doo holes with the dictator having 99.5% of entire countries wealth in a swiss bank account with the leaders name on it. Dont be surprized if Obama is embezzling all the wealth of the USA and putting it in a swiss bank account with his name on it.</Msg><Username>soccer_and_dodgeball_mom</Username><Timestamp>1370827538894</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:25:38 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>1</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>0</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="TopicMessage"><Id>1370828824150-73</Id><Title>76% of Americans want a special prosecutor to look into Obamaa's IRS scandal</Title><Msg>With 2 to 1 being DEMOCRATS. . THAT right there aught to to tell you the Kenyan's toast. . And so is his lackey henchman Holder. . The noose begins to tighten around the Nazinegrah's evil crusty Mxslim neck.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370828824150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:47:04 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message><Message type="ReplyMessage"><Id>1370830039218-74</Id><Topic><Title>76% of Americans want a special prosecutor to look into Obamaa's IRS scandal</Title><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370828824150</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 21:47:04 EDT</DateTime></Topic><Msg>Whatever it takes to put the Kenyan in cuffs.</Msg><Username>ivanhoeofloxxly</Username><Timestamp>1370830039218</Timestamp><DateTime>Sun, 2013-06-09 22:07:19 EDT</DateTime><ThumbUp>0</ThumbUp><ThumbDown>2</ThumbDown><Sentiment/></Message></Date>